I see the game you're playing. Alright, I'm cloning. I'm cloning.
Alright. Rowdy. Fuckers. Cop. Killers. In. A whole bunch of games. The whole gaggle.
Wait, wait, wait. Nope, that's a spoiler. No, we're not playing that game just yet. Whoops.
What a blunder. What an unbelievable blunder.
Yeah, that's a secret for later. You don't fucking... Anyway, we're playing fucking...
We're playing the game that's... We're playing the hit new game Road Toads by Charlie Batten,
aka Hippo's brother. Yeah, Hippo's younger brother, I believe.
Yeah, younger brother. His younger... Jesus. Is that loud?
Yeah, a little bit, for me at least. Let me hear something.
Oh, that's very loud. I always get confused. I'm pretty sure that Charlie is his youngest brother,
and Henry is the middle one, although I might have them flipped around. I might have them flipped around.
You never know what those fucking three little pigs...
I know that...
All I know is that they're tasty, and I shall blow their house down.
I've never... I don't think I've ever spoken to Charlie, but Henry is really funny.
Henry, aka HGB guy, is fucking hilarious, and I love him.
HGB guy is great. He was a big fan of me and the Japanese Juggalo, though I haven't heard from him in a really long time,
so he might not think I'm cool anymore, or he might just be gone forever.
I haven't even heard a peep out of him for like six months.
Well, yeah.
He was in The Rowdyfuckers, but then when Endless War was brutally attacked and subdued by the Megaslam,
he kind of fell off the map, which, you know, makes sense. Societies and ruins.
It's really been a real drag to move our entire PC gaming rig down here in the sewers with all the raw and the stench,
but you know, we're making do.
But whether our entire society and civilization has collapsed or not, we have to record this let's play due to contractual obligations,
so you're getting the show on the extremely regular basis that we record it. You're getting this.
Yeah, I mean, we have to... Wait, am I still recording? Yes, I am recording. Okay, that's good. A good thing.
Yeah, but you know, we have to do it because the only color, the only color that exists in the world anymore is in the form of video games.
So without it, I mean, life would... Shit, I control all deleted off the game, and now my cursor is gone, and I can't select anything.
Jesus. Alright, I'm gonna...
Rain? No, no, no. Whether it's snow, hail, sleet, shine, or rain, we will maybe record a podcast or let's play one day.
Like, no matter what elements are against us, we may choose to record a let's play. That's how dedicated we are to this.
Maybe. It could happen. Alright, let's do Cool Race. Should I be an egg? Should I be a car, an egg, or a bird?
Be the bird. Is that not a toad? Is that not what that is? What is this game?
Uh, okay, here we go. Drive through the yellow beams. I think, oh, I'm a toad.
Oh, you pilot these things. Oh, Ben, you're fucking bad at this.
Hold on. Oh, wait, oh, I move with the mouse. Okay.
Jesus. Okay, we're already losing.
That's fine. Losing is fun. This game is great. I don't even... I have no idea what's happening, but this game is great.
You gotta fucking Tokyo Drift through the beams. We should play Mario Kart Double Dash.
I hate racing games. No, they're great. I actively hate them. Why? Why do you hate racing games?
You're boring. No. That's false.
And some people are like, oh, but Mario Kart isn't just a racing game. You've got all this shit that you do. You pick up fucking items.
Mario Kart is the most boring game I've ever played. I hate it. I actively hate it.
I hate, like, you know, Gran Turismo or whatever. In fact, I've never even played it before.
But Mario Kart is fun because you didn't get ahead. And even if people try and throw the blue shell and stuff at you,
if you're a god like I am, then you know the strats and you know how to tongue your banana with the throws in order to destroy the blue shell.
What you were describing sounds like the opposite of fun.
No. No, it's great because that means... that means, like, I ruin the mood of the party.
You know, we turn on Mario Kart 8. I just get so far ahead of everyone that no one stands a chance against me.
And then the party is not fun. And then everyone starts to leave and all of my friends don't want to hang out with me anymore.
It doesn't matter. Because I'm top leaderboard, so Mario Kart 8.
I guess when you put it like that, it makes sense.
Man, I'm running out of toads. I'm getting low on toads. I need to, like, up my to- Oh, no.
In this economy, how can you spare a toad?
I can't spare any toads. But I think I'm about... Okay, I'm in the positive. I'm in the green for toads now.
I'm so glad that video games are cool again.
Um, are they?
Yeah. There was like an entire, like, year or two where I didn't boot up any video game.
Where I just had like a ton of games on Steam.
I didn't want to play any of them because video games are boring and they're a distraction,
and they make you lose sight of what's real in the world.
And they don't allow you to, you know, produce any content and they're just a distraction for people who are stoners
and slash who are chronically dependent upon masturbation and porn, aka degenerates.
But lately, I've just been turned on Nuclear Throne, just doing, like, a run or two, and it's really great.
Video games are cool again.
Wait, well, that... No, that doesn't make any sense because nothing changed.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Something happens.
Wow, you drove real good. First place.
Wow, I have these many to- Whoa, shit!
I never got this to happen before.
Um, look, nothing changed about video games. You just decided to play Nuclear Throne again.
Yes.
Now, afraid video games are still not cool.
No, no, no, that you're completely missing, you're missing the forest through the trees.
I have decreed that video games are cool again, therefore they are.
Uh, well, sure.
Okay.
I haven't, I haven't, I haven't stopped.
Lately, I've been, I've been licking my lips and I've been, I've been sweating profusely outside local game stops.
I'm sorry, I'm just, I'm, I'm wiggin' out because like, there's actually way more to this game than I thought.
Like, I didn't think, I thought there was only one map.
But no, apparently this is like a journey. This is like a journey to collect toads.
Uh, it's like a real video game.
Charlie's not gonna skimp out on the content.
I mean, shit, I thought this was just like some kind of little experiment that he did.
And I mean, maybe it is that, but it is also a real video game.
This is, this has like 12 Tony's under its spell.
Um, not more than SpongeBob the musical.
Ah, jeez.
You know, I've been salivating and having bodily fluids just, just splurge out of my body outside local game stops.
Just meticulously like watching like a hawk over the Nintendo Switch section.
I have almost like, just like straight up just like been in a mall and just thought,
today's just the day I'm gonna get Nintendo Switch.
I'm just gonna do it. I'm just gonna bite the bullet and do it.
I've just, I've just walked into the game stops and then I've chickened out at the last moment.
I really want to switch. I really, I want Splatoon.
Splatoon is literally in Rattyfugger's Cockilers.
Like, okay, okay, I think that Mario Odyssey is probably pretty fun.
And I think Breath of the Wild looks pretty cool.
But when I like look deep inside myself and ask, do I really want to play a video game?
That is either of those.
Probably not who fucking gives a shit.
But Splatoon, yeah, I would actually, I would actually play Splatoon if I had a Switch.
That's the one, that's the one video game that I would want to play.
Splatoon is like a miracle that it exists.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like, okay, so you got, you got Nintendo.
By the way, also I can hear myself echoing.
Wait, really?
Yeah.
Well, whatever, who cares?
You got, you've got this fucking, you've got Nintendo.
It's like the, like the, the modern like Marvel movies of the video game industry.
Where there's pumping out sequels and, you know, Smash Bros. and New Mario's and New Zelda's and whatever the fuck.
And no one really cares.
And then just out of nowhere, Splatoon comes out.
It's, it's a completely new IP.
It's super refreshing.
It's, it's a third person shooter.
And not only is it a great game and it's own right.
It's, it's lovable.
It's an instant classic.
But Nintendo treats it like it's an instant classic.
So now Splatoon's in fucking Smash Bros.
Splatoon's treated like, like one of the greats, like Mario and Zelda.
It's, it's like, you know, a new video game that's treated with dignity and respect.
And not just like, oh, that's just, you know, that's just like a new IP.
We can't put that in Super Smash Bros.
Some, some fucking shmucks of Nintendo actually made a new video game.
To be fair, it's not that new anymore.
Like it's what?
Like five or six years old now?
Maybe not that.
Well, still, they're still going shrugged.
They're still up Splatoon 2.
And with the way the video games are released,
it's not like there's, there's been any other brand new IP.
That is an instant classic the way Splatoon is.
Hey, is your, is the echo any better?
Yeah, probably.
I can't tell it right now, but probably.
Oh, that's so many toads.
That's so many frogs.
Oh, well, you're at 180.
I don't think I did that well that time because I like, I like stopped to do some shit.
But you know, I'm just going to get as many toads as I possibly can.
Prepare for a swift drift.
Okay.
Oh shit.
I'm going to go until I've seen every level.
Like I wonder if, I wonder if there's like something that you can unlock if you like.
The secret character.
Is there?
I don't know, probably.
Yeah.
Like I wonder if you can unlock more characters by getting more toads or something.
Oh my God.
That would be beautiful.
I mean, I'm already like really shocked that there's at the level of content that is in
the scene.
Oh God.
The only problem with Splatoon is that I don't want to play it at all.
What do you mean?
I like it.
I like all the gameplay mechanics.
I think it's a good game and I cherish it.
And I would play it, but I've grown up with a computer.
And so trying to play a game that requires any amount of precision at all with a controller,
like I just can't do it.
Like I just been spoiled.
I cannot do it.
Like I'm so used to having the control of a mouse that trying to like, especially like
shoot things with the controller, I can't do it.
I just can't do it.
I don't think I agree with you.
I mean, I like, I feel like normally I would be like the first person to agree with you
on that.
But because like, because I'm a PC boy, but I mean, I, I was playing.
Okay.
Yes, I did hate, I did hate the Wii U controller.
But nevertheless, I played Splatoon one with Wii U and it was fucking great.
And I loved it.
Sure.
I did too.
I bet it's a million times better on the Switch.
I'm sure it is too.
The fact of the matter is, I don't have a mouse.
So it won't like, like, can you imagine?
I, it's one of these times where I just wish the Nintendo would have like some of her periphery
where I can just like, you know, the Switch has USB.
She's really plugging a mouse and a keyboard.
How fun would it be to play Splatoon and like actually have some sort of like, like even
the phantom of a competitive scene, because now you have a massive keyboard, you can actually,
you know, have that sort of thing.
That'd be great.
I would love that so much.
But no, they'll never do that.
It'll never happen.
So I'll just kill myself then.
Do it.
I am going to, I'm going to get Splatoon on, uh, Switch though.
Oh, oh god.
This is like, I'm getting nervous.
Like, it's hard.
This is pretty, this is actually pretty difficult.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh shit, dude.
You know what?
I'm going to have to send a letter to Nintendo.
The next, uh, Splatfest needs to be, uh, Rowdy versus Killer.
I'm going to send that to Nintendo.
It needs to be.
Oh my god, dude.
We're going to have to, we're, okay.
Get, get the, get the top Rowdy fuckers tattooed, like, like New Los Angeles City physicians
and mathematicians online with some physicists and scientists.
Get them on the fucking line.
We need a mod of Splatoon where instead of like, Callie Marie's mean you.
Imagine that.
Oh god, yes.
Uh, yes, please.
Uh, I mean, I mean, I think we pretty much invented Splatoon at this point.
Yeah.
Uh, with, with the amount that we carry in its name, the amount that we set the beliefs
and constitutions, we might as well have created it.
The, the, everything about Splatoon, like, like the whole urban, the whole urban like
setting and style and aesthetic of it is just so, it's so, you know, they pretty much
just completely ripped off Rowdy fuckers cop killies.
What are we supposed to do?
Oh, whoa.
It's cutscene.
How are the toads coming along?
Whoa.
Sorry, boss.
I was distracted.
What was?
How are the toads?
They're, um, coming along very well.
Hmm.
This is enchanting.
Oh god.
I have a goal now.
I have to reach a thousand toads.
We, we, we've all said that under our breath at what moment.
This game is so much more robust than I thought.
Do the ships have different controls?
Oh my god.
Look at this.
This is good.
I like that.
Uh, no, they all control the same, at least as far as I can tell.
Oh, this place is cool as hell.
Wait, wait, wait.
Look at that purple sky.
Oh, oh.
I was hitting the wrong button.
This is, this, this game is a marvel.
Can we have like a link to this in the description?
Um, yeah, yeah, I can put a link.
I can put a download link.
Is this like public, is this public domain?
Is this like in the public sphere?
I don't know.
I mean, I just asked, uh, Hippo for, for it, or Hippo just like gave me the link to download
from.
I don't remember like if it was on like a site or something.
Uh, yeah, I don't know.
It's beautiful.
I love it.
If, if Charlie doesn't have a website or something, you should, you should get one.
Or maybe, maybe Hippo would host him on, on app.
I hope so.
I, I've recently caught up on episode.
I, I love jail.
I have, uh, I don't even remember what the name is.
I have not, I caught up a while ago, but I haven't read it in a while.
Um, is Bail Jade still going on?
No, no, no, not, not Bail Jade.
I meant, uh, what's the first one?
Cannon story?
Yeah.
Cannon story is over, right?
Okay.
Uh, come on.
What the fuck?
There.
There we go.
There's only ever been canned story in Bail Jade, I believe.
Okay.
Apparently Hippo is somehow coming to content Lord of Ghosts and some of the various purposes.
And there's supposed to be some sort of like project around him, but I don't know.
You never, you never know what the Lord of Ghosts, never know what he's up to.
I did hear something a while ago.
I heard whispers of that.
I don't know anything about what's going on with that.
Um, I know that, uh, I know that the, uh, the Endless Rocks are, uh, connected to Hippo's
work.
Come on.
Is this a secret?
Uh.
Should I not go into detail about that?
Uh, right first couple are just known for breaking boundaries and being on the cutting edge of
news, of news and publication of all sorts.
The Endless Rocks are, are, are Hippo related and there may be, there may be, it may hint
at some kind of connection there.
Oh listen, all I know about the Endless Rocks is that they're buried deep underground and
you'd have to be some sort of like, like drill sergeant, a sergeant of the drill you may
say, to find them.
To try, to try mining for them?
Yeah.
You would, it would be a mistake and you would pay dearly for it.
I mean, think about, think of all the people who have lost their lives and the slime mines
already.
To, to try, to try and mine for something so elusive, you just, you just place your entire
day.
Um, you, you would, you, you would die.
You would die.
Like, you, you're gonna.
There's no way around it.
Yeah.
I want to switch so bad.
I want to switch right now.
Oh my god.
It is going to take me forever to get a thousand times.
But you know what?
What else do I have, what else do I have going on?
Nothing.
I've decided to go with the egg.
I'm so happy that the world, and by the world I mean Nintendo, which is the only world that
I care about, has finally accepted that handhelds are objectively superior to home consoles.
Uh, you know, I'm not, I'm not really that into handhelds, honestly.
They're, they're so portable.
I don't, I, I, whenever I'm like, oh yeah, I want to play some Smash Bros for fun, then
I, I have to like, walk, get up and like, walk over and turn on my Wii U and wait for
the Wii U to turn on, then I have to get my gamepad and I have to wait for the gamepad
to turn on, then I have to turn on my TV and wait for the TV to turn on, and then I have
to wait for the insane loading times to get Smash open.
Just a bummer.
It sucks.
Maybe I should uh, maybe I can just kind of grind toads in this level.
Ah shit.
Oh, is that how you get toads?
Well, well you get toads by when, by finishing levels, but this level has like, toad, toad
boxes kind of scattered around.
This might be a faster way to get toads than like-
Toadly boxes.
Yeah.
These are, these are outlined, uh, outlawed in Belgium, you know.
These are outlawed in Belgium, you know.
Did Belgium outlaw loot boxes?
Yeah.
Good on them.
Yeah, I know.
Does that mean that people can't play Overwatch in Belgium?
I think they can, they just can't.
It's like a form of gambling.
Yeah, I mean it is.
Yeah.
So, uh, I don't know.
I guess they just can't use loot boxes.
I know it's either at Belgium or the Netherlands.
Two very distinct and culturally distinct regions of Europe.
Well, I picked up, I picked up all the toad loot boxes in this level.
Looks like-
And you've died, and you've died enough times for a toad to have mattered.
Looks like, looks like they're not a renewable resource.
Well, I mean, dying doesn't cost you any toads.
It's just the time.
The time costs you toads.
Oh.
Oh God, that guy came out of nowhere.
Oh my God.
That's, that's vehicular toad sliding.
I'll be alright.
My name's Billy MC.
I make puns about video games.
Why, why watch in horror?
Is there being played right in front of my very eyes?
Sometimes I'll be holding down the mouse button and I'll just kind of like lose momentum.
That's weird.
Ah.
Jesus Christ.
This is brutal.
Hey.
Yeah.
Let's, let's, let's respond to some, a comment.
I don't know if I would consider it a complaint, but a sentiment expressed by, by some members of our elite, our elite, invite only gamer faction slash white nationalist lobbying party, known as the procrastiners podcast, fellow members.
Uh, both Digi and Jesse don't have any idea what's happening with Riferous Cup players lore wise.
I mean.
And they, and they think it's like insanely hard to get into.
Do you think that's, do you think it's accurate?
Yeah, I have heard, I have heard that sentiment.
And like, I don't understand it.
It's, I don't get it.
Like what's, like what's so complicated about it?
I don't know.
Maybe should we just, should we just explain it for, for the layman?
I'm sure that a lot of people, I'm sure there are a lot of weird like outliers who are watching this video right now and don't even know about the discord.
I'm sure, I'm sure that's the case.
Yeah.
Um.
These views gets like, like, like, like, you know, a couple of thousand views per episode.
And I don't know if there's that many in the, uh, discord server.
In the discord server, I think there's like 600 or 700 people, maybe five, 600?
I don't know.
How could you even be watching the show if you aren't in the discord?
How is that even possible?
Well, I mean,
How did the show exist before the discord?
I mean, before the discord, the show did not have, it just, it just lacked direction.
You know?
Mm-hmm.
Uh, it was,
It lacked vision.
It, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it lacked narrative stakes.
There was, there was no, there was no central antagonist.
There is no, you know, narrative.
No, there weren't.
And it was frankly disgusting.
Um, I look back on it with great shame, as well as terror.
Uh, okay, yeah.
I mean, maybe it's our fault.
Like maybe we, maybe we kind of like sell Rowdyfugger's cop killers in sort of a Namco Dark Souls
kind of way where we like play up how fucking esoteric and bizarre it is.
Did you say that that's true?
I would say that's true.
I think that's kind of the thought of it from our end.
Yeah, I mean, it's fun.
It's fun that there's so much more associated with it.
It all makes internal sense, but we know obviously to the outside world that the slime, that
the slime economy may not be inherently understandable.
I mean, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like the reason why I wanted there to be a slime economy was because like it doesn't make
any sense.
Okay.
Uh, like it's, like it's bizarre and like it kind of has this air about it that like,
you know, like the economy, like what's harder to understand than the economy?
Not, not much.
Um, you know, like you have to be like deep, like you, like you have to be like deep, deep
involved, but like, I don't know.
What the fuck am I even talking about?
You're talking about how it's, it's cool to exclude people.
It's, I mean, like, I want there to be just like a wealth of like mechanics in the game.
I just want that like all interact with each other and like are not confusing, but are
like maybe a bit overwhelming, you know, mechanically.
Um, if you're a fool, it will take you an afternoon to understand.
If you're a genius, it will take you years to understand.
Yes, exactly.
Uh, like, like, you know, I want there to be just like a whole wealth of things to do
and mechanics to wrap your head around.
But like, I would also like also want it to be simple enough that like you can ignore
them if you want, like, you know, you don't have to fuck around with a casino if you
don't want.
Um, I mean, I didn't want you to have to fuck around with the slime economy, although
the slime economy was broken and it was the only way to get ahead of the game before.
So that was a bit was not successful in that way, which is why we're revamping it now.
Um, but anyway, yeah, this sentiment that rowdy fuckers cop killers is like hard to get
into, I get it.
It's, it's, it's by design, but also I think it's, I don't think it should be entirely
like it's by design that it's hard to get into, but it might be too hard to get into
to the point where it might not be smart.
I think, I think that that is them like buying into our hype, you know, possibly like I think
they're buying into the hype that we have made because ultimately like understanding
the setting, understanding the setting of rowdy fuckers is not that difficult.
I don't think you need to be in the discord.
You need a PhD to understand why slime is valuable and why thousands of children around
the world have dedicated their lives to pressing exclamation point M I N E over and over again
for hours upon hours.
Like if, like if you want to be in the thick of it, right?
Like if you want to be on the cutting edge of like new Los Angeles city culture and like
being a taste maker and like, like, you know, driving, driving our society forward, then
you, then you got to be in the discord.
You got to be fucking, you got to be fucking, um, you know, actively involved in it and
engaged with it.
But to understand like what's happening and what's going on and like the history of it,
you don't have to.
Completely superfluous.
You don't need to know God damn thing.
You just need to be a cog machine and you fund the economy.
You don't need to know why you're doing it.
Just do it.
Yeah.
Just, uh, just, just consume, just consume slime.
Even though we've done it in a PCP episode, I still feel like we kind of owe it to the
audience who may be watching this right now, but still out there to the discord to give
them a little bit of an overview.
How would you, how would you try and describe the discord and not a Dark Souls way?
Okay.
Well, I mean, right now, I mean, I assume you mean like when it's active right now, it's
a normal.
Under normal non society ruining.
Well, it's a, you know, it's a, it's a, it's a community.
It's a community.
It's about.
You know, like, like we're all, we're all citizens.
We're all citizens of this, of this place.
We all inhabit this digital space together through the medium of text.
You know, we interact with it via commands, you know, and you know, you can, the different
teams, you know, you kill each other, but you can.
You're doing a shit job.
You do.
You are not.
You do not know how to sell a video game.
I guess not.
Well, how would you do it then?
Hey, the discord server further average cop killers.
Let's play series is actually not a discord server is in fact a video game that me been
cracked, mostly been and cracked have created.
It is a functional video game that you can play.
It's a text based game.
Yes.
But it is, but it is a game.
It is designed and how it has mechanics.
It revolves around players collecting slime in order for not only the obvious intangible
benefits of slime that we not need to discuss because they're too numerous and obvious to
stay here.
You collect slime in order to shoot people and order to have more slime.
Yeah.
Those are the two things you want to accomplish.
Yes.
And I mean, when it comes when it comes back online, I was looking at the design document
crack has, you know, crack has implemented an inventory system.
You know, we're ready for like items to start being a thing.
We just have to make them the PVP.
The PVP system is getting completely revamped.
There's just a whole bunch of shit.
There's like so much.
Yeah, there's Pete.
There's it's so fucking robust.
It's so fucking robust and I'm so proud of it every day.
And it's such a shame that it's offline right now, but when it comes back, it'll all be
worth it.
It might be up by the time this is released.
Maybe I'd like that.
Either way, if you want to know the current state of things, me and Ben are both dead.
We used to be king pens.
Everyone's dead.
We used to be gang leaders and we used to command an army.
I used to control the rallies.
We used to control the killers.
We will have gang warfare on a near constant basis.
But now a Cthulian, an Orwellian monster by the name of the negative sign was summoned
by the mayor of slime.
The recently elected mayor of slime city.
Well, well, well, that's not quite true.
It was summoned by the collective spirits of the dead who accumulated a million negative
slime.
So it was summoned by that, but it was activated by the Lord of Ghosts, recently elected mayor.
Who used two endless rocks to activate its power and bring fucking Armageddon down on
all our collective asses.
You can watch an animated videotape created by God himself in reality.
Locate on the Gibbon Fortress 2 YouTube channel for some reason.
Godwress in mysterious ways.
It's also on the Twitch, on the Rowdy Frickr's Cod Killers Twitch.
The latest video there is a highlighted, the conclusion of the mayor of the election arc.
Yeah, and slime fest too.
God, slime fest are genius.
Yes, the slime fest are genius.
Too bad the economy spiraled out of control and made them, maybe we can bring them back
and they can be a little more rational when the game comes back again.
Oh God, no!
You fucked up.
Okay, no, we're fine, we're fine.
I didn't know that could happen.
Jesus.
Anyway, it's beautiful.
Click the link in the description now.
And that's all the help you need.
If you guys don't still understand it, then I'm sorry.
There's no one that can help you.
Yeah, I think that when Jesse and Digi say that it's completely impossible to wrap your head around,
I think that's them buying into the hype.
Hey, I'm noticing-
And what hype we spread?
Yeah.
The frogs are just stacking themselves.
They're just dynamically stacking themselves.
How neat.
Should you wait and see what happens?
Yeah, I'll just watch them.
I mean, I guess if I watch long enough, theoretically, it might just become one huge stack.
We all sit silenced off.
Behold the majesty of nature.
Endless war is literally split in.
It is literally the same thing.
It is almost the same.
The mechanics are a little different, but the goals and the philosophies are the same.
Not even just on the surface level, they both involve obviously beneficial slime,
but on the deeper, medic and textual level of what I was describing earlier,
but it has to be so refreshing.
The series has been along for a long time.
Endless war is a relatively new addition.
And it's just instantly become the go-to game for millions upon millions of children to play day in, day out.
It's the new world of Warcraft.
I was just saying right now, it's the new world of Warcraft.
In this time of tired podcasts and boring rhetoric spread weekly, it's nice.
It's refreshing to see something with such utter raw soul.
You know, streamers are streaming themselves playing Endless War on Twitch.
Hundreds of thousands of people collectively watching live footage of Endless War gameplay.
And if you're not in on this gravy train, my friends, then you're missing out.
Society is leaving you behind. That's all I have to say.
You will be left behind if you don't correct your sinful ways soon.
Sooner rather than later.
Los Angeles City, aka New Milwaukee, is the spiritual home of Silicon Valley.
It's like the tech industry of the Silicon Valley.
But instead of tech, it's all the soul.
It's the soul and personal divinity and chakras and shit like that.
Yeah, you know. All the usual suspects.
Of righteousness.
Yes.
I mean, we have defined righteousness.
Before Endless War, nobody knew what it was. It was all a matter of opinion.
It was a mysterious thing to learn to only in scripture, but now other people know.
Yeah, we've laid it out. We've made it clear. We've elaborated the truth.
And that bell can never be unrun. Things won't ever be the same.
We've taken subjective morality and made it an objective universal truth.
Which everyone was begging for.
How are you supposed to have scruples in a society where morals are subjective?
You can't do it. And it would be embarrassing if you even tried.
We've spared everyone the embarrassment.
I would say we've created the structure for society's rest upon with this video game.
With this video game for children. I think we finally cracked the code.
How is a nation supposed to function? Intellectuals all across the world have been pined to find out.
How is a country supposed to be run? Is absolute monarchy a good idea? Should republics even exist?
No, none of those should exist. Only Endless War. Only Endless War.
I'm almost there.
All the time you guys were building libraries, you were building forums, you were building discussions on the internet.
You were building those? No. All you need is one obelisk. That's all you need to construct.
Did you see... Wait, wait, wait. Did I ever post that picture of me and AJ?
Me and AJ shoot at the real life Endless War?
No, what are you talking about right now?
We went and we went because I was passing through Washington DC and I hung out with AJ.
Oh my god, did I forget to fucking post?
Yeah, wait, what? I did not know this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Me and AJ, we saw the real life Endless War and it was grey as fuck.
I completely forgot. I'm such a retard.
I can't believe this.
Yeah, okay. Well, as soon as this is over, I'm gonna go get that out of my phone.
What did you guys do?
How embarrassing? What?
We just went and hung out in front of the real life Endless War.
Goddamn.
We walked around Washington DC and feared for our lives.
As you do. Even if you were in the real life Endless War, being in Washington DC should fear for your lives.
We contemplated the meaty theoretical question, the meaty philosophical question of whether we should be more afraid of the gang wars in the streets.
Or the evil lobbyists and fat cats in the Senate.
The jury was out.
The jury was out on that.
Speaking, segway into a conversation that that bores me less, yawn.
Like asterisk, yawn, asterisk.
Speaking of you traveling through Washington DC to arrive at Boston, where you are right now.
There's been like a sort of like sub-plot, a sort of like, like, you know, underlying narrative through line through the past couple of Ready, Focus, Guy Plis.
That has touched upon and briefed the segments here and there.
Starting in, of course, I think the, yeah, Fraud Fractions 2 Episode 1.
Or we're talking about gay-ass PCP friendship stuff. I don't even care. It's only to serve this in.
PCP HQ is literally real right now?
Um, well, I mean, okay.
Like, question mark, but stayed as fact because it is.
Well, what do you, how do you define PCP HQ?
There are three PCP members living in one location and I visit that location every three months.
There are, uh, well, hang on, there's me, Digi, Tom, Tom, yeah, um, three.
I think Nate's planning to move here.
You're here a bunch of the year.
Yeah, yeah, PCP HQ is real-ish.
Although, to my great, great dismay, everybody's on the fucking south side of the Charles River, like a bunch of fucking cowards.
I am on, like, the exact opposite.
We're on, like, exact opposite sides of the city.
Well, Ben, it's because you lack morals.
No, it's because you're a freak and a degenerate.
It's because I possess intellect.
Like, morals and intellect are the exact opposite.
They are the exact opposite, and the city exists on a spectrum.
At the south are morals, and on the top in the north is intellect, and I chose right.
I made the right choice.
You will be obliterated.
Uh, okay, I have a thousand. I have a thousand.
Oh shit, do one more, I guess?
Yeah.
Oh, I'm excited. Oh my god, oh my god.
I'm excited to see what happens here, but anyway.
I don't think anything happens.
In Frog Fractions 2, Episode 1, we were all, like, the discussion in that episode was like, first of all, it was like, the idea of PCP HQ, like, Luke Warm at Best, me, like, I was debating, like, you know, the, the, like, when it would have happened.
When it would have happened, if it should have happened, stuff like that.
And if it wasn't gonna happen, me and you were both, like, thinking, oh, it's gonna be in Atlanta.
You know, I had just recently flown out to see you. It's gonna be in Atlanta.
Yeah.
And, uh, all this first stuff.
It seemed likely at the time.
And, and, and just in the, in the series of, like, what?
Like, just a couple months, everything, like, changed.
Changed rapidly.
Yes.
Like, the, like, the first day that I met with Boss, or met with Digi in, uh, December, I believe it was, for, for the Double 8 times 2 plus 1.
Uh, I, I, like, like, first night, after that, Digi just was set on Boston.
Like, he just was, like, I, I keep saying this over and over, and, and Digi, whenever I bring it up around, Digi, she's like, it's not that big of a deal.
But it's crazy to me, because I never, never would have expected Digi to actually go with this, with, with this, uh, hope that I had that Boston would be the location.
I had no real reason to suspect that that would be the case at all.
Like, I was pushing for Atlanta for a while there, because I thought that's where I was gonna be.
Um, yeah.
And, like, I couldn't get it to, I couldn't seem to make it, like, stick in anyone's mind.
And I finally was just like, you know what?
I kind of give up, like, whatever, whatever happens is gonna be whatever happens.
And, like, obviously I can't do anything about it.
But the stars just aligned on Boston, and everyone fucking wanted to go here.
And, like, that's fucking cool with me, because that's where I want to be, too.
It's really a, a technical marvel.
It's a modern, a modern marvel.
That, like, like, somehow, not only was it changed to Boston, but just by chance,
you were kicked out of your house and you had to go to Boston.
I was not kicked out of your house.
I left my house, thank you very much.
Okay, okay, okay.
Uh, anyway, that, that, just, just all that to say, just by chance, not only was it changed,
but also you were able to, like, you were, you were able to go to the new place where it was.
Um, yeah, well, yeah, it worked out pretty well.
Pretty sick.
Pretty fucking sick, dude.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh, I'm actually happy.
Boston's cool.
Boston's real cool.
I don't think there's a, I don't think anything else is gonna happen in this game.
Yeah.
What about, uh, rush predatory?
What's that? It was the second option there.
Okay, no, that just shows you your toads.
Uh, well, maybe that will trigger an event.
The guy will be like, oh, I'll get all these toads.
Uh, I already tried it after getting it.
Okay, the one, the one thing, okay, some of these levels have like a counter on the side,
and I don't know what that counters for.
Um, the one thing I can think of is that maybe I need to, like, get first place in every level,
which I don't think I have done yet.
You didn't say that.
Also to get a thousand toads.
Yeah.
I mean, it didn't say that anything would happen.
Just said that they need a thousand, but I don't know for what.
For what purposes?
No, for research of something, of test research of how toads perform in road races.
The results are staggering.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Alright, you just finish this level and then, and then check your toads.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Let me do, uh, let me just circle around to the first level again to make sure that, like,
I don't just have to, like, clear all the levels one last time.
Like, maybe if I get to the point where that initial cutscene was triggered.
Eh.
Maybe.
Maybe, but almost certainly not.
This level's good looking though, I like it.
It's beautiful.
When, when, when I eventually do come back to Bosmos, it'd probably be sometime in, like, fall to winter.
Like, like, right first cop killers, unfortunately, like, like the live ones recorded at Radcom 3.
We're not, we're not up to par.
The one that was released was the MeMaker one, and the fuckin' WeSports historical and such.
Once, once, once me and you are not on any sort of, like, real time crunch,
and we're just able to, like, be at a house, that, that's, that's when shit's gonna go.
That's, that's when the real thing's gonna happen.
We're gonna be able to record, like, a Game Grumps-esque session, just release one every month or something.
Um, yeah, we should.
We should do that, just, just, like, a whole bunch of them.
Yeah.
How long do you usually come for, when you, when you come?
Uh, it varies a lot.
Any, the minimum, the minimum was five days, and the maximum was a month, so anywhere between there.
Five days is not much.
But a month is a lot.
Yeah.
Uh, alright.
I usually come for, like, the, the average is, like, a week to two weeks.
Uh, okay, you know what, I think I'm done with Road Toads.
Okay, cool.
Let's move on to the next game.
What, what is it gonna be called, like, the power hour?
It's gonna be multiple hours, though.
How long have we been, oh man, I played Road Toads for 45 minutes.
Uh, sick.
Uh, this will be called, um, the, the sweet, the sweet house of blues, addition, um, runawayfromsnakes.com.
That's a really good title.
Thanks, man.
Yeah, this is Run Away From Snakes.
Uh, it was programmed by Charlie.
Um, same, same guy.
Same, same guy.
Um, but, uh,
also, it's based on the character by Hippocrite,
and the model, I believe, was done,
the model was done by Tom, Polystation 2.
I think he only did the character model.
I guess he didn't do the walls or anything, but I don't know.
The only thing that I'm sure he did was the, the character model.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god, this is cool as hell.
Have, have you not seen this?
No, I've never seen this before in my life.
Uh, yeah, it's awesome.
Oh, I will, I will do something, and I will, I will show you,
because I asked Hippo about this before, and the answer was the breathtaking.
I will, I will attack a statue when I see one.
Missed it.
Oh shit.
Great.
It's actually really hard.
Like, it's very, very difficult.
Is, is, does it change every single time?
Yeah, it's procedurally generated, so you can't just, like, learn the pattern.
Oh there, you see that green stuff that came out?
Yeah.
I think that is slime.
Whoa!
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Whoa.
How can we get our hands on some statues?
Uh, I mean, they must, okay, serious, serious.
Imagine, imagine a room, imagine a location in, in the discord, in New Los Angeles City,
that's like a statue, and like faction members can go there and use break statues for slime.
Uh, I, I, I, I, I, uh, oh, fuck.
Oh, there has to be, yeah, there has to be a solution point break.
There has to be, I've never, yeah, of course, of course this has to be here.
Yeah.
You want to make, you want to make, make a state from snakes real, make this cannon?
Yeah, of course.
How, how do we do that?
How do we, where are we, where are we in the fit statues?
Well, okay, so raid bosses are going to be a thing, right?
Yeah.
We could have things, they wouldn't be raid bosses per se, but we could have things that
are effectively raid bosses that are just inanimate statues, and maybe people could
break them in the combat zone or something.
Maybe, what if instead of them being just things that people fighting, they are items
awarded to people in the way that, it's just a cutesy way to hand out slime, so instead
of giving someone slime, you give them a statue which they can then break in the slime.
Oh, kind of like in Dark Souls, you have a soul item, and you break it to get the souls
inside or whatever?
Yes, yes.
Yeah, okay, I would be okay with canonizing runawayfromsnakes.com.
Why are they like little spears?
Why are the slime little spears?
Because it was probably easy to model.
Okay, that makes sense.
Would be my guess.
Is there an int of this game?
Yeah, there is.
Apparently, you can win the game if you run far enough, and then you can unlock endless
mode.
More like endless war mode, am I right?
Oh no.
Oh, but yes.
Oh, this game was beautiful.
Oh, it was really fun.
It's very difficult.
At least I'm finding it very difficult.
Also, I just switched positions, I just switched to laying down, and the blood is rushing
in my head, and I feel like I'm going to pass out.
Oh, that's right, you don't have a chair.
Well, you were telling me about this before the show started.
Why do you not have a chair anymore?
Well, I couldn't fit, all right, so when I was getting the fuck out of Georgia, I had
initially planned to rent a U-Haul to pack all my stuff, but, uh, God, how to fucking
diplomatically explain it.
Well, this is right, I figure it's cop killers.
This is known for our record-breaking news and publication of the quote-unquote real
shit.
All right, so the plan was to get a U-Haul.
I went back to get my stuff, but I went back, I used Econ's car, and obviously, I could
not fit, you know, there were a couple things that I could not fit in there.
My desk chair, which was pretty big, my squat rack and the weights, which was very upsetting
because that cost me a couple hundred dollars, and the, um, oh, it was the last thing.
Oh, a drawing table, but the drawing table was already missing some parts, so that was
not the huge loss.
Um, all right, so I packed these into Econ's car, and I went back to Econ's place, and
then I was just looking at the prices, and it was like renting a, renting a U-Haul would
have been like a couple hundred dollars more than just renting a regular car to make the
trip, so, and plus like going back for my other stuff would have been, I didn't, I didn't
want to do it.
It sounded like a fucking, like the worst thing ever.
So I was like, all right, it's, I'll just fucking, I'll eat the loss, I'll eat the
loss on the items, I'll make, you know, I'll save a bit on the, on the transportation,
hopefully it'll all come out in the wash, and I won't have to deal with a bunch of bullshit
that way.
So yes, I left my desk chair and I have yet to get another one, and my sitting, I'm starting
to get, it's starting to, it's starting to wear on my, on my back, the, um, the sitting
situation.
Well, well, what are you doing now, if you, if you, if you don't have a chair, what are
you sitting on right now?
Right, I'm just been like, I've just been like sitting Indian style on my bed, and
I have like a low table next to my bed that my, that my computer is, is on.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
It's, it's a bit chist.
Yeah, yeah, I can imagine, are you gonna get a new chair?
Yeah, man, when I moved in with Digi, we went like hunting around at thrift stores looking
for a desk chair, and we found that one, and it was like a, a big leather, like swivel
desk chair, um, for like $15.
It was like so cheap.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
Like, I honestly thought that the tag was missing a zero, um, but it wasn't.
It was actually $15.
So that was a good one.
It probably was cursed.
It had a soul of a dead person though.
I mean, sure, maybe, but, uh, never, never, fuck, never bothered me.
Ah, Jesus.
And then, and then the thing, the thing ended up getting clawed to fucking death by a cat,
um, down there.
So that, that sucked, but whatever, it didn't, it didn't affect the usability of it at all.
Uh, but it's you, but you really suck at this game.
Huh?
You really suck at this game.
You think I really suck at this game?
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah, that is what I'm saying.
Is that what you're saying to me right now?
You keep, you keep dying on the one that's just like you jump.
It's a, it's a, it's a difficult, it's a long jump.
Like it's like most, it takes up a lot of your jump arc to make it.
Well just hold it, just hold it down.
I am holding it down.
You fuck.
You're so mad.
What are the...?
Jesus.
I must be pretty behind on Bill Jade because I do not know why Pump is holding a Keyblade.
Oh, you'll, you'll find out.
Oh, oh, oh, looting.
Oh god, I didn't think I was going to make that one.
Come on.
Is there any reason to not just keep swinging your thing in hopes of just getting a statue?
Um, there's that because it would distract me and I really want to focus on making the jumps. Oh, fuck damn it
That one came out of nowhere. You saw that
Of course of course you do
You know you know what I'm fucking talking about
Of course
What are you gonna do about your squat rack is gonna I mean I I mean I guess just it is gone now
But it is it is gone now. It is gone now
And that's okay
You know I actually got it for a pretty good deal much like the chair like I paid like $300 for it
But that was like a steal anyway, that's not important
What's important is that it turns out and I did not become aware of this until I had already come back
That this house that I moved into which in case I didn't mention this already
It is the house that I was living in before I moved in with Digi in
They actually have an almost identical rack in the basement
So like it's fine. Yeah, like I didn't even need that thing anyway
And I mean if I ever move somewhere else, yeah, I'll have to replace it, but you know, that's okay for now
I fucking it's all it's all good
You know I've even looked at because if you decide to take it you might have like that might have been the straw to make you get a
U-Haul
Wait, what it would have wasted it if you decided that it was indispensable
And then you got on a U-Haul and you just would have to have the same thing anyway. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
I basically would have spent that money for for nothing
So it's probably you can find out you can find you get it. I made it. I escaped the snakes. Oh my god, that's beautiful
Yeah, all right, oh
Oh god, whoa. Oh
Yeah, there's a there's a there's a leaderboard
Uh
HIPPO said that HIPPO said the Connor was the leader before but apparently Gwyn has passed in whatever that is
That score looks illegitimate. I
mean, I
Wonder like let's see. Okay. I recognize Connor. I recognize meaty learner
These are all
Yeah, our rats lemon tart. Yeah, that's HIPPO who the fuck is that?
Yeah, dax tier our it's again
Ice killer your mom. Yeah, my favorite. There's a bunch of anti-cheats
All right, yeah, all right, so a bunch of bunch of cool dudes playing this fucking
Yeah, if you if you um
This by the way, you can play this on HIPPO's website
Like in browser as like a pay a comic page
Although it takes a while to load
I'm just okay this time. I'm gonna try to hit all the statues
Fuck no, you're not gonna be able to do it. We should move on to the next game
You think I should move on to the next game. Is that what you're saying? Is that what you're saying to me right now?
I think that's what I'm saying. Is that what you're telling me that you think I should move on to the night
Oh, whoa, there's a double animation
Wait like look I swing back and forth. Yeah, okay
All right, the main event this was this was baby shit
This was pushy shit. We were I want to show I want to show what happens if the snakes get you
Whoa, yeah
So, uh, all right, and I guess I have to fucking control all delete out of this one as well
Oh
Road toads is still running
We're on the main event now. Yeah, the real video game a real one
Instead of I'm gonna make the room right instead of a mere facsimile of a video game an air sats video game
If you will like what we've what we've had to deal with so far
Like this
Aerodynamic school been what what everyone went to aerodynamic school been you you can't use such fancy language
So thank God I've got some fucking Pepsi zero left
I I this is a good time to any I have made another vow
I this this second
Revolution in my life, and I had this is my the second time I have made the vow to give up soda
All or I think more specifically it was all sugary drinks in general. Yeah, yeah, but you can still drink diet soda, right?
Yes, but that's not it's it's all sugary drinks and also soda in general
I mean do what you I don't understand why people have I mean what's wrong with diet soda it well first of all
It tastes disgusting. No. Oh my god. Oh my fucking god. Everybody says that and I don't fucking get it
I don't fucking get it dude. Wow. It's almost the word taste that everyone argues everyone has different ones and you know
Is based upon actual real taste with your tongue?
Understand I just cannot understand how people can be like so disgusted by diet soda like yeah
I can taste that it's different, but it doesn't taste worse like at all to me
I don't want to say it
Because I know like oh you're an apologist for diet. So like oh, you know, I don't want to drink my car
It's fucking whatever your own monster. It tastes like ever so slightly different not even in like a worse way
It's just a little different, but that just terrifies you doesn't it you're scared of things that are different
Munchy the only thing I'm scared of is the warts and pimples that I grow on your fucking body
When you keep drinking a diet soda wait are is getting warts and pimples a diet soda thing
I thought you just got brain cancer. No, well the same thing you get warts on your brain. Oh
That explains that explains a lot that's been going on with me lately here get in this game right now
Mr. I'm very upset with you
Yes, yes, sir. Yes, sir. Oh here we go
Here we fucking go. Oh my god, okay nuclear throne
This is the first game we ever played I'm fucking refuse hyperlase at that point
It was not a let's play show it was like a podcast and we just played it and we did not have
Visuals and DeVue was just charm. Yeah, DeVue was there. Oh my god. Okay. I'm not literally asked DeVue is on right now
I'm gonna get him in the call. Well, we can't play with him, right?
Like he has the game. Yeah, well, no, but we can't we can't do co-op with multiple more than two people
Can we yeah, we can wait really? Yeah. Oh shit
I'm ready
I'm I'm I'm messing Jim right now. I picked the baby mode character
All right, I will keep watch of the DeVue situation
He might be out of the house. You might not be able to be here. Let you know as soon as we know
What's the steroids wall? Yeah, it's just a split the hideous. So
Yeah, I know
Playing steroids is for cowards of which I am one
The only time you've ever looped is when you were with me correct
I think I might have looped once like later on my own
But when I was playing with you, we looked twice which was unprecedented. Oh
You'd look okay. Okay. Oh, wow fucking got wrecked by maggots
All right, let's get rhinoskin probably wait, do we do we share upgrades? Yes
It's cool, yeah, I like it by the way some some fun facts cuz because I'm a I'm a deep lore nuclear-grown nihilist
Uh
Rami Rami Ishmael one half of the NBA creator of this game was on record that online multiplayer with nuclear-grown was
Literally impossible. It could not be done with the video game
And then and then and there I was the most requested feature
Everyone wanted it and everyone was clamoring for it and and he said it was literally impossible
This is a quote from Rami we can find on the wiki. What a fucking game
And then and then in comes this hero this unpaid hero
veteran nuclear-grown player just just champion of the people a yellow afterlife who just makes it
Who just make it not only does he make on the list or makes the four player multiplayer?
Okay, that's fine. Oh, did I fuck up? Oh, you want to get this also? It's fine
Wait, what is firing gives ammo for your other weapon? Yes, it's very good for steroids. It's very very. Oh, is this the one that like depends what character you're playing?
Yeah, yeah, okay
Although I actually really like gamma guts a lot. Oh
I had I have oh
My god, okay, I have no I have no weapon right now. I
Have almost no ammo
Okay, don't worry. Oh, okay
Shoot shoot you fucking idiot. Yeah, shoot
Shoot, okay, you know what that's fine. That's fine
Well, we'll make it we'll make it better
The book the longest I've I say alive. I think it. Oh, yeah, I died on throne two loop three
So I was just about to get to actual loop three and then I was destroyed
We're gonna go all the way here. We're gonna go all the fucking way here on the on this show
Yeah, we've done it only my favorite game is literally my favorite. Okay
I have not played nearly as much nuclear throne as I have binding of Isaac, but I think objectively speaking
It's probably a better game. Oh, of course. Hey, okay
The body of Isaac I respect because it's like saying that you don't like cities in Canada
No one will take you seriously. There's no reason to even voice your opinion on the subject
But I cannot play by an Isaac at all. Oh, it's
Trigger fingers it makes your reloads shorter if you kill people which is extremely important with YV and steroids
Okay, I
Hate the way I
Hate it so I like the way Isaac looks, but I do not like the remake. I think that the remake looks worse than the original I
Hate it just like looks like new grounds
It does. I don't really mind that so much. I
Think it looks gaudy. I think it looks old like they look slain
But nuclear throne is beautiful and all it looks it just looks like
Both impact risk and back muscle are I think second stomach
Say something's good for survival if you're pussy. I am a pussy. That's why I played steroids. Okay, that's fine
Jesus I okay, I've actually been playing this game a lot lately
You might not be showing right here, but I
Played this game in well over a year. Oh shit. I'm out of me
I'm out of it. Oh
Okay
No, no come what the fuck don't worry. Don't worry. You know click on me again click on me
You cannot do this. You cannot do this alone. You need me
But look on me again look on me again, what is going on?
We're
Okay, we're a beat we're exploiting a mechanic where if one person dies another person gonna revive
No, that was parted. What was the point of switching it back and forth?
So, okay
You have a timer with when you when you have when your course you have a timer before you are just
Like dead forever and that timer ticks down. So it's evidence for you just switch. Who's playing who's not over and over again?
I see I see
I
Think it's like right right in a skin
Okay
Rasky is way better than second time. It's like it's not because I was thinking I was looking at back. Was it back muscle?
Also, we can go to the secret level. Oh, let's do it or whenever you you ready I guess well, we have to wait to three one
Oh
It feels good it feels good to play this game again
It's it feels it feels it feels like like like oh my god. He's here. Okay. Don't worry. I got oh
God what a spot like like I'm like I'm in my youth
I think I think we're throwing is my third. I'm gonna see how much hours I have in this game
All right, I have six hundred and thirty nine hours
Is the other ones he is number one TF to yeah team for king for just do I have two thousand six hundred?
Oh, we should get blood blood lust, right? Or no, yeah
But both both are extremely good. Um, let's do I keep running out of ammo. Oh, yeah, maybe
But both are great yeah, I
Six hundred and I think thirty nine hours
I used to play it all the time as a kid, but ever since like
2013 I've had fallen off of it
Oh fuck shit, I'm still a master we should do that we should definitely play TF 2 on here
There's a lot of games that I want to play on this show that we just can't
That we just can't do to the fact we're not in person like like I really want to play the subspace atmosphere
That's one of the best little ones. I want to do ever since the show started and we can we like we can't really do that if we're not together
Yeah, I
Think there's a way to maybe do it with project him and homebrew and like online play with that
But it's just not it's not the same as as vanilla bro
Oh shit, don't worry, it's fun
There's a lot of bandits right here
Quite a few bandits quite a few bandits riveting commentary right here. I got a fucking topic
I
Loose it by late spoiler like like like behind the scenes back to do right now
We're recording this right after the podcast episode of the PCP
So if you want to watch this in chronological order from our perspective watch that first I
I I mentioned our point that I only briefly touched on but it was one of the first topics they wrote down for this episode
Here
Here hold on can we switch
Is there a weapon up here that we can switch? No, there's not. Oh, yeah here right here. Oh, this is just gonna cut damn
Okay, pick up that screwdriver
Uh, what with the ladies just press press E. Okay, how do I like okay?
How do I switch which hand I want to pick it up in?
You press spacebar
Yeah, we need the
screwdriver
Come over here
Come on
please
Okay, press press press on the car press on the car
Press on the car. Yes
Here we are we're in secret level now. Oh, let's get through a bit. Yeah
They'll help out your ammo. Oh, so you have the disc on this is gonna go terribly
Oh
Please please please. No. No. No, please. Okay
This is this is too stressful situation. Uh, the topic is
I've I've said the n-word now. I can never be president
I've seen a lot lately about how like like I I I've I've been led down the path of an internet
Okay, click on me. Yeah, you've been you can't you need to click on me as soon as I die because you cannot do this alone
Fine fine. Yeah, I want to I want to be a different character
I mean melting is my favorite character. He's the coolest character, but like wait, what the fuck is frog?
Frog sucks. Don't be frog
Uh, can do
Okay, this is fine
What was I saying? Oh, oh, yeah, uh
I I I've grown up on the internet and now all of my like gross weird team
perversions in the dinner seat is now just on the internet forever in like with the way back machine
Yeah, yeah, like there's no point in my life where I was not posting art or you know doing weird shit online
Uh, so now my entire life even like stuff like my real name
Just easily be found online and there's nothing that I can do to reverse that and do that fact
I can never hold a single political office
I just can't do it if I were to you would find my old like forum roleplay is I mean I would be laughed at the white house
I mean unless like
I mean, maybe that stuff could be hidden
With like some serious effort or like money or like funding
Uh, or unless unless like something seriously shifts with the culture
What did you pick?
patience why
Because we want you to get more better ones first. Okay
And it's not even like I particularly want
to be like the president or anything
But just the feeling of like like knowing that my life is
like
I don't damage
I don't say damage, but I'm definitely forced into a life now where where where my entire reputation
Is laid out for like an easy dual search and now no matter even stuff like
I'm coming for you
Like like I probably cannot collaborate with like small time more liberal minded content creators
Like at all they would they would just see what I've said online and think no
I don't want to participate with this person even though like oh, please bloodlust would be great. Yeah
Uh, then oh, this would be good for you. I wish you get this
Wait, isn't that only for melee attacks?
No, okay
Even even though I am I am a libtup just because I've said I've said retarded shit online before
Now I'm now I can never I can never undo that. Uh, I don't know. I wouldn't say never. I mean dude
Okay, hip-hop made this one vlog about how some I don't know if this route would sit away from that
You can damage it some I forget it was some youtuber was on some sort of british tv show
And people from like TV producers just like dug up some tweet that guy had made when he was like 12 ahead
The inward on it and he was kicked off the show
Uh, my god
Well, yeah
I mean, that's pretty bad. That's pretty bad
Yeah, so I'm like there's nothing I could say to dude. Oh shit. Apologize
Or do I even truly believe like I should but that just means that there's no there's no life for me
There's nothing I can do to right these wrongs that I've done
plutonium
Both these are good
up to you
I like this one more. Yeah
It's so it's sort of like I think I took about this on long step away. I'm gonna destroy this
I
Think that's why I feel this on ready for his cop killers. Yeah, I think so
Uh, uh, what specifically about how I it's been scary
Because obviously, you know, I've been around the pcb all my life and you know, just
Generally people have this meant that college is bullshit and a scam which okay, sure and I mean, you know, I still agree with that but
the like due to that fact when I when I was not so
What's the word?
Smart and I was just willing to believe with you with you know,
Everyone really was saying online at the moment. You know college is bullshit. You can't on corn food to do
I I I will admit I let that impact the way I thought about the world and the way that I like took school
Seriously, yeah, and so for like a while and like freshman for freshman year of high school
Like I just didn't give a shit about anything because I was like, oh, you know what?
I'm to get through high school and it'll be fine because I don't really need to have good grades and have to go to college
I don't need that because that's where I want to come like and even still that's not where you want to take my life
I don't want to go to college
But knowing that like I did really poorly in freshman year probably know
Like college will want I probably like will not appease
Buck up. No, no go off. No, please
Uh, no one will like wants to take me in. Oh god. So fucking cops are here
We're we're safe
And even though oh, yeah, oh this oh
Look at this look look at what we're doing right now
Uh, just just the fact that I am closed off from going to college
Is scary. You're not you're not close. You're not closed off from going to college
I don't know dude
If it feels and you know what what do you want? I think I mean aren't aren't these like bad
Yeah, all of them are bad besides this one which has some good to it. Let's just do none. I don't want them
Okay, I don't want it
I I know I know that I can probably get into some college, but like I don't know like like like what if
You know like lately I've been thinking our college seems pretty cool
TBH like it's a lot of money, but like it sounds like it would be a good time
It sounds like it sounds like it would be a good time. Yeah, it sounds fun and everything
Yeah, yeah, it does
Stuff but so
Well, make make maybe I'm not even sure if I would want to but maybe but but maybe I would want to do that in my life
Maybe that's where I would want to go. I don't even know if that is the case probably not
But think about how I how I decided to go with like, you know, the the choices I've made in my life
I've I haven't gone the best grades. I probably don't have a portfolio. Oh, what the fuck?
That that would they would impress many art college professors
And and I I I I've taken to putting most of my time into online stuff and if I were to go to college
I wouldn't be able to put in the time and effort that I would need to make good on
I mean, but it sounds like no off the side off the side. Please come down
Come down off the side off the side. Please. Please. I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die soon. I'm gonna die
I mean, it sounds like what you're upset about is that you're gonna miss out on a good time
Which I mean, maybe yeah college is pretty help help. No, I I'm sure it has practical benefits as well. Sure
Oh, fuck
And it's it's not it's I it's not even just college
It's just the the idea that I've made such choices that are blocking off from other paths in my life
Such as becoming president or going to college
Oh, shit. Oh long arms
Long arms. You want this? Okay, sure. What would you want to do? That are gamma guts
You know, that's cool. I have I mean, I like gamma guts because it can prevent you from taking damage from touching things
That is nice. It's about that
I am like out of
Don't worry
I should concentrate very hard. Really and now I'm actually out of ammo like for real
Due to Pluto, I keep killing people and then like stepping away to let you get the ammo, but then I suck it up anyway. Yeah
I I have 10 bullets for my fucking
Well, it's because you're you're you're fucking you're meleeing right now. So you're like
You're right you're right in the thick of it
Whenever whenever I play co-op. I always like forget what character I am
So like even though like oh, we don't have ammo right now. I could be spawning my ability
I could I could be doing that. You know what rebel is meant to do
Yeah, they could be doing that just be just maybe
Wow, it's been worked out well
Again, you stole my ammo. God damn it. Uh
Either this or this either one, uh, let's do uh
Let's do second stomach. Oh wait, this one is not about Pluto
Jesus what were we talking about?
Uh, we're talking about how you can't go to how you're closed off from college and being president
Oh, yeah
Because I've said I've said I've said the in world like nobody can be president right like to
Like that's not a thing that most people actually have it. Ah shit. Shit. Shit
That's not a thing that most people have any chance of of doing even under like the best of circumstances sure bin
It's it's it's it's the principle of the matter. It's it's not the specifics. It's the principle of the matter
Oh god, oh fuck
Ah, fuck
And and and what would be the solution that I guess I would just have to change my name but then but then but then I don't know
Yeah
Oh, I hope I hope we get bolt marrow. I even autocross bonnet. Oh, so this is where a little hunter spawns
I'm I'm looking for a shatter right now
Oh
Hey, if I shoot a rocket and it hits you will that kill you? Yes. Uh, that's really bad. I should get rid of this weapon
I killed killed the little hunter killed them. Ah, I died. That's funny. That's funny to me that's happening
We oh, oh
Oh my god, can he can we can he get in here? Can he get in on this shit?
I'm adding him right now. Oh my god. I am a little worried that he's gonna be a liability
I mean, I'm I mean, I'm already a liability
No, no, no, no, no
Wait
Am I not friends with the devu on discord?
On discord?
Yeah, yeah, not friends with the devu on discord. Uh
Huh
Hey, I'll be right back. I'm gonna grab another pepsi
Okay, gross
Hello furious, what do you think? What do you think of my current predicament? What what what do you think am I making am I making something out of nothing?
Have I just been too reflective?
It is is the path. I'm not I'm on honorable and not something to worry about at all
Let me know I'm talking about this with DeVoo. I'm sure DeVoo will have some mad thoughts about this
And now we enter
Yes, it's a right now thing also, they can't hear us
Be as good as you need a Pepsi right now
Well, I'm glad because that would have been a total surprise
Um, okay. Well, give me a minute. Uh, I don't think I have nuclear zone downloaded on my computer at present
Uh, could you get it? I'll have to read download it. Yes, but I don't I mean, you know
I have only mildly terrible internet right now. So
Shouldn't be that hard
You'll also have to download a mod but the mod is like you just export something into a folder
Is this mod all like required?
Yes
Oh, okay. Well, uh, send that my way then I will
You you have to download it just just click on download
And then it will like be like do you want to pay money?
And then you will click no and then just download the most recent one. Oh, shit. Oh, it's online. Oh, we're gonna actually do this multiplayer
Yes, of course
good
except for the whole
I
Oh, jeez. It's almost half a gig
Uh, no promises. I can do this right now. It might take a while. Oh god, really
Yeah, I have a gig my internet's great. It's like 10 megabits per second. Oh, Ben. Are you here right now? Yeah, I'm back
Could they hear us during that? Yeah
Oh, lol, haha
Don't worry. I'm always on my nuclear toes
We're all here. This is the original group. This is the original trio
Uh, well, but what's this about what's this about popular and ready fucker. What are you debu?
People have been calling you the original and the classic separately
Huh, what's your title? I don't know if you know about the gang warfare that is
Spawned around debu. Do you know anything about the rat what this current state of the rowdy fucker scop killers?
I know nothing about its current state. Okay. Okay fair enough
You're living under a fucking rock my friend
Aren't you guys like in the Grand Canyon?
Uh, we're on we're on the edge of the Grand Canyon
It used to be the Grand Canyon before it was flooded with a nuclear waste aka slime
Luckily, they download going pretty well. It's estimating in over three minutes. So that should be good
So are you gonna are you gonna finish up this run? Are you gonna join our fucking co-op?
I've been invited. I was like, oh, we're gonna be on variety fuckers. Sure. When will it be?
I get a call instead of the answer. What I am gonna turn you
That's how I do things around here because you are a little quieter for me
Oh, god, right. Okay. Am I quiet in general me? I need to turn up my uh, no, no, no, you're good. You're good. It's on my end
Uh
It looks like this download nuclear thermo together has like nine different versions
Do I need to just download the most recent one at the top? Yes. Yes. Gotcha
I
Do boo you you you are a conserver god. You are an intellectual unparalleled in the sphere in which we operate
Ben we're just going to head to head and an unrivaled debate for the century. Also, Ben, I'm gonna start
Oh, what a debate you say
Yes, and am I debate? Uh debate. I mean me whining and been listening
Right
Non-relate political
Uh, anyway
The premise is this
Wait, wait, wait. Did you start the game? Yes, dude. I'm gonna pause it. I'm not looking
Okay, okay, great. Uh,
Don't worry me, dude
Sad I'm sad aim slash or frightened
That I may not ever be able to be president because I've said the n-word online before
Oh
Well, my take on that is that within the next generation
I'd probably have said this on pcp within the last couple months
But my theory is that when we get to the point that millennials start running for presidents
Uh, all of their dirty laundry will already be known, right?
Everything will already go up to like peak Lewinsky within like a week of people googling your name
And so the only way to become a politician then is to either
Be a surile voice out which doesn't exist or if you just still fully own up to everything that people
Say about you i.e. That's just locker room talk, baby
Okay, so basically you say it won't manage us
And this is the way that the world's blowing and then it will just it will just be commonplace for people to be
To have all of their secrets aired online if you're getting big shots to me debate for fun
I mean, yeah
Culture and the guy is saying I can't believe
Okay, if you're like if you're running for president someone
Fuck tv is like chewing you out to your face. All you gotta do is just be like
Man, you're right. I did say the n-word. This tune's got a point
Oh god
Oh, hey, baby. I've just been impromptu invited to at least make a cameo appearance on the rally fuckers top killers episode
So
That's what i'm doing right now. Do you have something to tell me? Do we need to go in the other room to say something?
No, okay, you're just gonna take it back. Okay. She's invited on. She's invited on too
This is a communal show. This is this is the show for the people
Show for the people. Okay
So let's see. Um, almost downloading their throne. I've got the uh, I've got the uh
extension downloaded
All right, I don't I don't see how we can accommodate more than two people because like there's only two
Sides of this like character selection. Ben this goes up to four players. It's not it's not
Hey, what's up?
Yeah, that's supposed to be frogs you can see
You can see what's out. Oh, yeah
Well, oh no, no
I've been impromptu invited to a podcast all of a sudden after a minute ago
So today is unfortunately not a great time to be on on calling me. Why are we both toad?
This is this is the fate we've done. Yeah
All right. See ya wait, are you leaving?
Uh, okay
Oh, um, okay. Bye
I like that. Hey munchie. Did you decide did you decide that you would be pink and I would be purple?
Was that deliberate?
No, but it worked out just well. Yeah
All right, let's see here. So, uh, where do I go to get to
I'm right clicking on nuclear throne on my steam library. Where do I go to like to the file?
All you have to do is right click on your phone then then on top of these
And then it should be in the third tab. I believe uh files
Yeah, all right. Yes
all right, so
Of the other my other windows got the nuclear throne 9 9 2 1 nuclear throne together
I mean do I put the
Folder in there or just some of the files? No, just just extract the entire thing into that folder
Gotcha
All right. I dropped an end. So do I hit plan nuclear throne now?
No, you actually don't you you sir you what you do is you
Uh, click on the file run tt
Uh, yeah, yeah, I think it's actually compile tt something that effect where it's it's a it's an application
Uh, that has tt in it and it's it's asking you in tt assemble. Yes a symbol a symbol there you go
All right, so you run that
So let's say I have install nuclear throne together just just do that option. Yes
Gotcha
Couldn't find game files with assets. Did you extract the files into the game?
Well, I extracted them and then moved them over. So I guess I have to extract them directly in yes. Yes
Okay
That's the kind of shit that makes operating systems fucking confusing it is
All right, this is this is my life also. I hope that the trope of
Another pcp member joins refrigus cop killers only to receive technical advice is an is another running theme of the show
Because I've already done with it both sign up a minecraft server
It's still saying I extracted it directly into my nuclear throne folder and it's still telling me
Couldn't find any game files with assets
I think what's going on here is is a nuclear throne together is a separate folder within my nuclear throne folder
And it's just all the files have to be scattershot inside the same files
Yes, gotcha. That's what you meant by has to go directly at first. Yeah. Yeah
What a mess like like someone comes in my room and tells me hey throw the socks all over the place
Like uh ocd
You you will never be able to find the original files of that game
I guarantee you you will never be able to uninstall this whatsoever
You just you just you just need to say that that will never be a part of your life again
And
Once you install that all you need to do is click on nuclear throne together
They'll be like nuclear from together
Got exe and uh, you'll be good and you'll be ready to play
Ben you're getting shit on you do not understand the the mystique of frog
You told me the frog sucks that was your words
Yeah
So now they open up a nuclear storm on steam as usual. Yes
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, I'm sorry. You don't you in that folder that you were just in you know
The one where you put everything in oh, it's I'm gonna dive and you should probably click on me
Uh, you run the file that is named nuclear thrown together. It's you you can just search for it
All right. All right. Uh, this is together that you actually gotcha. All right. And now do I have you on steam?
Do you have me on steam? Uh, I don't know. What's your steam man?
Whoops. Oh geez. Oh geez
Uh, hold on. I'm just the devoo on steam. All right. I should probably put on a headphones, right?
Uh, I mean if you want
Oh man, you still have your old you're really old avatar. That's really cool
Where?
On on on yeah, yeah, I like having uh, we're probably not steam friends
A diagonal slice of all my old icons throughout the web, you know
All right. I feel like friend brings a tree stump or like different layers of civilization as you dig, you know
Yeah
Hold on Ben. Let let let let's wait for the boob. All right. Yes
You have to accept my friend request
Oh, except your friend request
It's uh
You you've clicked on the game and it works. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. There you go. I will invite him right now. I'm making a new video
Uh, how do I make the fucking screen bigger? I kind of need that. I got some full screen. There we go
Okay, uh co-op I'm hitting co-op so local 2p local
4p
I don't know what's next here. I I'm going to invite you right now. Hold on
Ron, do I have any do I need to record my own audio? No, not not at all
How convenient that is number one best way to persuade guests to come on your podcasts
Don't ask them to record their own audio
This is the shanty town operation
This like it's been said time and time again very frikus copcola is is the show of the people
There is no it's not only it's just the bourgeoisie of the public
This is a down-to-earth working middle class podcast that brings you the raw untainted shit
This is not this is not polluted by the ideas of the the uh, the upper class
Of the monarchy. This is just for the working the working common man
The working common man
Also, why join both of you
Who do I join? What do I press uh press tab shift? Oh, yeah. Oh my god. Holy shit. I totally forgot
I've never in my fucking life done any of the uh social media options of uh steam
Because I've never actually like don't anything with any friends in steam
Oh
Never even like I just tune out the fact that I can do shit like that
Operation gay rights obliteration. Here we go. Oh, here we go. Yeah three slots. Uh, fuck. I'll be eyes
I'll I'll be rogue. I am. Is anyone lagging a lot? Yes. I'm lagging hard
Is that because of me? Yeah, probably that's fine though. It's not really
It's really nice pretty bad lag
Okay, I I'm I'm used to playing on 2b2t where there are only two ticks a second
And it and it feels like you're not even planning him and you're actually just walking inside a slideshow
Of what your actions would have been two minutes ago. This is this is unplanned
Yeah, no, I don't know. I don't know why
We're fine. We're fine. Look
There's like a quarter. It's like a half second delay, bro. I don't know man. This is uh, yeah, this actually sucks
This actually sucks
I love that how like you're like trying to pretend that it was okay. It lasted like all of 10 seconds
Yeah
Well, it's it's because I tried to turn a corner and it like took a second before my character to even start to move, right?
Also, who's a rogue?
Oh, cool. Wait, is this competitive or cooperative cooperative?
Okay, I've been trying to slow place to shoot at you guys this little time
Well, it doesn't matter
This this won't work didn't realize we both had purple or is around us
Oh, I was hoping you'd have a blue
I'm shocked that I've been able to survive as long as I have
Don't think it's my fault though because uh probably is
I don't have the best uh
The best of king on my internet today
Yeah, forever. No forever
Well, well, well as foreshadowing you you did say as you're down this oh happy. Goodbye. I don't know if I can be on this episode
Yeah
I've never had good internet
God damn it
You may be realizing part part of the reason why I've never done social media shit on steam. I can't play online games
Yeah, I guess so. Oh, oh, Jesus Christ
I've never had good internet. I've never been able to play online games. Fucking ever the only time I had good internet was in
Freckin, Virginia. Why don't why don't you get better internet?
Oh, wow. Yeah, man. Check your fucking band with litch
You can't go out into the store and just get better internet. Oh my god. We're so
Every single time it's limited based on where the fuck you live and I've just always lived in shit places
It's
No, you can't you fucking can't oh my god, this is like telling someone hey like why don't you just get a job?
You know what I mean like
I mean, oh, it's true. All right. I could say so
I live in a small town, bro
I live in a small town and like my internet was all right
No, no, no, I'm sure you're right. I'm sure you're right. It's just I'm surprised
Thank you surprise. It's not like I have been frustrated about this for literally 20 years
Or anything, you know
It's not like I haven't spent the combined total of thousands of hours
Googling different providers that could provide always just narrowly not being able to access my exact fucking street
And and even when even when you live in a suburb suburb like I am it's always like you're gonna have the best area at all
I I just spend a ton of money to get a good router like I have right now
It all it all depends on if you have enough money to shill over to these fucking people
We're trying to fuck you over every second that they get. Those phones are for buyers and the internet
Suppliers do not care about you at all. They don't care about where you are
All they're looking to do is make a buck and you've been are just privileged to be in a scenario where not only are you in a city
But you're able you're able to spend your money frivolously
Doing nothing all day in order to get your internet to be where it deserves to be in order to play an online game
Pity on you to look down on us for just being the common working class people
Yeah, we're trying to make a name for ourselves in the world Ben and here you come looking down as a chip on your shoulder
Yeah, I'm pretty bougie. I'm pretty bougie
bougie
Well, hope you're having fun. Glad it was fucking worth bringing me on
Holy fuck
Uh, all right, let's stop this
No, no
What do you mean? Why?
Wait, I mean is the game just completely frozen for you. Yes. Yeah, let's let's not do this anymore. I hate it
Well, I mean
Well, it's compromise. What compromise on the issue. Let's go. Let's let's meet each other. Oh, yeah
Oh, it's running like a dream now. No, let's fucking drop the charade
Let's drop the charade
Wait, did you believe
Wait, are you are you melting? Yeah
Well, maybe it's still kind of it's still kind of like delayed
It's means the game auto said it's like it's like king mss
Uh to
Let's restart
Okay, that's fine. We're still on the call
Yes
It's in it completely he says, okay
All right, let's sorry I knew again. All right. Well, that was that that that that was the cameo
That was debu. That was debu everybody
That was that that was the cameo everyone
That's right. That's what you were all here to see
I'm I'm I'm glad that he was able to rekindle the fiery passion
Yeah on the original uh episode, you know, it was just like old times
Yeah, this is this is real stripped down memory lane. This went exactly how I remembered it last time
I'm pretty sure that the original reference hot players was the first time I was ever on any internet show ever
That might be the case. No, you were on the pcp before that
No, no, yeah, it wasn't
No, dude, I that was before that was before means the need to die, but you've been on as a guest
No, no means the need to die was to my first appearance
What no because yeah, no because the rowdy fuckers cop killers the first one I had already moved in with digi
No, you hadn't yeah, I had I think
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, that's that that that that was before radcon one
No, it was not. Yes, it was it was way before radcon one
Uh
Well
It was it was one of the first like 20 uploads to the channel
Uh, my god, uh, well if you say so
Yeah, I know I know
Okay, well hot damn
Uh, yeah
Time flies
You overestimate how much of a presence I had an early pcp. I was I was I was but merely a specter in people's periphery
Hmm
Get in here. You you you must play the game. You must do it
Wait, what?
Join the game. Uh, hold on
Hold hold your horses
Oh, did you say well hey, you know my internet doesn't die that much
Uh, it's actually the most I actually have the most stable internet I've ever had
It's only like just crashed randomly about four times the whole time
I've had it. So I think it's just trying to give everyone a vertical slice of all the things that can go wrong with my internet
Yeah, uh, I guess I should just play this again. No
No, no
No, I mean would would the results be any different?
Well, hold on. I'm actually tethering my phone right now
So that might be better. I don't know you want to try. Okay. All right. I'll give it another try. Yeah
Yeah, see if my phone's better. Although it's also going through wi-fi. It's not really tethering. It's just
Turn my phone into a mobile hotspot. I can tell it's not entirely my internet's fault because
This is clearly not well optimized. I'm sure it can't be too optimized and it's simply a mod
mod for game that is not
normally
Don't don't blame the game
Don't blame the game
Hate the player hate the player not the game as the saying goes
Join what are you doing right now? I joined the game. I joined. Yeah. No. No. Davoo's in here. Ben is not. Oh
Don't don't you undertail it me young man, uh, all right
All right late 2015 indie games straight motherfucker
I'm making a um
Sorry, I'm I'm shrinking
a uh
The the collection of art that I did on this on my stream yesterday. I'm shrinking it down
What we're in the middle. What we're in the middle of a recording. I know
But you know
Okay, you know how I go. I forgot. Have you ever have you not smoked weed yet?
Uh once
How was it?
It was
Weedy when
When was that when was that?
Uh, well, it was
It was literally right after we recorded the uh totoro cast which uh, that's
Uh, it was just you know, my wife's sister's weed. So it was like sleepy weed. So are you guys married?
Yeah, we're not yet
But yeah, I'm doing the same thing digi does of like fiance is a weird like posh word that you try to avoid because it sounds
Takes too many syllables, you know
When the only reason you aren't married yet is because of fucking like health insurance
Then why not just call them a wife? You know, what do you mean? You're not married because of health insurance
Well, because when you marry someone it like, you know, your health insurance all sorts of like fucking red tape shifts around
You know, but my fucking my fiance is still on her parents her mom's health insurance, right? So like if she gets married
You don't have that wait. That's that's where the
Insurance if you're married, yeah
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, man, this is the fucking libertarian wide government marriage
Fucking controls your life, you know, we also moved back that getting married would only increase your options for health insurance
I mean it opens up other doors, but it closes other other doors
This is part of the reason we moved back to oregon is because of health insurance reasons
It's the fucking government taking my guy damn the money
And then giving it back to me under their conditions libertarian
Funny you should say that. Um
Now I did not move I
One of the one of the best things about that. I'm back in boston. Okay, um
Georgia is a nightmare hellscape
um
Where I'm gonna let you finish Ben. Yeah, join the video game. Oh fine. Whatever who fucking cares about video games
We're talking about health insurance. Wait, I didn't get an invite
Jesus Christ. Oh wait, there it is. Okay
uh
Georgia is a nightmare hellscape where you can be too poor to qualify for government assisted healthcare
How the fuck does that work? Yeah, um
It's literally the worst place in the world
And I hate it and I and I hope the whole thing burns down
What what's even the point if you if you can be too poor to do the thing that poor people need to do?
It's just run. It's just it's just an evil place. It's just an evil evil. Watch. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Okay. My ping is insane
It's insanely lower insanely high insanely insanely bad like the delay on my input is
Yeah, I still have some pretty bad delay, but clearly this is actually like running at something resembling a framerate
Yeah, yeah, yeah, like I'm not freezing anymore. It's just the delay is massive
It's like running smooth but I still have delays
Do you do people get to play online games and the fucking computer does what you want when you fucking push a button? Wow
No, that must be great, huh?
It's nice. It's nice
You know, I want you to go on the record that digis internet despite having despite being quote unquote good
It was very unstable. We crash fucking constantly. Well, they're probably like a thousand people using it at the same time
No, they're really
You weren't that many people. No, it was just it's just a big
That was just like weirdly wired and shit or you know, whatever
Hey, both of you were in we were in the highly experimental
Digi house and you both and you both have gone on a grand adventure since then
Well, how would you rate? How would you rate the fall of rome to a k a the fall of the house and the years since then?
Like like like who's liking all these buildings the fall? Okay. I was
I was kind of disappointed when digi house fell apart
Uh, I was sort of confused as to why it was falling apart
because there seemed like
I don't know like a bunch of things happened in a row that seemed like they could or would
Spell the end of digi house, but then they didn't
and then ultimately it was just like
Digi's parents were just moving back
Or something I did for being I died what became flipper over the course of winter 2018
And was pretty should have been clear if fucking fall 2017
Is that digi wasn't ready to live with a bunch of dudes he needs a fucking girlfriends, right?
Wait, what do you mean ready to live with a bunch of dudes he needed a girlfriend?
Come put on me someone. Well, what does it mean?
Let me fucking watch it. Why?
Uh
I'll rephrase it as uh
Digi was really bored and lonely
Yeah
Boring moved in and we didn't fix it because we don't have tits
I mean, I was pretty bored and lonely at digi house too. I mean, I like hanging out with you guys, but like, you know
Yeah
You know, well, I was I obviously was too except that my standard for what is boring is is pretty fucking
Extreme so like it was still like having anyone at all was more than I was used to so I was fine
You know, I don't have like depression problems. So I can like make I can compensate for a lot, right? Yeah
Uh, did you just couldn't you know?
uh
I mean, you know, he was
I hadn't been going through a couple of straight years of working in my house all alone like he had at that point
Right, like like as digi was continuing to lose his mind and not knowing what he wants
I was on fucking dating websites just
BAM me everyone was fucking messages until someone liked me and then got hooked up, right?
Yeah, but you got an internet girlfriend
Yeah, but it was
I mean, I know it is more than that, but like right, okay
Like when I was in boston at first I was on I was on tinder like before I moved and I would and I was getting laid with like
Not all the time or anything but with like, you know some regularity and it was pretty all right
I moved into digi's place and
It's remote and there's nobody and like there's fucking nothing and I after like six months after like several months there
I was like, oh
I hate this
I was flying there except for the fact that I like did he was fed up
Like did he wasn't was just stressed out all the time and you know
my favorite my favorite is the fact that
Oh, you know, he's all right
to put him on low mid-key blast and shit like
for the several months leading us up to us moving in me and digi were
Constantly talking about how we were going to become a fucking like rlm style like vlog fucking
Super team, right? Yeah, and what happened was right on what I minded goals, right?
I was fucking ready for it. Did you made whole vlogs about like talking about ideas you wanted to give and so like
What happened then was when I move in the day of rad talk, right?
So
Radcon happened so after radcon is over digi's like burned out, right? I didn't understand us at the time
I've me and digi both have obtained much greater empathy
Fucking autism treatments thanks to having spouses, right?
But at this time our ability to like get what the other one's vibe was on was pretty minimal
So digi's all burned out after radcon, but I'm just like aching to go. I'm ready to go, right? Like at this time
All of 2016 has been this huge rush of getting everything I wanted, right? Like I finally quit my fucking job
I was finally able to do that and then I became a pcp member and then I like
Save up money and get an all-new computer and then I moved in with digi, right?
So it's like all of 2016 I'm writing this massive high of finally getting everything I wanted
Whereas digi has just been in this big slump for over a year, right?
And he was just really counting on us to get him out of that slump
But it wasn't really right. So day after radcon's over
I fucking go up to him and I'm like, yo, let's make content. Let's do it, you know
He's like no like like giving his like super tired look, you know, like
Ah, no, well
So the the next day happened and it's like, all right, dude content. Let's do content. He's like, I don't like content when we do
Right. So like four straight days in a row. I was like the last day. I was like, yeah, digi
Content, let's do content
I don't think you're being fair because like you can't just say let's make fun like what does that mean?
Like you have I guess
Fair enough, right? But I mean, you know, I mean
Hey, that's fair. I think it was also fair though to assume that like, you know, he's the creative director
He's the one with, you know, leading the charge. He's the one who owns the house, right? But I mean fair enough
I no no no fair enough. No, I totally go to mean I could have been more proactive about it when radcon was over
I'm sorry. When uh, when I moved away, did you like made a couple of videos where he
He kind of made it sound like it was all my fault. Did you was like, yeah, you know
Like the vood like wasn't getting the main videos done fast enough to be been working faster
I would have done more vlogs with them. I didn't get that five
I didn't really since get the sense that digi ever was like antsy to do videos, but right
I didn't really like seem like he enjoyed it. You know
uh
People don't like watching things with me because I get too excited and talk over it a lot
You know, I mean literally
If someone just reminds me once a month, like, hey, you stop talking over it. Oh, right. Fuck forgot us on how that works
Right. Gotcha. And I will but digi at least at this time isn't someone who will say things that might sound offensive, right?
Like I know I know I'm not supposed to fucking talk while I say things or while we watch things but uh
I get really fucking into it and I need to be reminded sometimes
Because I mostly watch stuff by myself and I'm thinking out loud of myself so when I'm watching something with people
Whatever the point is digi wasn't having any fun
Doing videos with me, which is why like you could like if you look at like every video featuring digi bro
and go through a timeline of around
Oh, when was it? It was like october 2016 through
April 2017 me and digi did like all of four videos together
We did one let's play series one vlog. That was it. Right steroids. Click on click on her click on her steroids
Oh died immediately again
Uh
No, we're not so I didn't get the same decision
I wanted to do shit with me because again the whole time he didn't seem enthusiastic about it like
Whatever and the reason why I didn't start getting videos until late is because I had been acquired a girlfriend
So, you know, it's been enough time on the shit
You know, but whatever um, I think it was just sort of a feedback loop of like what me and digi wanted
We're in opposition, right? Like I wanted to do more shit with digi and uh
Digi is just emotional energy for that and for me. We're very limited, right?
Um, because I'm very impatient and fucking speedy, you know, like I just like, okay, let's do this now. Let's do this now
Let's do that, right?
um
Like I'm like Casey Neistat without any of the hand-eye coordination
Is he renowned for his hand-eye coordination? I don't know but
Well, like he rides bikes, right? I mean, I got okay, okay
I don't think I could ride a bike in a city. I would immediately hit a car
And I I don't actually know how to ride a bike. I don't actually know
Really?
We are a post millennial. Holy shit. Yeah, I thought I was a loser when I when I didn't learn to ride a bike until I was like nine
I
Oh, shit
On the subject of being way too personal for literally no reason
Yeah, true
I remember there was one point in the chat. I don't even I I think I know who said but I'm not gonna say in case I'm wrong
And I don't want to be wrong for no reason. Uh, there was someone in chat who
When when we were talking about some like, you know, like retarded like long forgotten rk
Group drama. I just remember what was uh, there were there was something said on the subject of like like like you guys
being like
What was the term?
Turned into feeling humans by the hand of your girlfriends. Well, so I'm gonna come and save you
Who are you talking about Davoo and digi? Yes
Yeah, uh, where I I I think it was you if I was digi, uh, it was like one
One person was like my girlfriend comes up to me. It's like, why can't you guys just talk about it with
Talk about this issue with one another. Why can't you just talk to each other's face and come to an understanding?
And then and then he was like
What bit like babe? We're guys. We don't talk ha ha
And I remember very true that stuck with me as probably the most retired thing I've ever heard in my entire life
Like like probably the most your your post
It's not it's not a gendered thing to come to practice what how is that not a gender thing?
How is that not a gender thing? The whole thing is you're guys. We don't talk
I know it shouldn't be that way because that's required
Because because that makes no sense in fact, it shouldn't be a guy thing to do that because it's like
Oh, I'm gonna take matters into my own hands. I'm going to solve this. I'm gonna solve this right now
The very simple binary
If you want to act like a good person but without the moral courage required is to either
Uh be way too self-sacrificing to a to an extent that you cannot be right?
Like tell yourself you're going to be patient with people to an extent that you don't actually have the emotional energy to do
Or then just get so mad at them and so accusatory right that your accusations don't actually have much to do with what's going on
Right, so if you stick between those two binaries of either blaming yourself completely or blaming other people completely, right?
Then you get to be purely offensive and purely defensive without having to actually like
The reality of what is happening and what your problem, right?
Don't know what you're talking about. Yeah. Well, you know big enough. Whatever. I mean my maybe I wasn't paying attention
No, no, I was pretty big
Okay, shit. Shit. Shit. Ow
I'm using all my people's body shows right now
well
Anyway, the point of that is that you don't have to be a guy or a woman to
Face your problems in in the eye and you know take the bull by its horns and get things done
I think that's a pretty you know
Gender-neutral things do you want to solve problems? I will clarify though
Talking with people is something I'm fine with doing
Being all emotional and shit before I had a girlfriend very much so
Uh, you just want to honestly if it was like an issue with like
Ben maybe or you munchie, you know, I'd be like, okay, let's talk about it
It was with digi who was specifically like making speeches about how it's a good guy thing, right?
I want to specifically remember I say I I don't remember who said this original thing
I just know it was said in in this group and I thought it was
I feel like I feel like that's a digi thing to say
I feel like I said it but then I don't think you got it. I don't remember saying that so what
I don't remember it. I don't remember but it's just it's just a thing. I I hear it's not like it's just you guys at all
I mean, you know, it is a common name to be like, oh, we're guys
It'll work itself out. So to me when it's just
The problem with living it with digi became or not really the problem so much as the inadequacy of living with digi
became very clear when he moved in
And he started doing videos with her, right? Yeah, and okay. Yeah
What did you was saying after operation rad con castle?
Collins castle ended what did he suddenly his vlog was talking about it was
Yeah, you know, I realized within one week that me and dibu just have incompatible
stage presences, right?
And also sort of like work presences like I you know, like my type of work energy is different from his
So I guess it just makes him feel unwelcomed or
Um awkward working with me, right? He says that he likes working with jesse because jesse works the same speed as him, right?
Yeah, whereas I like I just I'm just too spastic and fast
again like without the hand-eye coordination so
So all that happens and digi mentioned like that was why we ended up not doing vlogs partly because like we just have all these very different energies
and I just want to say like
The original plan was to go to rad con and just do it as a trial run before deciding that we were gonna move in
But then digi's parents sort of like sped things along with the plans of moving out
And so I had to be sort of bite that bullet and take that risk, you know
That's what I was going to do on that record, right?
Why can't I not do it?
Why could I not do it? I was like clicking
And then what happened was once he moved in with may, uh
Immediately he started doing videos with her and people very correctly point out that uh
Their uh, that may just wasn't good at being on screen, right? May had this very different energy the slow energy
Just awkward in this tour, right?
And then did you was like, oh, don't worry she'll get better, you know, we'll work on it
And I'm like, ah, there we fucking go, right like with me. Did you just decided that we are
Personality's weren't compatible within one week. He gave up. He gave up the goose in five days
But with may he's willing to uh fucking spend months nurturing
Wow, I wonder why that could be
Right. Yeah. No, I get it though. I'm not like
Like I get it though. Yeah, he needs a fucking girlfriend not a dude
He doesn't want to like spend all day watching anime doing vlogs being in a sweaty room with another guy
He needed a fucking girl. I get it. No, it's totally fair, you know
I I might out myself as a faggot of unbelievable proportions, right?
But may I just say for the record for my own self?
I I I know that I am the outlier in this belief and way of thought
But I don't really feel that different talking to women
And I don't mean that as in like a like
Like somehow like I've caught you being sexist in a way
But I just I it's it's hard for me to relate to people who have different
Who feel like there are different airs talking to women
I don't know if it was different. I don't know if it was a gender thing. I don't know if it was like because you guys are guys
And she's a girl
But I definitely felt different talking to my ex-girlfriend than to you in the sense that talking to her
Was horrible and made me miserable
Talking to you guys was fun and I like
Well, I don't yeah, I don't know if that's a gender thing. It might not be a gender thing might not be a gender thing
Right now, uh, I definitely the distinction between talking to many women is definitely different now that you know
I have a girl person
So it's not like as much of a I don't feel as awkward about it because it's like all right
I don't have to like think about them and I and I can be pretty confident that they are going to like
Be suspicious of me because I have a fucking partner, right?
So that just makes me why would they be suspicious?
You know because you know like
You know if if you know a guy is taken then you know the odds of him like being lustful of you have produced
Not gone to the hell but just gone down percentage wise, right? Sure
Right
That just means I can feel more relaxed around women now, right? I get that. I totally get that
Especially with my girlfriend look at my fiance with my wife with my partner with my life partner lgbt is there with me
Just run down the mall also provide
My guys took all the
So yeah, Ben, uh, how
abreast of uh, Jackie's situation is the general public like like how much I've not said her name yet, so
That should
Wait what really? I mean
I was avoiding it. Yeah
Oh, well shit. Okay. Cool. Don't worry avoid. I mean it doesn't matter
It probably doesn't really oh, I will probably edit it out. But who cares?
Worry not. This is the rfck. So yeah
Wait aren't people sticking to this live?
How have how abreast our people? Uh
Not very I'm gonna die
Probably I mean, okay. I'm sorry if I'm gonna edit out here, but I'm just too curious. What is uh
People know that you went through a breakup, right? Uh, I think so. I mean, that's that's not exactly a secret
Okay, and people know who it was that you were with up to this point, right?
Yeah, that's why I don't think it's a big deal
To say, right? Oh, I don't want to go. I look. I don't want to go fucking saying her name
You know what? No, I am gonna edit it out. I would rather I would rather not talk about specific people
I shall not bring it up at all. I will be only reactionary about anything you want to say. No, I mean
I mean
man, it's tough because I like
Obviously, obviously I have a lot of feelings about it, right? Obviously I have like thoughts about the situation
Obviously you want to talk about it, but you're very much very probably very rightly afraid of your own desire to talk about it
I am like fuck that. I am
I don't know, you know, they say they say if you don't have if you don't have anything nice to say about someone
And I have nothing I have nothing nice to say
And I want and I want to speak and I want to say a lot of things out of anger and frustration
But I don't I also think that doing that
I also think that doing that is a bad look and I don't want to be that guy
I don't want to I don't want to be the guy who's going around shit talking his ex and making that a thing
So, you know, whatever
Yeah, definitely
Absolutely, it would be easier to talk about if it's a relationship where like both people are at fault or no one's at fault
You know, but when it's like when the only way to say what you're feeling would make you feel like a huge dick
And it's like well your hands are tied. Yeah
Pretty much pretty much
Nuclear phones too easy. I'm glad they added a five second delay to all movement. I think that's really increased the difficulty of this game
And I think that it's a little increased longevity. You're welcome. You're fucking welcome. By the way, debut
This is going back to what I was talking about earlier. I'm very happy to went on this big long digi house rant
Uh, and I and I thank you for it. But also that wasn't what I was talking about
Well, I well, hopefully it can be informative now that I've explained like where it ended, right? Sure
My maybe I just want to talk about is is just how like like you and ben have both come out of the same experience
And now you both are kind of in opposite scenarios
I would say kind of. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Um, well, I mean, what do you mean? What do you mean much?
What do you mean by an opposite scenario?
You round up exactly where you were right before you went to the house and debu is now is married and inordinate
Well, oh, oh, that's right. That's right. I was thinking you were still in
Fucking right, please. Don't worry. Don't worry about not keeping track. I've been very I've been very like
Minimalistic you're working. Hold on. I'm a little confused though
Does that mean that like you just moved from someplace where there was no good internet available to another place?
So there's no good internet. That's how I fucking like this, bro. I mean
You you were proven to be a villain earlier. Why must you continue to fight on this hill of being as happy with that?
Why would you do that?
Decide how much I want to talk about this. I might have to
I'm gonna I'm gonna clear it with cold first to see like how much detail I get into
Uh, I'm listening to going close the corner here. You're right back
This is fun debu's cool. Uh, I'm I'm enjoying him
I'll be enjoying him. We'll see how well he does. Oh, yeah, we'll see if he passes the next trial
I'll be enjoying him. I'll be enjoying him
All night long
Please click on me. You will die if you don't revive
There are you fucking happy?
No, nothing will ever satisfy me. Oh shit. I'm dead
Help
Help. All right. I'm back
Oh, yes
Just the man I wanted to see
Shit. Oh, well, it's over. It's only if you've been in a circus prison
Glad to be going right now
What was what's the word?
She gave me part as she had before she gave me carte blanche carte blanche to say whatever
But I want to be because like like, you know, she hasn't been internet famous yet
But like I've been you know
The thing is you feel like you're famous as soon as people are pissing you off because like they don't really know you
But they think they know you know what I mean, like that's the fucking definition of celebrity. It thinks the internet
It happens just news. You got five thousand subscribers, right? The word famous has become
You know, it used to be a giant loaded shit show now. It's a tiny microscopic shit show
uh
I don't like talking about myself that much
Because people will then come in and like talk really invasively about you like they're your fucking friend
And I hate them even if their advice is good, especially if their advice is good, you know, yeah
so
You know
Especially if you avoid anything specific then people won't know what to do with you
Here's what's going on. Oh, no, sorry
So once it was clear that we needed that we're like we need to get out of digi's house, right?
We need to like move on because digi needs to explore the world at this time
digi was talking about buying a fucking rv
So he could just like
There's so many
By the way, in case any of you think this talk behind his back. I know did you listen to this right now?
So I I'm speaking. I have so little space right before about the
In time I don't
Of course
No, I'm saying nothing about that, but all I'm saying is that there are numerous numerous ideas that you can come stuff with
Like becoming a mo been working on
Uh lately becoming a hentai manga artist in a month. Yeah, that's that only grow
Roman the world in an rv
Roman the world in an rv was not
I actually thought it might happen for a bit there, right?
No, I was speaking
This was a plan that never should have been uh talked about digi may not talk about this to you
But munchi digi was contemplating like bringing you on his rv adventure. Oh, I never heard that
Yeah, he was like yeah, munchi's a genius. I should bring him in on as my protege in my rv
I had never heard that
I never heard that you never wanted to be released. I don't know. Maybe those would be his plans
Maybe him and maybe him and may will kidnap you at some point and they'll adopt you as their child
I think I was aware of some sort of kidnapping though. I didn't know
This is actually a weird sort of thing with digi
What is that was his last girlfriend did the same thing right like talked about you like like you were just
Oh, oh, well, that's entirely other weird thing by digi. I don't I don't think many I don't think may as indeed do that
Uh, the weird thing about digi is that he likes me a lot
Yeah, which is very flattering and I'm very happy and occasionally to like say like munchi's a genius
I'm like, I mean wow. I think we all like you a lot. I didn't feel that way about
No, what what do you mean? I can't even give anyone a good
Well, I'm sure like I get the impression that like, you know people like like me
And so I think you're the one holding the pcp together more than anyone else right now
What what what does I do?
You're the only one other than Nate who's like willing to like really like
Put a lot of effort into the group and like do a lot of things help organize shit
And like put in a lot of energy for it whereas like most of everyone else is half-assing it me especially
Well, no, no, no, no, no, no
Well, because I think it's cool. Exactly. Uh, I mean, thank you everyone
I
This is all like that one on the pcp where Nate was like we all like like where where Nate said something nice about me
And I thought that he was he was building into a joke about how I wasn't cool at all and he just stopped there
I'm like, wait, did they just compliment me with no with no hint of insincerity
Did Nate just do anything sincerely? Yeah, uh, this is nice. Anyway, I was just gonna say about digi
Uh, like he's like
Of the way that digi is now the way that the life is it like I won't ever see him
For like a long time, uh, which is getting better now
But I usually don't see him for like, you know a while at a time and then we'll just come back
And I'll just get some whiff about how he's called me a genius in some podcast and I don't know how to respond to that
I don't mean to imply that like I'm like, I'm too sheepish to be like, thank you digi
But I don't know how to like should I like message him and be like, thank you for thinking that I'm nice because because I sure
You're nice
So hard
So weird and difficult
What the fuck does he want from people, you know, I I watch some some
Off off, you know one off a thing that he and may did
On the krupping your tit channel, which I did not watch at all. Basically, but I got I got with this
Shout out to in in obi noby in the rck chat. He told me on to this
Uh, it was it was one where he like talks about like how I made that burky stupid like funny thing at red con 3
That was like, you know, like like rating all of uh, my like like our our our like stat progressions
And and and he was like sad that like he was not that he was not higher up on my friends list
I didn't realize the digi felt that way and I'm really sorry
I didn't mean I didn't I like I didn't know that you
Like wanted to be friends that bad, I guess
Oh, it's kind of it's kind of weird to say I like I I never really like I like I knew digi like respected me for a while
But like more and more he's like acting like I'm real cool and stuff, which is really humbling and also like
I don't want to say the word weird. I don't why I don't want out digi
I don't want to make you feel like like weird at all
It's it's it's more just like
I'm stunned before ever
You were really like knowing anything about you or even seeing that much of your heart
Uh, digi had already built up you in my mind is like this like fucking like emergence god of like fuck fuck fuck help
21st century digital
died
Uh, well, I'm happy. I I I really did not mean for that to turn into a dick sucking moment of any kind
I just I just wanted to shout out my home dog real quick
Because because I see you I see you out in videos sometimes dropping my name
And it's increasingly like more and more like you did that in a recent gecko estate and whenever that happens
I'm always caught off guard and and and for all honestly
I'm surprised that you're not that cognizant of like digi's value of you like to me
It's a very known thing to my knowledge
I think it's because I'm I think it's because I'm a little like like low-key retarded. Yeah, and and like
And and and and like with with with the pcp inherently do the fact that I was a fan first
I I I always feel like like like I'm an ancient spot
In Greece
Like like I'm an ancient sparta in Greece and like I've invaded someone's homeland
And I will always be seen as an outsider to myself even though no one sees me
See, I hated it when did you call me the ascended fan boy?
I'm like, dude, like we all started liking each other's videos and then we started talking and then did you was like
Oh, well, you see before I ever before hip we ever watched my videos
I saw his kid up for me compilation videos and I first saw you debut as a commenter
So therefore you're the ascended fan boy. I'm like, yeah, I don't I don't like the sense of hierarchy that you established with that
you know, like we all like
Like it's it's not the same thing as like game grumps where you have like a couple of like serious celebrities
Or in this case just one serious celebrity who other people then latch on like we are all our own entities first and foremost, you know
So I don't have to say something that may seem woe is me in faggity
But I don't mean this in any drudgery term or to imply that I am disney's franchise at all
But I kind of don't feel like PCP mirror is kind of like a feel like a piece of key intern
Or like someone who's just kind of like
I think you're the number one PCP member other than maybe Nate
Really?
Yeah, I mean you're the most fucking no participative
I I think it's because I joined in the same update the same patch that mumky was added
It would have been just kind of feels like further reinforced that if you weren't a brony then you will not be a PCP member
We tried adding non-bronies
And it's brownies only we just like malaria. It never goes away. It never leaves your system
We just didn't share the history with the other people like I think that's why it was a mistake
Like that's why we should have known involved like like yet
So even though me and munchie were brought on like later, we were there like watching it happen since the beginning
Oh, yeah, it really was like the fucking the forging of the fires was 2013 and 14
Period and they'll never be more members. I don't think other than maybe some seven-year-old, you know
Who was watching back then who becomes like ascendant?
No, no, this is it. This is it. This is it. You know what would be great is if like like that fucking character from the last
Bit of bakuman shows up but for us like someone who was a kid
Watched our pony videos and now tried to create like a fucking sub industry of video makers to compete with us
I would kill him
and take his fans
Yeah
Well, in any case, thank you guys for being alive. I guess I don't know it feels gay
And yeah, I've gone full circle from having uh for for having sincere beliefs
So like for like for like the the jub now not wanting to express
How you feel about people and not wanting to express your beliefs in any way to the i'm going to express myself
And and and give love and happiness to everyone I meet and I wrap back around to
What what what what have you people done to earn my my love? I will give you love. I see this
Yeah, I'm just not used to people liking me still
Let me really start happening until the pcp. I didn't even really say a little bit
Right because I didn't have any human work until around 2013. You know, I there was no reason to like me
So then when I find out that people like ben like
What when I found out that ben wanted me to go visit atlanto with him and digi
I was like what the fuck someone wants me to go to a place with them. What the fuck people like me
To boot that is such hashtag just teen things to me. That is that that is so fucking relatable
Why do you why do you use the hashtag just teen things in place of hashtag related?
Because that's what is in instead of relatable. But nowadays it's hashtag just teen things
That's too specific
Have you have you seen the tumblr post that are just like an image of some teen looking up the sky and it has a lot of
Like filters over it and they'll be like when you do your homework and your teacher gives you an a plus
Because you did your homework just tag just teen things
I'm getting a instagram account called it just a dean at things
Oh, and it'll be like like a dean of a college. Yeah, it's like oh well your students
When you're when your students don't riot and demand like better better pronouns or something hashtag just teen things
How does one deal with insomnia slash extreme paranoia hashtag just teen things?
I am 13 which means not only my old enough to use twitter, but I can use the hashtag just teen things
Which is very important to me
Hey, I think it's a snow plow today just teen things
I did a daydream most of the time at school just hashtag just teen things and then hashtag
Yeah
I have now done my market research. I shall now make the hip trendy
Uh character design
Hey, by the way
Since we're on this whole retarded shit that everyone hates uh divu
I actually really like your illustrations. Like I really like i'm glad. Uh, yeah
You you're I hope
I can be like as I said in the art podcast
I can be like zoom a terrible artist
But with like an aesthetic sense that people then like and then make fan art of that's actually good
Yeah, the best part in in like, you know, all the gg was up. Yes for it
Do it now. I said old david gg videos. I'm getting so fucking mad at this game
When did you will have some sort of argument where he impersonates another person and then you'll draw you'll draw a little guy
I love it. I love it
And I only ever do that when I'm like completely out of other things to use for illustrations
Which I struggled with much more back in like 2015 and 16 now like
That's that's why I get very triggered anytime I see a video where obviously the person or the team making the video
Like didn't know what the show is like
Really stupid the show, you know
Oh, you mean like extra credits for a little duel of pun
And uh, yeah, well, it gets so much worse than that like I mean, I would say, uh,
Getting things there is much worse of puns, you know, but like there's this one like, uh
Sort of like a buzzfeed type of channel, but not buzzfeed and like they would like
Like because like Cole was watching like a video like speculating on like it was like a wreck it roll two theories video
And I was just watching over
Out yet. Yeah, it was like theory
This channel what they do is when they don't know what to show for a couple of seconds
They have like a series of like reaction clips of like people in their studio like doing a face
Sort of frames similar to those like 22 questions black people have for asian people type videos
But instead of them saying anything it's just been doing a shrug or doing a chuckle
And it'll just cut to them like one of these like, you know, one of these prist up like
You know dolled up like fucking tech company workers in front of a nice biffy little background
Making a face for five seconds as filler in between other visual imagery and I'm like kill this video. I wouldn't dead
That's
Weird
Yeah
Absolutely bizarre
If I was if I hadn't if I was just a youtuber still and wasn't trying to do other mediums at this point
I would probably have a series called your editing sucks episode one of one
Fucking I hate everything. What other mediums are you doing?
I'm just so confused. I'm still working on a video game still and I don't want to where's the video game
I'm still fucking working on it. I guess talk about why it's taking a long time. You know, it's only like it's a video game
It takes a long time. No
No video games are very stupid
It's very
Well, it's very you know, it doesn't have much uh interactivity. It's not got any action
You just win you just
You did not want to wait the one second of the fire. I didn't I don't give a shit
um
Well, so I guess okay, basically to talk about stuff. Yeah, is anyone at all still interested in the whole fucking uh
What happened after digi thing? Oh, yeah, sir. Sure. Yeah
So basically the idea was we need to go somewhere else now
The idea was let's get to atlanta, right now. I still had a decent amount of you know
I had like, you know a couple hundred dollars in savings. I can use to get somewhere, right
Sometimes I can't believe how little money people
Yeah, yeah, well, so like if I hadn't had a girlfriend at this point
I'd been single still I'd have gone to atlanta like I'd have like gotten an apartment in atlanta
And that's what would have happened then right? So that would have been a very fucking different story, obviously
Oh, but wait, wait, just ask her is to come back to later. I'm gonna let you finish
Uh, uh, let's come back to how do you feel about PCPHB being in boss?
Sounds good. It does sound good. And so whether or not I'm even gonna be in the PCPHB at all like
I don't know
Well, I still need to keep answering this question, right? So
Uh, so the since because I had a girlfriend instead the plan is let's move in with her, right?
Which means since we're gonna be you know, I mean
Don't do it
Just don't do it
Bad idea. You're too late too late, dude. Well, I'm doing right now those fucking cynical guys who says oh
What David didn't hear any of that are you gonna be one of those guys now who's like, oh
Bad, don't you with women? You mean a mig towel? Do you mean a mig towel?
Yeah, no
No, no
Need to wipe off your shit Lord sweat with a mig towel
I'm just I was just I was just thinking about I was just thinking about the dissolution of digi house and the
Circumstances surrounding me moving in with what's her name?
Uh, yeah, and how much of a terrible terrible mistake it was. I think that makes it worse
I think what's the name what's her name makes it worse?
Yeah, that's kind of um, that's kind of a literally who ish
Yeah, okay. Well
Yeah, so like
I'm only speaking
This is where I get to the part where I don't want people I don't want people giving me fucking advice
I want people giving me your sympathies, right? I'm an adult
Very broadly speaking
Cole has severe depression and anxiety, right?
So who gives you advice on the fact of whether or not she has depression?
She's I don't like when people are like, oh, hey, here's a like look up this article to help you or you know
Yeah, you know
I'm sure you're on top. I'm sure I'm sure you you've got a handle on it. Oh, yeah. So
So again, so she's fucking miserable in her house with her family, right?
So she wants to move out asap, right?
And so I'm planning on getting my own place or something. So the thought is well, what we should do then is uh
Focus on cheapness. Oh, you know, if we're gonna have a place for two people
We need to have like, you know, live in a cheaper area, right?
So I thought well instead of living in Atlanta, right?
I can just move back to Missouri where my family is and I can have my parents be sort of my safety net
They can like guide me through the very scary process of figuring out how to get a fucking apartment, right?
um
And also like, you know, be a fucking
If I can safety net in case I run out of money or some shit, I could raid their fridge, right?
That might help
So the idea is we'll go back to Missouri. So she leaves Oregon. She leaves her house in Oregon and I I leave Virginia
I leave both of Missouri. So the so the idea is
uh
like
We get a place there, right?
So I'm living with my family for a little bit and the idea is well, I'm just living with my family
Rent free for now just staying in a tiny room
A room it's not the same room that I wasn't before it's the small room that used to be my sisters
And my sister's now living up in the room where I live in so like I'm not having any expenses right now
My parents just covering it, right? They're just glad to have me back. So like they're okay. Just like getting me through shit
Something okay, cool. So it'll be just me with my family for a couple of months
I can save up and get an apartment this way
But here's what happened the same time I moved to Missouri at the same time digi starts traveling the fucking world
country western coast
And he doesn't give me any fucking videos, right? He doesn't give me any work through this whole time
He probably would have jammed out something if I needed the money
But the fact that he knew I didn't need the money means he didn't give me fucking videos
So he gave me very few videos. So I remained just above water
Uh with my fucking money, right?
I didn't make any money now
I wasn't complaining because this is when I got a lot of work done on like my video game projects and other projects
And read all the home stuff. So I just had a good time
Yeah, like there's no way I would have gotten through rack six without that
Without having just 15 straight days to do it, right? It would have taken forever otherwise
I mean, I would have gotten through it. I just wouldn't have been able to do it all at once
So I wasn't complaining but financially it was a bit of a tough thing because she eventually moves in because she's like
She's desperate to get out fucking desperate to move out
And this is when I start to learn that people's depression can't be fixed by me just showing up, right?
It already happened with digi
When I showed that I had
Me and my infinite fucking hubris my stanley hubris thought that digi was gonna be like great and have
Goal under the press because I am there and I don't fucking such a charismatic likable person
I guess people actually right?
I get I get what you're talking about
And yet I still didn't learn my fucking lesson my thought is oh, yeah
Coldest person with like serious crippling has been to a vandal fucking hospital over superior depression anxiety
She's gonna be just fucking fine when she moves in, right?
Yeah
No, no, so like the reason why I wasn't getting a lot of work done in virginia because it's because I was just talking
With her a lot and she was like, you know very emotionally dependent and like
Not able to like schedule things. I can't do something like you know me
I'm very like I want to always have a schedule even though. I'm not that good at doing it
But basically is I want my life to run very for stanley, but I'm very easily distracted, right?
So like I would say stuff like oh, hey, let's just talk over this over skype for two hours
And then we'll be done for the day
But having a timer overhead gives her more anxiety, you know, it's like oh, I don't want to like have a
Blooming clock, right?
So because she's like tough to like help out emotionally
And I'm so easily distracted
Sounds like a fucking drag
Yes, it's pretty fucking bad. You know, it's not easy
Right and if she wasn't a person who I thought like kick ass I would have left her within like two weeks
I would stop talking with her, right? But I guess, you know, I guess
The thing is, you know with okay to make a comparison to what's her name
You've told me that basically you were just like on a moment-to-moment basis talking with her, right?
Uh wait on a moment-to-moment basis talking with her
Being with her was miserable, right?
Uh for a large for large part for large large swaths of it. Yeah
For me it's like actually being with Cole is never bad
Always good. I mean look where you got, right? What a what a concept
Just the default status quo us being together is good
It's just that in the broader context of my life where I have a job and other things I want to
So it's a drag on other things, but it is in itself good. You see
Yeah, sounds sounds nice
With nearly as well, right never even remotely have I been as comfortable with someone as her
So ultimately I found it worth it. But the point is so she's still being really emotionally dependent and I'm still like kind of
I don't know what to do with myself, right?
And I've had to learn much greater patience than I ever have
convenience, right?
And ultimately what makes this kind of cool
Is that you know, we both as you people who remember the pct episode about fetishes remembers
We sort of met up over a fetish that kind of is a
That's sort of themed after the idea of being someone's parents
Even though they're a fucking adult and you're the same age as them, right?
So it's sort of like the reason she's into the fetish is partly because of this sort sort of like psychosexual emotional dependency, right?
Psycho
Whoa
I mean, yeah
It makes sense to me
Yeah, so ultimately it does sort of play into
Yeah, you know, like even though it's fucked up. I feel like
We're kind of made for each other, you know
Yeah fair enough
Learn how to deal with
Being a productive worker whilst also having real life issues. I never really had, you know, fucking problems before
Before that
But you know, that wasn't difficult to fix
Um, I hate the problem is that she was still like I still wasn't I still haven't started my lesson though
That people aren't gonna are still gonna be lonely even if I'm there, right?
Like yeah, Ben. I knew Ben was lonely in in virginia. I knew did you was only in virginia?
But I'm like, well, I'm not lonely. I have did you in bed, right?
You know, well, I mean, I wasn't I wasn't lonely like I mean, I let I really did like living with you guys
Right, you know, I just too, you know, I just I just didn't get laid for a long time and it made me really angry
Yeah, like like people need more than more than like two people in their lives. It's just for me having been home school
Very just very like isolated like I'm just mentally adjusted to living in like an almost absolute bubble
Right, but then like almost like memory levels and then it's seen it seemed great getting out of there and moving in with so and so
Um, only to find out that I was basically trading only two people for like one
And like nothing outside of that
And what happened with Cole was that like, okay cool. Now she can live with me great. She I'm her favorite person
But I'm not her only person now. She doesn't have access to her family anymore
It doesn't have access to her mom who she loves and her friends, right?
Yeah, and basically the whole relationship with me basically like isolated her from her friends, right?
Because I'm a crazy weirdo all of all of her friends were like, why the fuck are you with this guy, right?
Like, you know, I'm literally you're you're you're unlikable
What did you say your relationship isolated her from her friends?
Yeah, because she so she became so dependent on me that she didn't hang out with her friends as much and they
Popped her right and that's pretty that's pretty bad
And all of her friends are and here's the more fundamental problem her friends are like post high school friends
You know, like people get met in high school and stay in touch with but that's do you know, like 99 times out of 100
You're gonna drift off because you only were friends because you were in the exact same situation
But once you become adults, that's no longer the case, right? Sure
The the the internet has really spoiled me with like friendships because why would like like it was hard for me to become friends
with people in school
Yeah, because it was just like well
The only reason that I am talking to you is because we are in this school and we are together
Same thing happened with digi actually like when I first like when I got into digi
Oh my team he was always talking about how his friends would always be around
Right like digi apparently digi's house pre us moving in
Was like all about fucking. Um, how do you how do you activate your secondary weapon? Can you your right right click, right?
Well, no, no, you're you're setting your weapon. You have to press spacebar to make your primary. Oh, yeah
You gotta switch unless your steroids. You gotta switch weapons
Gotcha, so, um
Um, did you was always talking about how he has like this group of like nine or ten friends?
They're always at his
His house is like this bustling fucking. It's almost like a door, right?
Yeah, that's how apparently his house was for 2013 and 14 and he said like yeah, man
Like you know other people make oh apparently actually Nate made fun of digi for still being friends with his high school friends, right?
Um
Friends I can oh, you know, Nate Nate, you know, he's Nate boobity boobity. Nate's an asshole boobity boob
Anyway, so like digi had like put in my mind this idea of his house being like a fucking college form or some shit
But it's pretty conveniently over the course of 2015 and 16
All those people started tapering away as digi became a guy with like a very specific lifestyle that none of them were similar to you know
They were all like guys with like, you know, some artistic ambitions we be nerdy interests
But eventually they all had to like either get jobs or yeah
They sort of like got normal jobs and just played fucking street fighter all day
Digi was the only one who sort of ascended the the christ consciousness plane to become an internet being right?
Yeah, and disconnected with them as such and like literally right as soon as we moved in those people like officially stopped showing up
Right, like yeah, like they did one of the people the three people I wanted to meet the most in the digi extended universe with digi's dad
Uh, brin, brin and tolentino
I mean, I did I did meet all those people
You never met donks on did you wait? No, maybe
Yeah, I might have met him like once very briefly, but maybe not. Yeah, I met I don't think so
I don't I don't so like digi's dad was around digi's dad was cool
brin and tolentino like digi sort of like brin and tolentino was like pretty cool
I just like him in podcasts, right? Yeah, but donks on like but never show up the entire time that we were there
I believe digi has not once seen donks on since us moving in so it's been years now, right? I'm gonna be wrong, but
Which is a shame because digi always built him up as being like this cool person, you know with infinite knowledge and stuff
So, yeah, um
Uh, I I I
The funny story about brin and tolentino and josh specifically
I I love brin and tolentino and josh and I actually got to meet them at rad con too
Before the thing actually started
I was the first person to show up and they were just at his house
I think like took a victor or something or to do something
Anyway, I met them and like I was like, oh man, josh brin and tolentino
They're like, um
I'm like, oh wait. These are just normal people
It's really weird if I were to come up to them and like say that I know stuff about them. Yeah
That would be bizarre
Yeah, and and and the one part was before I consciously realized that I made a oh
This is so retired and like obviously stupid in retrospect right in the end at the time
I made a reference to what they had said in an episode
And yeah, I know I know I know and I and I laughed and they're like
What?
Who are you?
No one don't worry about me
Nothing to see here folks. Yeah
Amazing. Uh, that's um, remember when you came to Atlanta
And we went to that shitty halloween party and I introduced you to people as munchie
Yeah, I did not even consider that that would not be what you that that was not what you were expecting me to do
Well, yeah, I like you do that like two people and then like you did it over and I'm like, it's Anthony
I was I was honestly shocked because I was like, I only call you munchie. So like why wouldn't I introduce you as
It wasn't for the fact that Cole, you know just started calling anybody my real name because you wanted to do that
But I would have lost my identity entirely man
Yeah, a little bit same though though. I talk to my family pretty regularly who obviously don't call me much
Yeah
But yeah, yeah, but but but the geofront has helped my real name thrive again in in memory. Yeah
Oh, yeah, so like so because Cole was still kind of miserable. We spent a lot of money like
Room upstairs. We reclaimed the room upstairs and finally remade it
You reclaimed it in a battle of wits with your parents. No, just my sister was okay with moving back downstairs
Um, mother fucker fuck right like Cole was still really miserable
She didn't have access to her like her you know her life back in Oregon
So she eventually just kind of cracked like she was just like I can't deal with this anymore
So she had to like sort of emergency move back to Oregon because she was like
If you know what the reason is because her mom her mom is like a nurse like an experience like high level nurse
Right like nurses. I didn't know us nurses aren't just people who like like, you know, like wipe your face and your ass
There are also people who like do shit in the hospital and like know everything
Mom's nurse her mom's really good if you have like medical issues, you know
She's an invite level nurse who's invited to e-sports tournaments across the nation. She's invite love
She's a leading the level nurse you see in the last dungeon
Um, and also because it's Oregon she has better healthcare set up there and like, you know
She can get her like pharmaceuticals refills like overall
It was just she needs to go back there now, right? So she moved back there and the idea was okay cool
So then I'll stay here in Missouri for a few more months and make a bunch of videos and save a month
Right same fucking thing happened this last time
But in a new unique way this time instead of digi not sending me any videos
Digi sent me the video calls. We have accepted me to gokarty
Which was a video that was so big and so long. It took me literally the whole
No, I had to myself to make that one video
The idea was I was gonna make tons of fucking videos in that time and make a bunch of money
But because I was given literally the biggest video of all time
It took me like two whole months just to do it and that was it
Good thing did you paid me did he paid me like a whole lot of money for it?
But so so we just the reason why we got another house
We got an apartment with shit internet is because we had no other choice because even though coal has her Oregon life back
She no longer has me and she's desperate without me, right?
Um, because I'm like the only person in the world who almost has enough patience for her, right? Like I'm like
I'm not gonna give myself that much credit sometimes. I'm like, what the fuck
Be a normal person don't have a mental disability. Come the fuck on, right? Yeah, very good. Good. I mean it makes sense
I'm not gonna fucking I ain't gonna like hit myself as a white knight without some black streaks
Wait, oh, well, you don't you're a zebra knight. You're a zebra
Yeah
um
so
I guess a zebra knight is the kind of person who comes in and goes
You know, this guy's being really racist against me. I'm a black person and a zebra knight comes in and goes
This tune's got a point
Oh, no
So we basically just have to get an apartment here as soon as possible because unlike my family's house
Which is huge and there's plenty of room for some of the extra adults
um
My my girlfriend and my wife's fucking her family's house is like small so like we have to get our own place, right?
So we be like it was a miracle. We got this place that we did and now we have a one-year lease on it. So, yeah
Yeah, no, no, no. Oh god
All that all that in mind with all that like regarded like I think things are going
Good things are going better now. Like, you know, her fucking meds are doing her much better now
And we're just slowly building her up, you know, and it's like fuck man. I never felt like I was how to help
Like helped real people, you know
Like I helped her a little bit
I like actually like need to be alive for reasons other than making art and I feel like it's made me a more well-rounded person, you know
Um, yeah
I I think I I think I don't know. Okay. This will sound super asshole. We probably
But I think I think I think I've come this is not related to you
simply at all, uh
Yeah, uh, this
I have realized why a lot of guys will be like, you know, having a girlfriend like changed me and made me more empathetic
Is that maybe they've just been friends
like guys who just like
Are assholes and like they've never had to like maintain a human relationship with people who like, you know
Like they care about in the sense that they don't want to make upset
Like they've never had like the personal responsibility of having a girlfriend in order to like, you know, not to have their life fall apart
I guess maybe that's what people have
Oh, yeah, last bit of update to say is that
I think I've said this before but specifically I'm living in Oregon. Yeah. Nice. Cool. But it's east, Oregon
It's it's so east, Oregon that it's basically
Idaho like on the border of Idaho and like 50 percent of all the license plates are going to be Idaho
It's so fucking east that there aren't any dispensaries here
Well, like they're on the wild west, dude. There's a wild east. Yeah, actually. No, this is a part of uh
This region I'm in is honestly like more in the middle of nowhere than I was in Missouri
You're in the erratic east, dude
The erratic east. Yeah. Well, I'm I'm on the east of the west, you know
But yes, like this is a part of Oregon that's so like rural that basically it's nothing like what Oregon we think of Oregon, right?
Like they don't like the fucking weed there. They have a lot of problem with it. They don't allow dispensaries here, you know, so
Yeah, uh, that's why I've only spoken once right so far. Uh, I don't even like weed. You're not missing out
Well, I want to try at least a few different cuts. I didn't okay. The weed I tried was fun
But I don't need it like like like it was it was from Cole's older sister who's like even more
Guys like a lot of pain and like me sleep. So like it was very sneaky, right?
So it was really fun. It felt like, you know, traveling through time. It felt like like you come one time
Oh, you know, just traveling three times. All right. It was cool
It was interesting because like, you know, alcohol I feel changes my personality for his weed at least that particular strain
I feel like I was the same person that when you get drunk. It's a it's it's
It's an experience
Every I don't I don't understand
Davoo being drunk is like not different from just the cartoon interpretation of someone doing drugs
So I was not caught guard. Well, exactly. It's exactly that's exactly it
well
Davoo was like one of the first people I've ever seen drunk in my life
Like well like like in person. I mean, so it wasn't like that weird. I just assumed. Oh, yeah
When you're drunk, you just act like you don't have any bodily function. Well, let's be careful that
Uh, fucking mad bowl 34 was like hyping us all including me way the fuck more than the variation would by the fall
Okay
I'll I'll have to say I I had no problem with drunk blue. I had
Not
My way to try and not be a problem then it seems to work
But I remember like on like a
New year's only uh when 2016 turned over to 17
I was being very careful to like restrain myself as much as I could because he was like, hey
You're not like fucking ruining everyone's lives, right?
Oh, no, we didn't say that. He said no, we're being fine. That's what he said. Okay. That's just my interpretation of life
Uh, I said some jokes and they were good, but you know
I mean I tried listening to like some of the alcohol pct cast the bonus episode
Because I remember everyone like praising me and about being funny on it
But like it was of course funny to all of them because they were also drunk and listening back to it
But you know like like you judge drunk standards based on whether or not the other people who are with you
Like you not based on whether you sound good on the recording afterwards, right?
Anyway, so weed a sleepy weed. I had I was like I tried watching some anime
I watched like weeks ago moe on it while being a mistake under any circumstance
Oh, dude, it was amazing because it was like it had twice as much colors as usual
It was like colors are all twice as intense and also it felt like it was 3d. It felt like it was 3d. I don't know how that works, right?
Um, it felt like the world was 3d. However, that whatever sense that makes
But I was like everything that has plots is too intense for me. I can't focus
I need something like I need something with bright and poppy, but I need something very simple and easy
So I watched a I watched a long play of we golf
I watched a long play of we golf
I want to guys. I want to fucking scream. I want to fucking scream. I'm so angry at this game
Just get better. Just get better. I mean, this is the way I always played
Back today just run in and don't even think about but it's worse because of the lag
Like we've been to the sewers like what 50 times like
It's fucking garbage. This is fucking garbage. Why why?
I am so mad. I'm
It's it's the delay and the fact that no one's coordinated and that we're trying to do a show on top of it. Yeah
Yeah, nice
Yeah, so I don't think I would do that kind of weed again unless I was like going to take like a week off or something because like
It like spoke with my brain
I didn't I feel like I was still picking my brain up off the floor two days later and it's just it just disorganized me
But I do want to try the fucking kind of weed that makes you more creative and stuff. No, that's fake. That's not real
I you know what seeing did you do it? I am no don't fucking listen to digi. Okay. Like just don't listen to it
That's what he's saying. That's what he's saying. Yeah, I I I do think that like
Digi might give weed a little bit too much credit. No fucking kidding
Because like, you know, like
I just think that digi probably he's been talking about how he's been like working constantly
He's gone weed like he was just all day working on everything. It's like the speed at which he gets things out
I'm not sure if I'm convinced
I think what it is is he feels like he's working constantly because weed fucks with your perception of time
Yeah, right, right and it makes you like it makes you think that everything is happening super fast when it's fucking isn't
Now, of course, but he says to people who make that criticism is oh, well, I'm working on all this shit in background
You don't see well, I'm pretty other than they I'm the closest to being on the inside looking out with digi's productions
and
You don't you don't see it. You just you just don't see like I was okay. I'm fine. You only like like specific docs
I'll fucking make they're not really docs just insider fucking
Uh smuggling of information
Is uh
I was asking digi. Can you please give me a list of like things of shows that would become topics of how they market the episodes
Like what what is a list of how they market the episodes that you're planning on doing right?
And it took him like three weeks to get me the list and he's like, yeah
I've been putting it off because I don't know which notebook I wrote it in
Uh digi
Fuck you god you right now like like modern digi. Go watch who's listening to this
Can I stay at your house for like a week? I just want to stay at your house. I just want to see what it's like
I just want to I just want to say
You don't you don't have to talk to me. Don't worry
Yeah
I just I just want to be around and then see other I want I want I want to see how the magic's made
I want to see how he worked it did
And I do want to say like did you definitely get some things about anime straight up wrong because he's hot, right?
Like in the totoro cast
Digi was describing a scene. He's like, yeah, you know the little girl
May is like
May's walking over here and she sees a bunch of like creatures pop out and I'm like digi. I'm looking I'm on vlc
I'm looking at the scene right now. There's no creatures. He's like, oh, I guess it was the acid, right?
um
Now I know granted digi always gets some things wrong about about stuff that he's talking about like this
Commenters who always like point out things to get wrong like they don't understand
They didn't have to make a video right like making videos is hard
It's hard to like like backcheck everything you do, right?
um
This is the most he's ever been talked about this entire show, but
Will you bring me on, you know, so yeah, like why don't you talk about yourself?
Like
Has my internet died again?
No, you're fine
I think yeah, why are we talking about digi who cares? Oh, am I be like have we have we lagged up completely are we dead? Yes
Yes, I I can hear you. Oh, oh the game. You sure the game. Oh, jeez the game has come to us trying to come back
Do I hear the dial-up do I hear the aol dial-up in the background? I swore to god for a second. I heard it
Oh, there we go. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, wait taboo
I think oh, I don't know what happened. Oh, oh, oh, no
I'm still working
Yeah, it's pretty laggy, but it seems to be working somewhat
All right, are you in the game right now taboo? Are you in the game? Uh, why is my internet failing again? This is my
Ben you can hear me, right? Uh-huh. Yeah, I can hear you. Okay. Okay. Oh, okay. All right. All right. This is want to make sure it's not me
Okay, well then you just want to do like a round where like we try hard and it's just you and me so our internet doesn't suck
Yeah, I mean can taboo like stay on the call
Of course. Yeah. Yeah
All right, let's actually just play the game and I'll try and I'll I'll sweat really hard
Okay. Yeah, I'm getting very frustrated
Well
Well, I we even heard we never heard much of your side of the situation though, I
Oh, oh, do who says that's the end of that
um
You mean about the digi thing like digi house. Yes
Oh god. Well, I mean, yeah, I was gonna I was gonna springboard off of what taboo was saying
um
Did you call he says I see you so goodbye. No, that's why I'm trying to get the fuck back here you idiot
I'm mad. I'm mad that he would just leave
What but he his internet just was destroyed
What no, what does that mean? What does that mean it was destroyed?
It doesn't work anymore. It crashed or something
Fine great
Just just just join just join send me a invite or something. I just did. I just did. Oh, I see it. I see it
Oh
By the way, you're gonna feel like you're playing like an f zero game right now
You're gonna feel like you're playing the fastest game on fucking earth. Yeah after all that after that. Yeah. Yeah
Uh, just play your main just play your main
Uh, who is who even is my man?
I'm gonna be fish. Okay
Fun fact, uh
I'm gay me too. Uh, so this okay, so I don't know what was to do saying about the whole digi house breakup thing
Well, okay, okay
Do we were talking about like the entire history of like what happened like his relationship and stuff like that the original
Well, what I was talking about was
All I want to know was like how how has it been?
So did you house like like did you expect that you would wind up here? How like got that was that was the question
Yeah, I was just like like like like like what's it like being like like did you house was like
Because you there's you're like me and him are in like opposite situations. Yeah, that's yeah
Ah balls um
I mean, okay, well since all right, so I moved in I moved in with
Over the right. I'm fainted. I need to wait. Are you dead? Where the wait? Oh shit
All right
Yeah, so I moved in with somebody and that was fine for a while
But I mean it just it's neat. It's just neatly half so happened that that whole thing fell apart. Um
Like basically just pretty close to when like, you know did he was moving to boston and and like pcphq was
Seeming like it was coming. I mean I mean what we have now is not actually pcphq, but it is definitely like the beginnings of it
Oh, well, yeah
I would say it's pcphq. I mean, I don't know. It's not pcphq until we start like doing something with it, right?
Oh, well, okay. Sure. I guess also I just kill him and then and then
Uh, Jesus christ. I walk right in. I'm sorry. I'm stuck with shit. Yeah, that's fine
I the guy's gonna hit you from up. I'm dead again. I'm up here. Oh my god. Why? Why are you so bad?
I'm sorry for your start
uh
Oh, yeah, nothing's been made yet, but like ever as the game crashed. No, it's it's lagging, but uh
There I think
Everyone's like in the place right now everyone. I consider pcphq to just be like like when the place has been erected
And and everyone's in one place which is everyone's not in one place like three people are in one place
Well, yeah, but but I visit often so it
It's basically like like like sure. I guess and and who else is going to move here
Nate Nate will move here. And then who else? I mean, there's I mean, look
I mean, there's hippo. There's mage. Um, mage will not move mage will not move hippo hippo might at some point
Yeah, but he's on the other side of the country. So it's not like that's gonna be anytime soon. You mean he's on the other side of the world
Well, yeah
Um, so so the only people I could see debu moving
Well, he just said he's not going to because he's with his wife and why don't they both move
Well, we're not listening to the entire story because she no, I was not listening to most of that story to be perfectly honest
Okay, cool
Um, yeah, he's not moving and then you know, just he's obviously not moving
So so the only two people who will feasibly be at that
each ph here
Like in any sort of foreseeable future are me and Nate and I already go there. I mean so
Okay, was was there was there some reason why debu and his wife can't just move?
Yes, it's because she needs to be in argument is where her family are
Why
Because she's depressed a lot, I guess and she needs them for support
dumb
Well, well, okay, but that's that those are the facts as I see them
Uh, fine
Well, okay, I guess debu won't come and that's and that's
Yes, that does so
um
I mean, okay, did you see here?
Neonates coming
mage is not coming
Uh, whoa
The only the only two people I think will come besides me are hippo and I think I think jesse debu and mage are
We just need to count on I mean, why would jesse know?
Jesse has been talking about how much he hates living in his basement forever
and like
He just won't but he won't stop
Well, I don't know he just won't reasons and and I'm sure and he's gonna move in with his girlfriend or whatever
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know what he's gonna do. I don't think he's he hasn't he hasn't said anything about moving to
Boston, so I just know he didn't like to believe he would yeah
I mean, I I don't see him. I don't see him moving even if he could or felt that he could
Yeah, I don't I don't see that
um
So whatever
Yeah, okay. I mean, I guess pcphq is is is pretty cute up, you know, yeah
relatively speaking
Well, what are we talking about?
All we're talking about is is is is like like how it's been like
With the fallout of digi house and do you feel like it's funny? Well, it's funny that it's funny that the fallout of digi house
Uh, the period between the fallout of digi house to um, you know, the the the the re the reformation
The boston reformation of pcphq
Not not but to to a certain extent pretty neatly coincided with the rise and fall of a whole sordid and
terrible chapter of my life
um
And I mean, I don't know. There's no point. I'm not making any point with that. It's just an observation
Well, how about that?
Uh, yeah
Jesus
Well, that that that sure that sure was a topic. Yeah
I hope I hope you're all proud of me viewers
Uh, this is gonna be the run by the way
What this is gonna be the run by the way
I I think this oh god
No, I'm gonna die
No, no, no you are
I feel pretty good about this fun. Oh god, there's fucking lasers. Oh god, there's a ninja. Oh god
Don't worry, we're good. Where's my fucking radical? Where's my radical? There there's my radical
Yeah, that's me. I'm I'm uh, you know, I I'm an atheist. I'm an eight. I'm an atheist who plays uh
Nuclear throne that makes me the heretical radical
Dude, okay imagine this. Yeah, that's you two channel the eight-bit atheist
wait
The eight-bit atheist is that not is that not a real thing yet?
No, how could not be how could it not be? I don't know
Fuck me. Shit balls. Fuck. Look, there's so much life. There's so much life giving life right there
Oh, there we go. Okay. Oh my god. What happened to my guns?
Oh
Okay, okay
Yeah, this is the run. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh, yeah, this is the fucking run. This is the fucking run right now
Oh, wait, I should not have a fucking rocket launcher
I will take literally any any gun besides
This one
Many gun. Oh my god, this is literally the run right now
Watch out. I've got fucking bombs
This is just like the first reverence cop killers us trying really hard and the show suffers because of it. Oh, yeah
It's just absolute trash
Mm-hmm
This is the top level play that they come for though. Which one which one do we want here?
Up to you. I think laser brain or I mean, I could use laser brain
I have like a bunch of energy weapons or I have one energy weapon, but I have a lot of
Yeah, oh this money gun is just great
Ah
I keep seeing your minions and thinking that it's cops. No, there are no cops here. Don't worry
This is the lift there's a double flame shotgun up here, by the way, uh, do I want that?
Actually, yes, I do
Do you have it? Uh, yeah
Okay, this is the run. This is oh my god, this is so the run, dude
Oh
Yes, oh my god, dude, I have a super crossbow and
This is the redemption this is the redemption for all the shit that we've gone through
Oh, no, it's cops it's the fucking cops dude. It's the fuzz
Hey, did you ever make post the lyrics of that rap you made?
Uh, somebody like transcribe them
Wait, wait. Yeah. Yeah, I did post them in the discord somewhere
What why why is that not a theme yet guys come on
Sixten made a beat to rap over but like I don't know it doesn't really it's not the original beat and it's
Weird I don't know
Little hunter will be here soon. I don't know where he'll be. He's there
I hate little hunter so much. Oh, I'm down here. I'm down here. Are you dead?
Oh god, he's so bad. He's so bad and scary. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh
Where fuck
You know what it's okay. We made it to little hunter. We're finally making progress
Now that we've dumped the dead weight that is taboo
I'm feeling it. Oh, no, I did not want to be him. I did not want to be that guy. It's fine. It's fine. Uh,
Yeah, it's fine to worry
Yeah, uh, wait was I fished before? Yes
No, what were you saying?
I don't I don't even remember I was I was there was some point buddy, but I don't even care anymore. I'm just
I know I just want to win
That's all about cops. I'm glad that this game gives the opportunity to kill cops, you know
I'm gonna make us get a little quick. Hold on. What are you doing? Yeah
Uh, my my guys drop radiation on kill. So we were just about to get a level but we didn't make it
So I just spawned a guy and I wasn't know what I got the actual level
The rebel you absolutely need strong spirit like there's no other way to play the game
Strong spirit is the uh, the one that like if you die, you don't die
Yeah
Oh my god, okay, it's happening
Oh
There he is
Hey fun fact by the way, I actually
Like for the nuclear throne official trailer
They ask the community to send in clips and my uh clip of rebel is actually in the final
Trailer like the game official game trailer. Wait, what do you mean your clip of rebel?
Like like like they they asked to send a gameplay clips to have like as you know
Show up the gameplay of nuclear throne in the trailer and I sent in stuff and they got
Yeah, it's actually under my real name, which is why I don't mention it more
But I don't care so uh me
Yeah, that's that's fucking neat as hell
Yeah, it's it's in the gameplay declared not the cinematic trailer. Uh, it's it's it's the one even press me in the end
uh
It's it's the one where where rebel responds a bunch of big gannets and it shoots up the boy
I'm quite proud of it
Was it was it was it epic was it an epic gamer? Oh
Ben you know me I I do nothing that's not epic
That's true. Oh, Jesus christ. What do I I don't want any of these the one that gives more ammo
Yeah, okay
That was not it, but all right
No, the recycle gland only gives more ammo for bullet weapons. Oh, oh, that's
Oh, shit, I died
Don't worry. You're fine. You're fine. Be careful of that fire
Hey
Wow, now now now they're finally playing the game
Well, like like like now that devoo's gone we can play the game now, but also we can't have a good show
So that's a really good payoff. It's it's ruined
Did the people care? I think I think people might like this. I think people might like a stride
Maybe a bit
But but that a little wear thing. Oh, shit. No, no, no, I'm down
Don't worry, we're fine. We're fine
I can never be like an esports commentator of any kind
Also, I just I just ate shit. Oh shit. It's a fucking mimic. Oh, oh
Oh
All we need is blood lust and we're trying to get just get away from that
Get away from from what the explosion that was just there
I haven't been spying my guys nearly enough
Well get good
Thank you
Thank you. I I I come to you in a moment of vulnerability. You do this to me. I got you you fucking loser
Also, I'm I'm I'm out of ammo right now
Sit got the flame shotgun is fucking awesome
Oh
I want that me bloodless. Oh my god six six six six six six six
Oh, you got the minigun fuck you unit
I got the assault rifles
It'll do in a pinch
Oh
Oh, I I'm I'm over here. Oh, there are a bunch of snowbots, so so be careful be careful
I thought for sure that was the end of the run by the way never the run never ends. I hope so
I need strong spirit. Oh, actually I have a ramp. I'm gonna spawn as many people as physically can
I can't wait till I have an ultra mutation and I can spawn double allies
Yeah, I always think your dudes are cops and I shoot at them. They don't they don't they don't look like cops
It's just because they're blue. I don't know
Oh trip machine gun. Oh, dude. This is actually my favorite weapon in tagging. Oh shit. They're actually cops now. Yeah, I know
Oh my god, this is really good. What a act. Uh, this this is the line
I
Fuck it's that man
Wait, I'm dead. Fuck me god christ
Oh, fuck what? Oh, no, I'm you're in such a bad. I'm done. I'm done. Hey, I'm done here
Oh
Fuck fuck
God little hunter's the worst we keep we keep being terrible spawns for little hunter
We'll get them we'll get them
Never despair. Well, it's too late for that
Spares never whoa, whoa, why is oh, okay. I was hitting the wrong button
Dude we should just play video games like
For fun sometimes. I like don't play many video games. I don't either
But that can change
I guess it could yeah
But but why don't I play video games?
It's I mean, I mean
I don't know just I I never find myself thinking like boy. I'd really like to play a video game right now
It's a social experience. Yeah
it is
You you you were you were real lonely a lot of time in
Atlanta and I always wondered why you didn't just come to chat like like like you always talked about how you were so lonely
Yeah, but you never came into chat. So I felt like that would probably could easily be fixed. I
I uh
What if you don't want to what a fucking miserable time what you don't have to say anything if you don't want you
I don't know if you were
I
Mike I felt I felt like my time was very restricted. I I you know
I think I would have spent more time like in the chat talking to you guys
I just never felt like I could I somehow I was never able to find especially like
Like during the day I was always like, I don't know like at night. I never felt like I could I could get away and do that
Move away. You're yeah, yeah
Be steroids or someone
Why you know do whatever you want do whatever you want. Why not be fish?
You can be fish. He's fine. You know, I'll be crystal
Okay
I think
I'm pretty sure the pcp is the only group of friends that our relationship is not founded upon video games
where all all like like
All of the like several friend groups I've been a part of in my entire life
Have all basically been battered on the fact that we both like video games either we play them together
Or we just have a mutual appreciation of them like like how I met my
My like the irl like high school group of friends was just that I saw some guy with like a tf2 t-shirt on one time
Uh, yeah, sure. Um, I think that's
I mean, what else is there? What else is there these days?
true
Those people make what do people become friends based on before me serious questions
Uh mutual appreciation for fine arts
I mean, no mutual mutual appreciation for farming
You chuckle to yourself having pwned the opposition
I mean, well, I mean, you know
Books, you know, you probably like you know mutual mutual admiration for the same books or or movies. Yeah tv
You know, yeah, yeah, I mean there was lots of shit
There was lots of art to appreciate even before video games hard as it is to believe
Hardest to admit. Yeah, even even to the the sole video game audience grab your all all of these are shit
I guess this one
I think if we have a scarier face game with us, but you can actually kill rats just by touching them
Yes, this case
Wait, so we don't have to we don't have to waste any ammo here. Oh, oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's that's why I like fucking um
whatever it's called
Is this because we have a combination of scary face and uh, yes
Yeah, okay. Scary face and uh gamma guts
Yeah, so it doesn't just work with regular gamma guts, right?
No, you can only kill like maggots look like that. Yeah
I thought for sure that was gonna be a mimic
Nah, those are super rare. Oh my okay. This is this is going bad
This game is significantly harder to call up and I don't know why because on its face it would seem way easier
Yeah, just revive each other
I think because like ammo becomes such a problem
It it really does and like one I I feel like I'm the kind of player who trails behind
I I'm like constantly running out of ammo because other people are like running ahead and picking it up
Before I can get my greedy little pause on it
You gotta be confident in this game
well
Just like in life. Well, you know
Tell me that
Go back to to young young ben and tell him that he could he could use he could use it
Nothing could save him. Yeah
You chuggle yourself having been pwned. Yes. I mean as long as someone gets pwned, I'm happy
As long as they're pwned there's pwned in here
Who it's towards is largely
It's incidental incidental
Oh god, oh it's the dog
And I'm like out of ammo speaking of
Oh god, oh god, I'm gonna die. Oh, it's so bad. Oh, I got blame. I got blamed by fire
No, I got you. Thank you. Oh, please help me. Please help me. Please help me. Please help me
Nah, I don't really feel like it. Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh
You're tagging tagging. All right
Uh, do I need to help? Wait, are you dead? No
No, I'm alive
I don't want sticky launcher. That would be suicide
That would be okay. This is scary. This is this is a little bit what we would call scary and in the business
This is what we refer to as a scary moment
I don't know if you laymen know but but here in the podcast industry, we have these things called scary moments where we don't complete control of our body
We lost some ammo there. Yeah
Okay
Oh my god, whoo-hoo-hoo Gatling slugger. That's a really good weapon
Okay, okay, sit. All right, we're gonna make it. Not that okay. Okay. Okay. Okay
We're fine. We're gonna make it after all
All I have to do is just I just have to get in front of your bed. I want to add
I want to add uh mutations to endless war so much
Do you I thought I thought you didn't care about that. Oh, no, no
I mean it wasn't like the the the thing I wanted to work on right then, but I do really want to do it
Okay, and I'm not sure how I want to do it like whether I want it to be a thing that you gain passively upon leveling up
Or a thing that you have to like invest slime in you know
The jury's out and I mean we can always change it
We can always try it one way and then decide that we don't like it do the other
Would would you consider endless war into being a state of alpha and when it relaunches this can be in beta?
Is that how you would phrase things?
Uh, maybe the only thing is that like
Isn't it like a game starts in alpha and then goes into beta and then is its final release
Yeah, well, okay, then the only thing that I would hesitate. Do I want the blood hammer?
No, okay
The only thing that I would hesitate to say about that then is that it's not like I think that
It's in its semifinal form like it could change any number of times between now and forever
So I guess I would just say that it's in its phase two of its alpha
Okay, I mean, I don't know. Do you want to just continue develop?
Do you want to just continue developing it like in perpetuity?
Or do you think that it will eventually reach a point where like it's done and it's good
And we I think I I think we'll reach a point where it's done and it's good
I would say that we should probably call that like it's it's it's it's a little under coming by the way
Oh god, this is this is really bad
We should we should call that some sort of like of like a final release
But I don't think it will be the last time we ever updated at all. I think it would just be like a sort of
Honorific oh god. Oh my god. This is so terrible
Little owners over. Oh, I don't know. I don't know what you're doing. I'm just fucking
awash with monsters
And I'm also out of ammo. God damn it. Okay. I I kill blue hunter. Oh, thank god
I'm okay. Clearly the clearly though the way to do it was just to let you handle it. Yeah
All right
Don't worry. We're good. We're also we we're also doing the sewers which is extremely easy if you're rebel
Wait, the sewers. Yeah
I'm sorry the left. Yeah
All right, I'll run. Oh, okay. This is this is great. This is great
Is this the run
This might in fact be the run. This is I mean I mean killing little hunter is an achievement little hunter is the worst
Yeah
What do I want the heavy crossbow? Yes, I think it takes a lot to reload that dude
Well, never again
I I definitely want my final mutation
Ow, no, I got you I got you doing
I'm fucking out of bullets
Okay
What the fuck is that a
That's a super bazooka. Do I want to avoid that?
You probably want to avoid that. I imagine that will probably kill you. It's really dangerous
It's so it's so much on me. Oh my god, that was really scary
Okay
You're getting really good mutations right now
Be be wary of that guy. What guy that guy right there the cop don't shoot it. Don't shoot him. There we go
Ah
Oh
Okay, hold on. Oh, okay. Okay. All right. We okay. Okay, Ben you have your sound on right?
Uh, yeah, I mean it's kind of quiet
I'm gonna turn my sound on right now. Hold on. What are you doing? All right
I I have to explain to you the strap for the throne. Okay, so come up here. Don't don't hit the throne do not activate him
I'm gonna explain to you what we're gonna do. Just walk up here. Please follow my lead
The throne doesn't attack where it charges up at the base here and it shoots down the middle
This red carpet right here is where it is. Yeah, don't don't don't touch it
And we'll do a sound that will wind up and we'll do the animation up here
I have just looked to is the real and when it does the real
Then just get out of the red carpet. So we're gonna do is we're going to bait that attack
We're gonna stand the carpet and then when I move away you move away as well
So focus on the it's a focus on the you're not here these little generators down here
Just focus on these yeah and go in here and just make them stall. So we're gonna go up here or into attack them
What on the red carpet do not stand the red carpet right now. He will do that attack right out there
So do not stand there. Just do as I do
uh
No, no, no, just wait just wait
Okay, no, no, no, no, no, no, just just try these
Do not stand the middle
Hey, he's shooting things now. Yeah, I see that
All right, all right, the throne now now has no generators. So do we kill it?
So so so so we can loop so should I kill the throne or what?
Do I attack the throne or not? Yeah, yeah, yeah, you do you do. Yes, I'm dead. I I I I didn't hear you
Oh, hold on wait, I have to turn this down again
All right. Oh, oh my god, I almost just hit menu
All right, let's get let's get trigger fingers
That'll be good for your thing
Ah
Oh
God no
Uh, we're going to go into your shield then. Oh, right. Yeah, I forgot it. I haven't used it once
All right, stand back stand back stand back
We're in loop we're in fucking loop. All right. Hell. Yeah, we made it
All right, we're probably gonna get our old communication
After this level
Which I'm so excited for that will make things so much easier. Remember the the van is here. So be wary of the van
Oh, oh my god, I hate that fucking guy
Oh, thank god, oh, where am I going?
Uh, just wait just just stand. Oh, hold on. I just turn I have to turn my volume all the way down because you give me so fucking loud
All right, uh, I want that
All right, are you ready?
Uh
Do I want the hyper slugger or the gatling bazooka?
You want the you want the you want the this you want the gatling slugger
I have like no
Uh
That will kill me that will kill me a nuke launcher a dragon
Will this kill you?
No, okay. I want the dragon
It's not very good, but we can do it. Oh well
You know neither
Oh, I died really fast
Okay, this is gonna be really hard to get you so you have to act fast act fast
What oh shit, I fucking exit the game, okay, I'm still alive
No, no, I'm good. I'm good. I'm back
Okay, my shield cannot withstand
I'm up top. I'm up top. Oh
I saved you. Okay. I have no weapons. I'm sorry. I have to keep adjusting the volume. Hold on. That's okay. Hold on
Wait, wait, keep it paused. Keep it paused. Okay. Okay. I have to adjust my back hurts. All right
Lying down is not a good position to do this. Are you ready? Uh, not yet one sec
This is so fucking stressful
All right, hold everything
Oh
Okay, I'm ready. You know what we have to do by the way. No
It's not a true nuclear phone run unless we go for crown of blood
It's not a true one if you don't go for crown of blood crown of blood that that spawns more enemies
Uh, okay
Do you want to do it? We're gonna we're gonna go for score right now. Is it gonna be a score run?
Is it gonna be a score run?
I I have no weapons
That's fine
It's not there's some shit over here. There's some shit over here
Well, well
Uh, that was pretty good. Uh, I'm gonna kill myself
Well, we looped we made it we won we won the video game
We
Just stop let's just stop it. You want you want you want to call it here? It's over. We've been going for three and a half hours
Okay
I hope you enjoyed. Yeah, I hope you enjoyed our I mean I I I have fun
I I had fun too. We had devoo. We had the classic. Yeah, we've covered a lot of ground here
Uh, we we talked a lot of shit about a lot of people near and dear to us and also not near and dear to us
That's right. That's very very true. There were a lot of stones cast in in flipper
That manners, uh-huh, uh-huh with little rhino reason and and and nothing to gain on our part
No
It was it was just nothing to say
It was it was just mere it was merely it was merely viciousness for viciousness sake. Yeah. Yeah, my my favorite
Yeah, um
And frankly, I think it's time for it
I think it's time time for us it's time for us to put down our video game controllers and head on down to the local police station
And submit ourselves for execution
Um, I'm ready to do that. Yeah
When I you know
It's been so long since endless war has been, you know, all the color was like that slime city. I wonder how that's gonna go
Where are all that's gonna come back?
Stay tuned citizens. It I was looking at the design document today
And no, no, no don't
Close it's it's it's mysterious. It's a mistake. Oh, oh, right. We'll cut out what I just said
um
Wait, I'm confused
No, I guess why I just wanted to allude to the fact that like there's stuff happening in the game
And you should join the server and they will and and you should experience it for yourself
Okay, I will cut all this out. Um
Yes, he is
Shit. No, you do it
Bye
Later guys