By the way, whenever I look at this, I think it says E-Fuck, and I don't know why.
Yeah, dirt cheap E-Fuck.
Alright, I guess we can start at any time. Talking about the Nintendo Switch.
Hey everyone, welcome to episode whatever of Rowdyfuckers Cop Killers.
I believe it's the fifth?
Yeah, I think so too. It's just me and Munchy here.
We don't need any other people. They always mess everything up. They always bring their gay shit in here.
They always keep talking about how they're migtails and they love to rape women.
Yeah, and frankly, it's offensive and I won't stand for it.
We are the most blue-pilled people on the face of the planet.
I just eat blue pills for breakfast cereal. I have a big box of them.
Breakfast, lunch, and dinner, and dessert are all comprised mainly of blue pills.
I have not once entered a single red pill in my body and I never did.
If I ever did, I would cut off my hand in penance.
Anyway, me and Munchy hate video games.
More than a human could even describe, I think we are completely fed up with the idea of interacting with media in any meaningful way.
Like, it's not even real, man. It's just pixels on the screen.
Yeah, it's not even, it's not, it has no bearing reality. It's all gay shit.
Nintendo hasn't made any good games since they made...
I think you're...
...Mariochic is typing.
And how can video games be real?
If our eyes aren't real.
That's all I'm saying.
Okay, I think to say we both love that presentation and it was great.
Oh yeah, we just watched the Nintendo Switch presentation.
Yeah, and it was...
It was really cool and pretty good.
And I loved it. And we love video games.
And we are the most red-pilled people on the face of the planet when it comes to video games.
If I had $299.99 burning a hole in my pocket, would I get a Switch?
Honestly, maybe.
Yes.
Because video games...
I think might redeem themselves.
Yeah, video games have caused so much violence in the streets.
Racial tensions are at an all-time high due to video games such as Splatoon.
Yeah, because video games have gone off the fray.
Video games have been getting people to Pokemon Go to the polls lately.
We need video games like the Nintendo Switch to get us to Pokemon Get Away from those polls.
Stay inside.
Don't talk to people and please, please consider suicide.
Unless you're going to your platonic best friend's home for an evening of Ice Breakers with Switch...
One-two Switch made by Nintendo, Reggie Philamy.
Anyway, what games did we just see?
We just saw...
Well, first of all, I have a bunch of notes here.
Okay.
And we should start from where the presentation starts, which is the hardware.
Okay, yeah, we start with the hardware.
My first note is I've got something to dock for you.
The Nintendo Switch is a DS, but not at all.
And you charge it by putting it on a little thing, and then you use controllers and you play the games.
It's a DS...
It's a DS 3DS Wii U.
That's it.
Yeah.
It's those two things.
It went on extended period of time about how it has D&A from every game system.
But really just like two and a half?
Yeah, yeah.
Just like the last couple that were good?
Yeah, the last couple.
The Gamecube has a handle on it.
It doesn't fucking care.
What?
Yeah.
Stupid.
Gamecube's the best system in the game, however.
However is the best game system.
In spite of its crippling handle.
Yeah.
I don't even know if the thing had a handle.
It's bizarre now that I think of it.
I use it all the time, honestly.
When I went to go play melee with some bros.
Dude, that's sick dude!
Jack off, Jack off, Jack off!
I'm picturing like...
Okay.
It's the heart of Tokyo, right?
Yes.
And it's 9am or 8am or 6am.
I don't fucking know.
It's when people...
All the Japanese businessmen are all making their morning commute.
And they're all sitting there on the subway holding the subway poles.
You know, the camera pans across the road.
All, you know, all heights, sizes, ages.
It's all these men, all these big towel men.
Just holding their briefcases.
These important stuffy briefcases.
Checking their watches.
Pan too munchy and his pizza onesie.
Holding his Gamecube like a suitcase.
Checking his watch that he isn't wearing.
Looking out the window.
That is drawn on with Sharpie.
As I do every morning.
Every, and every, and every number says...
Burger.
One.
Every number says one.
It's always one.
Well audience, guess what time it is.
I guess it's time to...
One.
It does look janky and they aren't much far apart than any other
Controller, but that is normally where they are placed in the sense that like there's one out like north and one south
Wait, is the 3ds kind of like that? Does it have like two joysticks like that?
Well the the the there's like a proof
Okay
The fucking what are they called the joycon the joycon are tiny
They're very they're tiny and also to you're supposed to like you have that like top slider on that gives them
The the shoulder buttons, yeah, which is even tinier and there's so many fucking moving parts
Yeah, there's so many little things it is very small and very vulgar and very
Complex such as another man that I know named Ben saying small vulgar
Yeah, all these fucking parts. I'm not I don't care that like I don't think I would if I had a Nintendo switch
I don't think I would lose these parts, but I do know I would be I do think that I would be frustrated every single time
I had to like find the like the shoulder buttons and like slide it onto my joycon
I'm not worried about that what I'm worried about is I have big fucking hand come on man
Yeah, and it would be I I think I held it
Obviously, but I think it would be very uncomfortable in my hands be very close together because I oh I already feel that way slightly
With the gamecube control and if it were any smaller than that
I think it would be a bit excessive not to be racist no racism
But I think it's it's because of your race and die
I was gonna say that like I think that it's designed for like Japanese hands, right?
Oh, that is exactly why it is like yeah, it's small for Japanese hands Japanese people are
Categorically smaller than other races. That's not in the physics team. Well, I think so I because I find the truth offensive
We as a poor we are the most blue pill people
Get away from me man, I don't want to hear a single fucking thing about that. All right
I don't want to hear but Japanese people are getting my entire fucking blire. No, I've seen I've seen too many of them
Yeah, in this in this in this last hour
It's coming out in two months. Yeah, it will be here sooner than my cum leaves my body
I hope so
And all right, what else about the hardware? Um, I find it weird. I
I mean, what's what's the deal with like so like all the games that it plays have to be
Runnable on like portable hardware
Yeah, so that's weird. That seems like it's really limiting
They put a lot of effort into like because that seems like there's a lot of games then that won't
Like like like I mean already like the Wii and the Wii U are not like hard. They're not
Powerful like the PlayStation whatever in the Xbox whatever are so I guess that's probably fine and they're and they're okay with the sacrifice
You still though that means that like anything you're playing on your Nintendo Switch is something that you should you would expect to be playing on
Something the size of like an intended like a 3ds. Okay. Yes, but have you seen how those games look? Yeah, they look great
I guess I guess we're getting to that point where that's not even that big a deal
Yeah, yeah, no
Because the 3ds the original 3ds was in between the Nintendo 64 and the game
graphics wise, yeah
And I like and due to the fact that they are going out from the outside to make this both a
Home and a handheld system. They're gonna put a lot of fucking effort into like min maxing where everything should go and it's
Maximizes
It basically just looks like the Wii U, but I don't care
No, I know that I should grab her, but I don't I don't care at all
Yeah, I think you'll agree with me the graphical fidelity isn't the end all be all
There's way more important things in making good games not not to say that visuals don't matter visuals better a lot
Yeah, art styling themes and gay shit that I don't I I hate everyone
Japanese people the most
Yeah, because they made Nintendo. Yeah, Nintendo
More like and they've trapped us in the vicious cycle of video game consoles
Which is the hell that you can never wake up from?
Most definitely most definitely that is the case. What was it saying?
Wait 3d hardware small hardware portable hardware visual fidelity. Yeah. Yeah, we're just saying that
It doesn't have to look hd necessary. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, exactly. I won't disagree. It looks nice, but it's definitely it's not
important
Yeah, yeah, I think yeah, the hardware is good enough. Yeah, portable
Yeah, that's something it's good
So so you don't think do you think it will be a visual downgraded from the Wii U? No, no, it's an upgrade. It's a straight up
Holy shit. Yeah, it's impressive. I guess the Wii U is pretty small
Yeah, it is like the actual console itself. I have no doubt it will be heavy
Which I think will hurt it a little bit in the sense that we normally just won't want to lug it around. Yeah, look
Yeah, lugging
Yeah lugging the equivalent of a Wii U around and playing it like on the subway then again
It is much leaner though. I get the impression that is leaner, but bigger
How much how much is a 3ds cost a 3ds was originally 250. I believe and now it's a hundred and fifty
Oh shit. So like so like the switch isn't even that much more expensive. No, that's another note of mine
$300 to fuck off
What do you mean?
We pay fun $350 at $300. Sorry. Yeah, and we can fuck off after that
Are you saying that's good or bad? I'm I don't know what I mean
I mean, I think it sounds like an okay price point. No. No. Yeah, it's definitely it. Okay. I'm fine with it
Do you remember when like weeds were like a hundred dollars? Yeah. Yeah, it was recent like I mean, what are they now Obama like nothing
Yeah, well like original we know her like fucking paper. They're toilet paper. You can pack you you use them as packing peanuts. Yeah
Very hard packing peanuts. Yeah
Really not not advised however, it is but it is economically viable
I guess I was totally true that certain dollars to fuck off because there's online paid
Oh, yeah, the pay online is such it's so shit. Yeah
That seems that doesn't seem like a Nintendo move to make like a play online service a pay-to-play thing
That's weird. It's never been like no, it hasn't why would they do that?
You know, it's gonna make I mean, I'm not gonna buy it when it comes out
But it would make me mad to like you get the console and the online service is free
And then suddenly it's not yeah, you like you lose that functionality. Yeah, that's that's shitty
I don't like it. I don't like it. It is it is definitely shitty
the only reason they could possibly be doing this is because
No one likes Nintendo online and they want to it like they want to improve its quality
And therefore they must focus on it more and therefore they deserve like they they want money for
They want money for the fact that they will now care about online. That's the only that's the only reason I can
Meet me that's not to say that I think it will be good because I have no like they have never done good online and any capacity whatsoever
God
Fucking the festival Plaza and Sun and Moon is so terrible. Yeah, it is worse thing ever
It doesn't even fucking work. It is so hard. Yeah to do it. Yeah. Oh
It's
Fuck Rick you you gosh dang Japanese people. Yeah, man
What were they thinking they must you know, they must have just not cared because they can all quick connect with each other and they're tiny island nation
Because they're all literally like on top of each other. Yeah, 100% of the reason they're so small is because there's not enough space to walk around
You have to be they're involved. They're they're they're evolving into oh, you mean the people. Yeah, I thought you meant the hard way
No, the boat. Yeah, yeah, but the one feeds into the yes, they're both shrinking
They're both game video games are shrinking and therefore they must shrink to play video games. That's all
People get smaller
The selective evolution of people have to get smaller to adapt to the new video game
Oh my god, this is like in this is cycles of every like five years or so the people
This is smaller and smaller to adapt to the new video game rapid evolution unlike anything else we've ever observed the Japanese in the video game are truly
What's the word this is why I mean, you know the thing about like like Japanese elderly people are like really small and hunched over
Yeah, because they had to adapt too many times because the video games just they just wore them out
This is why I see a video games are destroying Japan in more ways
And now it's bleeding over
Destruction when will it ends?
Well, it's a good thing you're talking about other
Hey, it's Jesse
Rowdy fuck
I don't fucking know I came up with it and I really don't like
I
Came up with it, isn't that you're very fond of
My next oh
Jesse have you seen the Nintendo switch?
He's given through completely. Well, he didn't skip through like 80% of it was hot garbage. Yeah. Well, I was pretty
pleased with the games generally I
Don't really give a fuck about Splatoon. Everybody like that. I love splatoon. Yeah, we're gonna use
Plagueons, you know, I have notes that will guide us through
Oh
If I got if I got a we a switch
Splatoon would be my top my top. Well, unless I wanted to try out arms
We should have said this at the beginning. This is crucial. My dick leans to the left. Does that happen to anyone else?
Or should I ask the doctor about that?
No, it's normal. Everyone's everyone's leans and everyone's bad
Okay, every dick is horrible in its own way, but vaginas are way worse
We can all we can all agree that the giant every vagina is horrible in the same way
Well, but join us are like evil. Yeah, but a dick is a sin. Yeah, I agree like vaginas commit dicks
Like genocide, right?
Oh
Fuck okay, okay. Have we said everything about the hardware? No, there's still more
My next note no region locking you fucking cunt. That's good. Yeah, they're not region locking. Yeah, it's great
Why would they never why isn't it hasn't it always been why why is region locking a video game?
Yeah, it's the worst video game ever made. I mean, I don't understand why it ever was ever
But like in the modern era of
Gaming it's especially baffling that it was that it needs still around to be removed second that I've never been able to play my
Evangelion Dating Sim
And they've just been sitting on my shelf, and I'll never know their glory
You probably you probably have to like take out the PS the PlayStation motherboard and like put a spring on the reset button
Or something and it'd be easier to build
Truly
Yeah, I think I think all we have to say is that's just sick. Yeah, it's pretty good
It's good, but I'm not gonna praise them for it because it's the base. It's baseline
Yeah, yeah, you're right. Nate was talking about this as well
It's not something we should like yeah, like they should have done this in the first place
It's not something to get all perceived. Yeah, that's not the right way. Yes. I have a note
I don't know what it means Fabio edits entertaining DNA
Go on. That's it. No, what do you think Jesse is that like they could be a game
Is that the truth that that is the that if anything is a red pill in documentary
That's not like a documentary. That'd be like a high fantasy adventure game. Yeah based on like Fabio romance novel
Yes procedurally generated to resemble just based on all the different elements of romance
Weaving a tapestry of continuity between all these disparate covers of these novels
You play as a as a Buxom wench
Whose bodice is ever on the cusp of ripping
You play as Fabio on your love quest across the nine realms
Which includes San Diego, Chicago
Everyone knows the nine realms
New York City Toronto
And Rio de Janeiro
Toronto is the final boss
The women are so Muslim. It's hard to even walk
You have to go and reform it
Curit curits plague
This this is something we're gonna get married to their boats, right? No, no, no
Do does anyone agree with the with my opinion that handhelds are better than home consoles? Um
Um
But the Splatoon wait Splatoon is on the 3ds wasn't it? No, not at all
I mean, I'm actually I'm not really I completely understand home consoles and I like them just fine
However, I like the idea of like I like to always be at my computer
So the fact that I can just use like a DS while I'm at the computer is
very appealing
But then you're not really you're not using your computer
I mean couldn't you just have a home console right next to your computer wouldn't it be like the same thing?
I guess so, but I can also like walk around and I can also go to the bathroom
I can also you know do all the shit that a normal need does a normal need a good need
Like like every good boy should
It's um
But see what this is the best of both worlds because you can be gay and I can be gay and we can all suck each other's dick
Hang on. I've lost track of the conversation
Then into a switch this whole gimmick is it's a home console and a and no
Yeah, and it's you know what I think I just have a psychological bias against taking my home console on the road
Even though it costs like barely more than a 3ds would but I would still feel really weird like
Plants like the guy in the trailer like playing Skyrim and then picking up my Skyrim machine taking Skyrim on the bus with me
Maybe if I tried it, I would get over it real quick. It seems weird. I would definitely
Like not use it in the situation of that that that hideous monster uses
The boy the boy on the trailer that there's like this guy in like a trailer and he like looks like a normal human
He looks like he looks like a normal will just a human and therefore
Yes, yes, I understand. I mean
Yeah, I don't yeah, I don't get it either
It's like yeah, you play it up if you have like an hour long commute or something on the subway
I think so but like most people don't commute
You like you'd be like in like little five minute increments like oh getting on the bus getting sitting on the bus getting off the bus
Walking down the street. I
Like to flip out my DS if I ever go to say a restaurant alone
When I'm when I'm I can't spend time with my friends like I want to and I decide like well
I might as well just play a video game so I can remind myself
Well, I can lead myself in the thinking that people like me like I don't I don't need a video game to fill like
Little like five or ten or fifteen minutes. Well, I'm saying if I go into a fucking restaurant
Yeah, like like like while I'm waiting to eat. I'll play the game
I'm going if I if I had a yeah
If yeah, if I had a console a three-hand hill console, yeah
I like I like I'm one of those people who likes is like I'm going to play a video game
Yeah, you know, but I get but I guess I don't know
I guess I'm one of these guys who I like I like
Narrative and I like immersion and I like to get lost in a thing
I don't think I've ever been immersed in anything in my entire life
You and did you both think that and I'm like I get immersed man
That's what I'm looking for when I play a game is to like be have a fun
But the closest thing I've ever been to him probably immerse myself in is rape play because I emphasize so much with the main character
Is that the one where you're like a god and you have like powers to like blow the girls skirts up?
No, no, I think no, well, it's the one where you rape a mother and then her daughter on a Japanese
I'm pretty sure that's the one. I'm thinking. Okay. I'm pretty sure I've done that scenario so many times
My life is basically like rape in every way and
I'm Japanese. Where did the video games end and reality begin?
With digs predicts prediction
The world will become more like a video game and video games will more and more resemble the real world until the two are
Functionally inseparable
Yes, yes, especially in Japan. Well, I already that way in Japan. Can I eat vagina as Crash Bandicoot?
Not yet. Well in the future one day. I can't wait until all law
Reverse to like a Grand Theft Auto five-star system
Like I can rate like as long as I rate under seven people it'll stay under two stars
You can still like hide in an alleyway for five seconds
That ties into our hatred of cost statute of limitations is like 30 seconds to five minutes depending on the severity of the event
Yes, I completely agree
Home screen there were like three frames of it
Nintendo
I
Don't have any of you play the original BS. I had one
It does home screens better than any other fucking thing because it it takes like three seconds to get
It's just like a button, right? Yeah, just you just think yeah
It's like like you turn on it like the big button is like the game. Yeah, you hit the game and then the game
Yes, I it's the best of both worlds because I like game
I like old systems because you can just turn it on in the games there
The fact that you can just do more with video game
And you can like download games and shit
You know, I don't think I agree. I wish that we didn't need a home screen because like yeah
I currently I need the home screen in order to configure all my shit in order to make say the festival plaza and Pokemon Sun
Actually work because I need to like add people's friend codes. I wish we didn't need that. I wish I wish I wish it wasn't
This way
I just like having app like like various applications on my 3ds
But I never do anything but the game
I do agree that it needs to be downplayed as it was with the DS and it looked very similar to the DS
It's like it was just like like big squares and the first one you're on is like Mario
It's isn't it fucked that the 3ds like you open it up and there's all these like 20 buttons
Yeah, and like one of them is the game and it's like no bigger or more prominent than any of the other
Yeah, it's just what one of the many many helpful functions of your 3ds includes playing a video game. Yes. Yes
I I can really agree. Yeah, and I
Everything I've gone from from the way the hardware looks to the the way the the software you want to come in man
Recording
Bye
Thanks for stopping by I'm rowdy fuckers cop killer
Yeah
Ham boys and boys. All right. Oh, yeah, it looks like home screen. Yeah
Everything looks like it looks very modern. Nintendo doesn't make anything look fucking good
They can't make hardware or home menus look good
They just can't but now they can because I'm assuming they have like like like phone app developers to help them
They probably poached a bunch of Apple dudes
Yeah, yeah, and now they're and now they're caught up to the modern world because they're channeling the ghost of Steve Jobs
Who is gay? He's my favorite original character is the ghost of Steve Jobs
My favorite original character is the the skeleton
He doesn't have he only has one skeleton in his closet the man is in a doozy
You haven't even talked about the games yet. No, I'm there's a point
home screen the home screen
fucking
The way you is the worst game system ever made it looks like shit
Everything about it is shit and and the game pad itself. It's not the most uncomfortable
Disgusting the heaviest thing. I hate the game the game pad or whatever you call it. Yeah, the game
Like when it's fucking time to play a video game everyone wants to not use that. Yeah. Yeah
No, I don't want to be saddled with this burden. Yeah, it's the worst thing ever, but the switch
Does look good. I think it looks it looks like it looks comfortable
Yeah, well other than the fact that the controllers look like fucking tiny and like little toys and stuff
Maybe I could maybe if I held maybe I could get over there. Maybe it's maybe it wouldn't be as bad
Yeah, I think holding it in our hands. We would I think it will be bigger than over than what we're thinking
I do think it will be small
That's not how they aren't atoms better play. I'm playing the world's smallest video games you guys
This is an audio show. This is an individual show. They wouldn't understand that at all
I'm holding my fingers exactly together and rubbing them. It's like like the world's smallest violin. Yeah. Yeah, okay
Got it. Got it. Okay. Uh made for Japs very small. Oh, we've been over that. Yes, uh Fakie
Wada's gay the the presentation about it written in itself the presenters were a real wacky cast
I mean my my favorite one has to be the guy who comes up looking like this fucking this like he's like a
late 40s
Buzz-Cutted guy in like this kind of like pointy-looking tuxedo with like yeah
We have like a big like silver key
And he's and he shows up he shows up looking like some kind of Kingdom Hearts villain
Says something and then goes away with no consequences
He says like Sega makes video games. Bye. Oh, no
He what stuck out to me about it is that he phrased it in terms of himself
Yeah, as a game creator like as an individual creator and I have no idea who yes, was he a Sega guy?
Yeah, yeah, he was second. All right. Well, he's clearly him. He's clearly in nefarious
I was like this is a villain that I'm seeing here
This guy's gonna come back in chapter three and he's gonna fuck shit up things gonna be going really good for our main character Mario
Yeah, this guy is just gonna yeah, he's gonna flip the script on it. He's off the wall. Yeah
We're
Yeah, rowdy fuckers rowdy fuckers. Well, what was incredibly boring? Huh? No
Okay, um
Jesse remember remember that one guy from the presentation who was like dressed in a black tuxedo with a big silver key chain
And he has like he was like a head like squirt of like kind of a mohawk a little bit
He was just some I don't know he was he was just like this evil looking guy
He looked like a second guy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He looked like a monster. Yeah. Yes
He looked like a Kingdom Hearts villain. Yeah, that's what I thought
And then there was there was the guy the guys like let's switch over to this person and the guy comes in and he's like yeah
Oh, oh, right. Yeah, cuz he's talking. He's had a Travis touchdown. Yeah. Was that was that Suda of
51 oh
He comes out like yeah, oh that didn't go over there
But then he ends it with another yeah, which also doesn't go over the dub of that man in particular was the funniest thing
I've ever seen in my entire fucking life. He starts taught. He's like talking in Japanese
And the and the translation translators just like
Video games in this in this area. I don't think that translator actually speaks any Japanese
I think he just like he had like a made his best guess like a weird like sitcom day where he stumbled into that job
Like fill in for somebody
That there is ours got one point where I swear like the guy had been talking a fucking mile a minute
And then like like I like one minute later
You can like hear him like actually like knock his mic over like oh, oh, yes
video games and
Shit, I mean I could not repeat to you anything
He mentioned a Travis touchdown and he likes indie games, I guess yeah, I think we scooped over it
Well, when me and Jess were watching it with Victor, however, we went to extensive detail about the weird ice cube Arctic scene
Oh when he's like shaking the ice
Where it's supposed to I don't buy it
Looks really cool. Yeah, even though I can't
Imagine it. Do you know what it was saying? Yeah, but it has like some kind of like haptic feedback thing
Yeah, it has HD rumble capabilities
What yeah, which is like which is like high definition rumble which means like nothing
Well, I think well what it seemed to be suggesting was that like the rumble
Functionality is like it's not it's like it's like it has like
Spatial qualities to it like it occurred like in different places in the remote depending on like
What the object is supposed to be which I don't think there's any fucking reason for that
No, I don't mind it. I don't mind it at all. But what the fuck are they good?
Yeah, like what what is the purpose of this like I mean I like I like rumble
Yeah, like when when when whenever rumbles happening, it's like an explosion, right? Like something fucking crazy is happening
Yeah, and so there's no like there's there's never gonna be a point where an explosion is happening
Directly on like like on my left side only well if if they somehow crafted a gameplay
experience that like really made use of like this HD rumble
I think it could be pretty neat
Fucking sick nasty. Yeah, so I'm for it. Also. There was like a rock-paper-scissors section. Oh, yeah
Like how the Wiimote like sensor bar thing it recognizes the shape of objects and the examples
They gave were rock-paper-scissors with your hands. Yes, which is pretty neat. Uh, I
Feel like that's far more practical
Even though I have no idea what it would be used for I mean, I'll tell you what it's gonna be useful
It's gonna be used so you can do your favorite shadow clone jutsu is in our in Naruto fight
Never mind the best game system. Yeah
And so I can do my various game symbols
Yeah, and not look like in retard except I still will and the game will know I'm a retard when you start up
50 cent blood on the sand to 50 cent
51 cents when you start the official Wu Tang
License video game
Then you will you three you throw up your your chosen gang sign that the game
You know hopefully shows you how to make and then your character just like whoosh you become outfitted you become black in real life
It's kind of like Final Fantasy 10 to we're like the dress orbs like change your class
You throw up a different gang sign and then you get like new abilities based on what gang you're a part of um, I know
everything about gang culture
You look like it Ben you really look like an expert on gang culture. I'm an expert on what the fuck I'm talking about right now
Now let's actually talk about the fucking video games
One-two switch. I just I think did you try it as WarioWare for normies?
Yeah, one-two switch is not a video game making it the best video game of all time
You don't look at the screen the whole gimmick is that you look into the other person's eyes
And it's a various set of mini games that you are like you're you're first instructed by the screen and then like
I guess you look into their eyes and then you just sense out when to do button presses. I guess I think it's cool
I think it's cool. I don't think it's fucking gay. Yeah. Well, it's it's not a video game
It is quite. It's kind of it's just it's like a video game icebreaker thing. Yeah
It's for normies is the most normie video game ever produced
Yeah, like it's it's just like the game itself is just there to keep score while you and your buddies like you know play charades and like
With your dick sound do a sword fight. Yeah, you know do quick quick draw things or whatever and play times with each other
And I'm all and I'm all for it. You know, I just sound very negative just then I think I think it's a okay
I think I would I wouldn't buy it ever, but you know what?
One-two switch the first game
But you can shoot each other
Don't you understand you play the game by looking into each other's eyes a note that I have for this is face-to-face actual real life death
The gimmick
Okay, now let's move on from the gayest game ever to the gayest game ever punch out shit arms looks cool cool
It's okay. Yes, and it's awesome. You don't think it looks like
Retarded all retarded baby shit
Well, it looks like a really great time
No, I thought it looked really neat and
Notice how when they showed the gameplay of it. They just showed the gameplay
They didn't show the guys actually playing with it because they're not gonna look like they're doing stuff
No, you're playing it. You're just gonna go. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you're just gonna be making little like put
But I'm making very minor gestures with my hands. I don't get it
I don't go where they can't just make video games why they have to make a bunch of bullshit
I will agree the motion controls very severely will probably damage
However, yeah, you know what I like I like the idea like like he like the guy on
Presentation described it as like boxing you have to use you have to you have to punch
But it's like shooting you have to adjust where your opponent will be. I think yeah
I think it's a very good game idea the idea of like
Flicking the thing to punch and then turning to like adjust the trajectory of your punch seems pretty neat
And if it felt good, I think it could be because it's not it's not gonna be like that
It's gonna be like like that. Yeah, like like the trailer has these guys actually throwing like full-body punches as though
Like it actually controls where the punch goes, which is not
The truth. Yeah, not the truth
But I still think it was fun
Okay, my opinion on that is I know a friend who will buy literally every game that the switch pulls out
And I will try it at his house. And if I think it's cool about myself
I'm going to go in with low expectations because I don't like motion controls a lot, but I'm hopeful for the future
I mean, I think I think it
Very Nintendo has done motion controls good a couple of times and if they did it again
But not nearly enough times to justify that they've been doing it for like 11 years. That's true. Yeah. Yeah, that is true
It's time to pack it in
Yes, I
I basically
No, I'm excited for arms. I I already got arms
But they're gay
They aren't springs. They are like they only reach like this far man
I want to punch I want to punch a cute girl who's like way over there
I I think a punchy cute girl is pretty much constantly
You want to punch women? You've got to allow yourself to get close to them. You can't be a migtail
You can't be a migtail and still beat women
God, who's been great at the greatest conflict. Yeah of interest
Next is Splatoon me and Ben Loew Splatoon. I don't think you even know. Well, I'm sure you know what it is
I mean like in different
Yeah, it's fun man. There's all these different weapons that shoot different amounts of paint at the floor
I will say Splatoon would be the best game ever, but the Wii U is the worst Wii game console
It's so bad. Yeah, like like having to play it with the gamepad is the worst experience a human
Yes, Splatoon. It just felt like a game where nothing I did mattered
It was completely random which team ended up getting the most paint
It was the big cluster clock
Okay, it is true that it can feel like you can be feel like you're winning the whole game
And then you lose at the end and you don't know why
Okay, most of my experience with Splatoon comes from the competitive mode. They have yeah, which isn't terth wars
It's like a bunch of objective based game
It's and those game modes are very very fun unique and they do involve like putting like paint on the ground in multiple ways
However, they aren't as
Open like open in the sense that you can just paint anywhere. I don't count this boy's routine
It's much more again objective based and you feel far far more important in that mode
Wait, you're talking about like the single player. No, I'm talking about the the competitive mode
The there there's terth wars, which is casual and then there I
You should call it's called ranked mode ranked mode. I mean they have different game game modes in that
I don't think I ever played any of those. Okay. That's that's good. Um, they're fun. Yeah, uh single player is also very fun
Well, it's a single player single player campaign was kind of fun
It was felt it felt a little hollow the game is definitely meant to be yes
It's not meant for that. Uh, the final boss was very fucking hype. However, the rest is your favorite campaign
I could not fucking care less the final the final I have not actually played the final boss, but I've seen it
It's awesome. It is incredible. Um, he's black. He's on octopus and he's my dad
The um, I I love the inklings
Yes, I love the whatever their octopus enemies are called the octolings the octolings and the inklings
I love that they're like evil beast children. Yes, that hate and eat one another. Yes, I only live
They only live for battle and urban youth fashion
There's two there's two things that drive them in urban youth fashion and murder
Yes, it's true
And that's why I love it. Um
Uh, I like that you can change your hairstyle in this game. I am gay
And as such, I like to dress up my fictional character in many ways. Well, here's the thing
Here's the one thing that did fucking kill me about splatoon, which was that there was no local multiplayer
Well, no, there was local multiplayer
But it was like shitty and bad
Because it wasn't the actual it wasn't like a turf war
It was like who can like shoot the most balloons or something
It was awful
And I think the reason it was implemented that way is because like the real game has all this
Functionality that requires the Wii U game pad and you're only supposed to have one
So if they can fucking cure that well, they they have because the whole point of this which is you're supposed to have two
Yeah, if you want to play with some of these I guess well, I mean, I guess the point is that there's there's so many different ways to play
That's kind of a shit solution because then that's just being like buy another console
I mean, yeah, I could I could play with my friends by buying two. We use already. Okay. Think about this way
If you have a friend who wants to play splatoon, they are going to have a fucking Nintendo switch
I guess
No, what if you want to just bring a friend over really? Hey play this fun game that I have
Uh, you're right. However, I think that's far less likely than the scenario I have presented
Maybe maybe I do agree that it should be
Not that they should they should have some game mode where like just you you and a friend just fucking give each other
Your joy cons and just like have a little fucking mini
I think it will be like that
I that's what that's all I wanted was just give me the regular game in miniature to play with the friend
Locally on one concept. I I do believe it will be that however, uh, I think it's
Whatever
yeah, anyway
They they didn't they didn't really explain how exactly the multiplayer modes would work in the new, uh
Platoon, but I
They'll probably make it better. Um, I'm sure they will and even if they don't I'm gonna be mainly plain ranked
Yeah, and I will have a blast doing so I will be able to dress up my little boy
And he will be my son and hopefully I don't have my dick inside of anymore because the police came to my house that one time
It was it was a fiasco. Hopefully my dick doesn't find his way
And then on that note and then there was some anime shit
Uh
Well before the animation all right all right
Before the anime shit, uh a a a game that we all care about the new mario
Oh
Yes, you know very accurate. You know I was I was skeptical when I first saw because like the first thing they show is him in that like
GTA world with like the regular people walking around and I think it looks awesome
I thought it looked bad at first, but like the more I thought about it
Like every level of like yeah every level of the game looks so different
You said that when watching the trailer and like I don't know it's it's this is I don't feel like it's meant to
Maybe I was thinking a bit more is like the lore of the mushroom kingdom
We're like I don't I don't think that's what they're going for
Well, the as they say in the presentation the whole thing is that mario has left the mushroom kingdom because he's bored and the piece of
Shit is that I'd miss that well the game is called mario odyssey
Which brings to mind some kind of like weird wonderlandy like he's just totally in a whole different dimension
Yeah, he the whole the whole thing is mario is fucking bored and he wants to just walk around other places
Yeah, you know, I think I thought that like the whole game would be set in like a realistic looking city
Which is not definitely not no that would have been very weird
When tom and them were talking about it the other night
They made it out to seem like some kind of hub world like the sonic 06 kind of thing
That it looks like sonic 06. Just if you look at only that part of the trailer it looks like it's just one world of many
Yes, yeah, I think it would probably be like the first world
However, they're like again, there are like a ton of different fucking worlds. Yeah
and and they and I want to
Iterate that none of them look like fucking the gay shit we've been getting for a while now
They don't mean like 3d world and stuff. Yeah, well, yeah, they don't look like grassy plants
They don't look like fucking sky world. They don't look like any of that gay shit. Oh, yeah
There's like there's like pastel polygon world and there's like
Forest world there's there's a forest world that specifically has like like a rainy backdrop and like mario was swimming in it
And there's like rays of light coming through down from the trees
And it's like fairly like like a like a moody green and blue color scheme
There's also that one world that I can't describe in any other white way than red squares
I don't remember that one like it just kind of looks like there's red squares and trees and it's it's it's odd
A whole lot of rebel pixels. Yes
the the communistic
Overlord himself the rest of the rebel pixel. Um, um, um, okay, so I just
You know, I was skeptical at first and I was like, uh realistic world
But the more I think about it the more I'm just like man
I actually am really happy that they're just making a new 3d mario and it's been way too long
I don't know why they let it go on this long
But I'll fucking play it. Uh, I
Okay, I understand you not wanting like not you you but like you some of you
Yeah, uh, not wanting to have mario interact with normally proportion to human beings
However, I think it looks hilarious ridiculous and I love
Yeah, if it's him like
You know, yeah, if he's on like some interdimensional odyssey and it's just one of many wacky worlds that's cool. Yeah
It's good. Uh, and and I like the idea of being able to run around a city
Uh, and just fucking jump around because I want I I want to jump around in the city
It's funny to because like the whole like open world city game is such like a saturated genre
Now so like to have like fucking mario show up to like a world that looks like that
But like do mario style platforming through it? I don't know if that's like the joke
They were trying to make with it or anything, but it's funny to me think about it. I don't think it's a joke
I think it looks cool
And they wanted it. Well, definitely some humor in there and putting mario alongside you. Yes, that is true. Yeah
Yeah, I gear in that and
Not just the aesthetics of it the gameplay itself looks very fucking cool because there's a bunch of movement mechanics
Yeah, like throwing the hat throwing the hat was the big one that everyone noticed
But there are also many other things such as I saw the cake returning from samurai 64
I saw him rolling down a hill that looked like a whole new move
And uh, there's just a bunch of little shit and in at one point he was
Riding a fucking lion a lion and also he uh, what he was picking up something that like like a bladed oddish
Not an odd
Radish radish. I don't know if that will just be that but I hope it's like a mario 2 thing. Um
Not really relevant to anything, but I'll be pretty excited to hear matthew matosis review it when it comes out. That should be fun
Uh, what I really love the mario games
Because like I I like to just move around and it comes from a comfortable environment
Yeah, I like the what's the gay word that you do use kinesthetics
Well, he doesn't make that up. But yeah, well, yeah that he would he is he would use it
Yeah, that's what I because it's the word to describe it
That's gay. Yeah, it's gay
Uh
Yes, I like that and I like the idea of being able to maneuver in various different ways because in in in fucking galaxy
And shit, you just you just move and you jump you have like you have less movement options
Yeah, and that's why I love sunshine so much because the the flood adds so many layers of complexity
Yeah, it's the best working game ever made. Yeah. Hmm. Um
It's uh incredible, uh, and I'm coming and mario looks good, which is something I'd never thought I'd ever say
Yes, well, you know, uh semen is clogging my entire brain cell
Well, yeah, I mean new mario new 3d mario. It's pretty good. I want to play it. Yeah, what what more can you say?
Um, I'll no no moving on moving on. Uh, there was a bunch of fucking anime shit
Uh
Xenoblade whatever
Shin Megami Tensei like dude like anime like what the fuck even is a shin megami tensei
Some kind of some kind of some kind of you know creature every year. There's like 17 new shin megami Tensei games even though
People only care about persona. Yeah, I don't know why they even bother with the rest of this
I don't
You know the only thing that I like like the only thing that I know about
Jumagami Hidze that seems even remotely cool is if you kick someone's ass hard enough
They will ask you like a strange riddle and if you solve their retarded
They will join you. Yeah, it's like persona three and four are both great games
But there's 50 shin megami games and the rest of them are all hot trash. Yeah, no one do care about
Uh, another note
They got the animeist thing. Yeah, that shit brings all the boys to the yard
Uh, uh, that sucks and that everyone loves
80 games and development. That's a lot of shit. We have games. I promise this is indeed not the Wii U
Please trust me. We have video games
Yeah, remember when when when I remember when reggie fill me was like boy
It's the games that are important and boy what games and I was like, you're right reggie. What games?
What name even one?
Reggie looks like
No, I mean like toad creature. He's so rich
Okay, do you just see it looking at him? He's not rich like wealthy. He's rich like chocolate. Yeah. Yeah
Like he's just he's just dark and like if you like take a look at him
You just need a glass of milk to just wash him. You gotta wash him down. Yeah, I need to dilute him with something
He looks like fucking like like lord slug like a big fat Namek
Who found his way to earth and is just shitting up the place. He is literally a goblin. He is definitely a goblin
I think he's a hobgoblin
He's totally a hobgoblin
If you could add some kind of an even a third ob to that hobgoblin word like a slob hobgoblin
Awful he's a church really. He's a fucking gobb sloblin gobb sloblin
He's an everlasting slob gobbster and and then and and then and then you know
Shigeru Miyamoto's there looking like a special needs child playing playing nintendo games
Which he almost certainly is a special needs child looking like a soccer mom who had a stroke in 2005
And never fully recovered
And then and then and then some other guy pokes around pokes around
Yeah, he was totally hiding hiding behind hiding behind a bush as all japanese people are known to do
He jumps out and he's like oh reggie. I'm glad you're right to play a video game
Miyamoto looks like he's aging like benjamin button
But also like a normal person at the same time
He's shrinking and getting smaller and his his cheeks are getting chubbier, but the wrinkles just keep getting deeper and deeper
Oh
Truly unfortunate for all parties
Yes, truly a great source of shame for japan
They gotta hide that boy
They have to hide him away
They have to lock him away where he can't get out before he turns back into a side goat
A disgusting wrinkly sperm floating in a jar before before he regresses to the star child from uh,
Odyssey space odyssey 2001
Oh my god
Floating in a giant like egg
Mm-hmm
A game that is undeniably anime though. I was interested in the fact that it looked fucking weird
project octopus
Wait, was that a game?
Yeah, I thought that was like the subtitle for the new fire emblem or something. No, no
Octopath octopodio
Starship excel saga project octo mom. You play as octo mom. You beat up all of your kids
No
He's gay. Anyway, uh, the game is like it's like final fantasy. It has like pixel pixel graphics
However, it's like it's like 3d, but the prick the the pixels not the pixels the pixels are like
They're still like flat
they're like they're like
Like it's like it's like paper mario
What what do you what?
Uh, wait, I I have to pee really bad. Okay. Let's take a break
Okay, okay. I'm back for peeing. Uh, it was like octopath missionary
Uh, yes, that sounds right. Uh, it was like if you were playing with magnets like picks like pixel art magnets
Like in a paper mario s world
That oh, oh, yeah, it looked like it looked like jrpg. It had like jrpg pixel. I remember that and I didn't know what it was
Weird, I thought it was just like some retro like concept art for the new for the new fire emblem or something
No, it was not even the same game at all
Like they all that that anime segment of the whole game of the presentation was just all jumbled together
Uh, uh another anime that we hate uh skyrim
Uh, everyone was joking about how it was in the the original trailer
But it wasn't actually officially announced for the switch and everyone's gonna think
Everyone said it was just not going to be there. Yeah
Which would have been hilarious. It would have been very high room on there. But but Todd Howard the literal liar himself gets up on stage
In in in the in his aztec temple. He has built into his house
And he says that yes skyrim is coming and uh, fuck. Yeah, bro
But what I want to know is why anyone likes skyrim or or is pretending to like skyrim
Um, search me man. I don't play Bethesda games
Yeah, uh Bethesda is uh, awful and um
Todd Howard can suck my weenie
Uh, yeah, I don't I don't know. I just yeah
I know I said before that I like to get immersed and like have like a narrative
Which you would think I would love games like skyrim, but like I don't know
They're so big and overblown and like and I'm not they look so fucking bad
I I'm I'm not looking I'm not looking to be impressed with the scale of a game. Yeah, you know, I don't care about that. So I don't
Like yeah, like like the idea that a game is like a hundred hours long
And like the map is a million fucking miles wide. It's just kind of exhausting more than like exciting for me. Yeah, uh death
Uh skyrim looks bad and I've only heard bad things about I hear it's boring. I hear it's dull. Well, I have no reason why I want to play
I I only hear criticism of it
But it's criticism that makes me think that it's probably an overall solid game for what it is
But it's just got like does lots of little shit wrong that really pisses fans off. Yeah
Um, uh either way would never fucking buy it. It's a pc game. I could literally just bar it legally
Was that's like censored? Yes. Yeah, okay
I could yeah, I would never buy this game. I could literally just bar it
I see I see yes
Um, uh, then we got to the the crazy no more heroes guy. It was a stumbling mumbling joke
Stumbling mumbling fool that's sudo 51. I can't believe that was sudo 51. Is that true? Yes. Is that really okay? Okay
Um, I have never played a no more heroes game, but due to there's only there's only one isn't there? There's two, okay
Um, it it looks like something I would love and that picture of travis that was like on like the screen was so fucking hot
I'm i'm gay now. I am gay
What did his shirt say it was something like travis touched out of strikes bad
All right, um, but his face was so charismatic. It's so Japanese. I like I like that
No more heroes exist. I think I played a little bit of the first one was like, that's fine
Um, I it looks cool. I like seeing it around. Yeah, I don't feel the need to play it myself necessarily
Want to play
Maybe if I were paid to play that game, I'm definitely I mean I I do respect sudo 51's like weird outsider
Like auteur fucking game making ethos. I think it's great that he's around. Yes
Yeah, it's pretty sweet. Then after after I was turned gay live. Yeah
Uh fucking ea came out to talk about how like they like nintendo and they are going to make fifa
Yeah, wait, I totally
Do not even remember that happening. Yeah, I don't recall. Oh, wait. I do remember
I do remember the migtao soccer players appearing very briefly in the like the final trailer. Yes
Uh, he was the guy who had bill trin and narrating
The giant he was the the giant he was the giant from uh twin peaks. Yes with that guy
He's happening again
it uh
Literally, no, I don't think I've ever heard anyone say anything cause about ea
It's like searching through the library of his mind trying to come up with one thing to repeat that trying to remember what a video game
Is
Yeah, yeah, they're evil probably. No, no, do they make do they make any good games that aren't gay? Well, yeah, no
I'm not saying they're evil. I'm just saying they're just they're just gay. Do they no, but serious question
Do they make any good games? No, okay
They make sports games and they make just general gay games like what give me an example
I think they do like some sort of call duty stuff. Um
Okay, so
Modern gaming they're modern gaming for some part. All right, uh, then I have a bullpoint that says no games
No games
Yeah, there weren't enough games for sure and the games that there were were a lot of anime bullshits
Okay, okay, he there are four games in my opinion coming out for the nintendo switch
Uh, so far I announce. Yeah, uh, two of them
switch one or one two switch looks um
Like a look like I'm not on my raid system that ranges from a negative three to a positive three
It is a positive one. Yeah, and then arms looks like a positive two. Well, you know what?
Okay, I hope we were saying this as you're watching it
It would be really cool if arms had like a competitive scene. Yes
Like like and and corollary to that like for that to happen
It would need to have like there would need to be real depth to the gameplay
Like probably there would need to be lots of like builds you could make like customize your characters to behave in different ways and then like
You know strategize beyond beyond just the moment to moment dodging punches. Yeah, and just have general
complexity in in the in the combat itself. I mean they they
And they introduced the game with by saying like it's a game with lots of depth and complexity and replayability
Which I hope is true. Uh, if that were if that were true, it looks fucking fun
But like the game we actually saw in the trailer there wasn't much there. We didn't see it do very much
I heard from a little birdie. I didn't actually watch the nintendo tree house presentation
Which is where they show the old games and death
I heard a little birdie telling me that in the tree house presentation where the plane arms
One of the person one of the commentators is talking about
Frame inputs and how to save frames and maximize your your min maxing your your inputs like a like a real fighting game
That's pretty cool. It is fucking pretty cool
And it makes me think that they actually like care about this game. It's not going to be a shitty it
I like it. I hope I hope that's true. I hope that's true
Even though that kind of excludes me because i'm not going to get so fucking good at arms
And i'm going to be worrying about saving the frames, but I still like it
Yeah, uh, I now that jess is out of the room and i'm not scared to death. I
To a three
Thank god
Uh and and and fucking splatoon and mario they look incredible. They look like they will be the best game ever made
Um, if if splatoon is if splatoon is any better than original splatoon, it will be the best game ever made
And I won't accept any future games as valin. I just can't wait for new spot this
I never actually did any splat because I didn't I didn't have a Wii U
I just played it at my like friend's house when I was visiting in the future
If you get a switch, we will become the splatoon boys
Oh god, can I oh god? I would love that so much. But can I can I is there a place for
I want to make one
I want to make I want to make room for no I want to make room for it in my heart is what i'm saying
Yeah, and in my bed pokemon is out the door besides
Well, well that that's completely inaccurate because there's a pokemon game coming out for the switch. Oh, no
Wait, why didn't they show that?
Uh, because it it's like all
Even though like everyone who cares knows
Well, like apparently I don't care because I didn't know until you told me, uh, it you know how like there's platinum for diamond pearl
Yeah, yeah, the sun the moon is going to have a platinum on the switch. What's it called? Is it called eclipse?
It's called the codename of stars. I hope it's called eclipse. Okay, the codename of stars
Fair enough
Not not happy about it. You're gonna be able to walk with your pokemon. I think pokemon is
I hope that's true because the walking pokemon and harkol's soul silver is actually the best thing that ever happened
There's even more reason for it now
Because before you couldn't really do that much with the pokemon. Like it was it was fucking sick
Yeah, but there's not a lot you can do now think about fucking this
You're walking with your pokemon you turn around you press a you immediately go into the pokemon uh of me pokemon refresh
Oh
Cool. Yeah, turn around talk to them and you pet them and give them the pain. Yeah. Yeah
Just a little thing just the little things nintendo. Just give us these little things and then you promote them to uh
Potlitenit and then they and then they die. Yeah, that's right
Because I didn't fucking switch out to water. You fucking return because I'm an idiot. Yeah, that's correct. Um
Uh, there's also a curbie game coming. I'm fairly certain
I would hope so. Yeah, I would really hope so god
Every time a new curbie game comes out. I say the same fucking thing
But let me say it again. Please bring back powers and power combining from yes from curbie 64
Yes, please that would be fucking sick. That would make the switch the best console. Yeah, uh power combines before is
It's so good
And there's no reason they couldn't continue to do it forever
I I know why because curbie game there there are two eras of curbie games
There's the adventure era and these then there's the superstar era
Adventure era
Operate the abilities in that operate. There are a lot more abilities
However, that all the abilities have like one use they all have one move that you can execute
And a superstar there. Well, I shouldn't say that way more, but there's the same amount of abilities
But each ability
Uh is it has an entire move set dedicated to it. Yeah, which was amazing. Yeah, and the best and uh
Two more operates on an adventure
Uh style ability. So each thing only does one thing. Yeah. Yeah, you know what?
You know what? Yeah, I think I would if I had to have one or the other
Maybe I would like the the complex abilities that have like whole move sets
But why can't it be both? Yeah? Yeah
All the things that nintendo doesn't do yeah when they're fucking nintendo and they could do anything
Yeah, they could do literally
I
Hope I hope they do do that that would be crime at least even if it's not that at least
Not I don't have anything against like epic yarn and stuff like it is what it is and that's fine
But why have there not been new Kirby games that have the power system and like new powers and stuff
Like why don't why have they not made more Kirby games that are about the powers?
I
Agree, yeah, I mean like I love that. I mean the problem is is the Kirby games don't come out that often
And that's the problem right there. Yeah, and and
Like whenever there's a new like mainland Kirby like like they're two Kirby games
They're there are the side games that are experimental weird and have nothing to do with anything
Kirby related and they're awesome. Yeah, they're always like air ride
Yeah, like air ride like canvas curse shit like math attack. Yeah
I shouldn't do that shit cool shit like math attack. Yeah, I haven't actually played any of those games, but
Yeah, I hear air ride is really good. I heard math attack
It looks really the math math attack is good
Like like the gameplay itself is good, but there's like there's like really like a ton of mini games
And like a lot of the Kirby anime characters come up really. Yeah, it's it's odd. It's very odd
It's good. No, I like it. I do like it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right
And there's the mainland Kirby games. What? Oh, sorry. Just do you do we know what the Kirby game for the switch?
No, right? Well, I don't think it's even confirmed. I just know that howl is working
Okay, and howl doesn't fucking do this. Don't they do Pokemon?
It's your scheme. That's right. Well, why did I think there was a no, all right? I'm stupid
Anyway, mainly Kirby games are like shit like super star like a vision
And those ones always introduce at least one new
And shit like robo bot introduced like the mech system
The mech system in Kirby. Yeah, the fuck is Kirby robo bot?
Planet robo bot Kirby has a mech. It literally looks exactly like like like
Gurren
What? Oh, no, no, look on. Sorry. It looks exactly like we're gone the big one or the head
Okay, um, what game are we talking about?
Kirby planet robo bot. That's what?
What? It came out like two like a year ago. I've never heard of it
I've not heard of Kirby planet robo. I swear to God. This is the first time and you're making it up. No, no
It looks awesome. Yeah, I mean it is awesome. It is awesome. Anyway
What the fuck are we talking about you? I don't know Kirby and just we went on a Kirby
The point is Kirby's awesome. Please come to the switch. I love you. Yeah, I can get behind that
What games do you want to see like we're over the presentation fucking it was good
Yeah, wait, is there with or any like? Oh, well, um Zelda, which I don't really oh my god
I forgot about Zelda. I have notes for that. I don't really play Zelda
But if I had a switch would I
Honestly, no because it's kind of like Skyrim. Yes
It kind of has the same reasons I wouldn't play it as I wouldn't play a game like Skyrim
Even I don't the cutscenes looked really cool like the art style looks great
Um, I don't know. Yeah, it looks it looks neat. Uh, my note says hark zelda. It has locations
It has uh goblins and uh, yes, and there was a man with a shark for a head. Yes
Uh as someone who hates zelda that trailer looks fucking sick and I kind of want to play. Yeah
It did look pretty cool. Yeah, I don't I don't know if I would actually do it unless I'm less like multiple people
Independently told me like then you have to play the new zelda. It would surprise you in ways you cannot imagine
And then I'd be like, well
Fuck you. Fuck maybe maybe I guess we can't move my cold bitter heart
No, only only under
Oh man, kid. Did you did you see all the sweet undertails? They're releasing on another nintendo switch
There's zelda undertale curbie undertale mario undertale pokmon undertale pokemon undertale platoon undertale
And finally earthbound
Not never the best under tail never never in the world
Never what what if they release a new earthbound game?
Um, it will be shit because he toy has specifically stated
He does not want to do another earthbound and in fact they would give another guy and that new guy would be awful
Yeah, okay. I didn't think about that. That's too bad. All right, never mind then our earthbound doesn't need to be made again
They just need to release mother three
Wait, they already released mother three
No, is it only like fan translated? Yeah, what? Yeah, what they still haven't released mother three. No
Not even like the virtual console. No, what the fuck? Yeah, why?
Why just like like a year and a half ago they released the first mother
And not mother three. Yeah, and the thing about mother one is that it had been fully translated
Officially by nintendo
Since it since it was made like in 1998 or 1989 or something. So like it had already been released
Yeah previously and they re-released it. Yeah, they didn't release mother three
Well, like it like basically the idea like it was fully translated and then they just would put it up on a shelf somewhere
And they're like, oh, we'll release that someday
Oh, and they just finally got around to it. Yeah. Yeah
ridiculous
How fucking long does it take to translate a game from japanese?
Well, I don't think very long since the fan translation did it in like a year. Yeah. Yeah, this is nintendo
But this is nintendo we're talking about that can't be fucking bothered to model walk cycles for i don't know
20 pokemon. Yeah 30 pokemon. Yeah, you know
Ridiculous, uh off criminal literally criminal. Yeah, I the police are en route to japan
I've called interpol
They're going to arrest arrest uh miyamoto and the and the ghost of satori wewata. They're gonna send ghost busters over there
And sakura con
So send them to sakura con to stop all the video games
The source of all evil sakura con
I mean, there's got to be some mastermind behind it
Uh, you know how like in fiction like industry is often portrayed as like this big like uh
Cloud of black smoke with like giant pipes like lean out the smoke and like there's a bunch of work is being whipped
That's what I meant to sakura con is
It's not even it's just
It's not even related in a fiction anyway
But still but still
I think all these shit games somebody's making them
It has to be that
Who else could be so evil
As as as john sakura con the ceo sakura con
As he famously said I will I will poison video games
No, none of that. I will continue to make video games. I will continue to make video games. He said twirling
And gnashing his teeth his filed down
It is most who is the most heinous prediction video games will get more realistic
And real life will become more like
Until you can't fucking tell what's happening
um
Then until the switch coming out in two months
Do you have any other games that you'd like to see on the switch? Uh, yes. Let me think I
I I'm very interested in a new shadow pokemon game. Did you play it? Oh my gala of darkness?
I have not played any of those. Okay. First of all
They're great games in and of themselves, but you specifically would fucking adore those games. You think so?
First of all, they're super fucking edgy. They seem like edgy
Versions. Yeah. Okay. Do they do they have like pokemon battles and like actual normal? Yeah. Yes
Then why don't then why aren't then why don't?
Okay, what separates a shadow game from a mainline game? Okay, uh, it's much more like an rpg
This is that there aren't like gyms like it's it's a it's a much more involving story
Like like you use pokemon and like there is a story about pokemon
There is there is I have never even considered playing one. Yeah, but
Okay, maybe I was wrong. Okay, uh like like uh in pokemon. There is no story
And if there is a story, it's bad besides seven minutes and then there's a good story. Yeah, uh,
But xD gala of darkness has like an interesting plot
Like and it it basically has a narrative which is something that pokemon games lack completely
But is it is it missing any of the things that make a mainline pokemon game? Um,
It is missing extraneous details such as like gyms
fine
Yes, uh
Like there is no like root system
Like like the the way battle's working that is
Well, like like if the story needs you to go to a town your character will get on a spike and he will go to that town
And then you will like like the towns are fucking huge and there's a ton of shit to do in each town
Uh, and you can battle people in that town and you have to take down like in the evil corporation
Do you catch pokemon?
Uh, you can catch pokemon like you can catch normal wild pokemon. Yeah, however
Uh, it it's not like you don't walk in it. It's
fairly convoluted at least compared to walking into all grass
You you have to there there are specific. I think they're called poke. I think they're actually called poke spots
Poke stops poke spots. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, okay
And you have to get like I think it's like cheese or something and lay them out for the pokemon
Really and then like come back 20 minutes later, and they'll be like a wild like aggro on there
What? Yes
Okay, but that's not how you get pokemon the game the point of the game. How do you get pokemon?
Oh, you don't even know that. I don't know anything. It's it's okay. Okay. It's fucking sick. You're gonna love this
Okay, all right at the beginning at the beginning of xc gale of darkness. I know like this like that's on the game
Yeah, yeah, and so it's called him. Colosseum is the first game in series. Wait, colosseum is a shadow game
Yeah, does it have like a plot? Yeah, it like what? Yes. I thought it was just like a battler. No
Oh
Uh, but pretty much colosseum is like a like like a like colosseum
Like xc gale of darkness is an erect sequel like it has the same town, but it's like the same plot weird. Yeah
Does it have its own region?
No, well regions isn't it? It's oh, I mean, I don't know. I mean like like both of the games have their own
Like yeah, yeah, but but the both take the same thing. I get it. What what land are they in the or region?
Or are re yeah, okay
Uh, it's fucking cool
You catch hope like them your main method of catching pokemon is at the beginning of xc gale of darkness
You're given a snag machine
And you this is like like an arm like grip like like fucking like like dog
Like like dr. Claw like arm. Okay
And they're at the game. They're like like this this team called human. It's like team cypher. I'm pretty sure
Uh, just has made a bunch of shadow pokemon because shadow pokemon are just like the evil versions of ragan
Well, not even evil. They're more like like they like they injected depression and fucking crazy shit into pokemon
And now pokemon are just fucking
Flailing around and they're just they just can't even function like monsters. Yeah, they're monsters and they're in pain
Constantly, yeah, holy shit
And like like whenever like like I can't even like describe how cool is when you see a shadow pokemon
Because like someone throws out a pokemon
And then you get to see like the little animation play and he's like wait, oh man
I really want to have that book like that one looks pretty cool
And then like like like like I came like I'm gonna do like a visual joke for this like you're okay
Like like he throws out the pokemon like someone throws out pokemon and then your kid reaches this
Like a shock. Yeah. Yeah. He's like what?
And then like like his glasses like like lights up
He's like robot glasses and they light up and like fucking like like like shadow fire bursts out of the pokemon
Like it like it's fucking exploding my eyes are wide with with passion and terror and and and it says a
Shia like like that pokemon is a shadow pokemon in all caps
And and you know what you fucking do? What do you do? This is a trainer battle
Yeah, you whittle that pokemon down and you snag that trainers pokemon with your like mecca arms
And and and for every pokeball and like it has ultra balls and stuff
But the thing that makes this different is that whenever you throw it like and you know when the pokemon
Little when the pokeball opens. Yeah, a hand comes out and it grabs the pokemon
And it drags it fucking in and you know what you do with that shadow pokemon
Shadow pokemon like like are fucking like shit the shadow pokemon like our shit
They have their own like type and shit. Okay, and they only use like shadow moves
Yeah, and you you have you have to you have to get it to a high friendship
And then you go to like this like this like like
mossy cobble area in the second town
And it's like you have to do like a fucking like like up up here like jesus like baptism with your pokemon
Did like purify them? Yeah. Yeah, you purify you like like it's something like
Like your bedouf opens his heart to you
Yes, exactly. I know my shadow bedouf. Yes, exactly. That's exactly what it's fucking like
Oh, wow, and and you are now best friends with your bedouf
And by the way for I know I know bedouf is june 4. I just I just came to mind first
I don't know why I I just I assume that the shadow that like the shadow pokemon games were like
Like the pokemon card game video game. No
No, not at all. Huh, they are just normal pokemon badminton
And like you catch with balls and stuff. Yeah
Can you nuzlocke one? Yes, you can oh my god
I mean you would have to like change the nunchuck rules because like
It seems like catching is limited or like yes different or yes, like happens at set story points or something. Yeah, well
Yes, uh, so you would either have to make it so like you just keep the same nunchuck rules
Like you can you can only just catch the first book money see in each town. Yeah
Uh, or you can keep it so you can only catch wild like like legitimate wild pokemon
Or it's just you catch whatever you want or like is random each time you have to look it up
But it is feasibly to be my nuzlocke and the nuzlocke's of that game are very intense due to like like
Like he's shadow pokemon are hard to catch first of all and also the game is just like
Like shadow pokemon you have to really fucking grind it out with them and make sure they love you
Like you you form like a way deep bomb
Because because you you have to make sure every pokemon loves you or you can't open up their heart
So but you can use them as their shadow. Yes. Yes
Wow. Yeah. Well, um
All right
I didn't know any of this and now I hope that one does come out in the switch and maybe I'll play
Uh a character who is literally you is named mirror b
and he is
A very tall man very skinny who has a disco outfit and a giant afro that looks like a pokeball
And I've seen him. He has a team of six pokemon. All of them are ludicola
And and and all they want to do is dance
Why don't people talk about these games more because people are
Literally stupid
But do you know how many times I've heard like there's never been a real pokemon game on a console on a home home home console before
I'm gay people people just are just like don't view them as legit because they're like not handheld or whatever
Yeah, they're not handheld and dude. There's no like gyms dude. Like seriously. There's no gyms in alola. What what yeah? Yeah
Yeah, what now I I swear they are literally just like pokemon games. There's pokemon marty
You have to stop an evil organization. Like it's just a fucking pokemon game. Okay. I'm interested
But in 3d and awesome and sold man. I'm sold now the characters design in that game the character designs are also fucking
crazy
And it has so much pathos. It is the most autistic game. You know, I love pathos. That's my favorite thing in art
The the midget you fight at the end is is the best person
Um and you have to play
I think I should probably play gale of darkness. It's uh
I I mean, okay. Both of them are great
Colosseum is very fun
And like you'll you'll get all the backstory of because it like it is actually pretty integral to xc gale of darkness
Like story wise. Yeah, but gale of darkness is a sequel. Yes. Yeah
But but I would say xc gale of darkness is the much funner game and much much
So shadow march lights. No, you can't catch unfortunately. You have no idea how much I cry when I found out you couldn't catch much likes
I thought you said he was in that game
He's just looking at pc
Uh, what what happens is, uh, like sometimes when you put down cheese and the focus box
Catch them with cheese. Yeah, and and and when like sometimes they'll come back and much likes will be there
And he'll have eaten like like normally you have like like like like a full like block of cheese slash 20 per hours
Yeah, yeah, but they'll just have just eaten. Yeah. Yeah. Is he like tubs in neko at suma? Yeah. Yeah, basically
Yeah
And and then his his his trainer this like like really sweet old woman will come be like you mother fucker
You bitch what to the to the munchlax. Yeah, like come back here. I'm sorry for this. I'll give you a revival of her or whatever
Um, I'm a max revive just for you does for me Ben
um
Great game for the nintendo switch neko at suma
Yeah, definitely come out on the nintendo switch. I mean they are doing like iphone shit now. So
Yeah, why not? Um
The way they should make a pokemon runner game
You know what why not actually? Yeah. Yeah, you play different pokemon. You have different moves
Pokemon is able to be like the most diverse cast
The most diverse like asset of games ever any fucking game at all. Yeah with a different pokemon as the protagonist
Yeah, yep. Yeah. Yeah pokemon flights him ride your charizard around that would legitimately be awesome
Yeah, why not? Yeah, just fucking get your fucking mega latios and power up its fucking hyper plane engines and just
Uh, a pokemon mystery dungeon games would come out on this bush. It'd be fucking cool
I don't know another side pokemon franchise that i've kind of been meaning to get into
Okay, see the thing is
Everything I have consoles though, right? They're on handheld. Yeah, everything that I hear like like, okay
I was which is a handheld. So whatever. It's all it's all out the window
Uh, I I played all of the all of the games up to sky and then after after sky
Uh, I I haven't played any of the games and everything I've heard about them
Make it seem like they are the worst video games ever produced by men. Why what's what's what changes after sky?
The pokemon mystery dungeons. Yeah. Yeah, they they become so fucking like like sterile and with no personality
And there's almost no like actual like like autism
I god, no
The the I I I'm serious pokemon was born out of autism. Yeah, literally born out of autism
I feel like like the main selling point of explorers of sky
Is just how autistic can be with it and I love it so dearly
I I mean it is literally a self insert fan fiction. Yeah done extremely well
Uh, the like you like no matter even if you are ebony's or fucking screws age
Asian ebony's or screws. Yeah
You will form such a long lasting bond with both your partner pokemon and the people in your explorers guild
You likely has a point in this game where we're like where our tensions become
Uh high intolerably intolerably high just like race mix in the united states america. Mm-hmm
Which is also another huge problem. Yeah, um, uh that you will be heartbroken
Um, this this is how every day ends in that game. Once you get acquainted with the guild. Did you say dates?
No, I I well there are dates. Oh every day like it's count. Okay. Okay. Okay, uh
Uh, you will come home from like like like a like a fucking uh, uh
A a taxing day out on the job exploring and helping people. Yeah, you will come home and this exact same cutscene will play every time
Well, well, sometimes there'll be exceptions for the story. Yeah, but it will be like louder
It'll come out and he'll be like hey, he's back our best friends back
All right, let's have dinner together and then there's like a dinner cutscene where you're all you get the same
All your friends. Yeah. Yeah, all your friends are with you. Yeah
And and it's like much much much choo choo choo choo. Wow. I'm so glad I get to be friends with you. Today was a great day. Oh my god
And then you're you and your partner pokemon are sleeping like like like like like like head to toe and you're like
And the partner's like ever since I met you my life hasn't been the same
I'm so glad I met you on the beach that day
I I now have a purpose in my life and I love and I love you dearly chimcharr
Oh my god
And then he'll be like good night. I love you and he'll like kiss it
He'll kiss his treasure and and he'll go to sleep. I don't know how much of this you're making though
I'm not making a fucking any of it. That's why it's the best game ever made
Thanks for listening to the pokemon mystery dungeon podcast for the rowdy fuckers cop killies folks
I really no I really want to play them. Yeah, uh
Red and blue are like red and blue mystery dungeon. Yeah, are also very good. Uh
I I thought that was that was sky. You were just talking. Yeah, it's uh sky is by far the best one, but uh, it okay
Play blue and play sky. Those are those are the best ones of each one
The reason my blue is better than red is because for some weird reason
Red came out on the gameplay advanced and blue was on the ds. Yeah, I don't know why
Coverage coverage. Yeah coverage. Um
Blue just feels better to play and uh blue is like
Like it has just like like it has the same amount of pay posts I feel
But I feel like I wasn't as connected to the characters in that game. Which one did you play first?
I I played sky first
So you think do you think I should play sky first or blue first? Um
Probably blue. I mean
I honestly like like no knowing your busy schedule. You should probably pick one right this guy. Yeah. Yeah, maybe yeah
But but if you have all the time in the world label because like they are different plots
Yeah, uh, and they're they're both worth it. Uh, did you know, you know primal ground on primal chiroger in gen 6 and alpha ruby and alpha saffa
Yeah, I'm familiar with them
We hang out. Yeah, we have we have coffee twice a month. Uh
Uh primal dialga was in explorers of sky. He's he's the main bad guy
That's not even that's not a thing in like the regular games. No. No, it's not. No primal dialga and he's fucking sick
He's a delicate different gen primal like can't wait. Is there is there primal polkia? No
Wait, why wouldn't it be primal ray quasi? Wait, there's already a mega ray quasi. This is confusing
Why wouldn't sky be ray quasi be the main guy?
Well, first of all because it came out in gen 4 and they wanted to push, you know, the new guys
Uh
Well, and it was just carried over from the past
Okay, uh
And sky is like a different story from
Time and space, right? Uh, like it's it's time and darkness
And it's basically the same thing but like like there's different instances in time and space and they're just they're they're both
In they're they're both similar. Yeah, the sky is different. Yeah sky sky is
It's it's different subtle ways. It's pretty much just the ultimate experience
Okay, is it like the heart gold soul silver version? Yeah. Yeah, yeah, exactly. Okay, uh, they gave it they gave it the remake treatment
that game
Like like literally
There's there's so many subplots with different pokemon in sky. It's pretty much unfucking believable
There's a whole backstory about how you became a pokemon. Yeah, and it evolves
Uh, a a guard of not a guard of war a uh a grow vile and this a motherfucking
George Costanza like like I I hate him so fucking much
The the scum of the earth dust nor that you will come to believe is literally satan
Good, you know, when I'm on when I'm on bulbapedia, right and I'm looking at pokemon entries
Like I'll be scrolling down and looking at all the various
Data and shit and I'll see like I'll see some bits and pieces like from mystery dungeon
and there will be like
And sometimes like I'll scroll past the little thing and be like, oh, yeah, um, um, um
Simon Simon the yeah, I'm on the page for for bulbasaur like. Oh, yeah, simon the bulbasaur
Yeah, he always dreamed of becoming a gourmet chef. Yeah
And I'm like what
It's fucking awesome that the game is a much better like rpg than any other pokemon game
Yeah, because like does house people have personality and they change their opinion
Yeah, basically like like the entire hub world is just like the town and your ventures guild and they change so much
Like like like each level is a randomly generated thing where like you you just have to help like people
I mean there is like story relevance to the townspeople. Yeah, but the main like meat and bones of the pathos come from the townspeople
Oh, not the pokemon. Oh, wait the townspeople are
Uh, like like like the best thing about it is not everyone has the same opinion to every situation
Which is like basically like like that is how characters are written
But everyone's stupid and no one knows how to write characters and most of the time in shows
characters just agree to do things
Like like like there's a very little conflict
But in book of mystery dungeon, they're like they're like real
They're real people they're more real than most of the people I know
Even though they're fictional pokemon
It sounds great, dude. There's there's there's so there's so much
I think like I've been I've been thinking it over for a long time. I think I have no choice
Yeah to check out the mystery dungeon series
Maybe I'll maybe I'll like play blue and just kind of like blast through it
Just kind of like to get my foot wet feet feet wet and put in the door blue is pretty fucking cool
I won't lie. It is cool
There's a one point where you're you're like running away from home and you have to you have to like like like like
Like you you you have to like face mole trace for whatever reason I forget
Yeah, and your partner turns you and says well, it's been good. We're gonna fucking die, bro
Like it's over like we've been away from home for so long. We don't have any food
We're gonna die to fucking mole trace. Yeah, the thing that's really missing in pokemon is like the real
The real sense of scale of the pokemon because like
Yeah, like they have different stats and like the characters talk about some and some are more story relevant
But really each every pokemon is very comparable to one another in like how big and and important they feel
Like in battle each one is just like one chess piece on your fucking chess board
whereas like
Yeah in in in the in like a real pokemon situation such as the ones that I experience every night in my dream
um
If a fucking moltres showed up like you're fucking I imagine like your entire town would just be raised to the ground
Um, you know if he was it was a bad day for him
I remember there's like one screenshot like like that
I always like point to like like to show how edgy those games are and it's of like like an adorable Pikachu and a squirrel
and like there's like little sprites on the on the on the overworld and there's like a giant mole trace
And there's just dialogue box and there's just squirtle looking at you and he's just saying we are going to die
Beautiful
Like like we are like there's no fucking hope just just goodbye. I'm sorry. I'm so I'm sold man
I'm sold play play both of those like like every pokemon game is the best game I've ever made
Agreed. Yes. Wait. Is there any pokemon that isn't the best game I've ever made? Um, there was like that one like weird like
fire and bloom pokemon game
pokemon conquest
Oh, well, that well, that's okay first. That's not just pokemon. It's like a crossover. Yeah, I saw that
I thought it looked really cool
Although I didn't care about like whatever it was crossing over
But I thought that like a fire a fire emblem style game with wait, that's kind of what mystery dungeon is isn't it?
A little okay. It's not all right. Well, I thought it was a cool idea
to for use with pokemon
I thought it's weird that it's like mixing with all these japanese
Yeah, I don't know anything about it. It does look pretty cool, but I don't I I don't even know anything about it's game
And anyway, they fucking ripped off nuzlocke conquest. Yeah, my famous youtube series on the youtube internet
Uh, truly unfortunate. Yeah, truly truly unfortunate
Um, there's like when will I get my due?
for that
For my contributions, uh, I'm trying to think there's pokemon puzzle league. I don't think that was very good
I have no idea what that is like that one like anime spinoff game for the fucking uh
in the 64 is it like
It's just tetris. I was gonna say is it like uh, dr. Robotnik's mean bean machine. Yeah, whatever
It barely counts. Uh snap was the best game ever made. Yeah snaps cool snaps neat
They should make another snap on the fucking switch
Uh, yeah, the the creator of snap said this is the worst inferior thing I've ever seen
Well, like they're like phones. They're like cameras in your phones now, so it's not like special big pictures of pokemon
Oh
There aren't pokemon in real life you fucking hack. What an idiot. What is it? Oh my god
Wait, there's there's there's cameras in your phone. So
I can't even remember
So it's not special to take pictures of pokemon because everyone's doing I mean, I guess they're playing pokemon go
To the polls and I'm taking pictures of their pokemon. Sure. It sucks
It's not it's like
The no, I never really played I never really played snap except for like a little bit one time
Snap is very fun. It's neat. I like it. Snap is the funnest if you don't know how to play
Yeah, maybe you don't know how to like optimize. Yeah. Yeah a lot so many games
Yeah, because then often then we'll do something quick in the first level
I remember the first time I saw lapras like out in the ocean. I was like
This is the most complex game I've ever made
This is as deep as video games can go wait. Why because it was like too far away and you had to like figure out how to get it
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah
Like like there is no deeper video game than pokemon snap. That is legitimately what I thought
Uh and trying to wake up that snorlax
And you have to replay every level you don't have to but like you go back
Yeah, and and to like snap them all pictures and snap snap. Yeah
Yeah, this is yeah pokemon is could be every fucking genre of every game all the time every made
Because it has the most diverse cast of characters ever created. Yes. Yes. And that's and that's it. What else can you even say?
Nothing, uh, what other video games franchise is you want to see in the switch? Oh, man
you um
Undertale
What are you telling me from play well on the switch? It would just play like any other game. Yeah, yeah be a jrpg
You know, yeah, yeah undertale under house. Definitely. So what definitely undertale needs to come to the switch so that a new generation can experience it
Yes
You're ripping up homestuck toby stop toby stop toby stop
Um, yeah, he did rip off homestuck with his own
His own composition
Maybe he ripped off undertale before it even existed. Yeah, you know what that fucking hack
Someone's ripping off something and it's both and both. Some ones are toby. Yeah, and there's never been a greater
Undertale uh ripoff than lisa. No, no no release a year earlier
But clearly he clearly clearly austin jorgensen got jorgensen
I don't he got into toby fox's like file notes and just like just like stuffed his pocket
And then bolted out
Well, he didn't bolt he did he like took out his samurai sword and like sliced the window pane in half
And then did like a kung fu ninja kick out of it because he's a fucking incredible superhuman god
And um unlike toby who was a ninja and then ninja ran all the way across the united states to california
Where I think he lives i'm probably wrong about that
But the name like that probably lives in fucking hell
Um, who's just california? Yeah, he's america. He's an american boy. He's a good american boy
As all he's an all he's an all american ninja. Yeah, the leader of the alt right
He would be he sounds like he could be the leader of the alt right, but no, he's a good boy and a sweet boy. Yeah, um, let's see
I I I want like fucking I want smash to be re-released, but good this time
Which which will not happen have they?
Oh, because like instead of all slow and stuff. Yeah. Yeah, um, yeah
They haven't said anything about a new smash. Have they they said that it is happening, but we don't know anything about it
I mean, it feels like smash 4 just came out
You'd say that but it came out three years ago
That's pretty short for a re-release of smash. I guess but yeah, I mean they could they could do it. Yeah
God, it came out three years ago. Yeah, Jesus
Fucking video games
Video games and life just don't like progress
The same timeline like the two happen completely separate from one another and like and like a week goes by and you look at video games
And like a century has gone by or vice versa or whatever
Like years later you look at you look at games and like they've just announced announced like the new generation of pokemon
Has like 50 new pokemon and that's all that they've done. Yeah
Ah
Our friend tom tom Oliver said the other day that he didn't want like there to be new pokemon in new pokemon games
That was very infuriating. It was the worst thing i've ever heard before in my life. He seemed
Well
First of all, I didn't understand at all like he okay
He seemed to be saying that other things were more important than new pokemon. First of all, no
Second of all, even if that were true, it doesn't mean that they couldn't make new pokemon
Like yeah, again, he was coming from it like there are more important things
They should focus on other things, but like they're fucking nintendo
They can do everything and once and once but always always in a state of rage about all the things that aren't being done
By nintendo the literal god of mankind. Yes
unironically our creator
Is
I'm gonna kill that nintendo. I'm gonna get him. I'm fucking calling up. I'm calling the intergalactic intergalactic space squad
To attend they're going to kill all of japan because it's too hard to distinguish them from another
I need to kill japan. I have to kill. I I have to kill japan before fully cooly 2 comes out
Maybe if I can if I can stop the monster that is nintendo at the same in one fell swoop
That'll be just dandy as well
If they do do a port of smash bros
First of all
It fuck dude
Second of all, which is like they really smash four on the switch. Yeah, I could see it like like like they're doing that with marikari
Is we gotta call marikari the ones. Yeah, okay. Yeah, I could see them doing
But they would have to get rid of monster hero sakurai
Be a sakurai is like 10 times worse than Miyamoto in the sense that he ruins game game series
How so?
Well, Miyamoto destroyed paper mario, but so sakurai I get feeling he literally unironically hates video games
Miyamoto definitely loves video games. Yeah, I don't think anyone
He's a coup. Even though his love is is his love is
Evil. Yes. His love is sick. Yeah. He has the mightest touch
The mightest touch like
That's a weird metaphor because like yeah, it turns it to gold, but also ruins it completely. Yeah, yeah, exactly
Yeah, I don't know. I honestly didn't mind like new like super paper mario
Still no no one claims that super paper mario super mario was awesome. Oh, well, what do you mean by he ruined it then?
There have been two games that come out for mario after woods like what?
Sick of star and fucking paint splash
Oh
Right. Yes. I don't think about those. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. I forgot. I forgot. Yeah. I forgot those were paper marios
Yeah, they fucking aren't. Yeah, I don't know. I don't mind. I don't mind things like woolly world and epic yarn and sticker star
I don't mind them
but when like beautiful franchises like paper mario and kirby get
Like bastardized and those become what they are
Benefit well, okay
This meme has been perpetrated by you and your brother ben that epic yarn is not an amazing game
Is honestly disgusting in my hate. I never played it. I played like a little bit of it
I don't know. Okay. First of all, it's a it's a spin-off game. That is literally a one-off
But it's been like there haven't been another that's there hasn't been another main kirby game
since then
Right? Am I wrong? Are you in your own fucking universe?
Yes
Return to dreamland planet robo bot fucking triple deluxe
There's there's there's been more that I can't even fucking recount. There's been so many other games as well
Fucking rainbow curse, but have they resembled the kirby of my you? Yes. All of them have I don't know
Listen munchie. I don't know anything about video
All right, I don't I don't I don't research anything before I say it and I'm proud of that
I'm proud to spread misinformation and to base my and to base my my opinions and my beliefs solely on hearsay
and and complete and complete just invention just
internal invention of events
A totally self-constructive narrative that there's no relation at all to reality
And this is what you have to know about me. There has been not there's not been a game even similar to epic yarn in any conceivable way
In the kirby series since that day. Okay. All right. You know what? I don't mind epic yarn
My perception was that kirby was was like not doing
Powers and shit anymore. No, but I guess I'm wrong
Not at all
In every fucking way
Uh, we talked about this earlier and I said I want there to be more kirby games that are about the powers
And you didn't correct me that see I
I didn't think that was weird
But I thought you meant like really bring like the powers themselves to the forefront like in kirby 64
I do want that. I I do want that more
Yeah, I mean, I guess that is still fucking wrong
Okay, okay. Okay. Well. All right. So these new kirby games that I've never heard of and I have no idea
Do they I mean, do they have like what which which kirby games that I would know do they resemble?
But I like superstars or superstars
Superstar, okay. Yeah, are they like are they like that? Uh, they play exactly like that. Uh, do they have new powers?
Yes, well, okay, never mind then kirby's doing just fine. Yes. Kirby's doing exactly what I want
New powers and they've upgraded the old powers and there's so much more shit to do and
You're you you just have no no basis in reality. What's so I've I've been misled for years
And and it's a I'm in a cage of my own ignorance my own self-exposing
Kirby's never gone came in like 2010, right? Yeah, I know it's pretty old by now. Yeah, but it's okay
What what can I say? It's like it's like the last it's like the last kirby game that I heard like major press coverage about
That's that's the only thing I can say in my defense
I mean
You do live in a trash can bin so that is easily you would not hear the news about these current video games
Look, I'm too busy scavenging for sustenance to pay attention to video game journalism
Well, I'm looking right now on my fucking phone. I'm getting all the kirby games released since kirby's epic yarn. Look, okay
Let me just I'm just admitting that you're completely right and I've been completely wrong this whole time
I I know but from my own sick interest
I I want to I want to destroy you even more like the last the last time I formed an opinion was when
Kirby's epic yarn was the newest kirby game and I was like man
I wish kirby would go back to its roots and then I never thought about it again
Okay, kirby mass attack kirby's return to dreamland kirby triple deluxe kirby and the rainbow kerb
Kirby planet robobot all of those have been completely in the fucking style of of super star besides um
What's it called mess attack? What console are they on?
They're on all of them such as the ds the we the we use 3ds. Maybe I'll get the one which ones through 3ds
There too. There's triple deluxe and there is planet robobot. Maybe I'll get one. I love Kirby. Uh, Kirby's the best game in
Yeah, it's pretty good. It's pretty good. Um
Uh, fuck you
What
I'm the worst. You know what would be would be a really like like a really funny joke by nintendo. What's that if they released?
um
Say a star fox game or a metroid game or a f0 game or a donkey kong game or a yoshi game
Go on
Um, you know how like those guys are like the original aid smash bros and like they were kind of like like a big deal
Yeah, you know they used to have like game produced for them. Yeah. Oh, you're saying they don't yeah
Okay, okay. Maybe this yeah, this is part of I guess I just assumed Kirby was part of that trend of like beloved franchises
That don't get games anymore. Yeah. No, I guess that because yeah, like other games are like that
I mean, they are making dk games, but like
Very slowly. Yeah, like well, I I don't think
They did make a dk platformer like just yeah, yeah, uh by just recently if you meet in 2012 then yes
No, no, there was one that was like you played it with like a drum
But that one was that was in like 2005 then what no
That's bullshit. It was on the fucking game queue
That's not true. That that is what it is. That's the most recent dk game. I can even remember
No, no, I know that wait, there was a plat. There was a dk platformer in 2012. Yes
I don't own a nintendo console. I don't play video games
What have I been talking about?
What have I even been talking about? I only I only care about pokemon. Yeah, the only gaming news I pay attention to is pokemon
It's it's sad, but it's true
Yeah, but but uh star fox got a game like a year ago. I think oh, yeah, and it was terrible
Uh, it was literally star fox 64 again in hd. But wasn't it didn't have like awful controls? I hear that
Yeah, I yeah, I do I know about that one
um, so
What what's funny is after star fox 64 people always claim that star fox has just been shit after that point
However star fox, I think it's command. It's either commander
The the one where you're the one where it's a star fox game again
That's fucking awesome. Uh, when was that? Uh, it was in 2000 and in like six. I think okay
Um around like early. So it just is another star fox in the vein of the original. Yes. Yeah
Nobody talks about it. Uh, they must all be suffering from my same delusion of like video games ended after I turned like 19
And then everything else has just kind of been spinning it's wheels
And I won't bother to learn otherwise. Yes
But it's like the exact same predicament with xd go of darkness like people are like complaining about it
But if you just play the video games in the series, then you would know
Why would I ever play a video game? I mean, it's like Nate was talking about kingdom hearts
He gave his kingdom hearts lecture and like I'd never fucking heard of like half of those kingdom hearts
But just because I don't own the consoles. I mean, I don't I don't have a we or we use so
Yeah, I didn't know about anything anything that came out of those. I only just recently got a 3ds
I had a ds before but I never played anything on it. Um, um,
Except pokemon
Okay, i'm a consumerist pig
Or i'm the i'm actually the opposite of that because I don't buy things except for the one thing that I buy that everyone else buys
Yes, yes, excellent. Yeah, uh, there has been a yoshi game recently new yoshi sound
I literally have only heard intense negatives about it
Why what's wrong with it?
Uh, I hear the the controls are unresponsive. It looks like she it sounds like completely
Uh, there's there's one song that's been reposted a lot that literally sounds like someone ripping ass over and over again
Okay, yes
um, and it I and they also just say it shreds old water and there's nothing there's nothing even on me
What game does it most resemble will yoshi's islands? Yes
People like that one. Uh, yes, but it doesn't have to he doesn't have to see martin. Yeah, he's a classic classic game
What i'm seeing i'm serious. I know but the new not related to anything we're saying classic game yoshi's island nine out of ten
But switched by nintendo
um
Yeah, if they make a new game that's not shit and if they make a new metro game that is that that is a metro game and not
Like like four swords
I don't know. I don't even place four swords, but like it's like a
It's multiplayer, right? Yeah multiplayer is all that done. Have you heard what metroid federation places?
I have heard that it I've heard people that don't like it
I don't know what it is and I and I know that metroid is in a state where they just don't make any new metroid games
And fans try to make games that are like metroid and they get shut down. Yes. Yeah
garbage
metroid is
They're they're too much for games. They're the prime game is just like an fps. And then they're they leave it on my plate
They're like essentially. Yeah. Yeah
uh
Federation force is a
A I'm pretty sure like over the top third person shooter co-op game featuring
NPCs for pbs games not NPCs as in nameable characters, but as
Generic soldier from from prime. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah all those beloved characters
That I've never heard of interacting with no metroids
characters
Is ridley there? He's the only metroid character I could name. I I don't think so. He's gotta be in there somewhere
Maybe somewhere in there
Uh, why do people hate federation force?
Uh, because it's nothing like any other metroid game. It looks and plays badly
Uh, I don't know if it plays badly, but it looks like a complete shit
And we've been starving for a new game for so long
And they they're like it literally seems like they had just slapped on metroid to another game
That's nothing to do with it. Is it coming out for the switch?
No, it's gonna have to
It was enough. It was announced a really long time ago. Oh, I don't know. I think honest to god
I think the backlash was so big that they just can't
I see
Uh, I don't it might be out that happens sometimes where I like that one game in war
It was like I heard a lot of game and what game and wario for the oh like game and watch but little wario
Uh, I I heard a lot of like like press about it. Yeah, and then like two months later. I was like, hey, wait
Game and worry. Let me look that up. It released like like a month ago. I heard fucking nothing about it. Yeah
Oh
That reminds me game that needs to come to the nintendo switch
No
My favorite game and munchies too
I hate overwatch. Uh overwatch is the worst video game ever made
I've never played it and I never will because I hate it
I hate how it looks like a pixar movie and I hate how it is focused tested to a mirror shine
And I hate that everyone loves it and if you and everyone that loves it is just uh, he's just been duped
You're just a corporate shill. You've been you've been tricked
You've been tricked into liking the game by the fact that they made it so you would like it
God damn it's not not only does it's aesthetic
Uh, it's aesthetic
Be awful. I also don't like I mean some of the character designs are kind of neat. I guess but the overall aesthetic is dumb and bland
Everything visual about overwatch is terrible. Not only that though the game itself. I think some of them would look cool in other games
like
Bastion
mercy
I think in a in a game that I think in another game
Mercy's like robo wings would be really sweet. Yeah, you know what maybe yeah, but but by and large everything visual better than
Yeah, uh
But the game the gameplay it has very highly
That's a highly controversial opinion that no one will agree with us on but we both feel it really strong
Yeah, it looks very that it looks stupid and we hate it
It does have graphical fidelity. Oh, it's got it's got graphical fidelity in space
It's like i'm right there with all my favorite characters such as a girl. Um, fast girl
There's like a robot dude robot dude and big big pig. Yeah, and big pig my favorite
Big hook guy big big fat guy. He's he's there with him
And I just hate I just hate how it was the subject of so much
controversy about nothing meeting up to its release and it all just propelled itself to just massive success
On the back of the fact that it was focused tested to be something that you the idiot consumer would buy because it looks like other things
You like yes
Not only that but the gameplay itself is so fucking like like dumb down and casual
I've never played it. Okay, and I never will but I believe I have played it
Extensively and and I have a somewhat high sr
Uh, which is like the record
If you compare every single individual like aspect about it to tf2
I know i'm gonna sound like an asshole for sandals, but tf2 is just so much better than it in every fucking way
In like like visual and gameplay. It's pre fucking boggling. Uh, I do like tf2
Although well, I liked it. See I stopped playing it before there were even hats
So like I don't even know what's going on with tf2. Uh, tf2 is a completely different situation in which I
I will have a listen buddy where I talk to myself about how much I hate tf2 and then I will also defend I will also defend tf2
Just to summarize the maps are fucking indecipherable and indecipherable that in tf2. No in in
Uh, and all of them boiled down choke points and all of all of the capture points and I'm objectives are very big
And this seems like a minute detail
But this allows the this is this allows timer stall
And and ask someone who plays pokebomb, then I'm sure you can come. Do you know what timer stall is?
um in overwatch not really I guess
Just running down the clock while your team is still in the lead
Uh, basically what you do is uh do the mechanics of how control points work
if one person is on a
a
A point and keep in mind in tf2 the points are like the size of maybe three people
Yeah, I don't watch they are the size of maybe 50 people. Mm-hmm. And uh
If just one person, uh, like like say you're on blue team and you're attacking red team, uh, red team is defending
Yeah, if you're on the final point of red and literally every single human on blue is on red's point if just one red
Uh, like let's say may the worst example
May has an ability where you can shoot up a an ice wall and that takes like 250 health to destroy that
Which is somewhat much you team has to focus on very
Very fast. Okay. Okay. It's going to take like at least like three seconds, which is a lot
So it sounds like what you're saying is that
That the the points are so large that like the defending team like it's just impossible to control the point
Enough to not get the fucking defending team to just be jumping on it and like fucking around and like it's unfairly favors the defender
Yes, yes, and and every it is a slow
Slug and and just go back to main because it angers me. So once the ice wall is down
She can like freeze yourself and ice and make her invincible, right? Yeah, and just capture and just keep the point for six fucking seconds
Yeah
Yeah, I see and then once she's done, I see. Yeah
That's that's fucking me
What that may literally says that
Oh
Oh, no
Uh, then then by that time her team has already
Respond and come back because there are like there are so little respond games
Like respond time
And if you have two
If you're defending
Uh, and and the blue team is at or yeah, yeah, the blue team is at the last point
You will have a response I can have like
Like 14 seconds. Mm-hmm. These those seconds really fucking matter in fps fps is are like like a millisecond millisecond games
Did they matter but over watched they're like six seconds at most
Which means that you death is so inconsequential in that game
You can just jump right back into the fray with basically like like no like scratches on it won't be that
It's off I can go on and on about how that game is so fucking poorly designed balanced
I've heard I've heard you talk at length about it. Yeah, and I just I just hate it entirely on principle
Yeah, like I don't have any actual arguments against it other than my feelings. Yeah, which are strong. Yeah, it should be considered valid by all
um, but yeah
Um, come to the switch, please. I love or watch my favorite game of 2015. Yeah, um, and it will be my favorite game of 2017
guaranteed
If you just rerelease it and just put just put even more unnecessary bullshit
I love it. Please put in uh, even more micro transactions and uh
just
Blizzard, please just come and fucking read me. It's just while I'm asleep. Just come and just and just destroy my ass
Pikmin
Pikmin, uh, I played Pikmin 2 Pikmin 2 is the best game ever made. I've never played a Pikmin. I
It's kind of a thing, right? It's kind of a thing they keep doing. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
It's all right
Um, Pikmin 2 is about money
Is it and and and greed like by the producers or in the game in the game? Okay
Uh
This is not like a hugely popular franchise. Oh, no
Uh, the first Pikmin is your your name and all maria crash land on the like a planet and there's like the command name
Like they help you but we load your ship and you go back to space
Uh in Pikmin 2 it picks up right as soon as you land on your home planet and and like the the the company you work for
Is like, uh while you were gone our company is is it got foreclosed and we're out we're bankrupt now
And you're like, oh fuck
that's not good
and then uh like like you like like
In Pikmin you like pick up trash
and and so like Pikmin uh all mar is like, oh, uh, also I think like like a bio cap and then
Nice, and I think that's literally the item they use as well
And then the like the ceo's like that's worth fucking five trillion dollars on this plane
Because he picked up a bottle cap on Pikmin world
Okay, and then and then he's like you have to go back to Pikmin world and mine it for all of its resources
In order to reclaim our company. I see and then you proceed to do that and it's awesome
Cool, you just destroy all the natural wildlife and just take all of the treasures from from the planet
Grace
That's pretty good. And you use the Pikmin to do so. It's it's it's incredible. This sounds this sounds radical. Hey, is there a new uh
Uh, what about animal crossing?
Uh, I'm shocked that they didn't reveal a new animal crossing. Actually, I don't know when the last animal crossing was 2013
Okay, they could do another one. Hey digi
We're talking about we're talking about Kirby extensive. Yeah
What
Give us one second. We'll be done in a second. All right. Yeah, we've been going for two hours
Animal crossing is coming. It'll it'll be there soon. Yeah, I'm sure I'm sure I'm surprised. I didn't see it
Yeah in the presentation. Uh, it is confirmed
There are some in the works
Uh, that isn't like a fucking Mario Party group like the last animal crossing
Uh, final thoughts on the Nintendo switch
Um and not overwatch or or or how you don't play video my final my final thoughts on the Nintendo switch
Is that I really need to check out pokemon mystery dungeon and possibly the shadow pokemon games? Yes. Um
High five. This has been the ratty fuggers cop killers. Oh, Nintendo switch edition new newly formed spice bros spicy bros
Okay, is that gonna be on your channel? Uh, yeah, uh, well, they'll be on the bill on me. Well, okay
Wherever it ends up. Well, we'll link to it. Yeah. Yeah in this episode we'll link to
Me and munchie and victor forming our spicy bro packs. Yes, that that is incredible and needs to be deeply embedded into your mind
I I want everyone to see I want everyone to see what happens and to
Not to I mean, they won't they won't be bros, but I wanted to inspire other people to become spicy bros
But they're all spicy bros indeed. Um, this has been munchie wear shiny hats
They're retard and this has been been saint the game
Uh signing off
Nintendo
Video games
Thanks for joining me munch. Yeah, uh, I'll never come back. Bye. Bye