Routy, Cop, Killers, Inn, Getting Over It, Bennett, Foddy, I don't know what this game is, I don't know what's happening right here.
Before this episode, I told Ben that I thought it was going to be some Zoey Quinn, Depression Quest, cinematic gameplay experience, where it's just like a text-based adventure, or some mood piece with millennial dialogue. This is like a streamer game, right? This is a fucking Twitch streamer meme game.
It's a thing about dealing with loss, or whatever. And it's a little bit that. And it's a little bit of a streamer game. It's an art piece. This game is an art piece.
You know, I'm just going to start at the beginning, because progress doesn't mean anything.
Oh, this is charming. I love this.
It's way charming.
You know what I love? You know how Tom's all about low-poly shit? I don't care about low-poly 3D models. I care about 3D models that are creepy and scary and uncanny about it. That's kind of the 3D art that I like.
That's kind of part of the point of this game. The theme of this game is... Well, actually, I know a little bit about the history. There's this other flash game called Sexy Hiking that is very similar in many ways to getting over it.
But it was made out of pre-made assets for other games that were stolen. And this game is also made out of mostly bought Unity assets.
But the narration of the game talks about how the game is trash, because it's built out of trash assets that were cobbled together from other things.
Well, it's a good thing I won't be paying attention to literally any of the dialogue or narration in this entire game. I will basically be tabbed out the entire time.
Hey, speaking of the first thing I'm going to be tabbing out over to, this is going to date the episode. I'm about to release the RFC Killers 11 meat channel live right now.
Like, there we go, it's done. Good. The meat channel, the one we did at Radcon.
Okay, what we did at Radcon was, like, originally we just wanted to do, like, Wii Sports Resort, because we had done Wii Sports.
And we didn't do it just because we didn't get our, like, we didn't have a webcam, like, you know, a camera recording us.
So we wanted to make right on our initial promise of having RFC Killers live.
The way it worked was that we didn't have time to do it, basically, because we were doing other shit.
And it came down, like, the last day, and we just decided to do, like, a Meme Maker, and then Wii Sports Resort.
So we released all of our good material on Meme Maker. And so Meme Maker is, like, this great, great episode, like, iconic, and will be remembered throughout the ages.
But this, but the fucking actual, like, what we wanted to do, Wii Sports Resort, was, like, absolute shit, and, like, all silence.
The game sucks, and we were bored.
Okay, so, Ben, a lot of stuff has happened since last RFC was recorded on, like, for YouTube.
And I think a good set of gray is for me to publish the announcement video for our Twitch stream service.
Yeah!
RFC Killers is not on Twitch, it's out of the video. Save changes right now.
There's a sense of truth in that lack of content.
Okay, well, fuck.
I haven't seen the announcement video, what is it?
It's, uh, back in, like, 2006 or whatever, Egoraptor made a video entitled,
Metal Gear Awesome is not on YouTube, where he talked about how all the uploads of Metal Gear Awesome on YouTube were illegitimate,
and you could only experience it the way it was meant to be seen on Newgrounds.com.
So basically what I've done is just take everything that he said, but rework it to be about Twitch and RFC's copulators.
And so I made an impassioned rant with many big words about how RFC is not on Twitch,
but then, uh, immediately in the description, I say, uh, we've actually folded, and it is on Twitch now.
And I, uh, I lean to it.
Uh, okay, so, so it's, you know, it's art, basically.
Yeah, like, all of RFC has got to be on the front, it's art.
It's through and through.
It has a deeper meaning, but you know, it has a high skill floor.
For engagement.
The RFC might be, like, the highest skill floor to any Let's Play series.
Like, I'm hard to, like, like, viewers.
If you can find a more, like, niche, fucking, like, clicky, like, unbelievably daunting to newcomers.
Like, like, can you imagine trying to watch RFC and not knowing what the PCP is?
Can you, can you imagine trying to parse what we've woven here?
Um, it would be, you know, you would, you would be lacking, you would be lacking in comprehension.
You know, once we're all, like, once being your, like, millionaires,
and the RFC is typically as a brand has exceeded our well of expectations.
We have t-shirts in our own amusement parks.
People will look back and be like, you know, my first, my first introduction to all these people
was, was the fucking get in and over with fucking Benjamin Freddy or whatever the fuck this game is.
So you know what? Preemptively, welcome.
Yes. Well, welcome to, welcome to the past.
Uh, it's now, now you got, now it's time to go on an extensive YouTube search
and find all the previous Rowdy fuckers content and then go over to the Twitch
and experience that, experience, uh, we're playing, um, over on Twitch,
we're not playing, um, Pokemon Gale of Darkness XD, lol.
Uh, which is way sick.
Yeah, oh, oh, I'm so glad you think so. I'm so glad.
We recorded, like, a test video for YouTube and it was super fucking gay
and, like, we thought the game was bad, but we were actually proven wrong
and that it's an fantastic game, that is perfect.
Also this, what you're doing right now is agonizing to watch Unfurl.
Yeah, yeah, that's kind of, that's kind of the point.
Okay.
I mean, I, I, okay, when we started recording, I was here
and then, like, I was testing the audio and I was just kind of flailing around
and I threw myself over that boulder, over on the left there
and I ended up back at the start screen.
This is, I think, okay, I haven't gotten to the end of this game
but so far this part is easily the hardest
and, like, I've done it many times but it's still, like, way difficult
and, like, not at all a guarantee that I can successfully do it.
I had to, I had to look up how to do this part
and I'm glad I did because I didn't realize that the lamps are grabbable
and grabbing the lamps is, like, the entire way of doing it.
Fuck.
Oh Christ.
Come on.
You know what this game reminds me of?
It is fucking, I think, I think it's Quap?
Is this the game I'm thinking of?
Actually, this is made by the guy who made it.
Bennett Foddy is the Quap guy.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Okay, well, perfect.
I'm a fucking genius. I didn't even know.
But this game has, like, themes and, you know, messages.
I'm, like, Quap, who has the theme of, like, like, mental retardation
not being in control of your own body
and flailing around your lips and floundering.
People have been predicting that games would soon be made out of prefabricated objects.
So, I'm up the devil's chimney and it's kind of,
it's kind of smooth sailing from here.
From here?
Okay, getting up the devil's chimney requires luck
and you sort of have to flail around
and just hope for the best to do it.
After that, after this,
like, the next obstacles are ones that you just kind of got to take slow
and they're not that bad.
Although you can still fuck them up and, like, throw yourself all the way back to the beginning.
Yeah, fuck.
Oh God.
God, don't let me fall back down the devil's chimney.
Okay, okay.
Let's go out, like, like, what we're doing on Twitch.
Like, not just the basic, like, where we're doing Pokemon XD.
But, but, but, I forget who thought of the idea first.
But, one of us came up with the idea of doing Street Fighter and Reciprocaliz.
Because it made sense because all of the Reciprocaliz are, like, super fucking long
and all, like, sort of meandering and, like, fluid,
not, like, structured, let's play content anyway.
And it made sense to make them do, like, be streamed.
But are they trash culture?
Yeah, it was your idea, and it was the best idea.
It's, like, when you said it, and when I saw, like, the Twitch channel
with all the art and stuff there, I was like,
this is kind of way more logical than YouTube.
Than YouTube videos.
So, we're testing out streaming.
We're still gonna do, like, YouTube videos.
We don't really have a schedule, Reciprocaliz.
The brand is to not have a schedule, basically.
But we're gonna test out streaming and see how much we like it.
And then we're gonna decide if we wanna do YouTube videos still,
or if we wanna do Twitch streams.
There's pros and cons to each side.
And as I keep saying, to remind us of our roots, as I am,
both the procrastinators and the Reciprocaliz Tribune of the plebs,
always looking out for the little guys.
The sheer ecstasy that fans get when they just log on to YouTube one day.
And just by chance, they've been blessed with the newer iFreq Skype Killers.
And just, like, they have not seen this be recorded.
They do not know any step of the way, like, like, what's been transpiring here.
All they know is that one day, instantaneously,
they just have, like, six hours of content, brand new, to their virginity.
The live stream, like, it's like, you announce it on Twitter that it's happening,
and then they get themselves up mentally.
And then they are, like, forced in a way to, like, watch it live.
And, like, it feels, even though the streams have been shorter than Reciprocaliz,
they feel like they've been longer.
Just by virtue of, like, the constant fan interaction.
It's like streaming on Twitch with, like, you know, notifications and stuff.
It feels like high fakes in a way, you know?
Like, you're in the thick of it right then.
And you have to be engaged.
Or there could be disastrous consequences.
You know what it is.
It's that when it's just recording a video, it's just me and you, and we're just talking.
But when we're streaming, there's, like, a silent third party who, like, is talking,
but only intact.
So, like, you just have to, like, like, every so often, you're just like reminded,
like, I have to be entertaining this person who's in, you know, who represents the chat.
Like, I have to be a good, funny person.
Whereas it's a normal Reciprocaliz.
It's just me and you, and we're just floundering constantly, and we don't mind.
Yeah, and we're not funny, and we don't entertain anyone.
Yeah, exactly.
I do, there's a lot of obvious good with a Twitch, though.
Like I said, it makes sense, the kind of content that we do.
And it's just nice.
No, no, oh god.
Oh god, you're so fucked, you're so fucked.
No, no, no.
I think I'm good.
I got a firm handhold, a firm hammerhold.
Yes!
You're, like, balancing this game.
Huh?
I guess it's because of the pot.
You can, like, fling yourself and, like, and, like, what's the word?
You can, like, bounce up and down.
You can, you can, like, you, like, can jam your hammer on the ground underneath you
and, like, pogo stick yourself.
Uh, uh, uh, uh.
Oh, you're, oh god.
Okay, this one.
This is a tense game.
I kind of forget what to do here.
Oh, Christ.
I don't know how I can play in the game, but I can just imagine how fucking agonizing it is.
Fuck.
Uh.
This is definitely, like, like a total, like, streamer, like, like, this is, like, I want to be the guy.
Yeah.
But, like, even more Twitch-ified, you know what I'm saying?
It's got the-
This is so easily, like, like, oh, I've reached new goal, fucking test one and donate now.
It's got the, um, it's got the, um, yeah, it's got that, like, super, like, frustrating,
like, screamer kind of appeal where someone can pretend to freak the fuck out for kids
and they'll have fun.
But it's also got that, like, goat simulator absurdity to it.
Yeah.
Um, how distasteful.
It is the perfect, it is the perfect, um, stream game.
So it's great that we're playing it on YouTube instead.
Yeah.
I-
It's just, we are kings of marketing.
We know more than anyone ever know.
I-
People think that we're making poor decisions, but we're just on a completely different level
than they even are aware of.
We're playing the long game.
We're playing chess and they're playing checkers.
I completely forget.
Oh, God.
Oh!
Oh, Christ.
I completely forget, um, how I did this before.
I have done it.
Do you want me to look up a walkthrough?
Um, oh, God.
Yeah, if you want to go and, like, look and-
Oh!
Ah, ah, ah!
This is real genuine fear.
This is not fake shit.
This is real.
That's, that's, that's why.
That's why it's the best game for this, for, for Twitch streamers like us, boy.
Because these are always fearful for your fucking life.
God.
I feel like I pogoed.
I feel like I have to pogo myself, but, like, I can't.
Oh, Christ.
Oh, fuck.
I, I just opened up a YouTube video and, like, the loudest sound I've ever heard in my entire life
was this guy going like, hey, what's up, YouTube?
And what was up, YouTube?
What was the answer you were seeing?
It was like, because I immediately muted it.
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, boy.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, I have made, I've made it past this part, like, maybe, like the part with the, the stairs up there.
I've made it past that maybe, like, three or three times or something.
Alright, I'm watching this guy.
This part sucks.
You're just standing fucking still, though.
Climbing this tower, I hate.
This is one of my least favorite.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
Okay.
Jesus fucking speed up guy.
Fucking, oh, God, this is always the case.
Oh, God.
This is always the case.
Oh, my God.
I could not have fucked that up more.
I could not have possibly fucked that up more than I did.
You just got raped just then, dude.
That was embarrassing.
Like, I, okay, I saw my hammer doing all the things that it shouldn't be doing, and I, you know, it's my responsibility.
Jesus Christ.
You know, that's really sick that, like, like, like that you can just fucking, like, eat shit and, like, go back all the way to the beginning.
Yeah.
That's sick in all the ways that the word sick could mean.
It's like, it's like grotesque that he would program something like that.
And it's also cool as hell.
Ah, fuck.
No, I don't think.
Well, maybe I can.
Oh, yes.
You're supposed to, like, you're supposed to, like, pogo stick yourself into the stairs and then wildly, like, I don't know, like, like, like, flail your hammer back and forth up, like, against the wall and the stairs to, like, get yourself height in a way.
Um, sounds difficult.
Sounds chancey.
Chancey?
Yeah, it's super, super chancey and it's super fucking looks retarded.
That's what you have to do.
I mean, this part is chancey, but there's, like, nothing, there's nothing at stake.
This part just feels like flailing.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Oh, oh, hey, hey.
Yeah.
So, the first comment on the new reference cop killers 11, MeChannel Live, by HappyD, ah yes, good old YouTube, much better than Twitch.
Great.
Okay.
Alright.
HappyD has spoken.
Yeah, we know HappyD's a pain on the subject.
I don't know.
I mean, well, we don't have to do just one or the other, right?
Yeah, we don't.
We've both got big minutes.
We could do like a monthly, we could do like a monthly stream and like a monthly video, I guess.
I, oh god.
I mean, I think we should, ah.
We should definitely stream all of XD, like for sure.
Yeah, that's what I was going to say.
We should finish that at least.
Ah, balls.
Another thing I like about streaming is that it allows us to like do like long four games because the reference cop killers like structure on YouTube videos really incentivizes us to just do exclusively one shots.
Yeah.
Oh.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Fuck.
I don't know why, but I definitely, I definitely as well viewers like the idea of reference cop killers being a YouTube show.
They're like, I don't know why and like it kind of doesn't make sense, but just something about it feels right.
Ah.
Excellent rebuttal.
I'm sorry, I'm very focused.
This game is Zen.
It feels like the opposite of Zen.
It feels like it's fucking like waterboard torture.
Well, tomato-tomato.
Guys, what if I made a fifth UKM that was really hard?
Impossible.
I'm, I'm, I'm so, this, this is like the most, I know, I know like a,
I know like it doesn't actually matter like literally at all, but it feels super like it's a defined moment in reference cop killers history.
The fucking, like will we do Twitch or will we do YouTube?
Even though like we will do both.
Yeah.
No matter what the results are, it feels important to me.
Uh, well, I mean, I'm, I'm really liking Twitch a whole lot, like a whole fucking lot.
Yeah.
Also, also people donate sometimes, which is nice.
That's nice.
Oh, we, what fucking child musters we are, we haven't even mentioned far more important than the fucking Twitch.
Yeah, the discord.
Far, far more important, the discord.
The discord is a defining moment in Rowdy fucker's history.
Yeah.
Unquestionably.
This is literally the best thing to ever happen to this fucking show.
Yeah.
The show is real now.
This is like on par with like the, the frog fractions saga, like no question, no question.
In some ways, I think it's even more like defining.
Yeah.
Because, because, because the Rowdy fucker's cop killers now has a cannon.
There is now a, there is now cannon.
There's now more.
Yeah.
I, I was actually like in my mind before this server was created, I was pretty adamant in
the sense of the fact that like, like, Reverent Circular should not have lore because I was
surrounded by so many shows that had like, like obtuse and absurd lore.
But now that it does, just by nature, that's just the way that me and Ben make things is
that we fill it with fucking lore to the brim.
Yeah.
I'm so happy and it has literally the best lore of any narrative ever created.
It's um, I've been really getting into it.
And I've been like, I've just been reveling in like all of the, all the shit people have
made and all of the art of Slime City.
Actually, I have a, I have a grievance, not a grievance, but I have a concern, which is
that I don't know if I like the name Slime City.
I don't know if I like it either.
It's on, it's too on the nose.
I would like to propose the alternative name of Fuck City.
I know, I know you said that, but I think that's just as bad.
You think so?
I think both of them leave something to be desired.
When I was making, like, like, like, I made, I made like a map for the setting of Reverent
Circular.
Oh no.
Okay.
So, Reverent Circular is a city that is on, like, like a peninsula in the Grand Canyon.
But the Grand Canyon, due to a nuclear meltdown, has been flooded with nuclear toxic waste,
aka Slime.
And it's basically a gold rush and everyone is flocked to this city to get their hands
on some Slime, which is worth like twice its weight in gold.
Slime is, Slime is the most powerful resource.
Slime, if you, if he who controls the Slime controls the world.
And we control the Slime.
So, so the Grand Canyon, this like iconic, like American, like National Park, it's just
flooded with fucking Slime and there's just a bunch of gang warfare in the city.
And me and Ben, of course, moved there to try and make it big and get our grubby little
hands on some fucking Slime.
And so basically we just have an apartment in downtown, whatever the city is called,
and we just record Let's Plays and we make fun of each other and troll each other online
using proxy child warfare because we're too pussy to fight it in the wild.
And meanwhile our minions, like, rage through the streets committing untold gang violence
and atrocities.
Oh, it's perfect.
Yeah, I'm, I don't, I don't like Slime City either.
Yeah.
It was just, it was just, I don't know, it felt like a placeholder name that just kind of caught on.
Oh God.
I feel like if we do want to change it, we should change it now.
We don't want to have it be solidified.
We don't, we don't want to, we don't want to let that Slime settle.
Slime City can always be like, you know, the nickname for it.
Like the, like New York is the big Apple.
The big Slime.
No.
Fuck.
We're tired of it.
I don't know.
What, what can we call it?
Um, New Delta City.
No.
I'm pretty sure that was in Robocop.
Great.
Yeah.
Los Angeles 2.
New Los Angeles City.
New Los Angeles City 2.
Um, Neo.
I, I, I kind of like New Los Angeles City.
I kind of like that.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's, it's, it's really fucking stupid.
But it's really funny.
Yeah.
New Los Angeles City is pretty strong.
What about like, what about like, um, wait, an idea is calcifying.
Um, like, uh, I'm thinking like Neo and then like a town that is like, sounds like, oh,
oh, oh, oh, wait, wait.
Um, hold on.
Hold on.
Neo Albuquerque.
Neo Albuquerque is pretty good.
Um, oh, Neo Spokane.
Spokane.
Oh, that's not bad.
I like Neo.
Yeah.
It definitely, it definitely needs to be like, Neo Milwaukee.
It needs to be like retarded and funny.
Those are the two requirements.
Is it to be retarded and funny?
Yeah.
And like vaguely imply like, relation to like a populous city.
Uh.
Neo Milwaukee.
You know, Milwaukee too, in the deserts of Arizona.
Uh.
It'll happen again.
Keep on trying.
Bullshit.
It's not that bad.
You're at level one again.
Yeah, but I have to do this part.
This, this is like my least favorite part.
Cause this part is totally random as well as like relatively high stakes.
You know, I've seen my favorite streamers Rodney Dangerfield play this game.
So I, to me, from my perspective, you're, you're kicking ass.
I don't, I don't have a frame of reference.
I mean, I've gotten pretty good at the part like up to this point.
And then this is where I start to like not know what the fuck I'm doing.
Uh.
Oh, I didn't even mention those important fucking part in Slime or Los Angeles too.
In, in, in, in new Los Angeles city.
There is a, there is a, an obelisk standing in the city.
It's not pyramid.
Oh fuck.
Yeah.
It's not, it's not a pyramid.
No.
It's been depicted as a pyramid because people have misinterpreted the avatar.
Yeah.
Which is understandable.
But it's an obvious thing.
Think like the Washington Monument only way better.
Yeah.
Uh, there's an obvious called endless war.
And, uh, I, I don't know if we have concrete rules, but just know that he,
that he washes over as constantly and he, uh, and he fuels getting warfare in,
in ways even we can't fully articulate.
We don't fully understand endless war.
We know that the bodies of the dead are like put into him and they like power him somehow.
And he like regurgitate slime.
Um, and other than that, you know, it's all pretty, it's all pretty much open to interpretation.
Is this real?
Is this metaphorical?
Is endless war an actual thing or just a discord server bar server bot that we have
made to troll each other online?
No one's to say for sure.
Uh, uh, balls.
Oh fuck.
Oh my God.
That was really funny.
You just, uh.
I just ate shit.
Shit.
Yeah.
You just ate shit and died.
Oh God.
Okay.
This is so fucking tense.
This is nerve wracking.
Yeah.
Imagine what it would be like to be you.
Beating this game would be just so me, you know.
That would be so you.
That would fit your aesthetic so hard.
Yes.
Being the guy who's like, oh yeah, getting over within a body.
Yeah, I beat it.
It took me like a couple of weeks, but I did it.
Whatever.
Wasn't even that hard.
Yeah, you know, you just get into a groove.
Oh God.
I don't want to bag anything, but you know, I talked to the developer and he basically
said I was the one.
There's a part later that looks fucking retarded where it's like there is a like box hanging
from a chain and you have to like, I don't even know what you're supposed to do with
it, but you're supposed to like do something with this box on a chain and like jump up to
like another level using it.
And that part looks literally impossible.
This game is, I'm convinced that this is the worst game ever made just by virtue of the
way that it makes me feel.
No, this game is art.
This game is art, art, art, maybe terrible.
Yes.
Oh God.
No.
Oh faggot.
Okay.
I have to stop.
I feel like look away from the screen and so I stop doing streamer noises.
Yeah.
I don't have that luxury.
Yeah, I know.
You have to be glued to this shit.
I'm, I'm, I'm, the, the number one thing that the discord server has solidified is the
fact that undeniably you, if you want to describe or ever describe, you have to use the term
subversive or genre defined.
You could not get around using either of those two adjectives.
I mean, yeah.
There's just no way around it.
To not do that would just be, I mean, it would just be dishonest.
It would just be intellectually dishonest.
Yeah, I know.
You've done more for the further of like, like let's plays and discord servers than all of
you fucking schmucks have ever even dreamed of.
Hey, should we like talk about, should we like talk about what the actual server is now?
Yeah.
Well, it's, yeah, it's a, it's a game now.
It's been turned into a game.
It is a, it is a site of gang warfare.
You can go there.
You can, you, you kill people, you mine slime, you become powerful and you, and you just,
you know, try and try, you commit warfare in the name of, you know, the rabid fucker,
the cop kill.
You choose a side, you know, the factions are heavily divisive and at each other's throats
constantly.
Again, to, to fuel me and Ben's trolling campaigns for one another online, you, you can join
either the rowdies, my faction, or the stinky killers that is officially named the stinky
killers.
Yeah.
Ben's smelly faction.
Just today.
Okay.
So a little, a little history.
There was a, there was a long period there where like I took, I took the lead and like
a pretty commanding lead for a while there.
In overall slime count.
Yeah, in overall slime.
I was at like three million in something and you were at like one and a half million.
So then yesterday with the new patch, the casino patch, there's now a casino where you
can gamble your slime on, on craps and the slot machines.
All with any discord server by the way.
This is all in a discord server.
So there's that.
And I just gambled away like half a million slime, um, betting on craps, uh, and losing
every time.
And then today, um, you, you orchestrated a scheme with one of your rowdies, uh, to kill
one of the most powerful juveniles.
I organized with one of my most trusted mercenaries, the dreaded player, uh, ready player one,
this is his official name.
I've contracted the, the, the, the merciless mercenary ready player one.
He's in my, he's in my league.
Yeah.
So, um, so that all happened.
So with my losses and your sudden gains, we're now like way closer.
I'm, I'm at like just over three million and you're at like, what, like 2.6 million.
Yeah.
2.6.
Okay.
So, uh, yeah.
I designed some of these people.
I got, I got, some of these people are looking like a snack.
That's all I'll say.
The, the killers.
Okay.
The killers have been like mobilized and like organized and they have like, you know, they
hang out in cop killer town and they just like talk strategy.
Like they talk shop.
Yeah.
They're super, they're super like in like the math of it and, and like the art, they're
basically, they basically treat like it is chest, which would have no rainbow had the
eyes, no tears.
Also nice job.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Well, they're treating it like it's chess.
But the thing is that the rules keep changing because, uh, oh, the new, new patch, dead players
can now haunt the living from the sewers.
They can steal their slime and actually crack just implemented, um, cracks the developer
by the way.
Um, he just implemented a thing where now, um, dead players that haunt, they gain negative
slime.
So they, they have negative slime now, um, which is fucking sick.
And that's probably going to be relevant later.
There will probably be a way to like stop the dead from haunting you if you can do something.
That's probably all, I'll be like old news by the time.
Yeah.
We'll be like six more patches deep.
You know, like there will be like, you know, there will be like collect, you know, there
will be like a collectible card.
They'll be like a full on collectible card game in the discord server.
Oh, then you just ruined my life.
I'm going to have to make a fucking right.
Yeah.
I'm writing that the fuck down right now.
I'm super into that.
Okay.
Good.
Oh God.
Oh fuck.
No.
Mother fucker.
Dude, I got a hollow lord of ghosts the other day in a booster pack.
It was super fucking lucky.
Jealous.
I need that to round out my manicurve, my slime curve.
Oh my God.
It writes itself.
We're just printing fucking slime at this point.
We're printing slime.
Oh, it's too easy.
Guys, viewers, think about it.
Think about it for one fucking second and you'll understand the ramifications.
What other let's play show?
Mind you, this let's play show releases exclusively like two hour plus content in like bulk of
like meandering, flattering topics.
This let's play show.
What other let's play has a discord server that actively incentivizes gang warfare and
has like a playable gambling within its perimeters.
What other fucking let's play show has that?
The game grumps fucking.
I don't fucking think so.
The other shit?
What do they have?
R slash polygrams.
Get the fuck out of here.
Yeah.
R slash endless war is what we're fucking working.
Yes.
There should probably be a subreddit for rowdy fuckers because there's so much.
There's so much lore.
Like there's so much.
Yeah.
You know what?
That makes a lot of sense because that'll be that'll probably be a better way to post
Fanner and shit.
Yeah.
Actually, oh shit.
That's a great idea that I just had.
I'm gonna pat myself.
Yeah.
I'm gonna back for it.
God, the right.
Like right for this.
We'll just will not stop growing.
Like you just can't.
It can't.
It can't anymore.
No, it's just too powerful.
There's nothing we can do.
But mega slime achieved.
Yeah.
That's gonna be that's like brain blast.
But like now it's mega slime achieved when you have a really potent.
When ever, you know, when, when, when you've made strides, when you've made strides towards
conquest, mega slime achieved.
But like you're also afraid of the consequences.
I feel like, like, like I'm almost, I'm really excited, I guess I would say to see what the
viewers like, like what you like the modern day viewer, like if you're seeing this on
like day one, what does endless war look like to you?
Because it's like a concept state of like development right now.
And we're not totally happy with it, of course.
No.
So like we're continually updating it.
So like, what does it look like for you?
Like, like maybe some of these, maybe some of these concepts are like defunct.
Maybe you can't haunt players anymore.
Maybe we decided that that is not like streamlined enough.
I don't know.
Anything's possible.
Uh, man, me and Crack, a while ago, we were, we workshopped.
We were just like, we were just talking shop about it.
About like shit that could be added later.
And it was so fucking exciting for me.
I, you guys have like, like a test server where you guys iron out all this shit.
Yeah.
And I used to be involved in like, in like when, like the first couple of things.
But I've been totally off the map and like, and like not playing the game.
Because, because I've been editing rad con shit and like doing other things.
Yeah.
Which we will get into later.
I have, I have, I have a little bit of notes here that I am keeping track of.
Oh God.
Uh, but I just want to say.
Oh no, no, no.
Okay.
Anyway.
Are you watching this by the way?
Yeah.
Oh, oh, I'm watching.
I'm watching eyes glued, dude.
Eyes glued.
You're in fucking, you're in the hell pit.
You're in the cesspool.
God.
Damn it.
I feel like I did way better on my first try and now I'm sucking shit again.
Yeah, I know.
You actually got to the place.
Yeah.
All right.
Anyway.
Uh, I forget what I was saying.
Some fucking bullshit.
Something about the test server?
Editing rad con shit?
Oh, oh yeah.
Yeah.
You guys have been doing insanely great, like, like constant work.
Like much, much like endless work itself, you guys have endless work.
And it's really endearing and nice and I'm glad you've dedicated yourself to this goal.
Yeah.
I am, I'm way into it.
I like, okay, I try to do as much as I can.
Like, all right.
Like before Endless War, I was talking about Endless War before it was real and like I
was doing my best.
I spent like several days studying and learning Python to try and code it.
Turns out there's like all this other shit because like it's not enough just to write
the program.
It also has to be like run from a database and like communicate with the database.
And that is some like advanced shit that I do not know how long I do not know what I would
have had to do to get them all.
So just thank God crack was like, Hey, I'll write it.
And because he's like an actual programmer.
So he like developed it in the beginning.
And that gave us like a foundation to work off of.
And he still does most of like the updates, but I like, like for the casino, I like take
his existing code and I like just like kind of fuck around with it and try and like make
it into new functions.
And it kind of works most of the time.
By the way, I'm eating gum right now.
Fuck you viewers.
Gross.
Sick.
I'm getting, I'm getting frustrated.
I'm getting frustrated with Bennett.
I can tell you're foaming.
You're foaming right now.
I'm I plan to be more reference cop killers or endless war more accurately, like like
meetings because I am interested.
I am interested in this game.
I mean, it's been bogged down with other shit.
Now, okay, the way it works right now that there's a couple of problems.
One, it's, well, actually it was too easy to die, but now it's too easy not to die because
now the PVP flag system means that if you don't do anything, you're invulnerable, which
is, I mean, yeah, you know, you can't like accomplish anything, but like it's kind of
like people just haven't been dying lately.
Well, well, maybe there's not enough people playing.
Yeah.
What I want to know is what in the beginning before endless war, we just like had the server
and there was like minor elements of gang war there.
And both of us on either side, it needs at any given time, there'd be online about like
20 killers and about 20 rowdies, you know, but now for some reason, our numbers are so
fucking small.
They're so fucking small.
Right now there are like seven killers.
There are three rowdies.
Why is this the case?
Well, I mean, there's also, there are also juveniles and corpses, like the corpses are
actually pretty active.
God, it's so sick.
Ghost pride is the number one plague on fucking society.
It is.
It's, it's disgusting, frankly.
It's, you know, it's subversive in all the ways that rowdy fuckers itself is not.
It's all the wrong types of subversive.
We're all the good parts.
Yes.
We've got the market cornered on subversiveness.
Everyone else needs to quit right now.
We've got all the subversiveness.
There's none left for anyone else.
All other types of subversion are now just, you know, degeneracy.
Disgusting.
Okay.
What I want to do is I like in this war, like this is, this is like, you're like an indie
dev, like that's been like, like breaking his back and I'm now like the corporate like
AAA publisher who wants to get your game off, you know, into steam, but you're going to
make some like, like hard buying like creative decisions and, and, and work with me, the evil
tyrant.
Yeah.
I like in this war, I like what you got going on here, kid.
But I think that we need to have like a conference where we like, where we like, we try and
like streamline and like simplify things and like understand like, like design philosophies.
Because right now it feels, it's not like actually, but it feels bloated.
And I think, and I think that we can like, we can, we can get to the point where like all
the like, we can get to the point where it is literally and all of like the ends tie to
one another.
And like it is narratively and like aesthetically sound and like in one.
Because I feel like there are some mechanics that kind of like are dead ends and aren't
really cohesive with the overall like design, if you know what I'm saying.
Like what?
What do you, what do you mean?
The dojo specifically, the dojo.
The dojo is, the dojo was kind of a stopgap measure to like keep players doing things.
Like even the dojo was an attempt to stop stagnation because players that had aligned with a faction
had nothing to do.
So the dojo was like, okay, well, you can't mine for slime, but you can spar and like it's
something.
But yeah, it doesn't really do anything except, except get you a little bit of slime and then
like flag you for PvP.
So it is kind of an under, yeah.
Okay.
All of the myth that sparring is underdeveloped and doesn't really serve that much purpose
at the time.
Oh God, Jesus.
Oh.
Okay.
You know what?
That's all right.
I'm okay with that.
It's all right.
We'll make you less miserable now.
Abraham Lincoln.
I think like we just need to examine what we want the game to be on like the average,
like like what we want the day to day of the game to be and like what are the design
that we want to entail because I, what I want is for the day to day to, I want to return
in any way that we can to the like 20 killers and 20 routies at any given time.
I want, okay.
Yeah.
I want death to be, okay, I want death to be easy, but also like less common.
I think that what I want is for, yeah, I want a world where like, you know, the routies
and the killers are not constantly killing each other, but they can at a moment's notice.
Like, you know, I want, I want the threat of like, because now with the PVP flags, the
threat of death is largely eliminated if you don't want it.
I like, I want the threat to be there, but also like, you know, rare enough that you're
not just like, well, fuck if there's no point of playing.
I feel like it says, it's just a complicated web of alliances.
I mainly just want there to be like, again, there to be, you know, a healthy number of
each gang.
Yeah.
I feel like there has to be some sort of like, because the invulnerability for not doing anything
is like fine, and that's like a fine solution.
Yeah.
But it's just, there's just too many, there's just too many corpses with, with corpse pride
not wanting to do things, and there's too much, there's too much like people just not
doing things.
Yeah.
It's just too, like of a passive experience, like, like, it's too, it's too easy to just
not do anything because there's not like, aside from like the core of like killing, like,
like being juvenile farming and then getting killed is like not like a whole bunch to like
act for quintessential juvenile experience.
I love the casino.
I really love it because that's like, that's like a use for slime.
Yeah.
Like, even though like the actual benefit of it is just to get more slime.
You can like, spin the slime on something.
Yes.
In an ideal world, there would be some sort of like slime shop where you could like, buy
something with slime, but I don't know how we could fit that into a discourse or like,
or like what the rewards would be.
Okay.
Like other items are feasible.
Like I was thinking about like maybe a way to change combat so that it wouldn't be as
like instantly lethal would be an item that was like armor and like if you can like buy
a bunch of them and if you've got them, like, you, it like, like the enemy doesn't know
you have them, but you can, but like you, they'll shoot at you and it'll cost them,
you know, what it costs to kill you, but you don't die.
But you just deplete one of your like armor pieces.
So you could like build up like a strong like resistance to death by like just buying a shit
ton of armor, you know.
And that could mean that, you know, your, your, your AFK like a, like we could remove
maybe not completely, but to an extent, the invulnerability for being like passive.
Yeah.
By just allowing you to have a defensive like option in the form of armor so that it's just
like, you know, if you like, like if you want to just be AFK, then get a fucking armor.
Yeah.
That's, that's what I was thinking.
Cause like, yeah, it removed, like you still have to kind of be watched.
Like if someone wants to kill you through your armor, it's possible.
It's just, it just would be like, it would become so expensive, like so prohibitively
expensive that it's like, it wouldn't generally happen, but like it can.
I think you agree with this, let's go back to like, like the general design.
I want, my ideal server would be where like the main brute like, like, like brunt force
of the gang warfare is a verbal and shit talking that is punctuated by like frequent, but not
constant war.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, like a lot of, like a lot of shit talking and like when someone is mad, they can kill
you and people do get shot over these like scuffles.
Yeah.
It's, it's, it's just hard to, I almost feel like a part of it is like cultural.
How do you mean?
Like, I feel like if we like instill what we want into the fans, they may do what we want.
If you know what I'm saying?
Obviously we should have the system itself be prohibitive and, and, and, you know, make
it so like, like what we want to have happen happens, but I almost feel like in a way,
they, like people feel incentivized to just constantly kill and I feel like they're like
there are ways that we could like just societally say to chill out possibly.
I'm not entirely sure, but I feel like we can do something.
Well, I don't know.
The thing is, I think the reason why people were incentivized to constantly kill was that
it was strategically valuable.
Like killing all the rowdies meant that like you got their slime and they could not like
kill you anymore.
Okay.
Actually, actually wait, I had another idea.
I had, I had kind of forgotten about this, but I had thought that because right now you
can kill someone with more slime than you.
You can kill someone if you have about like 60, 55 to 60% of their slime.
I thought maybe combat would become like less lethal overall and like, you know, more of
a, more of like a threat than like if, if it was just harder to do, like it just maybe
you needed like, you know, 1.2 times their slime or something before you could kill them.
But then I mean, the problem there with that is that like the strongest person, well, okay,
that means like the strongest person is invincible, but also he can't really kill any, well, he
could kill small people all day and it wouldn't matter.
So that kind of sucks.
But if he killed anyone big, he would lose a bunch of slime and he would probably lose
his position.
I don't know.
It's a little imbalanced, but it might be overall better than what we've got.
Yeah, maybe I, I, I think one of the biggest things is that juvies, even though they have
new productions and are basically considered filled within our government system, they
like have the most to do, like, like mining is like a huge thing and they can do it constantly
and that's where all, that's like what the economy is like based upon.
Yeah.
Whereas like, gang fraction members like kind of don't really get to do anything.
Yeah, that's why, that's why I thought sparring would help and it kind of did a little.
I, I think, okay, I've not thought this through.
Yeah.
But I'm, I'm thinking because this will help the numbers system as well.
If once you enlist, you are enlisted like, you know, forever.
And once you die and you respond, you just are on whatever team you were on and then
allow the traction members to maybe not explicitly like mine, but do something to gather slime
so that, you know, you could still get slime whenever you respond.
We were talking about maybe making like a different, like, like a different room, like
a farm, like maybe, like maybe we change it so that faction members can mine, but Juvies
can farm and like farming works a little differently, but is overall like a more efficient way of
getting slime.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
So it would be like, okay, I like that a lot because it gives, it gives like a reason to
be a Juvie.
Yeah.
I want there to be a reason to be a Juvie.
Wait, what?
It gives everyone a reason to be on whatever side that they are.
Yeah.
And that's important.
We're also talking about like, if there were items, like maybe Juvies could be, like maybe
Juvies would have to like make the items or something like that.
Maybe something like that.
I like this.
I feel like I need to like watch the entirety of extra credits and then come back to this.
Yeah.
You know?
This is, this is not like pissy baby shit.
This is, this is like, I, like I, I want this to be good.
I want this to be real.
Same.
You're going to have to like, oh, what you're supposed to do is you're supposed to like
flail back and forth and like have your hammer, like just kind of like bang up against
both of those walls.
This fucking sucks.
I know.
Um, yeah.
I watched, I, I looked up a video and I'm trying to, well I'm actually like not doing
what he did.
Yeah.
You're not doing it at all.
Oof.
When games were used.
Yes.
Oh!
Fuck.
Yeah.
This is the furthest I've ever gotten.
Save, save.
Players played stoically.
Oh.
Now everyone's turned off by that.
Oh my God.
I know.
That's not you.
This is the hardest thing I've ever done and also the least rewarding.
I know.
It like really sucks.
There's no like, due to the fact that you can go, like you can just like die and go
back to the beginning of the game.
There's no like level, like you're entering level two or anything.
Yeah.
Like the only progress you make is that you like learn how to deal with the shit which
you will inevitably have to deal with like many, many more times.
It just braces you for more pain.
Yeah.
Okay.
I know what I have to do here.
It's just going to be really hard.
I would actually be like probably like pretty like infuriated, like annoyed if I had to
like listen to like, I'm assuming bullshit pretentious narrative.
It's probably really annoying.
It's not narrative.
It's like Bennett Foddy talking about like game design and like, you know, like the power
of like, you know, frustration as a motivator and stuff like that.
I got up to go.
That just makes me feel like, that just makes me feel like Dave, like Rose, what are you
talking about?
We don't, we're humans.
We don't have character.
That's what that feels like to me.
Yeah, like, like the absence of a narrative is like a pretentious design choice in and
of itself.
No, I'm saying that like the fact that he's like talking about like the benefit as frustration
as a motivator just makes it, I don't know, something, something about it doesn't feel
right to me.
Something about it just feels like I don't like it's self congratulatory.
Yeah.
That's, that's exactly it.
Like, like, like he's there extolling.
Like he's here talking about why the thing his game is about is like a great thing.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
Exactly.
And it's not only that, it's that compounded effect that it is frustration and generally
considered a negative thing.
So it's like, I've subverted like troops and here I have made a flood scheme that makes
you feel terrible all the time.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know.
I don't know.
I kind of shout outs to Brady fuck wit or whatever his name is Borscht Mcmick Mcfowler.
Incredible.
I have a square in a way all endless war things we want to talk about.
Oh, keep you updated.
I mean, I mean, obviously join the server.
Join.
You'll get to see this in real time.
Let me, let me make this, let me make this plea to the viewer, join the server and don't
stay dead.
The stay deads are a plague that are actually kind of like bumming me out.
I mean, okay, I think they have a place in the lore and I don't mind that they exist,
but I do mind the extent to which they have like kind of taken over.
It's pretty lame.
I mean, I guess it's my fault, you know, it's kind of our fault for like making, especially
in the beginning, like in the beginning, it was so easy to die that people were like,
I'm just going to stay dead and like remove myself with a conflict.
I get it.
But it's, you know, it's a little different now and I hope the people will like give,
give it a chance, you know, give war a chance is what I'm saying.
I, okay.
I like, in my ideal world, normal, normal people who just like graphic techlers would
want to join routies or killers, then like the, the, the like funny memers who are, you
know, assholes and fuck them want to be Juvies for like, for like the hipster reward, you
know, satisfaction they get.
And then like, like, like, like, like Juvies and gang fractions will all have like benefits
to themselves and like will have, you know, reasons you would want to be on either side.
And the stay deads are just like fucking like, like insane people who, and they have no benefits
other than the fact of like gathering negative slime, which is just like a stupid, like,
like bullshit, like hipster, hipster statistic that only retards care about.
But due to the fact that like it is so stupid, there will be people, it will just be like,
like five or six corpses who are just continually trying to get like the least amount of slime
possible.
Yeah.
Hmm.
You know, yeah, we really, we really should not incentivize.
We should not create like a, like a corpse power structure.
Like corpses should have nothing to aspire to.
Okay.
That's true.
That's, that's making me rethink some, so I was going to have, like I was going to have
negative slime, like do something, but maybe I shouldn't.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
Yeah, I think I agree, but you know, I think I was kind of, I think, like, we were all
really feeling kind of in a slump lately. I think we all kind of felt like distant and
shitty and I think, I think at least some of us were counting on Radcon, like, you know,
bringing us back together and like making us feel more like real friends again.
I definitely did.
Yeah, I do. I feel, it was great hanging out with you and Tom and everyone and, you know,
that was pretty cool and I guess I didn't hang out much with like Hippo or Jesse. It was,
it was good hanging out with Digi again. Also Nate, that piece of shit was there too, I guess.
He was there.
Yeah, but it was way fun and it reminded me that we're all human beings.
How good was it to see Digi?
It was great. I love Digi.
I know. I do too.
We were like tight when we lived together. We hung out like a bunch.
You know, I, for a while there, for like a while there, like, like, for like a couple like months,
proceeding Radcon 3, I forgot that I liked Digi, you know?
Well, he hadn't really, he hadn't really been that active in the discord and like that was like,
you know, that's like our main interaction with each other.
So if someone's not really typing in the discord, it's like they're gone.
And the only other thing that we could ascertain from Digi was the fact that he smoked weed a lot and all of his content was bad now.
Yeah.
And even though all of his content is still bad, I remembered that I like him a lot still.
Yeah, yeah.
He is to suffer.
To survive is to find some meaning in the suffering.
Anyway.
The PCP chat, I, I, this is so revolutionary for me because I don't feel like I'm not incentivized to like post and chat.
Like I don't feel like it's weird to post in the PCP chat.
Yeah.
Like, like, I feel like I can just say a message if I want to say a message and like it won't be weird or like, or like I'm entering,
or like I'm going over the top of the trenches and entering no man's land and I'm about to be berated with enemy missile fire from all directions.
I, I have actually not been that active in the chat, but like I should be.
So I haven't really, I haven't really seen that much of what you're talking about, but I have gotten the overall sense that things are like more cool and chill now.
Yeah, it's great.
Like everyone's talking more.
Everyone's talking like way more.
Yeah.
And it is just an overall sense of like, yeah, we're friends again.
Like, like we've done it.
We've really done it.
Well, it's kind of odd how easy, like, it's not like we did anything.
Like, like, like the real friend initiative was like a concerted effort to make what has happened happen.
But like for Radcon, like we didn't like really do anything.
We just hung out.
Yeah.
But you know, there's a lesson in that.
You know, it's gotta, it's, you can't force it.
But, well, but you kind of can't by having Radcon.
Yeah, exactly.
It was really nice.
You know, you know what?
I was upset that we didn't do among many things.
We didn't do a PCP decompression chamber like we did a Radcon too.
I was really hoping that we were going to do one of those.
Oh my God.
Because I wasn't even able to, I wasn't in the first one and I was cool.
Oh fuck.
Did you see that?
I don't know if you saw that, but the way those stairs are shaped.
Like, when you try and like, when you try and like pull yourself up by the hook of your hammer,
the stair above like pushes back against the hammer and like knocks you off.
So it's like not an option.
That's devilish.
That's devilishly designed.
But frustration is so motivating.
It doesn't make you just want to stop playing the game and get a refund on Steam.
Or does it?
Oh man, did you see, I tweeted a Steam review of this game.
Like when I first got it, like a couple, like maybe a month.
Did you see that?
I didn't see it.
It was like, it was just really funny because it was like clearly like a teen or a kid
trying to be very eloquent in saying that he did not like the game,
but just sounding ridiculous.
Yeah.
It was just like, I am not giving this a bad review because of, I'm not doing it justice.
He like misused a bunch of long words or like semi misused a bunch of long words,
trying to sound like like a perfectly logical being who is just like, you know, I don't know.
Talking about how like I fail to, I have failed to receive a, you know, a supply of dopamine to my brain
due to the highly, the overly, frustrational nature of this piece of digital media.
And it was fucking sick, is what I'm saying.
I'm scrolling through for it right now.
Look at all those Biscopades.
Have you made a fucking Tumblr yet?
No, because I, I have been, I have, Biscopades is on hold.
I got to finish Vapors 3 first.
I forgot about Vapors 3 for like ever.
And I love Biscopades and I want to do it, but I have to finish Vapors 3.
It's like more, it's not more than that.
It's like, you know, a lot of the way done.
I can't be fucking sitting on all these unfinished product projects.
Vapors 3 won't take me that long if I like really fucking hammer it, you know.
So that's, well, actually, I got to do my fucking, I got to do fucking, my tail gets trolled lecture.
And I got to do, I got to edit 10 paces, you know, 10 paces and draw.
We might just, I might just have to be like, that's going to take a while.
Like, I'm, okay.
10 paces and draw might not be out for a while.
But the draw, the draw cast and the, and the lecture.
The draw has, doesn't have to happen because it's like a normal PCP thing.
Wait, what?
The draw cast has to happen because it's like, you know.
Yeah, that, yeah.
But like, okay, I'm missing footage and I want to like double check with everyone about like if they have the missing footage.
But I kind of don't know.
So I kind of don't think anyone has it.
I think that probably it's just lost, which is sad, but whatever.
Oh, found it by Nova post March 1st.
You found what?
I am not mad.
I'm just not playing to proceed on attempting to release dopamine caused by the satisfaction of EG entertainment.
Because this electronic software product only manages to cause emotional anger within the human brain due to its unnaturally advanced levels of frustration or design choices.
This is made by an artificial intelligence.
No, this is made by real emotional intelligence.
I can't build.
Because this electronic software product.
Right?
I love it.
Couldn't just say fucking video.
No dude, no.
Like get, get, get real.
Oh my god.
Okay.
I thought I was not going to be able to get out from that.
I, I, I honest to God, I hope that no one like watches the Refikis Copulus because this is like, like visually this will be like the worst episode ever recorded.
This shit is gripping dude.
I don't know what you're talking about.
This shit is unbelievably insufferable.
This shit is horrible.
It's, it's ugly on purpose.
This game is shit.
Fuck this game.
Shit, this game is art.
This game means something.
This game has something to say about.
It means something, what we don't know, but I guarantee you that it means something.
Oh god.
I'm watching with Badebreath right now.
Ah shit.
Christ.
I feel like I would have better luck at doing what this guy's doing in real life than playing the game.
Ah fuck me.
My fucking hand on the mouse is sweaty.
No, no, no.
That's why this game is stream.
Stream boys, yeah.
That's a stream.
Stream.
Everyone jump in the stream.
This is, why is this the game that we're playing fucking on video?
It was, because it was suggested by our beautiful, by our beautiful fans.
Also, because I owned it already and because I like it.
The last part is suspect.
Okay, okay.
Ever since, Radcon 3, life, for my perspective, life has just been way better in all regards.
Yeah.
Like, like, Radcon 3 has just made everything great and perfect and there's been no problems, basically.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I agree.
Radcon was great and things have been good and we're all, it does feel like we, it was just great to reconnect with everyone.
And it just, I don't know.
Yeah, you get it.
And I, for like a while, I was like, I was just kind of like not, I just assumed that I was just going to do like a little bit after Radcon, like a rush of, you know,
uh, everyone was talking because, you know, post-con depression and all that.
But it's going, it's going like really steady for like the past like weeks.
Like, like it's really, it's really like, it's really here to stay, I feel.
It's really here to stay.
Like, fucking, Nate's typing right goddamn now.
Nate's typing right fucking now.
That's crazy.
That's crazy making right now.
Okay, I'm gonna do it this time.
I'm gonna do it.
The chat's super active.
People like DG.
Dude.
Anyway.
This is awful.
No, I'm gonna, I, when I hit that orange before, that was, that was further than I've ever been.
I've never touched the orange before.
How long is this game?
Uh, I don't know.
I want to say that I'm probably like, probably like, whoa, whoa, whoa, what the fuck?
I've never grabbed this.
Whoa.
Can I like, oh, can I skip?
No, no, I can't.
Of all sad words of tongue or pen, the saddest of these.
I mean, I'll bet that someone who's really good at the game could do it, but I have like no confidence.
No!
Okay.
That's it.
Didn't matter.
I could have swung back to the other side.
Andre Tachkopsky.
What were you saying?
Something about how Nate's talking in chat right now and how it's more active than it's ever been.
Oh, and like DG, that elusive, that rare beetle of a man is like talking like regularly.
Has he?
Well, yeah, he's not the most active member, but like he, like, like I see DG not unreasonably often.
Um, man, you know, I have, I have kind of not been that active.
I should get more active because like, I remember how inactive it got for a period there.
But if it's like more active, I should fucking hop in.
You actually the most inactive member, and that is including Mage.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, well that's no good.
I don't like, I don't like that at all.
Yeah, Mage pops in.
Like all, all the people who were like pretty inactive are like all like the same.
Like, like, like, you know, it's no secret to all the fans that the PCP has become the me, Nate, Tom, and Hippo show, basically.
Tom too?
Yeah, Tom's on like every episode. You are too, actually.
I've always been on like almost every episode.
Yeah.
I only mess them like very occasionally.
Everyone's like on the, everyone's jolly. Everyone's on the same playing field.
Everyone's about, like, like about the same level of activity.
Some are a little bit more than others, but like everyone is friends with one another.
Everyone is in the know.
Everyone knows what the fuck's going on with one another.
We're all in tune, we're all synced up, we're all gelled up.
It's great.
Oh, also like Victor is in the PCP chat for like, for like, for like Radcon planning stuff and like no one just bothered to kick him.
So like, he hasn't said anything?
No.
Yeah, I didn't think so.
Victor's just like there.
Yeah, and that's fine.
That's cool.
Yeah.
That's quite great.
I felt, I felt weird like, like Victor, like, okay, like I like Victor, but like he didn't, he didn't, at Radcon, he wasn't there to like be a real person.
Like, like all he did was like be ordered around, you know?
Um, yeah.
Which is like fine.
Like, I don't know if I should feel that, wow, okay, that was a great jump.
Like I felt kind of bad because I was like, man, we're kind of just like, we're kind of just like, just like kind of bossing him around.
Like I know he's being paid, but like still, but I don't know.
Maybe he just, maybe that was like what he wanted.
Maybe he just kind of wanted to show up and like, you know, do his work and get out of there.
He was sufficiently goofy.
He was a bit goofy.
He was really, he was very shirtless very much at the time and I'm not sure.
Yeah.
He would take his shirt off for no reason.
He just was hot.
He just was hot was his reason.
Well, I mean, okay.
Even when he was outside the fucking freezing time.
Yeah.
Oh, is there a single more iconic PCP moment than fucking the group piss?
No, the group piss is a miracle.
And part of me.
That was all, that was all me by the way.
That was all me.
Wait, was it?
Yeah.
That was, that was when I was very adamant about there being a group piss because I wasn't a part of the group shit at Brony.
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
The um, okay.
You know, I'm of two minds about this.
Part of me like wants to like digitally add in the other people.
Which I could do.
But the other part of me thinks that like the moment is pure and like to alter it or doctor it would be to, you know, to corrupt it.
Bismarck.
Yeah.
I feel like it's fine right now.
Eventually when that fabled PCP style guide comes out, then we can do something about it.
But for right now, there's, there's no better, you know, it's a symbol of Radcon 3.
It's a symbol of the PCP.
It's iconic.
Who, who could, who could deny its relevance?
If I had.
Who could deny?
If I, I mean, if I had a picture like from behind of, you know, say, you know, Jesse, Mage, and uh,
D'Avoo.
And D'Avoo.
I could, I could put them in.
And it would look cool because I would like it with more, you know what the reason why I think about that is just because I would like it to have more colors.
Yeah, I agree.
Ugh.
I, I, I think I'm sure you're the same way because we're both artists.
But like, to me, it's like weirdly imperative that every PCP member has like color associated.
I was just thinking about that.
And what endlessly frustrates me is that some of us do have like a strong color association and others do not.
I know.
Tom, Tom and Digi are like malleable and I hate that.
To me, it's always, because I, when, when like, like doing like various prototype versions of like PCP design things I want to, it always comes out.
Like, if I go with my gut and just do what, like, I imagine everyone adds, there's always way too many greens and blues.
There's too many, no, there's too many like purples.
Well, there's too many like cool colors.
I guess I can brown that too.
There's too many cool colors.
Yeah.
Because.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah.
Like hippo, like hippo and divu.
And they hippo and divu and they are too close to each other.
Exactly.
Those are the exact three that I was thinking about.
Yeah.
There's that.
Also, like, there's a whole, okay, like you and, all right.
Well, first of all, oh no.
Oh my God.
Lol.
That's fucking epic.
That's so fucking funny.
All the way back.
Okay, whatever.
You, all right, so Tom, I have generally settled on depicting Tom as red.
Yes, I completely did.
Although, okay, you know, Jade's like alignment chart that she did, which is fucking sick and I love it the most.
Pretty good.
But it made Digi red and Tom blue.
And, like, I used to make Tom blue, but I stopped at some point because there were too many blues and because his new icon was red.
And I was like, okay, he doesn't need to be blue anymore.
And, like, frankly, he's only blue because his pony used to be blue.
And that's, like, not relevant.
Well, no, I guess his channel icon was blue for a while, but it's red now and that's what matters.
Plus, like, the Rebel Pixels thing.
Anyway.
Yes.
So Tom, so Tom used to be blue and sometimes he still gets depicted as blue, but generally I think he should be red now.
Which generally leaves me, okay.
So there's this kind of muddy space because I generally make Digi purple, but, like, Mage is purple.
But Mage is kind of like a pinkish purple, but you're pink.
So I kind of settle on, like, a spectrum of, like, you are, like, bright pale fluorescent pink.
Mage is, like, Mage is kind of, like, a pinkish, a slightly pink violet.
Digi is, like, an indigo.
And then, yeah.
But, like, it's crowded.
It's crowded.
It's super crowded.
Because there's not a whole, like, like, only, like, only really Tom and Jesse are, like, warm colors with, like, red and yellow.
And, like, the greens kind of get there, but, like, not enough.
Like, like, we're pretty much, we're really on one side of, like, the color wheel.
We're really on one side.
And, like, it's hard because, like, I think the way to go is to make Digi a magenta.
I think that because his avatar was, like, a magenta.
But she's, like, I'm saying make her, like, a deep purple.
Okay.
I would, but, like, she, like, specifically asked me, like, to make her, like, pinker.
I don't know.
She's really picky about colors.
And she told me that, like, she didn't like the colors of her old OC, which were, like, kind of, like, a more indigo.
And she was, like, this is me now.
And, you know, was, like, you know, used this, like, pinker version with the horns.
You know what?
I think, I think the only thing to do is just to pick a set of, like, nine colors.
And we just have to be, like, conservative and strict.
Like, like, like, like, nine base colors.
We just have to assign them to people.
Um.
Hmm.
Yeah.
You're opening it right now.
Okay.
Let me, let me just, like, eyeball what I think it is.
I think we should start with, like, the things that, like, are obvious.
Okay.
Nate is obviously a nice, vibrant green.
Yeah.
Obvious.
You know, Nate, you, I think, Nate, you could argue.
And, like, a green, green.
Not, like, a yellow green.
Like, like, a green.
You think so?
I think he's kind of, like, a lime green.
Oh, well, yeah.
Like, like, that is perfect.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, like, um, so that's Nate.
Tom.
Is this being recorded, by the way?
What?
Is this being recorded?
Like, like, can they see the screen?
Um.
You know, let me, let me check.
Yes.
Oh, although, wait, hold on.
The color correction is making that green black.
Um.
Let me, hold on.
I'm going to turn the color correction off.
Uh.
Well.
Okay.
This is fucking bullshit.
Um.
Okay.
Window capture, uh, properties.
I'm going to capture, uh, uh, capture getting over it.
Okay.
I'll put that up on top.
There we go.
All right.
So.
Uh, you, you are obviously black or white.
I'm, yeah.
Black or white.
I can see you being either.
Like, I think, I think what we should do is, depending on, like, the saturation and values of the other ones, we decide if you're white or black.
Okay.
So, Tom, I think is maybe a little more on, like, the orange end of red.
Like a blood orange.
Like that, I guess.
Um.
I, I think he needs to be easily identifiable as red because, because, you know, the rebel pixel and he's a communist.
Yeah.
Okay.
Sure.
And then Jesse is just like yellow.
Yellow.
Yeah.
Maybe, maybe a little bit lighter than that.
Like.
There.
Okay.
And you.
Davoo is sky blue.
Davoo is, yeah.
Davoo is like light sky blue.
Yeah.
Yes.
Okay.
There.
And then you are, like, like, maybe a little redder, but like that.
I don't know.
The fact that it's on a white background is kind of, I don't know.
I usually make you like a light pink.
Yeah.
You know.
I, I usually put myself as more of like a harsh magenta-y, but like this, like for the purposes of this.
Yeah.
Like, yeah.
I mean, this is more, I don't know.
I may, I generally make you light to like kind of differentiate you from mage.
Yeah.
That's understandable.
Okay.
So right away I'm seeing the problem that like Tom's, what's the word?
Not saturation.
Value?
Yeah.
Tom's value is like way too high.
I actually, I did kind of lighten his red on the group piss just to even it out.
Yeah.
I'm looking at it right now.
I actually, actually like, I kind of feel like we, like it's not that Tom's is too high.
Because ours is too low possibly.
Uh, yeah.
Maybe.
All right.
Yeah.
I'm, I'm, I'm just black or, I'm black or white depending on whichever one like shows up better.
Okay.
So what do we got?
And then we got hippo, who is?
Yeah.
It's, it's hard.
Something like that.
Like he's always going to look either too much like Davoo or too much like Nate.
Yeah.
Like what you have there is like the best you can do.
And like his logo is blue.
Yeah.
It's, you know, this is the color, like this, this color is kind of just like grandfathered
in because it was his pony's color.
Kind of like Tom and like the reason I used to depict him as blue.
Um, but like it's not like this is like still his iconography.
Like I think it is his favorite color.
But other than that, it's not like relevant.
You know, I
I
It was still to look a lot like Davoo.
Okay.
Try and do a little bit darker of a blue, but like keep, like keep it like still like
a light blue, but just of a more like, like, like farther on the color wheel.
Like further into the blue.
Yeah.
I don't know if that's really any better.
Okay.
I'm just going to leave it as that and come back to it.
So mage is like this.
Yeah.
And then generally for Digi, I do like this.
I could go a little blue.
I feel like I feel like Digi is the problem.
Digi is a problem for this exercise.
I feel like Digi has like it's it's a real fucking problem, but it's undeniable that
due to recent events, he totally is like a magenta guy now.
What do you mean due to recent events?
Due to the fact that like there was the whole meme like magenta filter over the blog and
like his, his like icon is totally magenta now in retaliation.
His icon.
That was a huge, huge, whole big.
I made his old icon and his old icon actually was it had like the magenta line work.
I'm like the yellow background.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, mage is magenta.
What if I am changed to something else?
I don't know what I got.
Yeah.
Maybe I'm like, I'm not comfortable doing that.
I just got to say I'm very, it makes me very happy that I'm the black and white guy.
Yeah.
I love, I love, I love that in any array of colors, I am either black or white.
That's like so cool and I'm just so gratified by it.
It's, it's really sorry now mage.
Okay.
It's, it's all three of the guys at the end, the problem.
I, I, well, okay.
Tom's value is bugging me, but other than that, it's fine.
Also, let me, your, your pink is not doing anything for me.
It's like,
I think it's too flaccid.
Yeah.
That's what she said.
Well, of course.
I didn't even feel the need to say that because of course she would say that.
Yeah.
I like that more.
These are like, I feel like these are like dull.
Like I'm using like fully saturated colors, but they feel, they feel dull to me.
Here, here, I'm going to do it.
I'm going to fucking do it.
But we can't see you.
That's true.
Here.
Um, here, here.
Well, I'll just like open up paint and then I will tell you what I, what I'm thinking
about because, because I want to like, okay, here's, here's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to like get like, I really feel like the only way to do this is to just be
cruel and give people colors that like aren't perfectly them.
Like, like, like, like we have to like figure out.
We have to get the rainbow and then assign colors based first, like, like who identifies
with the colors the strongest and the people who don't identify with like a color that strongly
will just have to take the hit.
I don't know.
Like Burgers.
Like some of the problem, like, I mean, this whole problem has arisen because there are
some pretty strong color associations for some of like the, like for some, for some of
the very close together guys, like Hippo and Nate are like pretty strongly in their color
aspect.
But like, what do we do about that?
Like, I don't feel comfortable changing either of them.
What, what have you made?
I really like Nate's.
Nate's I feel is.
This actually looks really good.
So suddenly I like this a lot more.
Are you, are you seeing this?
I don't like, I'm seeing it.
I don't like it.
Digi's.
I don't like Digi's.
I feel like, okay, I don't like Digi's and I feel like the contrast between Nate, Hippo
and Davos is not strong enough.
But otherwise I do like it.
I could make.
Hmm.
Okay.
Well here, I'm going to make like, I'm going to make like a secondary like set that like
nudges the values a little bit.
All right.
I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to make one as well.
Okay.
I'm going to, okay.
Nate has to be like a vibrant, a vibrant green, a vibrant like lime green.
He has to look, he has to look like how Sprite tastes.
Yeah.
He's got to be that gamer Mountain Dew.
Okay.
This is, this is highly experimental.
Yeah.
We just have to like start out with like what we know people are like, we know Jesse is
yellow.
We know Nate is lime green.
I did that by the way.
I made him lime green.
I know.
Well that's that because you drew his banner.
Yeah.
I feel like you should lower some of the values for these to differentiate them.
You mean make them possibly make them lighter or darker?
No, darker.
Yeah.
But I don't know on which, because try with hippos, though it might be a little bit.
No, when I say, when I say lower the value, I mean like a, like, like move the like point
downward, like, like, like in the box.
Yeah.
I know.
On hippos?
It runs the risk of dulling it, but all right.
I like that for DeVoo.
I like, okay, okay.
That for DeVoo is nice because it still is like a light blue.
Yeah.
But like, it differentiates them from hippo more.
Okay.
So hippos, I don't think, I think that's worse.
Maybe we should give them like a terezi, like a lighter terezi teal.
I don't dislike that.
I don't think I like it.
No, I feel like going darker is not.
Try making it a little bit more blue, just a smidge.
But still lighter.
That's fine.
Just try that right now.
They're like is pretty terezi.
Yeah.
Maybe this could stand to be just a little, actually this might work.
Try making them go lighter.
I did.
Because both DeVoo and Nate are like vibrant.
Try making Nate a little bit more green and more saturated.
Nate is as saturated as he could possibly be.
Oh, he totally is.
I mean, I made him a little, I made Nate a little yellower to kind of like make room for hippo.
Oh, okay.
This is good.
You know, making hippo lighter there actually, it makes sense and it works and it kind of.
Maybe his hippo is like a quieter boy, so he shouldn't be as vibrant slash loud as you know, Nate.
Maybe.
Yeah, he's a little, it's a mellow color.
I feel like me and Mage are like fine.
Like all these can be twerked.
They can be twerked.
Yeah.
All these like will be, like these will not be like the final, you know, rule from now on.
But like, these are a good starting point.
Like, like, like, like, like that's, that's fine for Mage and that's fine for me.
But Digi.
I really don't like Digi.
It's um, no.
In general.
I've never, I've never been happy with Digi's color designation.
He doesn't really have a strong one.
It's magenta, dude.
I don't like it.
Oh, I'm too purple in that.
Too purple?
I think you're too light.
Yeah, too light too.
There we go.
You like that?
I was thinking maybe a little lighter.
I think Mage is too dark.
That's fine.
Too intense.
Like, look at the contrast between you and Mage and value right there.
I do.
Okay.
I know Mage wants to be perceived as like, like, like, you know, a little bit more pastel.
But like, isn't her whole thing that she's like a demon?
Like, when dark makes sense?
I, I don't even know anymore.
I don't know what Mage's the deal is.
Um, okay.
You know, I actually kind of like, I mean, I think she, I think that works.
And I think that's like a pretty decent like distance.
I actually like that better.
Okay.
I think it works better with the whole.
Let's give Digi a really, put Digi in between me and Tom and make him really vibrant is,
is what I would.
In between you and Tom?
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Well,
Uh, wait, where did I, I guess I'll just stay on the end here.
Between you and Tom.
Uh, all right.
So that would be like, that way you can be magenta.
Like that.
Yeah.
Although I don't know if that's, I feel like that's in the right direction.
Okay.
So like Digi is like a bright, like chart, not chartreuse.
Yeah.
Okay.
You know, it kind of like a, like a bright magenta color like that.
Yeah.
Like that.
I mean, that's pretty close to you though.
I feel, I feel like go back to what he was before.
Like this.
Maybe a little bit lighter, but like, yeah, something like that.
Yeah.
That way you cannot mistake him for me.
I don't know.
You're both still like, you're both still like definitively pink.
You know, and that bugs me.
Well, then again, I mean, the only way to fit him in here would be to have like, the only
way to fit him in as like a distinct color word would be like here he was indigo, which
is fine.
And then like, it could maybe, it could make him orange, but like, no.
No.
This is around the color that, that he was in your avatar for him.
It's kind of, he was a little purple, purple.
That's way too close to you.
Yeah.
I'm going to, I'm going to fuck with you.
Okay.
I'm going to make you, well, if you're more like that.
I'm getting close to Mage there.
Yeah.
Well, maybe Mage can be a little bluer.
Will she like that?
That's like barely even a perceptible difference.
Whatever you say.
She sees all.
Yeah, maybe.
I don't, your pink just seems so dull to me.
Well, it's because you're basing off the Kirby shirt, which is dull.
No, no, it's not that.
It's that I'm like fully saturated pink.
And yeah, I know I'm making it light, but like, it just feels dull.
It just feels, I don't know, I don't know how to make it brighter.
No.
No, I feel, moving it closer to the white is the problem.
I think you have to move, make it more to the right there.
A little lighter.
Like that.
Okay.
And then.
That's personally where I would identify myself.
Okay.
Well, that works.
Around there.
I'm going to make Tom a little yellower.
You run the risk of losing that like red.
Yeah, he's definitely definitively like orange now.
Yeah.
Because saturation is a problem for me.
This is like, okay, this is actually not, I'm not making it any more yellow.
I'm just lightening it a little bit.
I'll actually make it a little more red, but a little lighter too.
Yeah.
I would make him red.
Like red.
That is like solidly red.
Just lighten slightly.
Then, okay, between you and him.
Okay, there is some wiggle room there.
I feel like what we had before for Digi was like peak Digi.
Like that was good.
I like that, but now he feels too close to Tom.
I can make him a little pinker.
I mean, that's like magenta.
I mean, would you describe that as a magenta?
I would describe that as hot pink.
Oh, god damn it.
Mother fuck.
What the fuck?
This is killing me.
Try to lower the value of that.
Try to make it a little bit darker.
Darker, huh?
Should I keep it fully saturated?
Around there.
You know, I don't hate that.
I don't hate that one bit.
Although now he's the only one who's not like as bright as can be.
Well, unless you count me.
Well, I don't think they should all be as bright as they could be in any case.
I don't know.
You know, that is distinct, but it's a little weird.
Okay, it depends on how we want to calculate the style guide.
Do we want this to be like every person has like a clear base color
and then from that base color color them like as you see fit
like around the general idea of each color.
You know what I'm saying?
Like do we just want to have them be as bright as they can be?
So it's just easily identifiable like, okay, it is this color.
So you can make it a little bit darker for shading.
I mean, that makes sense to me.
Yeah.
So that is that like, if you don't want to just have your like shading just be the color but black,
which is terrible and bad and you shouldn't do that,
then a lot of these will like kind of blend into one another.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, of course.
Like this is like a baseline.
Yeah.
Hmm.
I...
Okay, like what?
I mean, is Digi...
I mean, Digi is now like kind of a maroon.
Hmm.
I think that like design wise,
these are just...
He's really close to Tom.
God fuck.
I'm gonna make him a little purplier.
I feel like we're hot.
I feel like this is...
When you tinker with it, I feel like this is around the color that Digi should be.
Yeah.
I don't...
I feel like Tom is too orange.
Well, I made Tom a little orangeer because if he...
If Tom is like red red,
then there's just...
Then that's crowding in on the Digi space.
All right, here.
I'll make him...
All right, I'll just fucking fully saturate him.
What the fuck is this shit?
Okay.
Hmm.
Hold on.
You know, maybe I'll feel better about this if I just like...
That.
I feel better about this already.
Yeah.
You know, yeah.
I do like this.
Let me see.
Now for me.
You know what?
You are the one that stands out as like the most weird.
Try using my color from the top one.
First, I'm going to try making you a little bit like pink-purple-er.
That's better.
Okay, that's more distinctive.
That was more munchy.
Hmm.
Maybe not.
I don't disagree that we have to work what we're given, though.
And we do kind of have to smudge a lot of this to fit in line with what we're given.
This one from the top is a little too red for me.
Yeah.
But this one is a little too purple.
God, no.
Could you try lowering the value of and darkening Tom?
Darkening Tom, okay.
Just so that he's a little different from Digi.
That could be worse, though.
Hmm.
Eh.
Not crazy, though.
Not me either.
Also, he would be, yeah.
Something that would, it would bother me about that is that he would be the only one who's not fully saturated.
Like the idea that one of them is dulled when the others aren't like bugs me.
Yeah.
You know what?
You and Tom are both known for black and white comics.
What if, like, you are black and he's white or something?
That's not bad.
The only thing is, though, that like red, like red is like a color that is like calling out to be filled.
And like, I don't think Digi should be red.
But someone has to, and I think Tom is a solid choice for it.
I do, I agree.
I mean, he's the record pixel.
Yeah.
Although, I mean, well, okay.
I don't think one can be white and one can be black because like one doesn't necessarily always work when the other would.
Mm-hmm.
Well, okay.
Think about it like this.
We have Jesse's yellow, which is like a nice, proper yellow.
But like, what if we had like a nice, like, brown, like, piss yellow?
Like a real like piss yellow.
Gross.
A yellow that just like-
Yeah, like the color of piss, like really dark brown and like a little bloody.
Yeah, yeah, like a little bloody.
You can see some spots in there, you know.
Some molds.
You look really close.
You can see yourself squirm around in it, you know, stuff like that.
It just like, it just screams urine at you.
That's what I'm thinking about right now.
Interesting.
I like where your head's at.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, tell you what, I'm gonna save this.
I wanna get back to Bennett Foddy for a little bit.
What do you think?
I think it's pretty good.
I think we can sleep on this.
Viewer's way in.
What do you think?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, this is a viewer show.
Yeah.
Alright, well that was interesting.
See, I think a lot, I think a lot about color identities of us.
I do too.
Then I have to be right back.
There's just piss like all over my desk.
Like unbelievable.
Alright, well you go-
All over.
And then I have to pee also.
So you go and then I will, when you come back, I also want a pee break.
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Interchain the mom gone.
No.
I can't fucking do that.
I need to-
Alright, I fucked with my-
I fucked with my OBS settings to get rid of the green screen effect,
which, come to think of it, is totally pointless and unnecessary,
and I don't even know why the green screen effect was on.
And now I really hope that it hasn't been like green screening out the leaves or something.
No, of course not.
I also hope that the in-game sound effects have not been drowning out our voices,
which is highly possible because I have the in-game sounds playing on a different device,
but I cannot hear at the moment,
because, well, for reasons.
Actually setting up the audio and video for this stream took like an hour and a half for some reason.
For no benefit.
Here we go.
Devil's chimney.
Yes.
Oh my god, that was-
I'm impressed with myself.
I am impressed with myself,
which is what this game is all about,
just feeling like you're way cooler than everyone else.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
First try.
Oh, how am I so powerful?
Watching this game, it looks really easy.
You watch it and you want to be like,
dude, just swing your hammer this way and then you'll fucking grab the thing
and it'll throw you right up,
but actually moving the hammer is way more cumbersome than it looks.
I'm back with the towel to wipe up all of the pits.
Good.
We got to start pissing slime.
We got to get in the spirit of things and start pissing slime.
Can you imagine your bodily waste being currency?
Because that's what I'm imagining.
Dude, that just gave me an idea.
What if one of the rooms in the discords was like the bathroom
and you could just go in there and piss
and it would like do something to your slime or something?
I don't know.
To your slime.
Yeah, like you would get slime from it
or you would lose slime or like something,
you know, like if just like peeing was like an important strategic decision.
Yeah.
Workshop that.
It could be like, you know, replace the dojo with the bathroom.
So instead of sparring to get slime, you piss on people
and it makes them angry.
And there's no other...
It just makes them angry.
Yeah, nobody gains.
Nobody wins.
Ah, shit.
Hey, I have to go pee.
I'll be right back.
Yeah, yeah.
Hello viewers.
I just would like to take a moment here to say that when I piss on YouTube,
when I piss on this show, always, without fail,
I am caught off guard with how much piss I have in my fucking body.
It's like astounding.
It's astounding to me because I was just doing a funny joke.
I was just comparing the color yellow to piss.
I was pissing away.
I was hearing it at the screen so I could make sure that my audio was fine.
And I looked back down and what do I see?
But piss all over my desk, the large Japotli cup that I was pissing into
completely filled up, overflowing with piss.
And so I had to stop, get a new cup, a Starbucks vente,
and fill that up halfway before I could clean up the piss on my desk.
So I'm currently...
And because I don't have like a towel near me,
I just got a small washcloth.
That's just clogged up the piss now.
So now I have to use one of my shirts to clean up this piss.
So right now I'm just scrubbing my desk with a shirt to clean up all of the piss here.
That's just what my life is like.
And I think we can all agree that this has been swallowed.
This has fucking been swallowed.
It's all the fucking killers.
It's conspiracy against me to make my life a living fucking hell
because they just can't deal with my unadulterated swagger
and persuasion of beautiful women to my arm.
They just can't deal with how much of a fucking player and Casanova I am.
They just have to manufacture scenarios where my piss backfires.
And my room is quite literally flooded with piss.
I think we can all agree that Ben is a fucking conniving, backstabbing, fucking street urchin.
And that his crimes against piss will not go unpunished.
I think that his transgressions are too numerous and too true to be disproven or proven faulty.
And I think it's only a matter of time before he's convicted at a court of slime to be 100% a faggot.
And I think that's just, I think that's what we all have to understand.
And so we all have to come to grips with and that's what we all have to appreciate about Ben.
I appreciate about my co-host Ben St.
He's a villain and a killer and a sociopath and a fucking bad person.
And he hates pee and he hates all forms of urine.
And he's out to get me and he's out to ruin my life.
Much like I will ruin his life when I pull a bullet through his fucking skull.
So I'm taking this moment right now while he's gone to make grandiose claims and incentivize violence against him.
So please, so please, before he comes back and has something to say on the matter, please, if you're a rowdy, this is my personal request.
Kill a killer right now. Go to the chat, go to gang violence, go to the combat zone and strike down a killer right now.
And say something along the lines of die, you prudish fuck, urine is natural.
Say something into the fact that urine is God's gift to man.
And we were made in God's image, so therefore God pisses.
And it's the only truth that we have is pee.
And you must acknowledge that when you claim life of another discord user.
So that's all I want to say on that end of the conversation is that fuck you, Ben.
You made my pee go everywhere.
And also I'm going to kill you and all of your friends and your family, or is it going to be gone?
That was me drinking piss, by the way, in case you couldn't tell.
Let me go over my notes. It's been taking a real long time to pee.
And as I'm sure you all know, I cannot carry a show. I can't even co-host a show.
I'm dead weight here, I don't know if you've got killers. And you all know it.
And you're just waiting to be betrayed me. You're just all waiting to be betrayed me.
I'm waiting to betray you.
You're all cultural vultures and you're all going to betray me in a moment's notice. Thank God you're back.
I'm back. One second.
There we go.
Excellent, thank you.
Let's see here. What were we talking about? We're talking about colors, we're talking about fucking real food initiative, we're talking about fucking...
Oh hey, there's like, obviously the actual real food initiative is long defunct and like not used.
And like, you know, outdated and old fashioned and clearly behind the times.
However, there's like a new like, pseudo real food initiative that we all keep forgetting about.
Oh, the draw boys, yeah. I haven't been working on comics lately, so I haven't had anything to post there.
But I really love that it is there and around and just for draw boys.
I realize that just for draw boys, we are like, we need to like better communicate with one another.
Because we are clearly the best artists, like just in all categories. We are clearly the best people in the PC.
You and me?
Like, there's no doubt about it. Well, no, all the draw boys.
Yeah, I mean, the draw cast is like the best PCP content. Well, I don't know. It's good. It's good and I like it a lot.
The best regular PCP content.
Yeah.
The best like on a schedule.
Also like the least popular.
It is at least pop. I thought people liked it.
Well, people do like it, but it doesn't get the views that like, it gets less views than the regular podcast for some baffling reason.
Well, fuck off.
Probably a problem marketing.
You know what I want?
Yes, I want. I think I talk to you about this briefly. And you know, this is like behind the scenes things.
Inside baseball.
Inside baseball. Real shit, real shit.
I want to like turn art apologies into like a real show.
When I got to Radcom 3 and you told me about art apologies, I was really excited about it.
I hate the game.
And I wanted to be a part of it somehow.
I totally want to like turn art apologies into like.
Actually, I haven't listened to it yet. I started it up and I didn't get very far through it.
And then I paused it and then like the tab got closed and I forgot.
So I haven't actually heard all of it.
Oh, it's good, dude. It's good. How far did you get?
Not very far.
What were we talking about?
Um.
Okay. Probably just interaction.
Yeah.
I want to like turn it into like, into like, I don't know.
I don't know.
A bi-weekly or whatever. I don't fucking know.
Um, show. We're like, all the drawboys get together and we complain and whine about art things.
I want that.
You know, they're talking about art.
I mean, I used to really love just like listening to people talk about art.
So yeah, that sounds like a show that I would watch.
For various purposes, I've been rewatching old PCP and horse cast episodes.
And one major thing of modern PCP.
And one of my notes is to get into the weeds of modern PCP since I've been on my mind lately.
But one of the trappings is that we don't like talk about our work ever.
And like that was like a major thing early on.
Yeah.
Was that we were talking, we were all like grungy internet content creators.
And we all like bitched about work and you know, et cetera, et cetera.
Well.
And you know, gone to the weeds of what we did.
That was important.
I got annoyed with it because it was a lot of YouTube talk that I was not interested in.
But it's all art.
Yeah.
So like if we did that, but it was just the draw boys, I would be way into it.
Hold on.
I'm going to take off my shirt real quick.
Good.
Okay.
Come on.
I feel like it's been, it's been a while since I did this.
So I'm like, I have no confidence.
Oh shit.
Oh, you're back here.
Oh God, we're playing a game.
Oh gross.
I know.
Sad.
Pitiful.
Yeah.
So like imagine, imagine like a show where it's like, you know, it comes out whenever and
it's like an hour to two hours of like the art boys.
Like, so Ben, like what are you going to apologize for?
Like what have you done wrong in your art?
And you'd be like, I haven't fucking done this or something or like it's too hard to
whatever.
And then we can all talk about how either you're gay for not doing something or like,
yeah, totes dude, I know that feel bro.
And it'll be circle jerky as hell and super clicky and like whiny and bitchy and great.
I like being clicky.
I do too.
It's, it's, that's what this whole thing was about.
Ah, that's what separates us from the animals.
I summon up remembrance of things past.
The fact that we need divisions, not for any practical purpose, but to feel powerful.
I would be down to have our apologies.
I want that.
Be regular.
Yeah.
And like a real thing.
Wouldn't mean you got together.
And like, like I had the idea for like the PCP drawcast iron chef show.
Yeah.
But like, wouldn't mean you got together and like really brain store.
Patience is the foundation of eternal peace.
Well, make anger you're in.
Anyway.
Harm comes to those who know.
And brought 10 patients and draw to life.
It was magical.
It was really magical.
It was.
It was falling short of your own goals.
And like we were, we were doing it fast and it was easy and it was breezy and it was beautiful.
It was covered girl.
I went and I watched some, some, some, what's the, some strip search.
Strips search.
Yeah.
To try and like inspire myself on like how I want.
Ah.
And like how I want 10 paces and draw to look and the, there's just not enough B roll.
There's not enough fucking B roll.
It's cutting back and forth between like two shots the whole time.
But there's nothing for it.
If I may add my input, I've not seen strip search.
Okay.
But from what I saw of the, of what you said, it was great.
But I feel like it wasn't silly enough.
And I feel like the PCP like, I don't think, again, okay.
I feel there's an important distinction here between jokes and memes.
And people will confuse them and it makes me extremely upset when they do.
Because in mind, there's a clear division between memes and jokes.
Where I hate memes, but I like jokes.
This part is like actually pretty difficult and like easy to fuck up.
This, this part's not easy, even though it's like the first thing.
But I kind of have a system.
You were saying jokes versus memes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're like, like, I feel like, I feel like it should be,
Ten Pays and Drugs should be like a little silly.
It felt like it was, it was like pretty like played straight.
Which, which like, I can't look at Digi and not laugh.
Yeah.
Okay.
I feel it.
But I don't know how to make it silly with what we've got.
Like the.
Yeah.
Like, like, like in the footage, we kind of take it too seriously.
Which was kind of a point.
It was kind of the point.
I feel like, okay, I feel like I'm glad that it is the way that it is.
Because it's the pilot and it's like the proof of concept.
And like, here's what it looks like guys.
Yeah.
Check it out.
I feel like Next Radcom, when we make like episode like one or two or whatever.
And like, and like, we know what we're doing.
We know the structure.
We know what's having to turn out.
And we can turn on that, that like classic PCP improv, you know, fluidity and dynamicism
that we're known for.
I feel like that will be where the show really comes to life into its own.
Because we don't really need, like, like we don't need or want or should be a super
like serious game show.
It should be like, in my mind, the ideal for 10 pieces and draw.
Should we like explain what that is?
Because I feel like we keep mentioning it by name, but I don't know if anyone knows what it is.
Yeah.
You can explain.
I got to go do something real quick.
I'll be back in like two minutes.
Okay.
Gin Paces and Draw is, as I described, it was originally supposed to be like a draw cast
iron shaft type game show where it would take the draw boys, then you would have them
like you would unveil the topic for them and basically do like a mini draw cast and whoever
was deemed shit from that, like mini draw cast would be eliminated until there was only
one person left staying.
So there would be like three or four rounds.
And there would be judges and you know, it would be like iron shaft, but for art and draw
games.
Gay.
And so we did that.
It was great.
We came up with, you know, we came up with a lot of like, like neat shit about how like,
like, like the artist, like, like, like, like the, uh, the fucking the artist, like before
each round, it would take 10 paces, like, like it was a Western and then, and then draw
basically, you know, illustration draw.
We're fucking geniuses.
Uh, and it was really, it was really cute idea.
It was really nice.
It was really clean.
It was really great and fantastic.
The, uh, I mean, should I explain what iron shaft iron shaft is?
That is like, I guess I'll explain.
Ten paces and draw is like, you get, we got all the draw boys.
They're all lined up.
The judges explain what the show is, which is what I'm doing right now.
They do 10 paces, then they rush, you know, the judges unveil what the theme of the round
is.
So for the first round, it was like enlightenment.
I think it was.
I think it was enlightenment.
Uh, and so all the artists would have to come up with like enlightenment.
They would have come up with an illustration that matched the theme and then they would
all turn in their illustrations to the judges and they'd be like, I like this drawing because
it captures, it captures, um, fucking enlightenment in this way.
They, like, like the artists would have to like, the artists would explain the drawn,
like first the judges would judge it with like no context, like just based on their
own interpretation and then like the artists would have like, you know, a chance to say
something about it and explain what they were trying to do.
Uh, yeah.
So, you know, it's a bunch of art talk and shit.
I, I really, like, like the concept itself, I think is fucking like, mwah, like beautiful,
like absolutely beautiful.
Here's what I think would make it better is if like there were more, um, like, I think
the, I think the artists need more time to work so that like what they end up making
is better and like more discussable.
I think, okay, I agree, more time and I think there's no real reason for them to have pins
and not pencils to the erasers.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, more tools and more time.
Like, like because, okay, if we were doing like a challenge, like speedrun type show
where it's like make the best thing in this like small amount of time, like go, like
like balls, you know, fucking hard as nails do it, then pins would make sense.
But like we're trying to make a show where it's like you have a time slot but you're
trying to make like the best drawing that you can and the time slot is just there so
that you stay on track.
Yeah.
So like by erasing, you're going to be wasting time.
You're decentralized to do it anyway.
So like why not just allow you to do your art better?
Yeah.
And I just, I think having like more fully realized pieces in the end just makes...
I mean, that's what it should be.
Also, this is of no fault of Nate and Digi though we need our, we need judges who are
like our artists.
Yeah, yeah, we do.
I mean, they did fine but...
Yeah, they did fine.
Yeah, we, at least one judge needs to be like, you know, an artist.
I think ideally we would have like three judges, two of which are artists and one of
which is like a lay person, like Nate or Digi.
The problem is just that we aren't like, we're kind of, you know, we have to work within
the confines of the PCP.
Yeah.
I mean, at this point in time at least.
Although I thought that, yeah, if, if the show continued like at say PCP HQ, if that
ever materializes, I thought we could have like guest artists on as like competitors,
you know.
Oh, totally.
That's totally the dream.
Oh, like imagine if the PCP were the judges and like we had like guest artists as contestants.
That would be dope.
Okay, here's my absolute dream.
In PCP HQ Boston, I want Timbases to draw to be like a regular thing and what we do is
we get underground indie Boston artists to be on our show so we can promote them and
get young blood and pump life into ourselves and signal boost and promote upcoming...
That is a beautiful, beautiful dream.
Yeah.
And I want...
That's what I want to do.
I know.
Dude, okay.
Timbases and Draw is one of those rare projects that like I'm just so fucking into.
I'm just so into it.
And like I'm so upset that like we really don't have the necessary tools to make it as great
as it should be.
Yeah, no we don't.
But it could be great.
It could, it could be fantastic.
I'm so into the idea.
And I'm dedicated.
Next time we will do another Timbases and Draw.
And it will probably be better because we'll have finalized...
We'll like have...
Oh, oh God.
Okay, okay.
Guys, when it comes out, please critique it.
Please God critique it and tell us what we can do.
Tell us how to make it better and what it needs.
Or like what it...
Like suggest things that like it could take inspiration from or like be more like, you know?
I think to keep in mind, like what I want the show to be is I want it to be...
As I want it to be artists, trying their all, making good art, and then like...
And like, you know, like have it be like a silly fun show, but the end of the day you come there
because you like the artists and you want to see them do art stuff.
Yes, yes.
So like, so like...
Like art first, comedy second, but comedy like close behind, like I don't want this to be like a...
Like I feel like it took itself too seriously.
Yeah, no, no.
But it should be about the art.
It should be fun.
Yeah.
It shouldn't be silly.
It should be a fun, art-centric romp.
I feel, I...
And the point of that was to veer it off, which is fine because I loved him based in Draw.
But like, would mean you got to do that.
That was great.
And I feel like, I mean, I would like to do something similar for our apologies.
Where like, I don't know, if me and you want to do it, it will be done.
Yeah, yeah.
Because we have the power.
We do have the power.
We have immense power.
Two is enough to rock the bow on the PCP.
When you're one guy, it's hard to organize things, but if you've got two people, then shit gets fucking dead.
Yes, yes.
Historically true.
So, I feel like, I feel like I want to workshop the idea, because I do like our apologies.
And I want there to be, I desperately want there to be a like, a podcast or show for the art voice to discuss their work.
Like, okay.
Like, we have the draw cast, but like, it's not really suited for like, in-depth conversation about the art.
Because like, we're trying to draw, you know?
Yeah.
What if we like...
Yes.
Okay, I don't...
Oh, fuck yeah.
Finally.
Okay, I don't know about this.
But like, what if, this would take way more work.
But like, what if we like, did the drawings and then like, did commentary over them?
Because there's always...
Are you talking about for the draw cast?
Yeah.
Oh, like, like the way we do the races?
Because the problem with the draw cast is always that there are periods of silence, because we're always like, trying to work hard.
And like, it's hard to multitax, being funny and entertaining and also draw them.
It is.
That's why, you know, Stripsurge was really great, because the artists they would be sitting and drawing, they would have like, 45 minutes or an hour.
And I think they had like, an hour and a half to make a comic strip.
And there would be just like, a bunch of cameras.
And like, you know, periodically through the process, Gabe and Tycho would like, kind of like, comment on them.
Or like, try and fuck with them.
Or like, just, you know, crack jokes or whatever.
And so it's whole like, hour long process was like, condensed into like, you know, maybe like, 5 or 10 minutes of, you know, footage of them actually drawing.
And, but there was like, breathing room, you know, and there were like funny moments that could be like, captured from it.
But it wasn't like they were that pressured to be funny.
Yeah, I agree.
Well, I think the thing to remember is that we are comedians.
Yeah.
Like, that's just who we are.
So like, even, I don't know if you feel the same way, but like, I feel like even in serious situations, it's hard to be 100% serious.
Just that's just the kind of guy that I am.
I like to make jokes.
Yeah.
Like, no matter what, even if it's not the goal, I think that it will be funny.
Yeah, we, yeah, like, we can't not be funny, at least a little bit.
It kind of sounds egotistical.
What I mean is we can't not make jokes, whether or not they land.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, like, that's just going to come out organically.
You know, our resplendent personalities will always shine through to the delight of all.
By the way, oh god.
Fuck.
Well, okay, I was going to say a spoiler.
I was going to say a spoiler, but I'll just phrase it like this.
I'm really, it's, it's, it's complete, like, dramatic, hilarious irony.
The way that, like, the first two rounds ended after all that was said.
Yes, and I'm glad.
I'm glad that it went that way.
It's really fucking funny.
I'm so glad.
I was not expecting it because I'm a genius.
And wait, I'll strike that part.
Let's go in it.
Oh fuck.
But, but, but I'm glad that it happened the way it did.
I am, too.
Yes, yes, yes, oh god.
Oh, what the fuck?
Oh, what, what, what?
You were just so, you were so fucked out.
Did you fucking see that?
I saw that, I saw that.
Okay.
You know what?
I think I can recover.
Yes, yes.
Did you fuck that?
Oh god, that was choice.
Oh.
Oh, who, who, who, who, yeah.
Yeah.
Stream games.
This is the greatest game ever.
Ever since Radcon, I've been bursting with creative, like, flow.
Like, more so.
I, I, I told, I told this, I, like, I think it was a common knowledge.
Where I, where I, I felt like I've been in a real, like, creative and, like, energy slump
for, like, the past couple months.
But, like, I really feel, like, super reinvigorated and with, like, a whole new passion
for being alive and being an artist on the internet and doing things.
And it feels really good.
In one sense, I feel that way, but, like, it hasn't, it hasn't, it hasn't turned into
comics, which makes me sad every day.
Well, it hasn't turned into comics for me yet, either.
But it's turned into, like, like, oh, okay.
I am going to suck my own dick super hard real quick for a little bit.
Please.
Because I have released two, like, like a couple videos that, like, I'm actually proud
of.
And, like, I've never, like, really been proud of, like, videos I've done.
But, like, the two vlogs are, like, super, okay, okay.
The last one.
The one I want to focus on.
Feeling Closer to the Dead.
Have you seen the video Feeling Closer to the Dead?
No.
It is, it was originally just a straight up vlog that me and Digi recorded, where we
talk about the two-critic Y2K Skype call specifically, where he's calling out for
being a pedophile and a Skype call.
I want to talk about how I like Skype call conversations.
I have not heard that call, by the way.
Oh, it's legendary.
It's absolutely legendary.
I didn't know there was this Skype call.
Also, how the fuck am I supposed to handle this?
You're fucked.
There's no other way.
And, eventually, we start talking about how I like morbid content that's, like, scary
and stuff.
Oh.
This part sucks, Dick.
I know.
Okay.
Right.
Morbid content.
Yeah, that is morbid.
That is some morbid shit.
Yeah.
And, okay, and so, I take that.
And, here's what I do.
I get someone at 3 AM to call me on Skype.
And, like, the start of the video is, like, me browsing pimple popping on YouTube.
Yeah.
And, then, I get a Skype call.
And, then, I answer the Skype call.
And, then, the person, the fan, his name is, like, centerpoint.
He's in the...
Oh, yeah, centerpoint.
Yeah.
Shout out.
He starts screen sharing.
And, then, I edit out his screen.
And, I put in the vlog.
And, the vlog is, like, edited, like, fully.
So, it takes place.
Like, the vlog takes place within a Skype...
MAH!
Oh.
Okay.
Not the worst thing ever.
But, they're pretty bad.
It takes place within a Skype call.
And, then, towards the end, once I reach my point of I like to feel closer to death, I
turn it into, like, a Slender Man ARG.
Where, like, I splice in some, like, footage that we recorded earlier about me finding a
Slender Man, like, symbol in the place where we had recorded the vlog.
Which, like, happened.
And, then, and then, like, I edit it in, like, like, like, some, like, some, like, images
of Digi to make it look scary.
And, it ties into the whole theme of, like, morbid content and shit and feeling closer
to death.
And, then, the video ends with, like, the Skype call that the entire vlog is taking
place in.
In being.
And, like, that's it.
And, it's fucking cool as hell.
And, I'm really happy with it.
Um, interesting.
And, I would have never, like, had the gumption or, like, passion to do such a thing.
If it weren't for Radcon 3, they got me super fucking hyped for being a creative and doing
this again and kicking ass and taking names and doing shit.
And, it was nice.
And, thank you, Radcon 3.
Thank you, Radcon 3.
So, the best video you've ever done?
Probably.
Um, why didn't I do more just like it?
It didn't even take that long.
But, it was sick.
Okay.
Here we go.
Yeah, right, just hand over fist.
Yeah.
Double it's weight in gold that video was.
Probably made like, 20 bucks tops.
Oh, yeah.
No, God.
Oh, you're so fucked, dude.
One of the main things is helped me achieve Godlike creative status.
Yes.
It's like, once I got home from Radcon, like, like, I obviously, I just naturally made
like a to-do list.
Like, you know, there's the stuff that I have.
It's, let's crank out this red content.
And having a to-do list is so fucking satisfying and good and incentivizing to like, get things
done.
Yeah.
It feels so good to wake up, check your checklist, like, like, check your to-do list and be like,
all right, today I'm going to work on this project.
And then you work on that project and then it's done at the end of the day and then you
can delete it from the to-do list and like, you've accomplished something.
Like, you have accomplished something in a Google doc and you are now closer to God than
you will ever be unless you do the same thing again tomorrow, which I did for like a couple
of days and it was great.
Oh my God.
Oh God, no.
Fuck!
Ah!
Oh!
Whoo!
Okay.
Saved.
All right.
I need to fucking wipe my ha- Ah!
I need to fucking wipe my hands off.
Because they're sweaty.
Mom's spaghetti.
Your teeth are on the edge, dude.
I was wrong.
The Devil's Chimney ain't shit.
This is the worst part in the whole game.
This is my, this is my, this is my Sophie's choice.
Uh, um, uh, creativity.
Um, I've got, God, I just...
You know, okay, so the thing about like the Radcom videos, I feel like the creative energy
there was already spent and the idea of just like editing them and like getting them ready
for release and then releasing them just makes me tired.
Cause like, I already did it, you know?
Feels like release, releasing them just kind of feels like a formality, at least in like
an emotional sort of way.
I understand what you mean, but I don't feel the same way.
Because most of my, I don't know, because because when, when like I did our apologies,
I didn't like feel like I had done it.
I only felt like I had done it when it was released.
And like in order for it to get released, I had to edit it very slightly.
But, uh, I just feel like, like, like, I think it helps that most of my, most of my stuff
that I got down at like at Radcon was like components of things that like I need to work on still.
Yeah.
Like I'm working, I haven't like stopped working on that thing with Hippo.
Oh, that's, oh my God, that thing with Hippo. I had forgotten about that.
I know.
Oh, oh, oh, I have not. That's been on my to-do list.
And I actually have, oh, I don't know how to describe this in terms.
Part of it is done.
Okay.
A big part?
Part of it is done.
Uh, one, like, like, like three of the components of this project is done on my end.
Okay. How many more do you think you got to do?
Uh, like I think four.
Okay.
God, I gotta fucking draw comics again.
Yeah.
I gotta fucking draw, I gotta fucking draw Vapors 3 again.
I miss Beast Capades so much, but I gotta finish Vapors 3 or I'll never forgive myself.
I've been saying that for years, but it's still true and it always has been.
Let me ask you this.
Yeah.
I don't know what you think.
Uh, this is an investigator question, which may be like extremely influential to its,
it happened.
Okay.
I, as you know, I'm quite a fan of the home stuff.
And so all of, like, like, like, I, and because I grew up with it, my brain literally thinks
in terms of like home-sucking animals.
Yes.
And I know for a fact that, like, investigator would be done, maybe not like particularly
quicker, but it would be done way easier and I would like it way, way, way more if
it were in home-sucked panels.
I don't mean like, you know, are you seeing this?
Like, are you seeing where I am right now?
Yeah, I'm seeing where you are right now.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, fuck.
I got it.
I got a good foothold.
You were, that was really dangerous.
It looked like you just left off and you were ready to go.
I thought I could push myself off and grab this one, but it didn't really go the way I
planned, but that's fine.
Okay.
That's fine.
So are you, are you considering doing it Biscopay style?
Well, not Biscopay.
I don't want to do, like, read or input.
Oh my god.
And you should remember that.
Christina Rossetti.
Anyway.
I don't want to do the input.
No, no, no.
I mean visually, like in homestay panel style.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
I'm considering.
I feel like you would behoove me to make my first comic a traditional comic book.
Yeah.
Well, you know, on the one hand, I feel like it's worth going outside your comfort zone.
On the other hand, I feel like whatever it takes to get it done.
Huh?
I don't think it will be a major impact on its dullness.
I just had a conversation, I think, with Steve about it.
I can see that it's a lie.
Maybe not.
Chad, Steve.
Yeah, okay.
Somewhere in the chat that we're both in.
About doing it homestuck style.
We're like, I just like not considered doing it that way because I wanted it to be hard
on myself, I guess.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't think, I mean, I don't really think it makes that much of a difference.
Ultimately, which way it ends up being, unless you want it to be one way or the other.
Yeah.
Like, I think in terms of the end product, it's a lot.
I mean, it's like kind of almost semantical in a way, I would describe it.
Like, it doesn't really matter.
It's just like the language of it.
Yeah.
Hold on.
I thought that you would have like pages drawn already.
Would you like redo them?
Yeah.
Okay.
I do have like pages done in the traditional comic style, though they aren't that many.
I mean, I guess you could always just like.
It wouldn't be crazy for me to restart.
I guess you could always, I mean, they're digital, right?
Yeah.
I guess you could always just like.
Besides one, which is reassuring.
Huh?
Okay.
Well, I guess you could always just like convert them into like homestuck panels.
Why not?
Yeah.
You know what?
The more I think about it, the more I think this is retarded and I'm not going to do that
at all.
And I'm just going to make it a real comic because I'm not a hack.
Solid.
Solid choice.
Well.
What kind of person do you have to be to play this game?
Let alone design it.
Whoa.
Could you?
Are you going to try and hack that?
I know you can do it.
It is totally a thing that people do.
Let me see.
Let me see if I can.
Let me see if it's feasible.
I'll just try and jump as high as I can.
Mmm.
I got higher by swinging.
Oh, whoops.
God damn it.
You're going to have to like catapult yourself up there.
Yeah.
It probably shouldn't spend too much time doing this because in the end it's just going
to be like you could have gone there.
Yeah.
If you just done it the wrong way.
It's probably not worth it.
Unless I was going to spend like hours and hours practicing it so I could do it consistently.
But I don't need to do it consistently.
Yeah.
Stupid.
Ah, God.
No.
Fucking ball.
Okay.
What were you saying about re-
Something about redoing some shit.
Just fucking turn it into a...
Motion.
Motion comic.
Yeah.
Probably.
That's probably the best way to go.
That's probably the best thing that anyone could do.
Shout out to Tom.
He's made mistakes, but it's okay.
Dude.
Oh my God.
The literal best part about Radicon.
Like the best moment was after our apologies.
Me and Tom just like sat like back to back alone in the basement silently working on investigators
versus loss.
Just like we didn't like talk to one other.
We just were there and we both were doing it for like an hour and a half.
I love that.
For a while there I used to hang out with my friend John and I would be drawing on the
computer and he would be coding on his computer.
But I just wanted to like do that for a long time, but he would like stop and like talk
to me and like tell me about what he was doing.
And in one sense I understand why.
But that kind of wasn't what I was there to do, you know.
I have always been fascinated by this one panel of a homestuck, of an influential homestuck
fan comic entitled Panty Rain.
But what I cared about was the depiction of the characters in said comic and they were
just, they were just like, like it was all like the boys basically in a room and they
were all like, like, like some of them were like playing on the TV, like like a video game
or something.
And then, and then I think like John was like on the computer and like Dave was just like
watching like the fucking game.
And like, I always thought like one day I'll achieve this level of Brodom or like I don't
have to like talk to my friends because God forbid that I forget.
But like, but I could just like work on things and like they're around and I can look at them
and appreciate them as the trophies.
Yeah, yeah, I feel it.
It's great when you don't have to talk.
Talking overrated.
That's, that's one of the main things.
Like, like.
Because I grew up as a sheltered boy.
I had always been hardcore on the like, you know, fucking online friends.
The same as offline friends.
I still do understand and emphasize that attitude.
Like I come obviously with maturity to understand their vast differences.
And one of them is that when you're in it, like, like, like being in a call is way, way,
way, fucking different than talking to someone online.
And like, I know that's like a basic thing.
But like, you know, most of my conversations with my friends were like over scale.
Yeah.
So like only only like really, you know, in the past like three years or so have I really
appreciated the difference.
Because like, because like that moment with Tom was great.
But like, we can't like, I can't like call him and then we are now silent just working together.
Like that.
Sometimes me and Mage call each other and just like watch anime and mostly in silence.
Well, yeah.
That's not weird.
That's like a collaborative.
Yeah.
That's like, that's like, like, like, like, like, it would just be me and Tom like just like doing.
Right.
I'm getting worse at this.
Anyway.
Sorry.
No, it's fine.
Just like not saying anything to one another.
It's just not conducive.
Most of the time in my life, I like don't want to be talking, you know, do you feel that way?
Sometimes, not most of the time.
Most of the time I want to be talking.
I feel that way like a lot.
Yeah.
Is this a new development or have you always felt this way?
No, it's, it's, I think I've always, I've always been this way.
I mean, maybe not always, but definitely, I remember feeling this way even in like high school or maybe, maybe college was when it started.
I don't know.
I don't know if it ever started, but I know like, I remember like thinking about it consciously in like college.
It's like, I don't want to talk.
I wish I could stop.
I wish I could just wish I could just have like silence for a long, long time.
There's definitely a great, it's always the best feeling when you reach that tier of friendship where silence is no longer awkward, no matter the situation.
In the end, we only regret the chances we didn't do today.
Truly.
Lewis Carroll.
So you can like call up your bro and you guys can just like talk for a little while and then like start doing something and just kind of like be in the call or you know, hanging out in person.
And like, and like, and like, while you still have like, I have to talk like a little bit like, you know, it's, it's not like a bad, there's no bad silence.
There's no awkward, like I should be saying something.
Yeah.
That just means you're like not that comfortable when you feel like that.
Yes.
Ah.
What are the controls of this game?
You just use the mouse.
You just move the hammer with the mouse and that's all you do.
Fucking dangerous.
This part sucks because it's like, it's not that hard, but it can be fucked up.
And it comes right before this other part that is like way hard.
Yeah.
Ugh.
Maybe, maybe if I like pushed myself on the other underside of this.
No.
I feel like I really have not like gotten this part down at all.
Like every time I try it, I'm just like praying.
Like this is, this is the best I can consistently do getting to this point where like, my hammer is on the thing,
but I'm not like making progress per se.
It's always so weird because whenever you do that, do it.
It just is like a super quick and super fluid and easy.
No.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
Whenever I do it, it's like, because I keep wanting to like stop and slowly approach it
and like carefully make progress, but that never works.
Um, it's only when I like go for it, but I like, I don't know how I make it work when I do go for it.
Blindly do it until it works.
Yeah.
And then still don't understand.
Yeah, that's, that's, that's the only way that it ever works.
I hate this game.
Okay.
Yeah.
So then with all, with the PCP friendship rekindled and with all of our minds constantly, let's see the fuck out with creative genius left and right nowadays.
Yes.
And with us reaching a whole new renaissance in, in, in what we want to do with our lives and reaching creativity and Nirvana.
Um, let's, let's address how the procrastiners podcast is shit and terrible.
Yeah.
Well, naturally, it's, um, yeah, it's like you were, yeah, we used to talk about our work a lot and now we don't, but like, that's what we think about all the time.
So like, what are we talking about?
That, that, that's like the smallest issue, dude.
That's like, that's like fucking fleas on it.
I think that's a big issue.
I think, I think it can fit comfortably within the, the, the issue of we never know what the fuck we're talking about.
And it's all just completely fabricated bullshit.
Um, let's, hold on.
I'm really afraid that my power might cut.
I'm suddenly paranoid.
I'm going to stop recording and then start again.
I don't know if I was imagining it, but I thought I saw the lights flicker for a second and because like, yeah, because I guess the viewers wouldn't know.
Like before we started recording, my power went out for like 10 minutes this morning and I'm afraid it might happen again and I would lose footage.
I think, okay, ah, it depends on file format.
Like depending on what file format this is being saved in, sometimes a power outage will cause it to lose everything and other times it won't.
Like it's being saved continuously and I don't know which one is true right now.
So I'm scared.
Terrifying.
Yeah.
Um, at the very least you can hear my audio.
So that would be luxurious.
What, what do you mean?
Oh, like if this all gets lost?
Mm-hmm.
Well, but then they won't be able to hear my audio because I'm recording my audio in OBS.
I know.
Yeah.
So it'll just be Munchy talking to everyone.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
It'll just be me talking to all the people who are now currently listening to only Munchy and wondering why I'm so...
Wondering what this conversation is even about.
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, okay.
Context.
Fucking...
I'm actually going to put an asterisk on this entire conversation.
Uh, and that actress is, except it's, it has, it except the last episode that we recorded was really great.
What was the last one?
It gave jobs and, jobs and working.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Uh, besides that.
PCP.
I've noticed this ever, like, like, like, like, like in, like, the mid-90s.
Mm-hmm.
Where I, I, I started realizing all of our comments were from, like, new people and all of them were shit.
Now, when, when, when, when, you know, when you say that the comments are shit, a lot, a lot of, you know, recent events and drama comes to mind, you know, maybe that's the reason why.
But I noticed something that I didn't consider.
Fuck!
None of the comments were from, like, veteran fans.
Like, I wasn't seeing, I wasn't seeing, like, my boys.
I wasn't, I wasn't seeing people, like, like, old fans who I knew the name of.
They had all but disappeared.
Like, like, I wasn't seeing, you know, the, the usual names, the PCP comments.
And so, uh, I think I've described this before.
I have, I have a, I guess I have to fucking go to the history since it's highly contextual.
But back in the old days of the PCP fan chat, when that was a big, huge thing, I was there because I was a PCP fan level.
Uh, and, uh, I, I, I gathered all the people who I thought were cool and put them into a super unbelievably clicky, uh, like, secret club chat room called the Golden Child Foundry.
Yeah.
And, uh, like, like, all the people who there were cool, uh, were cool.
Name names, there was Steve, there, there was Dan, there was Steel Viper, there was, you know, all those people, all those guys.
Yeah, all the boys. All the good old boys.
All the boys. All the, all the little baby boys.
They became friends.
And so now, and now, and so now I'm at this head of a cult, a secret club cult called the Golden Child Foundry with a bunch of old, like, like, it's comprised of, like, veteran PCP fans who are good people and I like them.
So, I confronted them and, uh, basically there was, like, there was, like, a Magna Carta constructed and they basically told me that the PCP was shit for this, this, and this reasons.
And, uh, all of them made complete sense and I had been thanking them for a while.
And so, it just slid right in my mind that the PCP was bad.
Yup, super bad.
Yeah.
Um, yeah, I read the Magna Carta.
And there was a bunch of good stuff in there and then we did not, like, do any of it.
We did?
Okay, okay.
We did some.
There have been things that we've done that have definitely helped the issue immensely.
Uh, I mean, I mean, I don't know the structure of how I want to discuss the topic.
Uh, since we are on the procrastinator's channel right now.
Uh, whatever.
Yeah.
Uh, we're inside baseball.
We're inside baseball.
Real raw shit.
Uh, I mean, okay, okay, okay.
I, the main reason I wanted to bring this up is because the right-finger scot killers is the best thing to ever happen to, like, society.
Uh-huh.
And I wanted to compare and contrast it.
It's now achieved that status.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh, and I wanted to compare and contrast it to the PCP in terms of, like, effort and stuff.
Yeah.
Uh, but, but, but to do that, I think, I think I had to lay down some groundwork to the people who, like, like, are, are, have not been, like, like, like, rattled with this line of thinking constantly for the past, like, months, like I have.
And I think you understand, like, a firm grasp of it as well, too.
So, I, I mean, I guess I'll just jump right into it.
Uh, I think the PCP has become super stagnant and super, uh, like, like, samey and super boilerplate and super uninteresting and flaccid and, and, and boring.
Mmm, yeah.
Do you, do you agree?
Well, I see what you mean, but I don't know if it's that the PCP has changed as much as that it's just been going for long enough that, like, the same things have started to feel that way.
I don't know.
Okay, okay.
There are many things that I think have changed, like, have changed for the worse, but I do basically agree with you that it is an issue of time and that we've just been going for so long.
I think that that's, like, the core, like, hidden issue.
Yeah.
That, like, behind all the things that I would like to institute and change, that's, like, the main thing that I think is an undeniable, like, like, like, I don't, like, I mean, how, like, how can I fix that we've been going for a long time?
There's not, there's not much I can do.
So, I would prefer to focus on, like, the practical, you know, uh, tangible details.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, I mean, here, let me just get up a Magna Carta right now.
In fact, let me do that right now.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
You're, you are literally always in a pictorial situation.
This is not, I did not intend for this to happen.
Do not, ah!
Ugh.
Fuck.
Sorry, I just keep screaming.
I just, I just keep screaming.
It's like radcons.
Yeah, it's like radcons all over again.
All right, all right, all right.
Got it over here.
Okay.
So, reasons why the PCP is boring and stagnant.
Uh, article number one of the Magna Carta.
Everything is boring and no one cares.
Uh, this is, uh, this, this just goes in detail about how the topics, uh, like, like, like, I, I think this is Aeroids who said it eloquently.
Or, sorry.
I guess I haven't used these.
People don't want their names be, uh, associated with this.
Um, but I'm not gonna edit it.
Hell yeah.
So sorry.
Um, but, but, yeah.
Uh, fuck.
That's what you get.
That's what you get with the raw shit.
Yeah, the raw shit.
Sometimes you taste some sewage.
Mm-hmm.
Um, it was like, like before, um, the topics necessitated a podcast were like,
earn the early days of the PCP.
Like, every episode would be like,
we were talking about this in the chat.
And, like, we, we were fucking, we're brimming, we're brimming at the seams.
Like, well, we've gotta talk about this.
This is the shit that we've been brewing on and we've been discussing amongst ourselves for fucking eons.
And we've gotta get it out there to the fucking masses.
Mm-hmm.
You got shit like fucking, how much are rules?
Legendary.
Fucking legendary.
Like, like, like the very first episode, best game ever, was just Nate was thinking about it a while.
All into a call to do it.
Fucking, like, a ton of shit like that.
Yeah.
Where it's just, you guys were talking in chat and like, we gotta make a podcast about this.
Now, the podcast necessitates a topic where each week will like, okay, it's, it's taken for granted that we will do a PCP.
What are we gonna do a PCP on?
And we, it's not like we look back, okay, what are we thinking about through the week?
It's like, well, we have a preordained list of topics here.
Let's just randomly pick one based on what we are in the, in the, in the appetite for.
Yeah.
Um, it's, it's true.
It's true.
It has now become a fact of life that a PCP is happening.
And we just have to accommodate that however we can.
Ah, hmm.
Yeah.
I mean, maybe, maybe we should try to like, you know, use the-
Use the, use the fact that like we're talking in chat more as like a foundation for picking topics better.
Like, what are we talking about?
We should podcast about that.
We actually have been.
And so this is all like, this is all kind of old hat.
Well, not old hat.
I think a lot of these problems are still, are still-
No, fuck crap!
Ah!
Oh, okay.
Excuse me.
Excuse myself.
about you know we've had stuff like sex and you know like that I feel strong
about obviously we had you know we've had recent topics where we care a lot of
it I'm worried about it I don't think it's it's it's reached the same like you
know we were talking about this in chat and so we brought up but we have the
potential to change that now so I think we're on the up and up on that yeah yeah
keep in mind viewers the reason I'm saying all this is even though I think
we're on the right track I still think that there are problems we can fix and
also this is where I forget to get the real shit and also I want to talk about
how cool right because capitalism is compared to the PCP that that's why I'm
trying to get across here so keep that in mind with all these article 2 the
topics are too broad the fucking topics like like most of these like almost all
of the problems generate from either the bureaucracy of the PCP and how it's like
weirdly like democratic and like and like bureaucracy defined and like paperwork
heavy yeah it is it has become a well-oiled machine yeah and by well
old machine we mean bogged down and needless paperwork yeah a night a
nightmare dystopia where nothing is ever when nothing ever changes and nightmare
you can't wake up from but yes oh yes so it comes from bureaucracy or topics and
topics are far easier to you know change so the topics are too broad and this
this this was actually like this is actually pretty well quashed because the
this was taken at a point when we were doing shit like hey let me just go to
the channel reason that I went back and like and like and like looked at all the
PCP episodes like calculate when things went wrong and I notice like like from
like around like like like the mid like 60s till like like the 90s we were
talking about like bullshit philosophical nothingness that like didn't
matter at all mm-hmm and and and so we got we started talking about like
fucking gay ass shit that was not really relevant to anyone that just that
just like like that like just start off way too broad and we always floundered to
figure out how like like like what to say on the topic and it turned out boring
and stupid like like key example this is monsters way too like a broad and like
like like what are we gonna say about monsters like what do you mean by monsters
what is happening right now let's just look at funny images and it was awful
yeah yeah it was truly a wake-up call yeah monsters was totally a wake-up call
and in all ways we were like guys this something's gone wrong
I want to read most of this basically I mean all the news we said it was I felt
it was stagnant for a while and we're taking steps to do that but here's the
point here's the point here the right focus cop killers its entire brand and
like reason why it's good is because again it's fucking genre to find you
never know what you're gonna get when you fucking click our focus cop killers
video it can be a it can be a let's play like it will always be like you know
there's like a game in the background but you never know what kind of topics
you're gonna get you never know what we're gonna have you never know when
we're gonna launch in to fucking into which color is the PCP you never know
when you're gonna get that shit when you say genre you mean genre defying like
like genre busting like it has no no god ah shit I wish I was dead I just yeah
like that hate that orange so much time to climb the devil's staircase once
again anyway yes genre busting no no rules no rules and like there's there's
no other let's play that operates in such a fluid and dynamic manner such as
us there's no there's no one that's so fucking meandering and and broad and
fucking we are we are literally kill the kill we are no other no other let's play
where if you don't like someone in the comments you can go to our discord and
literally shoot and kill them it's it's it's legendary and the thing is like
like all all this creativity and like effort we're putting in to the right
first cop killers because we're putting in like a crazy amount of effort you you
more so than me yeah I've been I've been working on on shit but yeah we're
really like we're putting in we're putting in saying ours to get this shit
just perfect in in the discord I I've been thinking about fucking you know
YouTube and you should do twitch we we we've both been like you know brother
for this has been we've been going over time we've been going over time we've
been going over time because we genuinely care of the product and and and we're
constantly we're constantly doing a new creative crazy shit I feel like the PCP
is not crazy new shit no the point not really like whenever something new
happens like when Tom made that like D&D attack video I was excited about it and
I went and I made my response video and that was like a breath of fresh air for
me at least but that kind of thing I mean it still happens but not as much like
the PCP has kind of calcified in what in terms of what it is and like what it
contains which is not good it's that's that's not a good setup for success like
that's not what it should be about I feel like we've reached a point where like
the podcast itself is solidified and like pretty like like you know standard
and like you can pretty much guarantee like what's gonna be on each episode like
you know to start open the Urban Dictionary we're gonna we're gonna you know
try and find our footing for a while it's gonna bring up we're utilitarianism
for no reason and we'll be great and we'll argue about that for like 30
minutes yeah and yeah everyone goes home happy yeah yeah but even though the
podcast has reached that sort of standard you know appeal like everything
outside of that is like new and like pretty refreshing like like like like
Digi even though I'm not totally pleased with what is happening with him he is
undeniably doing new crazy stuff yeah true and and and and and and and you know
I'm working on that thing with Hippo which is like a completely like that's
like gonna be like a new thing like like like that kind of thing has not really
happened in the PCP yet no at least unlike you know well and there's been
there's been a bit like I mean it's yeah it's not it's not gonna fucking break the
world with how fucking revolutionary is but it's it's definitely like a like a
new like a new step to doing the thing yeah like shredded before absolutely
yeah I'm not hyped up too much maybe you know I'm saying like like there's new
stuff like and like ten pieces and draw what the fuck dude ten pieces and draw is
the newest hottest shit and it is a property that I'm so invested in and
that is why it's gonna take forever before it comes out because I will not
release it until it is as good and as professional as it possibly can be and
and so we've reached that this point where like the PCP like like like podcast
itself is probably like you know like fine and whatever but like everything
happened around it is super fucking interesting and here is where I bring
in my fucking point that will I've actually tricked you the PCP is actually
perfect because it's it's it's this understandable it's just understandable
and and like you know what's the word what's like the word no it cannot
recollect when it began the same thing like five times around now where you
just like like you've got up there you flounder well that time I actually got
up on the rocks above Emily like I was I did better that time you're right but I
still fucked it up inexplicably we don't mean you know the first time I went up
there I took it slow and I it was pretty successful so I think I should do that
again okay anyway you have a PCP is perfect agreed the PC is perfect
because it's it's it's a it's because of Koensburg it's it's fucking what I'm
I'm I'm thinking I'm my brain is correct but my but I don't have the correct
vocabulary it's it's like it's like what did you use to describe the
asher sport and McDonald's as it's it's it's like you understand what it is and
like it's it's normal it's it's what's the fucking word he used what are you
fucking say familiar comfortable familiar it's familiar yeah you like you
understand what the PCP is gonna be and while it might not be you know a fucking
crazy new experience it still is it as it has always been besides the parts where
it's been shit and boring yeah it's always been a meeting of creative minds
and it's always been people you know our art and I feel like the fact the fact
that we're all women with you I think we're all I should say I feel this way
so I'm going to project it upon other people because I vaguely know it to be
true on like some level I I really feel like we're doing fucking God's work and
we're doing new crazy shit with the fucking right fuckers cop killers yes
just one example yeah like and and and the PCP is is facilitating that the PCP
is allowing this to take place it's allowing us to bring like you know our
minds together in a week on a weekly basis and we're allowing us to stay
friends and allowing us to use that as a launch pad to bigger and greater things
well you know well I can be sad that you know sure I don't think the podcast is
like a super you know great piece of art as as I believe it once was it's
facilitating bigger and better things and has ever been done before you know to
me munchie that's what the PCP has always been like the PCP was never like an
end in and of itself the PCP was a way for us to stay friends and also like a
platform for people like you know find us through to facilitate the other stuff
we wanted to do you know I okay I agree but I feel like the PCP has like had okay
the PCP okay what I'm going to describe the term PCP as the podcast and I'm
gonna use the term procrastinators as just us okay obviously so I can
differentiate these things sure I feel like the PCP at one point had like a
die-hard fan base like like like of like actual like fans of the podcast and
while the podcast was of course sold on our personalities and friendship
basically entirely it was like there's no doubt like that the podcast itself had
like an extremely influential role in getting those people invested in us and
our relationship with one another yeah but I feel like the actual like fan base
of the PCP has diminished well like the procrastinators fan base well maybe not
has like drastically like skyrocket or anything I feel like there's more there's
more hypocrite fans now and there's more like been saint fans and there are PCP
fans now at least that's how I feel I agree I don't think yeah I feel like yeah
you're saying that like enthusiasm for the podcast in and of itself has waned
mm-hmm but like well you know if that's true then I think that's a worthwhile
trade-off like I think I think that our stuff that we do our art is the is more
important than the podcast in and of itself I mean I like the PCP you know
I've worked really hard on the PCP on like you know doing stuff and making
stuff for it and like you know I want it to be a success and I want it to be you
know good and enjoyable and something that people like and they're excited to
hear but I mean if the PCP had to die or not die but like you know if I guess
I'm saying is I would like I would I would I would accept a loss to the PCP
for like a gain to like us as individuals you know because it's about us we
are I completely agree I know this was kind of scatterbrained to follow but
just just know that like for like the past couple months my concern talks
about this but I kind of like well again like like it's been really like you
know I really hate it and I've been really trying to you know push myself to
like you know find ways and like and like develop methods to like fix it and
you know make make you know make it great things right make it great again
yeah but maybe that's not really what I should be doing and I don't think that
our focus is focusing I think that our focus should not be on the PCP itself
it's like not that we shouldn't focus on it or think about it or try to make it
good but it's not the most important thing yeah I that's how I feel now too I
feel I feel a sense of like okay the PCP has I feel like it's gone out of it's
like it's like okay we're like fucking like episodes like I'm just gonna
throw out a number like fucking like you know 60 to like 90 we're like pretty
fucking that was like a drought of like good shit with like a few things that
were that that punctuate like that my little pony one that was great you know
there were a few ones that were nice but overall it was kind of a slump in
quality fucking okay okay okay here I have the perfect one everything from
fucking the drama podcast to fucking I think it culminated in like the holiday
special like everything there was like like unbelievably awful and gay sick but
I feel like we've reached like a fine level and like like the PCP like like
like as Nate always said it was just an excuse for us to talk more yeah and we
are talking more now you know do your ad con and and we're making cool ass shit
so you know what I guess I'm fine the um I mean if we're being chums and if we
like like each other and are talking to each other and having a good time with
that I think what will naturally occur as a result is that our conversations on
the PCP will become more lively and more enjoyable you know what I mean I know
you mean I think like like it really was it really like like I feel like I was
being too harsh on the PCP and and more so than I was being harsh I was not I
was I was thinking about like like the broad the broad problem was like even
though I knew it and I preached it I didn't like fully like like understand
how much of a difference it made that we just weren't talking yeah because like
instantly now it seems like we are just fucking like like we have too many topics
for the first time in like forever like because like like like they're like last
me we actually had like we had to decide among three topics that we wanted to do
desperately and we're like okay which ones do we want to do first and we had
to decide it based on that whereas like like you know before it was like it was
like someone think it's something to pop someone picked something and whatever
yeah yeah yeah yeah shit cookin yeah and I'm really happy about it and that's
why mad because I didn't get to do the topic that I wanted to do whatever we'll
do it I was I was encouraging that one if I think that was a great one I mean we
could still do it I guess although although it'd be less topical that was
like super topical right then so I thought if there was ever a time to do
it should be then but what fuck Christ anyway that that that labyrinth
conversation the end point of all that naysay and papoey and you know saying
the PCP is bad even though it's my job and I like it a lot and I was a fan of
it and that's the entire reason that I have a livelihood is that I like the
PCP too much oh that god video games are so bad look at that human in the pot
it's gay oh the human in the pot is like apparently he's he too is a stock asset
he's like unity male model number one or something he too is a unity asset I
I can't that's the name my autobiography he I kind of want to play sexy hiking the
game that this is like based on it look it's like really like crappy like pixel
looking yes you know I think wretzu pray wretzu prayed someone who was let's
play sexy hiking yeah it's um I've never heard of it before I feel like it's
probably gotten a little more noticed now that this game is out although I'm
sure people didn't know about it I'm sure I'm sure people knew about it before
but I don't know it just looks like this game but like a lot like rougher but
yeah okay I've decided like this ladder works better when I kind of like fling
myself up it instead of like trying to like slowly fuck my way up okay we've
already failed then have I oh ah ha who's a failure now mom
then yeah okay enough enough about the PCP enough about our livelihood enough
about working enough about creativity it's time for the only shit that actually
matters fucking Pokemon go Pokemon go dude um I got an Ampharos I went out
from a reap day and I got myself an Ampharos okay Marie day was like the
best day of my life yeah I missed both I missed out on Bulbasaur day but ah but
I got the you know I like Ampharos better than Venus or anyway I dude oh my
fucking god I was in Boston Common on Bulbasaur day it was so fucking fun it
okay okay it's kind of weird because especially in my area San Diego
Pokemon go players like hard to come by and like it's hard to do raids and like
you like you can't really get everyone organized in like a convenient way and
like you only see people you know out and about but on fucking Marie day I
would like like a density populated like park called Babbo Park um hashtag
docs even though it's extremely the hashtag docs um and like I swear to
God 80% of the people there were playing fucking Pokemon go to the point where
like all of like the street vendors like you know we're doing like Pokemon go
themed shit like that's so much so awesome that's so I know it's fucking great I
didn't go anywhere like special I just went to like I just went like around to
like some stores and I went to but I did like end up at a park and the park did
have like there were I did see groups of people walking around playing Pokemon
go even that's just this tiny little bullshit park yeah it's really nice and
I really like it whenever that I don't know if you'll feel the same way but I
think the Pokemon go is like like will be like the best thing to like ever
happen to me network slash socially because when I was in Boston and Boston
has like a really like active like like discord server Pokemon go especially for
instincts hashtag instinct best invest team by the way it's mystic mystic all
the way number one now and forever please refer to the remember the Pokemon go
school review didn't say by legendary author and esteemed New York time best
seller hypocrite he did a Pokemon go video yeah Pokemon go miniscule review
it's what it's my favorites woman it's one of my favorite videos of all time
it's great I missed it anyway yeah yeah so so okay I met so many fucking freaks
and geeks and colorful characters and and great overall human beings oh in my
time from Pokemon go in Boston my favorite of which is this like the pain
in knowing this has happened like like like 30 and knowing what more tears six
year old man maybe even only like 30 like 42 or something yeah it kind of
portly thick ass box next and and whenever he was dual wielding he had
to he had like an iPhone and Android both plain Pokemon go on like an old
account like like he was like both of his accounts like level 40 or like super
high level and and whenever he got a bad IV requires it because I raid with them
every kind of bad IV he would like oh this one loves the cock us all this
requires it loves the cock it loves the cock it's terrible genius genius yeah
absolute fucking genius and he would say this like loudly in like crowded areas
I fucking got a bad eye climbing a mountain with a hammer in their ropes
required did did the Rayquaza love the cock was he right obviously yeah if it
had bad IVs obviously well then he should say it he should say it loud and
proud fuck ah god I hate this rake I hate the slide I hate this wall this wall
is so fucking slippery fuck my ass this wall loves the cock is what I'm saying
it totally does that'll be the new insult oh so yeah I just I I love
seems no more a soulless thing I love rather as a shape of I like me new
people like meeting me in the windows of chaos born yeah the law oh
crouched enormous in a steer before who's oh well you know this will be a nice
break George sterling a nice break from that sunny shit up there back to my back
to my roots at the devil's chimney I'm sure this is so relaxing for you no this
is the worst mother I'm actually making my own because the San Diego like
Pokemon go scene is like so scattered like the only discord that I could find
oh I think I think I told you about this on a stream was this fucking like like
weird like nest of like cheaters and like scammers yeah yeah yeah the yeah the
people with their own memes yeah yeah with their own like shitty hacking memes
yeah like hey guys we're all just a bunch of Pokemon hackers am I right
all just love cheating what are we gonna do all the map scanners are down
brain same thing we do every night of pinkie try and take over La Jolla with
our with our mystic gyms quality quality me right there wow real hashtag
relatable so yeah I'm gonna make my own server it's gonna be great and I'm
gonna be the leader and that means it will be perfect what your own Pokemon
discord server yeah why can't I do it you'll never succeed I don't you'll no
one believes in you you can't do it I'll rise above hate I'll resist hate no
you won't you'll be just like me one day I've already got all my cronies flooding
it your cronies yeah my cronies I'm I'm glad that you have cronies yeah it's a
good it's good feeling all my all my goons are just mobbing it
this Pokemon go local server I've got a crowd gathering I I can't wait until I
like I do like a like I want to like do like a weekly Pokemon go walk and it'll
be great for exercise and it'll be great for social well-being and it will make
my life 10 times better and you know one day people will be like so what do you
do and I'll be like you know I'm a comic book artist and I'm a god and you should
like me because I play Pokemon go and I'm cool and I'm a good guy and they'll
be like wow I'm going to follow you now and I'll be like sit yeah I feel it I
wish I wish I lived in a more populous area so I could like go out and do that
with Pokemon I do too Boston was like insane for Pokemon go yeah absolutely
insane when I lived in Medford I used to like I used to catch so many ghastly's
and drowsies like I would go on I would go on Pokemon go walks and it was
fucking awesome oh not even just for the Pokemon the Pokemon was great but like
fucking just like just like for the people just the raw like not only do you
get colorful characters like the loves the cock guy but you just get like
genuine like like hardcore dedicated people who are like like noble samurai
sages who are all business and like no jokes but like they're dependable and
reliable and like you know when you go on the fucking Tim instinct Boston
whatever the hell discord server then you can fucking meet up with like like
you know love authorities who know their shit and we'll help you out if you're
in a pinch in a newbie in a raid or whatever and it's wholesome and it's the
way that God fucking intended the world to be it's the way God intended Pokemon
go to be it's perfect it's perfect Boston was great
Pokemon go yeah San Diego is pretty gay dude a bin I have been to no less than
seven Latios raids at hatch and no one's fucking showed up not a single god
damn person I have never even been to a raid not a single one no dude they're
really fun they're really fucking fun they're really great they're this
dude okay raids in Boston solidified the fact that Pokemon go is like the best
game ever made to me because it was so fucking cool to walk up to a raid to get
like a fucking grout on and then see all these geeks and gamers hanging out in
real life and then you walk up and they'd be like hey they'd be like yeah
dude I mean my second fucking ground on the first one had good IV so I hope this
windows too and you can talk about like fucking nerd shit in real life and it
was great and you could be chic in a hipster at your fucking local Starbucks
and charge up your phone and fucking like mindless to tap on your phone we
spoke one go has a bad combat system but it's okay so it facilitates social
interaction and it was Pokemon go had a good combat system it would be so much
of a better game I would be so much more incentivized to play it I'm actually
planning well and my plan I mean vaguely have thought about it once or
twice and have the capacity to do so so I might do it one day make like a
Pokemon go like fucking like review or something you know he's like I care so
deeply about it like it's it's seriously consumed all of my life do you know
what I wish more than anything I wish the Pokemon go just worked like regular
Pokemon I okay okay here's here's what would be like the bombshell like fuck
you if you ever even look at me in my Pokemon go review is people are always
like well of course they had the simplified the combat system because
did they like like like like people are always like you know like obviously like
you know it's a mobile game of course that is simplified to you know to reach
you know the casual audience top 50 highest selling games of all time seven
slots are Pokemon in the top selling games of all time I think normal Pokemon
has a pretty broad reach you fucking idiots yeah they could have they could
have done it they could have made combat work like in a regular Pokemon and then
like you could have had fucking you could have fucking battled your friends
and in turn-based battles and it would have been like easier like it would have
been easier and it would have been so much better because it would have felt
like a Pokemon game I mean I'm not saying like I don't hate Pokemon go I
don't hate what it is I think it would have been better if they hadn't tried so
hard to make it its own thing I I like particularly care with the social it
the social aspect of Pokemon go and how it facilitates me talking to new people
but I do like like okay okay Ben here's the world it's not the perfect world but I
think it's the world that is the perfect like feasible world that could like
realistically like probably maybe happen yeah imagine if like you had like it was
like Pokemon battle and you had four moves and they just were on like a like a MOBA
timer so you could still keep the like gimmicky like you know what casual mobile
phone like you know tap and there are cooldowns and you know it wouldn't be
like a it wouldn't be like a strict you know turn-based system because they're
because they're obviously not gonna do that they're too pussy to do that but if
you just had like a cooldown system and more moves then you would have it would
dramatically dramatically fix the fucking combat system and also um I seriously have no idea why
this is not already uh do the fucking physical special split split like already like Jesus Christ
why would they not do it yeah like they changed all these things and I don't know why I don't
know why it had to be so different I guess I mean it's like they designed it like we need to have
players tapping on their screen all the time like we need to have that happening because
I like again Pokemon is like the most casual game of all fucking time you don't need to make it like
because all you've done is just remove all tension from fights yeah they are just completely
determined like before the battle even starts like there is no strategy to be held yeah and it's
gay yeah it's it's it's pretty good the combat is absolutely horrendous and like like again I'm fine
with it because it just facilitates social interaction yeah like I still play it truly is
it truly is like a terrible combat system uh yeah like like just just imagine imagine you tap on a
gym the battle starts you just have like you know you know where like like like just like below your
Pokemon or something is like four moves and it's like you know uh oh scratch that has like a two
say like two millisecond cool down like you can do it just a ton you can tap it like you you do
normally or like fire but like fire fire blast has like a seven second cool down so you can only do
like every once in a while so you have to like strategically do I want to do a bunch of scratches
or do I want to do a fire blast or I also have toxic I can do a stash effect there still are stash
conditions in Pokemon go by the way there are still not stash conditions a staple of the Pokemon
series still not there yeah they just like took all this great stuff out to make room for a new
system that sucks oh boy yeah it's really frustrating and I mean I don't I don't know why
the insistence on like cooldowns and like screen tapping like I guess if you have to have that then
yeah your your system works like I said like I said it's not the perfect system but I feel like
I feel like cooldowns are like a like a like a vast step in the right direction and also like not
unfeasible yeah well wait isn't like like well I mean they kind of already have cooldowns it's just
that they have like only two moves and whatever well they're not really cool oh I thought I had
it's like a charge eater yeah like in the fighting game yeah well which is absolutely retarded
like why two moves yeah why
I just why hey um my ampharos has dragon pulse is that good that's the like community day event
only move like so series community day the pokemon you evolve during that we'll have a special move
so ampharos has dragon pulse um here's another reason why the pokemon go battle system is bad
there's literally no reason to not have stab moves and coverage literally does not matter well
I mean you um you might you know I used to watch uh I used to watch uh trainer tips
oh I love trainer tips and that guy had like oh my god that guy had like uh
I mean it's been a while but back in the day he he would like he would get pokemon that had like
like he would have like a strong grass type but then give it like strong water type moves
because he would anticipate that like a fire type was oh wait wait but then it's like isn't in pokemon
go like stab and type advantage are like the same yeah gross gross wait like like something to that
effect yeah like yeah it's like like like type advantage just like doesn't matter as much
like it kind of does but not really well it's it's more so that just like because the stats are
like so narrow like there's just attack and defense and hp yeah and because stab is like super powerful
and because you are like you're basically only going to use your quick move for like most competitive
play and and and then just like fire off like there's no like you would never like save your
charge move you're just going to fire off as soon as you have it's like the bulk of it is just going
to be you tapping yeah and just all these different like like elements compounded upon one another
there's like no like you're not going to want to like save a coverage charge move for like the off
chance of like you can countering a pokemon that will like could benefit slightly from you having it
you're just going to want to be able to do like the maximum about of like raw dps yeah you can
with your pokemon like like just generally for any like because it's like for like a normal game
like in the normal pokemon you're going like like your pokemon is going to be one of a team and you're
going to like you know switch it out strategically and like you know move your pokemon it'll be
turn based and there will be strategy like pokemon go like you don't really need strategy it's just
tap a lot it's like the only strategy is in which pokemon you're choosing yeah exactly and like I
guess you could fuck up timing your charge like you could just like forget to use your charge move
or something yeah and that's like it that's like the extent that's like the extent of the decision
making the most fun I've had battling are again with raids we're like I really had to like
think about what pokemon I'm going to send in because I have to do the max amount of damage to
this fucking raid pokemon and to get that like to like to get this requires it down I have to send
in my best fucking jinx and I have to level up my jinx so fucking hard to get that ice move and do
quad damage to him I have to fucking do the most bad damage and that was the most I thought about
pokemon go combat was just I need a jinx I need to yeah I need to get my jinx really strong yeah
yeah and that's that that's that could be better to cool down so you would all be
Niantic would be happy because they have their weird insistence on having gimmicky mobile bullshit
and fucking trainers would be happy because there's there's like there's like there's it
steps towards being like you know traditional combat system and and like you know there is strategy
yeah I mean I hate it because it's not original pokemon when it totally could have been imagine
if it was just like playing pokemon in real life fuck it's madman I really don't know why
you don't know why I'm mad no no no no I don't know why it was normal pokemon
like the system works and it would totally work in a mobile format like there's nothing
stopping it from from just being fine except for some kind of like archaic belief that like
a turn-based combat system is unacceptable okay okay I'm about to go into like like a big topic
that I'm sure you'll feel the same way about yeah and I just want to preface with this the
complaint of like why isn't x out yet is usually meant just as like a you know like like a a short
form for like I'm mad that x isn't out yet yeah but for this for let's say I want to literally know
why isn't trading and pvp out yet like literally why like what like what is stopping why are they
not out yet I mean I guess they were doing raids which is like yeah like that's a pretty big thing
that you I'm sure you were working really hard on for quite a while but what have you been doing
since then yeah that was that was like a long time ago
yeah um raids and I mean pvp pvp I could see being challenging like I still think it should
be doable but pvp I could see being challenging but trading like what like how like that just seems
like the easiest thing you know like like like like like what could it like like what are the
challenges just like like is it just coding it like like how normal pokemon has trading normal
pokemon has trading why don't you have trading it's not like you can't program this because there
are video games that have it programmed uh I mean sure you have to like do it in a way that's
consistent with the way the rest of go is coded but like I don't know ultimately it just comes down to
like a transfer of like a packet of data that represents said pokemon from one phone to another
right I mean I think so I mean oh well I mean only I mean I guess you could like you could
potentially maybe they don't want to do it because like a high powered player could like transfer to
a low powered player and it would like break the progression or something like could it be a balance
issue like okay imagine your cousin trades you like a 200 cp pokemon you know uh uh before you're
able to uh you know how the normal games dealt with this the pokemon just won't obey you yeah there's
already a fix for this there's already a fix for that that's already been accounted for
in the normal games you're exactly right so it can't it can't be balanced it can't be a balance
issue the only thing that I've seen suggested and this was like by fans I've not even seen
niantic comment on this niantic doesn't comment on things or at least they didn't use to maybe
they're better about it now but especially in the early days of go they were like what I understand
if they're very slightly better okay well all right um but like the only thing I like like it
it there have been rumors that like spoovers will have an advantage because they'll be able to like
you know zip around the map and like trade things like like you know at their leisure wow like that's
such retarded acid and fucking non-existent argument like there's no like sure they will
have better pokemon but like they already do spoofers are not like like a huge like unbelievably
rampant pokemon like a problem they already have better pokemon so like just whatever and like
why deny this staple of the pokemon series for just on the count like like you are literally
negotiating and letting terrorists win you are literally letting terrorists win
that can't be it that can't be the reason again literally why is not literally maybe
they think that it would like maybe they think that if you could trade for pokemon then like
it would like just make the game too easy in some way like maybe they think that would disincentivize
like buying shit or something I don't know maybe they maybe maybe they think that like that would
be giving players what they want too much to the extent that it would like hurt the game's
financial performance or something because I'm sure if they wanted us to have trading we would
make a make a trade pass or you have to buy a pass to trade a pokemon done
huh pretty good pretty good
good
look at this i love pokemon go
huh i love pokemon go i miss playing it it was way fun playing it again it was great and i love it
yeah and it's the best game ever made yeah like it true
i just
apparently trading is like coming up and like and like they're working on it but like
it's it it's it's it's a rich investigator status in my mind it's it's rich it's it's
delays at this point night and take yeah like like like i don't care anymore oh oh i see yeah
yeah i mean i mean would i even trade like would you trade your pokemon
i would trade i would trade all the time uh i mean
what would there be to really trade for like just some shit that you've never got
and you want in your pokedex region exclusives uh uh things like like like like like i'm in a
desk biome i could use stuff from like an ice biome oh my god okay well i mean adding trading
does kind of render region exclusives like almost pointless um you have to meet someone from the
country and they have to willingly give you one no because like people in that country are going to
be trading out of the country and those and like they're gonna make they're gonna make their way
elsewhere like they're gonna disseminate through the go player population uh i mean okay eventually
like an english person will trade their fucking mr. mime to a guy in america and then that american
guy will trade that fucking mr. mime to another american guy but like
like will make them pointless it will that will still be like a pokemon that had to have
originated in europe yeah like it still like would have had to have spawned naturally yeah like like
you will have to and like it will be a stop a saw after pokemon so it will still be like wow this
guy has like a mr. mime cool i want that i will give you a strong pokemon for that because i cannot
get that normally yeah well i mean i yeah they'll still be cool it will it will heavily devalue
them but at this point like the fact that they're valuable i mean the only thing that that does is
make people travel and like it's not like that makes niantic any money is that people are buying
plane tickets to go to japan to catch a whatever yeah barfetched so yeah no i mean i think that i
mean i think they should be re i think they should be gettable without going to england
or whatever what have you
yeah it's fucked up retarded oh god shit i'm not super mad about pvp not being in
even though i do think it's bullshit and they're all hacks like it just wouldn't be fun i don't
think it would be like it just wouldn't be fun no because there wouldn't be any skill required it
would just be if they had just made it like real pokemon then it would be fun for her there to be
pvp but they didn't yeah so it's not it's not going to be cool so who even cares this is what i mean
this is what this is what makes me mad about it it's that by making this this by making this
unnecessary change they just like they just ruin so many other things they're like i don't even
want them anymore uh right now pokemon go is just a game about like having pokemon in your phone
yeah it totally is which is you know not like i don't want that not like i don't want to have
cool pokemon in my phone i do i admit it but it could have been more could have been so much more
much
why okay what well okay actually i i guess i was about to ask what purposes do the team serve
but they serve the same team they said the same purposes as the fucking
grouties and the killers yeah that's just a popularity context and and shit talking and
community ability yeah so i guess that's fine but i don't know i i just feel like there's
a squandered potential certain answers to pokemon go hey um oh well let me just get about this what
like why are there small pokemon and big pokemon yeah apparently it makes no difference to the
stats yeah yeah but just some pokemon are really big and others aren't and it's just a thing
yeah i mean theoretically like uh uh moves like like low kick interact with a pokemon's
mass but i don't think they do that in pokemon go yeah i don't think so either
finally finally
get ready to watch me fail yep you're you're gonna tumble on fucking down again
yep uh oh i'm drunk oh god i'm so drunk i'm so drunk i'm so so drunk right now
the fucking upper body strength of this guy is fucking insane
true come on there we go okay um i have no fucking clue how i'm supposed to get up this thing
you know what i'm gonna watch a video i'm gonna pull up youtube and see how he did it
we're not getting underhanded tech feels like that the pcp say what we're not getting this
out of hand tech feels like that in the pcp no okay okay he he okay he goes slowly up just the way
i did all right he slowly goes up the next rock okay and then to get to where i am i'm assuming he's
gonna just yep just kind of hook himself and just slowly okay then he gets himself right up against
the rock like right where i am oh is he just okay and then he does it again okay he just
kind of does it again and okay oh my god what oh my god here here goes here goes
oh no i'm scared here's what he's what he here's what i gotta do
well oh oh i almost saved it but oh
okay so what he did was he kind of like grabbed onto the rock pulled himself up
and then like without coming to rest just kind of lowered himself down on the rock and then
pogoed himself off it to grab the next ledge up because there is no place to like sit on that
on that's that rock that i was going for it my hammer just slipped his hammer didn't slip why did
my hammer slip it's bullshit you don't have the tactical precision that he does you don't have
the years of advice under your belt you don't have the precision german engineering the only
thing under my belt is gonna be your ass when i'm beating it
oh god oh god i don't know why that happened okay all right well anyway game sucks now
how about you say there's one more fail and then we get the fuck out of here one more fail at that
at that ledge yeah okay i i've exhausted all my topics yeah uh all right i think i can get back
there relatively quick compared to how i was doing before yes uh oh shit oh all right you know what
yeah you want to call it quits munchie yeah let's call it okay let's call it it's been great
we've had a good game let me just i'll just beat this bathtub in frustration oh whoa what
what is this like a secret oh oh fuck oh it says wrong way okay yeah there's like there's nothing
over here whoever requested this game fuck you you're thank you i i like it i like the game
this game sucks and it's a fucking pretentious hipster meme asshole game it's for streamers
and it's for people who have no souls unlike us who have more souls you could ever imagine
we've killed so many people our hands are stained with blood join the replica scope of those discord
and literally kill people along with us yeah and be be our ponds please be our child a proxy
yeah please please fight one another in a proxy war that me and munchie are too cowardly to fight
ourselves for slime superiority and that's it um that's what it's all about beautiful uh next time
i think i think next thing we're going to record will be a stream so whenever you're
fucking check check out our uh twitch tell us if you like twitch or youtube better uh judge
it from the comments uh it seems everyone likes youtube more but uh i like twitch i like twitch
well uh we're just gonna keep going until you like it basically yeah yeah you'll learn to like it
just like you did the first time yeah yeah wait wait i'm gonna try this one more time since i'm here
okay one more the world's rushing on your shoulders
i did it okay i did it you're doing it you're doing it okay get back get back up to the place
okay if i if i fail if i fall below again then that will be the end of an era
and also if i make it um you owe me a million slime no i'm not gonna fucking agree to that
give me a million slime no matter what give me that coveted mega slime i want it and i deserve it oh no
okay
look i need i need it okay i i need i have a gambling addiction now
i gotta bet it all on slime craps
i won my first gamble it made me so happy i have still i have never won a game i have not won
slots or craps once i'm just getting fucking oh oh oh oh i made it save i'm so strong
oh come on come on this game is unruly easy does it now how far into the game would you say that you
are i think i'm more than halfway through here like i think there's maybe only like
two more significant challenges before the end but i'm not really sure because like i've never made
it i mean i've i've seen someone play it through but only like once there's like there's not this
is okay i would guess i'm probably like three quarters of the way down you you were so fucking
brazen just then well i knew that i wasn't going to fall because my hammer was going to catch the
table okay but it was kind of an accident this is all it this is what the episode's writing on okay
this is what the game reference collector's brand depends on
oh
easy now
okay killer killer pride killer pride is on the line
if if you win then then then killers get a free day of of slurpees at 711 and they get
they get they get they get slurpees for free for an entire day oh my god and if you lose
then routies get slurpees free slurpees for an entire day i don't want i don't want flavor of
the fresh exactly so you have to you have to fucking energize yourself okay and not be a
weak-willed fucking feminine bitch i'm so scared this is i'm so scared of what i'm about to do
i got my i got my hand on the phone i'm about to call the fucking 711 manufacturers right goddamn
now and have them hand deliver some fucking slushies to my fucking goddamn rowdy roughass
because i know it's about to happen to you right fucking now yeah
this guy's this fucking youtubers hammer didn't slip why didn't fucking
oh omg it's zoopy big o period little oh why didn't his hammer slip shout out start drama with us
all right that's it that's the game yeah we all get slurpees whoo
rowdies rowdy life killers you killers you know what to do
violence oh i i think they know what to do that that's to be dead commit commit no well don't
don't stay dead never stay dead heaven forbid you stay dead fucking okay cut the rowdies down
before they can enjoy their slurpees we can we can argue all day about who deserves a slurpee
to not but we can all agree that no corpse deserves a slurpee let alone do do not okay killers when
you're bullying the rowdies and like you know kicking them kicking dirt kicking their sand
castles in their faces and stealing their slurpees do not pour them down the drains because they will
wind up in the sewers and i do not want the dead i do not want the stay deads enjoying them
we're at each other's throats but but but even we even even we can come to the sensible conclusion
that corpses should stay corpses even stay corpses i mean burn in hell and die even we can even we
can agree morally diametrically opposed as we are even we can agree on stopping mutually beating
up the juveniles which is what we were doing and moving on to the deads and beating them up instead
oh oh we're having a lower contest by going on like in our discord i think it will probably be
done by the time you're doing it but we do art contests every time that we stream so uh join
the discord and see what that's like see what the fucking contest is go and make and and like enter
into our you can we've done we've had music submissions we had art submissions they're
fucking there's a lot they live as hell yeah and um we pick we pick winners on stream we
announce them on the stream so uh fucking go join the discord join the fucking discord or else
you shall perish all right let's get the fuck out of here all right bye bye you later