This is a podcast called The Pro Crastinators Podcast. A variety podcast running since 2015.
This is a special edition of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. We are going to be talking about and playing everyone's favorite game, Nuclear Throne.
Tell them why I am.
I'm your host, Ben Saint. Patreon.com slash Ben Saint.
Didn't you draw something?
The.com slash Davoo.
And I'm the first person who's talking over other people.
And you're Munchy.
And Munchy. Our friend Munchy.com slash Munchy.
I'm going to become a wrestler.
Didn't you draw something, Ben?
No.
Okay.
Yeah, I didn't think so.
Yeah, patreon.com slash Ben Saint.
Is the exclusive portal to find my work.
All right.
StComics.com.
I drew a comic.
And Davoo, don't you also claim to do something worthwhile?
I made a video about Nuclear Throne. And that's the only video I've ever made.
Oh, mama. That's really greasing up my.
Something that may be relevant to the people listening to this is that Munchy, you're the one who's drawn all of Digibroses' YouTube avatars, eh?
Yes. That's true. And I hate every single one of them.
Oh, you.
I like your work, Munchy. I think your work has a lot of character to it.
You make that hard line edging looking look better than most people do.
That's what I fucking hate about it.
Well, you hate the hard lines.
You do a pretty decent job with it.
All right. Well, this is about the one and only game, the one game ever made, Nuclear Throne.
Right, so Munchy, you are the resident expert because you're the only one that's beaten the throne.
You double looped, oh my gosh. I don't even know what double looping means.
It means beating the game twice.
All right, well, I guess I could have used my context.
In a row, like without dying. And it gets harder the second time.
God, you're fucking, I'm supposed to see his magic sage, Davoo. He doesn't know anything.
He's like a little fucking baby who can't learn anything.
I'm supposed to be the teacher.
I haven't looked up anything about the game. I've tried not to spoil myself.
That's good. That's what everyone should do.
I've just watched my video on it, a status update.
I still haven't gotten past Little Hunter, but well before even making the video,
I've watched play sessions of people looping up to four times.
I've even watched people looping twice on the most recent edition of the game.
So I am quite familiar with it. So, yeah.
Are you guys playing right now? I'm playing.
Yeah, I'm playing right now.
I don't know if this is the thing that's ever going to catch on.
It's this new genre that we've invented, this terrible abomination of content.
Ultra podcast 3D. Let's play a radio show, but you don't get to see the game.
Don't get to see it. And it's not like a podcast where one of the people is only,
is playing it and everyone else gets to just talk.
We're all going to be distracted playing it.
And you have to hear us making the noises.
This is going to be as much bedlam as the world of Nuclear Throne itself.
You know, I'm okay with that.
Listen, guys, I'm going to update you on my progress right now.
I have employed the secret ancient technique of ignoring weapon chests,
and I just got a super chest and I just got, I just got a wrench.
Fuck yeah, I just got a wrench. That means I'm all set for the sewers.
Yeah, well, I definitely found that out.
Wrench is my way of life.
The game tells you.
Well, Wrench was my way of life until I unlocked chicken.
I'm currently playing chicken right now.
When you have chicken, you don't need the wrench, which is great,
because I don't even, I never, there was to be, sometimes I'd start playing
and I wouldn't get the wrench in the first couple of levels,
so I just start over.
Yeah.
Because without the wrench, it's not worth it.
I mean, I can manage the sewers with a gun, but I don't like to.
You people are fucking babies.
It's not that I think the wrench is kids.
I could pick you up and throw you to do.
No, no, it's not that it's not, it's not, it's not that the wrench is easy.
It's that it's fun as hell.
It is fun.
By the way, I just died in the sewers, which obviously means I'm pretty distracted.
Oh, my gosh, God.
Okay, hold on.
How many hours do you have in this game, Davoo?
I have like 23.
Oh, man.
And you haven't even seen the labs yet, dude.
You don't know what labs.
Well, I've seen them on YouTube.
I know.
Wrench, that's absurd.
How do you know they even exist if you haven't seen it?
Everyone could be lying to you, Davoo.
Yeah, I've always been on the lookout for that kind of stuff.
Wrench, did you check how much time I have?
Yes, yes, you have 19 hours.
Oh, cool.
Yeah, I know.
Wow.
See, because for me, 23 hours is impressive.
Like, that's as much time as I spend on games these days.
Davoo, Davoo, Davoo.
I have 372 hours in this game.
Excellent.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
All right, well, I'll just, I think I expected to get, I expected to get good at this game faster than I actually have.
It's been harder than I thought because I was already in Binding of Isaac Pro from back in the day.
This game is very different.
And I mean, it's basically the same game.
No, it's so different.
It's basically the same game.
It's, it's in principle, in principle, it's the same.
One, it doesn't look bad.
Yeah, exactly.
I don't...
Binding of Isaac look great.
What are you talking about?
I mean, okay, maybe it'll look great.
Cause like, when I'm actually playing Super Meat Boy, I think as, that's the same artist, right?
Yes, yes.
Right.
It's not fun for me to watch, but when I'm playing it, I'm like, okay, whatever.
I disagree actually.
I think...
But even it doesn't look that good in my opinion.
I'm just like, it just looks like everything is really dull.
Maybe it's because I spent lots and lots and lots of time on Newgrounds.
I'm jaded to that look.
But with Nuclear Throne, it was, I was looking for something to make a video out of and then one screenshot into looking at Nuclear Throne.
I'm like, that looks like something I would be into.
The art is the only thing I can't nitpick in this game because I fucking love it.
Yeah.
One look at Nuclear Throne and I was pretty much sold.
It immediately looks exactly like the kind of game I want to play.
This was actually, this game, getting into this game was the end of me like, talk, like being worried about pixel art.
Talking about how maybe we should stop doing pixel art.
Pixel shit!
I love pixel shit.
Cause I was like...
Yeah.
What is this Undertale game?
Pixel art always...
It's just some pixel shit, man.
Pixel art always works out well.
And I'm just like, it makes games look so similar.
But then I was like, I was playing Nuclear Throne and I'm like, you know what?
Yeah, but that's not really true.
Fuck it.
Forget about it.
Yeah, exactly.
Oh yeah, they all look way different.
That's the other thing.
But also, it's just too effective.
It just works too well to not use it constantly.
And I mean, it's a simple, effective way.
To look professional.
Like, yeah.
And it works.
And it fucking works.
So why shouldn't people do it?
Cause in my journeys of trying to dig up random obscure Steam games to make videos out of,
I've discovered just how many...
Like, we all know about those Steam Greenlight trailer things that are utterly terrible.
But there's a lot of stuff that's like in a middle ground period where it's a competent game.
It's like on the level of an old LJN game rather than on the level of Big Riggs, for instance.
And those are the most unpleasant in a way because it's like, wow, this person is actually good at one thing.
Like, some of them will have decent level design.
Some of them will have decent graphics.
And it's like, if only this guy worked in a team where he only had to do the one thing he's good at,
instead of all the millions of other things he's not good at.
They always have terrible font choices.
They're usually really badly optimized.
And things feel gross and unprofessional.
But when they're pixel art, that's never...
That's almost...
That's not as much of an issue usually.
And I'm just like, dang it.
I guess pixel art just has to be a thing.
And we just have to love it as much as we want to.
Well, see, I think pixel art is better than anything.
Yeah, I can't necessarily disagree.
I mean, that's why I don't like...
I just like the aesthetic.
I just like the anti-Islist and shit.
I don't like it.
I just like the aesthetic, even aside from all the development advantages it offers.
Yeah.
It's like, in order to have an aesthetic that's as appealing as Nuclear Throne without pixel art,
you have to be Ori and the Blind Forest level.
And it's like, nope.
Have you guys seen...
Have you seen a sword and sorcery?
I've seen it.
I don't know anything about it, but I've seen one screenshot.
Now there's a game with pixel art that's really attractive and really unique.
It really has its own atmosphere to it.
I'm sure I know the name.
I'm sure I know the game.
I just can't connect the name to the game when the name is that generic sounding.
Yeah.
Dude, imagine a dude with a sword and he's in like a medieval times.
It's that one, yeah.
It's a girl though.
I don't want 90% share.
I got to the rainy zone and then died again.
Again, I'm just running shit up.
The rainy zone?
It's a junkyard, right?
Yeah, junkyard.
I just died on Mad Dog.
Scrapyard.
Yeah, I just died on Mad Dog.
What I like about chicken is that I can run into fucking everything.
And then even when I die, I have a chance of coming back.
Actually, when I died, I actually did come back, but I got my health back by hitting one of those explosion sniper guys.
So I killed myself in reviving myself and died again.
Dude, I used to do that all the time.
I've pretty much gotten over.
I haven't unlocked.
I've only unlocked like half the characters.
Like chicken is the most recent one I've unlocked.
I haven't unlocked white bee yet.
I just unlocked chicken today.
Dude, white bee, I keep telling you how to do it too.
I know, but I haven't gotten around to it yet.
I'm sorry.
I can do it in this podcast.
I don't know.
Yeah, you should do that.
He's the second best character in the game, dude.
Wait, who?
I gotta get the freaking...
Oh my god.
He's the cool one.
The Eskimo.
The triangle.
Oh, young Venus.
Yeah.
And it's so cool because it's like, I've seen like one fan art picture of him with Bill from Gravity Falls.
Oh my fucking god.
They're the same character.
I know they are.
It's like reliving everything that I used to be.
Not in like a bad way, but like reliving my experiences with this game, like down to a T.
And I like that.
Oh, I see.
So it's like, so it's like you're looking at it through our fresh eyes.
Yeah.
You're like a newborn baby.
It's the fact that this is new.
In all the right ways, Finn.
This is what I hate about early access.
This is a new game, but you're an expert in it.
You have all these memories in it.
You know, that's FU.
Oh yeah, that brings me to the point.
Like I said before, as soon as I saw this game, I knew I wanted to play it, but I refused
to because it was an early access.
Oh.
Well, I mean, I've seen very early versions of it.
It did not look very different in its early ones.
Yeah.
It had most of the same stuff.
But I still didn't, I still didn't, I didn't want to play it in early access because I didn't
want to get good at a game that would then go on to not count for anything.
Like, like I play this roguelike game called Dungeon Crawlstone Soup and the game is an
active development and every time they update it, like the classes change around all the
time.
Like the first time I ever beat the game, I was a crusader and now the crusader class
doesn't even exist anymore.
It's been completely retooled and renamed.
And like, so like if I were to tell someone how I won the game back then, they would be
like, they wouldn't even mean anything because the shit didn't even exist anymore.
Gosh darn it.
I died in the sewers again.
Again, I'm just running right into everything.
This is great.
I'm having a good old time, yo.
You know what?
I'm okay with that.
And I'm sure the game is too.
Yeah, I'm not, I'm not really trying that hard.
I just killed like three basilisks or salamanders or whatever.
Yeah.
The single shotgun blast.
I remember when I first got this game, it was gifted to me by a friend.
He said, you should play this game, dude.
And I said, all right.
And then six months later, I decided maybe I should play that game.
Yep, destination steam, y'all.
I think the, like literally the second level was just, all right, this is my favorite game.
It's so, it's so, just the way you move and the way you interact with everything is so
crystal clear and nice and polished.
It has, okay, I maintain that it is basically Binding of Isaac, but it does have a way better
game feel.
I don't know how you can even like, like say that though.
Well, there, dude, they're both, they're both, you know, top-down shooters.
Yes.
They both have roguelike elements.
They both have randomized, you know, power-ups and permadeath, randomized levels.
And that's it.
That's it.
Wow, they're both in the same genre.
Yeah.
All right, fine.
Face it then.
We don't like you anymore.
Well, what other games are there that fit that description?
Other than like obvious knockoffs of one or the other?
The Binding of Isaac Rebirth is not like the Binding of Isaac.
I haven't played Rebirth.
See?
Uh, whatever, man.
Everyone could be lying to you.
It could be a Gallagher.
Eventually I'll go back to it.
Yeah, it was, it was an interesting story with, you know, the YV thing because obviously this
game came out after Gravity Falls, but YV is based on an older game by the dude from 2010.
Yeah, it's better.
Yeah.
It's better than Gravity Falls?
Well, yes, but then this...
What's better than what?
Uh, Gun Gods is better than this game only because it sets out to what it achieves to do, I feel.
Wait, this game doesn't set out to do what it sets out to do?
Well, I'm very jaded with this game and I'm going to explain why because I got, well,
what were you about to say then?
I was going to say, yeah, tell us why you hate this game.
Yeah, dude, what the heck?
You're supposed to... this isn't...
What is Vayre Emotion, y'all?
All right, okay.
I got this game, I would say, five months before release and there were a lot of features that
Landbeer, like, wanted to do.
Well, I wouldn't say wanted to do, but needed to do.
And they didn't deliver and that's why I'm sort of jaded to the whole thing and I feel
like whatever...
You think it could have been better?
I think that's the one thing with Early Access games that is just inherent.
It's that you, like, see the process of, like, how it's...
Like, all games are like that.
Like, all games don't end up being quite, you know, if they were initially...
The problem with Early Access is that the audience then shares in on that disappointment.
Yeah, exactly.
So what the heck was missing from this game?
Because it feels quite complete to me.
Yeah, yeah, maybe I don't even want to know what it's missing.
Yeah, you know what?
Yo, we're doing this podcast for a reason.
What is it missing?
Cheese, Davoo.
You're getting hostile.
Okay, it's missing Friendship Mode, which was four-player co-op, which is a real thing.
Oh.
Hey, hey, hey, Davoo.
This podcast would be a lot better if we could all be playing it together.
Yeah, it would be.
No, it would be a lot better if we were all playing in co-op.
That would be rad.
Yeah.
Is there a planned multiplayer coming?
Well, well, there is multiplayer.
There is?
It's...
Oh my...
Yeah.
There is?
It's local, though.
Oh, that sucks.
Oh, I want to tell you my new band name.
It's called Extremely Donking Technical Challenge.
And that's because a quote from Rami when the developer says they're not going to put it in an online multiplayer,
because it would be an extremely daunting technical challenge for a 2D Twitch game.
And I really like that quote.
I'm going to put it up on my wall.
Extremely.
I got the screwdriver, so I'm going to hit that against a truck or a vehicle in the junkyard, right?
Do you know the car?
Do you know what it looks like?
No, you can describe it to me when I get there.
It's a slightly different color than the other cars.
That's all you need to know.
Yeah.
Right.
Yeah, because I've seen footage of YV and read him on the wiki.
I'm like, whoa, that is wicked cool.
More cool.
He's more cool than...
He doesn't seem like the kind of character that I'd want to play,
but then again, I think I'm playing the game wrong,
because I only get real defensively.
Chicken's the character that I want to play,
but I just appreciate seeing YV and knowing it's a thing.
He's more cool than Bill, because he doesn't mess around with a bunch of random kids in freakin' Washington.
He does whatever once he goes and kills things.
It's way cooler.
I like him more because he's black.
Yeah.
Who? Young Venus?
Are you black?
Are you going to be one of those surprise black people who I didn't think was black?
Surprise black people?
Dude, the number of people who turned out to be black, British, or Australian,
who I've known online is impeccable, the number.
Well, okay, okay.
First of all, we're going to transition to a new topic.
What do you think I look like based on what you know about me?
Like, you're scribing great detail.
Oh, shit, Sledgehammer.
Well, it's weird because you have such a high-pitched voice or like a pretty high-pitched voice,
but I vaguely remember Digibro describing you as being like looking way older than you are.
Am I getting you confused with someone else?
No.
No, that's him.
Okay, because...
I don't know if he looks older.
He just looks bigger.
Okay.
Well, I mean, I did have a full beard when I met you, so...
Yeah, but it was a young person beard.
True.
I feel like it's gotten way thicker and I feel like between my fingers when I rub my face
sensually during my sessions...
It's very intimidating.
Yeah.
It's a very intimidating description.
I want to talk about the game.
Okay.
I want to talk about strats.
I want to talk about builds and how you guys...
Builds.
...prefer to play.
Because like I was saying, because I've been playing Crystal and I'm just...
I'm very disposed in games in general to play with them defensively and to be like very
healing.
Mm-hmm.
And so I...
Crystal suits that urge in me, so I'm always getting bloodlust and I'm always getting a
second stomach and just trying to, you know, heal myself as much as I can.
Yeah, everything I pick is healing related pretty much.
Mm-hmm.
Except for the melee extension.
That's the only thing that I always pick that isn't healing related.
Oh, you got the melee DLC, the extension pack for it?
No, like the thing that makes your melee more...
Yeah, Davoo!
...makes you move further.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, Davoo.
Yeah.
Brilliant.
Excellent.
So I just came...
Whoops.
I came back to life with chicken and then immediately died again.
Oh, crud.
And there was a freaking health pack right in front of me.
Dang, dude.
That's fucking rough.
I like how we just totally just didn't answer a bit.
Davoo, you go first.
I'm gonna die again.
I'm a mad dog.
Fucking mad dog, man.
I need concentration for mad dog.
What is it that I need to answer?
Uh, what have we been asked?
I don't remember what you asked.
Loadout strats.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, what's your strategy and like what kind of character do you choose to play?
Um, well, I was playing eyes constantly because it was...
One strategy I had, which was probably stupid, was holding down the right key constantly
because then, as eyes, it would cause everything to move in a slightly more predictable pattern
because it's all moving slightly towards me.
That was my philosophy.
It was my theory.
Is that if everything is moving towards me, then I'm more in control of the environment
because I know where everything is going slightly.
But then, of course, it was also very distracting holding down the right key constantly.
I actually do that, actually.
And I think it gets less distracting, but I don't know if it's different strokes or different people.
Eyes seems really weird, and I don't think I want to fuck with them.
Eyes, if you get euphoria in his throne butt, you don't have to play the game.
What's his throne butt do?
It makes you win the game.
What?
I'm confused.
Basically, it makes his telekinesis much stronger, and by much stronger, I mean, you can stand in front of the throne
and it won't be able to hit you.
Oh, well, yeah, I've gotten that, but I haven't been able to win the game with it.
Maybe you can beat the final boss with it.
I mean, I would say that I thought his throne butt was much better than it actually is
because on loops, you don't want that many freaks inside of your vicinity.
But I think if you get euphoria and then just normal eyes, he's still good.
I think eyes gets a bad rat.
I hate Crystal's throne butt. I never get it.
I can see why it's good, but I'm not good enough to get the most out.
Crystal's active is a shield.
Crystal's throne butt doesn't last as long, but if you keep holding down the mouse,
when it cancels, you teleport to wherever your cursor is,
which is really weird, and I can see how it would be so good,
but I always spaz out, and it ends up ending before I expected to,
so I don't have my cursor in a good position.
I end up teleporting to some places I don't want to be.
It doesn't make a whole lot of diegetical sense.
It's kind of ineligently conceived right there.
What the heck is that supposed to be in the universe?
I don't know about that. I'm just saying it kills me more often than it saves me.
I'm actually going to tell you a secret before I go on bin about why I hate this game more.
Do either of you know what the purple weapon's mean?
I'm in the snow town, by the way.
Do either of you know, have you ever seen a purple weapon?
No.
Died in the sewers again.
You're really good to view.
When you get a crown, or have you seen a crown before?
Yeah, I got the crown. I got a crown once.
Okay, when you get a crown, there's a chance that the weapon chest will turn into a purple weapon chest,
and that will give you a cursed weapon.
Oh, the cursed ones, yeah.
You can't drop them, but they are like a higher tier than the level that you get it.
If you get a cursed weapon and you go to the crystal caves, which is 4-1,
something scary will happen, and you'll pee yourself.
Not like in a funny way, but in like a scared, like home alone, like I drank too much Pepsi way.
Home Alone is a funny movie.
I got tired of just running it, so I'm going to actually try now.
Yeah, I feel like there should be a nuclear-thrown character based on Kevin from Home Alone.
What would Kevin's action be?
I just had a snow golem throw a car at me, and it hit me, and it's never happened before,
but luckily I'm crystal, so I can take it.
Oh my god!
Oh man, that sucked.
When that happened to me, I was like, what the fuck hit me?
Thankfully, I was recording to find out, and I was so mad,
because I was like, that doesn't look very threatening.
There's no giant wind-up, there's no giant arrow going,
watch out, this is going to kill you immediately, all at once.
You know, I can't forget to take advantage of Chicken's weapon throw ability,
because that means I can get through this while wielding both my sword and my screwdriver,
without having any actual guns, if I take advantage of her weapon throw ability.
I'm concentrating so hard trying to dodge all these fucking wolf bullets.
I'm going back to eyes, all eyes on me.
Ooh, that's something you just said.
Yeah.
First level of Snowden is done.
Wow.
Let's talk about how this game is literally undertale.
One, you have pixels on screen.
There's hearts.
Yeah, there's hearts in this game.
It's a bad time.
It's a bad time? You always have a bad time.
Well, I mean, the character does, that's for sure.
Yeah.
And also, there's someone who wears a coat.
There we go.
I think we should get Toby Fox to see this.
Rebel looks exactly like Sans, and it's really distracting.
Well, let's see.
I mean, I guess I can see what you mean by that.
I mean, I saw the sprite and I thought it was Sans for a second.
Wait, who do you think it was, Sans?
Rebel in her costume.
I thought you had bought like a skin.
No, but believe me, I worked for this.
So I've got really shitty mutations right now.
I've got Throne Butt, which I don't want because it'll kill me.
Wait, wait, what do you have?
Extra Feet, Hammerhead, or Bolt Marrow.
Bolt Marrow is fucking amazing.
Shut your garbage eating eye hole.
But I don't have a bolt weapon.
Well.
Alright, fine.
Just because I've never taken it before, I'll take it and I'll get a bolt weapon, I guess.
Believe me, dude.
I didn't tell you what my strats are.
No, you're the only one whose strats matter.
You're the only one who's winning and won the game.
Why don't you tell me what your strats are, and I'll tell you what you're doing wrong.
Yeah.
I've told you my strats are get all the healing items.
Killed by Little Hunter.
Yeah, get all the healing items, get Bloodlust, get Second Stomach, get Rabbit's Foot, and Rhino Skin,
and just heal myself into an early grave.
Alright, well.
Rabbit Paw is necessary for any good run, so you're right there.
Also, I just looped, by the way.
Oh, shit.
And I died two times, of course, so that's why I'm behind.
But anyway.
Hold on.
I can't fucking speak.
Crystal, her throne butt.
Let me tell you something, first of all, by the way.
Yeah, please.
Before it was like this, it was still teleporting, but you teleported before you went out of your shield.
You would click on some part of the screen, and you would instantly go there, well inside your shield,
and then you would come out of it normally.
Oh, so you'd hold the right mouse button, you'd be in the shield, and then while you were shielding,
you'd click and it would teleport you?
Yeah.
That sounds cool.
Yeah, it was much better, but they decided to nerf her because she was too good, and she still is too good,
because she's a safe character, and I hate safe characters in video games.
Yeah.
And then you just not play them, because I almost never play freaking Crystal,
because I'm like, okay, I'm tired of dying, time to play the character with the shield,
but then I go into the shield, and I immediately get bored.
I'm like, all right, back to the crazy ones.
Yeah.
See, I don't find Crystal boring, because with Crystal, I don't have to wait for enemies to stop.
I don't have to be safe to come out of cover.
I can just rush right out of cover, and I don't have to even fucking worry about anything.
True.
Like in Dark Souls, almost everything I did, I expect myself to basically be able to run up at things.
I didn't wear pants, didn't have any armor, and I got the Demon Spear, because it has a crazy long range,
and I just played that constantly.
I've never played Dark Souls before, so I can't comment on that, but I will say I want to play Dark Souls,
because you can be a black guy in it.
Continue.
Well, you're mostly without any skin.
Your blackness will not be appreciated.
But I can be black, right?
My brother did make a black knight called Sir Homie in Dark Souls.
The point is, I tend to favor characters like chicken.
One recent exception is in Downwell, I picked the version of the game mode where you have the most health,
because you are really slick and fast, no matter which version of that game you pick.
Nobody agrees with me, but for me, Floaty is so much easier than any other mode.
Playing Floaty feels like easy mode to me.
I do like Floaty, that's pretty good.
I can't, yeah.
Maybe it's because I don't do any other mode, but I've never won on any other mode.
Well, I have never won on any other mode other than I've never won it.
So, let's talk about Nuclear Throne's characters, which are great.
Wait, no, before you do that on Downwell, I remember I played it for two seconds and said,
this is the hardest thing I've ever seen before in my entire life, and I got my money back, I refunded it.
Oh, bullshit, bullshit, fuck you, that guy.
Downwell deserves so much.
I would consider Downwell and Nuclear Throne to be pretty similar aesthetically,
not aesthetically in terms of visuals, but aesthetically in terms of how it makes you feel with its challenge,
because it's just this impossible challenge that you can just bang your head against 5,200,000 in three times,
and it's still fun every time, so, you know, that's what I like.
I play Nuclear Throne and Downwell for the same reasons.
They give me the same kind of thrill.
I don't like going down, I want to see things go up.
That's why I play RuneScape, classic to this day, because I like seeing numbers go up.
I got very tired of ever since Bloons Tower Defense, I permanently jaded myself to numbers.
That was my...
That's upsetting.
It was Bloons Tower's Defense, your 9-11 DeVue.
Yes.
I couldn't defend those towers.
Everyone has, like, some giant grind-em-up game that they played a million hours of,
but it's usually something famous, whereas mine was...
I have many of those.
Everyone has at least one.
That was my only one.
That's like the only game I've ever gotten big into the grind of,
just because instead of... I can't deal with, like, killing things all day,
but popping Bloons as a monkey or as a million monkeys is great.
So I've sunk between Bloons Tower...
This is relatable, right?
You say so.
Between Bloons Tower Defense 4 and 5, I've sunk about over a thousand hours,
which I know isn't that impressive by many people's standards, but...
Oh, my God.
Point was, that's how I got jaded to numbers, and now I don't care about numbers at all, hardly.
I'm sure I'll get back into them,
but for now, I like something like Nuclear Throne or Downwell,
where your numbers don't mean shit the moment you fuck up just a little bit and you die,
and you get to start back to zero, my favorite number.
Here's what I like.
Here's something I like about Nuclear Throne.
If you, like, fucking up, isn't that frustrating?
Because, like, in another game, like in Downwell, if I get hit early on,
I say fuck it, and I quit, and I restart, because messing up early on
is like you pay for it the whole game.
In Nuclear Throne, if I get, like, if I completely mess up and I'm, like,
ah, killed by an assassin, if I completely mess up and, like, get down to one health right away,
it's not really that hard to recover.
Oh, yeah.
Like, I play smart for a while.
Yeah, ironically, well, I guess it's not ironically.
Nuclear Throne is a lot less depressing than Downwell.
It's less oppressive than Downwell.
Yeah.
It's way more fun.
I mean, don't get me wrong, I like it way more than Downwell.
It's much more interesting looking and more fun to play and stuff.
Interesting look.
Dude, I love the aesthetic of Downwell.
Holy shit.
Oh, yeah, Downwell is great in its own way, but I do, like, Nuclear Throne more.
I think in terms of aesthetics, I would have to go with Downwell,
just because it's, I don't know, it's just a little more unique in its presentation.
Downwell has a more distinct and thick presentation,
and of course, you can pick your own palette.
Although, once I unlocked the Vivid palette, I was like,
this is the only palette I want.
If I had unlocked that before making my video on it,
that would have been like all the footage you would have seen.
Vivid? Which one's Vivid?
The best looking one. It's like, I don't know, it's like,
it's just the most pleasantly looking one.
I don't like any, I don't like any of the non-standard ones.
I think they're all inferior to the original.
Well, I guess they do kind of dilute the amount of your Innawell,
and it's dark, and there's things that shine.
I just make it harder for me to understand what's going on.
I can't believe I just figured that out.
The whole reason for Downwell's color scheme, how things are brighter on the top,
is because you're in a well and you're seeing the light from the top.
I can't believe I just realized that's why things are colored that way in Downwell.
Yeah, I guess that's kind of true.
Alright, well we'll discuss this more in depth in Downwell cast.
Going back to Nuclear Throne,
when meditating on 2015 games, and like, what's my favorite character from 2015?
Oh dude, we should totally do a Downwell cast.
I would be so up for that.
What's going on? Who's having a seizure?
I died.
I died in the freaking desert.
I died in loop 3-3 to Big Bad Man. Stupid.
I just died, I just died to the freaking, the big, the big bandit.
That's how distracted I'm getting, but at least I'm talking well.
Yes, I realized that the whole cast of Nuclear Throne is my favorite character from 2015.
I'm going to be a dang downer right now, because I honestly don't feel very much for the characters at all.
What's the big deal?
What's the big deal about the characters in Nuclear Throne?
They're just there.
They're mechanically different.
I read the Wiki, because I wanted to make sure I knew my stuff before making videos.
I read the Wiki, and they all have one paragraph bios.
With video game characters, I can judge them based on how they feel to play as.
That's how I judge video game characters.
It's like, as eyes, I can freaking pull stuff around.
And it's like, that's a cool character to be, and so I like him as a character.
Something very progressive, of course, that Nuclear Throne does is it has female characters that don't look female at all.
That was obviously something they went out of their way to do.
I mean, Crystal looks a little bit female.
Not hardly. I didn't think she was a girl.
No. That's not accurate.
Are you saying she looks totally female, or that she doesn't look at all?
I'm saying she looks like a rock.
Right, exactly.
And I think that they were trying to respond to the sentiment, not to the video itself,
but to the sentiment of one Jimquisition video where he pointed out, in his observation,
there's very few female characters in games who don't look attractive and don't have any motivations that are related to traditional woman-ish things.
Like, if they just want to be either or just want to make money or something.
I can appreciate it on the grounds that we take a generic looking character as assumed to be male,
but it doesn't have to be that way.
The generic one is the male, and the one with the bow on it is the girl.
Yeah, exactly.
But these characters are fucking monsters.
I do love the bow principle.
I love the idea that putting a bow on something makes it female.
I understand why Cartman understood that same principle.
But I can also love a game that doesn't do that.
And chicken obviously is a chicken, so it makes sense.
But then there's the one human character, the freaking rebel.
And what I loved is that rebel...
Well, it's cute.
It's cute and all, but I don't agree with it.
So I appreciate that nuclear throne goes out of its way to subvert it.
Yeah, well, I just actively enjoy that fact.
Hi, we're back.
The call kind of got broken up.
I was making a point about how rebel can help you confirm that you aren't racist,
because when I was looking at Rebel on the wiki,
I live in a place where almost everyone is white.
So if someone isn't white, I make a mental note,
like this person has this kind of hair, that kind of face,
and this is their skin color if they're not white.
One time I lived in Africa for a bit.
And you're saying that this helped you find out you're not racist?
It gave me a minute.
And so when I killed myself with my own buzz saw launcher,
it was a time I was in Africa, and if someone was white,
I made a mental note of them being white.
So that's just how you do it, that's just how you categorize things.
And when I was on the nuclear throne wiki,
I didn't even think about the fact that she was black because she was human,
and that stuck out to me more, you see?
So yeah.
Okay, when I was making that point originally...
I don't like her.
I don't like that she is such like a normal looking human
in a cast of like crazy monsters.
Now on the one hand, I can kind of appreciate that she's...
I can appreciate that she's like the control, you know?
Like everyone else is a horrible mutant,
and she's like the one normal one and sticks out for that.
And that's fine.
I think in-game she looks pretty good,
but her character art on the wiki looks really like,
really cartoony in a way that clashes with it.
You know, it's no wonder that nothing happens in your comic,
because you just hate ideas in general.
You know, just like anything that's like an idea,
you just don't like it,
and that's why your comic has nothing happening in it.
It's just characters sitting around.
Whoa!
Personal attacks, here we go.
Coming out swinging.
No, your comic is great.
Explain to me.
Your comic is great.
I want you to go more into depth with what you just said.
But first of all, I want to say that
when I was first making that point about Rebel,
that was when the call broke,
and so then I just thought you guys were like dead silent from awkwardness.
I'm like, oh no, this is not coming out right.
Oh God, I'm racist.
By the way, you're thinking of Rogue, not Rebel.
Oh wait, which one is, wait.
Rebel is the mummy.
Rebel is the one with allies.
How can a mummy be a rebel?
If they're a mummy, that means they died in royalty.
Because she's a bandit, dude.
She's a bandit, and her brother is a big bandit.
Don't you understand the deep, convoluted, deep-full, good, insightful,
insightful, progressive, deep-full.
Yeah, deep-full is my new game.
Deep-full just came out of early access.
What do you do?
Oh, everything is so deep-full.
It's a great story, and my favorite character is Undine.
She's my favorite character in this game.
I like to play as her, and let's stop talking about this now.
I never told you what my strats were.
Yeah.
No, you didn't.
But before you do, I'm hung up.
I'm hung up.
What did you mean, Davoo, when you said that I hate ideas?
Well, I don't know.
What did you mean?
I don't know your opinions enough.
I was just, that was like a random joke.
Obviously, your comic is great.
Okay, but what were you thinking that made?
I'm just not sure what that phrase means.
Well, disliking the fact that she's a human as the only human,
because for me, if I was in the creative department of Nuclear Throne,
I'd be like, all right, guys, we obviously want to have the one character who's human,
but where's an interesting costume and stuff.
That's the idea that I would have.
And so when you said you didn't like that as a concept,
I'm just trying to compile all the different negative opinions I've heard you say,
and I feel like just a wild guess.
There's a chain of ideas that you would probably want to include in something.
Like, oh, in a world where I want to monster have the one human.
That's a pretty obvious idea.
And so maybe, again, I have no idea if this is true,
you have a personal inclination against those kinds of ideas,
which is why you've decided to make this comic.
You told me that nothing happens in this comic that you're making, right?
Well, it's not that nothing happens.
It's a comic about nothing.
Right.
I'm just thinking maybe there's a connection.
But let me restate.
I think you're right.
I don't think it's actually, I have a problem with her being the only human,
but I really did not care for the big MLP eyes on her character art in the witty.
Maybe they could have toned it down enough.
I wasn't into it.
Maybe they could have toned it down a bit, but I love them,
because it like her eyes just beam out of every, you know, like her eye.
You can't see that much of her face, but what you can is mostly eyes.
Very adorable.
And, you know, she wears a giant costume.
And it's like, whoa.
It's like, even though she's human, she wears this crazy costume, you know?
She's like a ghostbuster.
Cool stuff.
There's one fundamental flaw in what you're saying right now.
There's one big flaw.
She's not a human.
She's an ape.
Oh, she's not human.
What is she?
No, no, she is.
I called her an ape.
She's human.
Oh, sorry.
The call cut out in that part.
Oh.
The call cut out at just the right.
The call is cutting out all racism towards Rogue.
Munchy, let's hear your strats, because you're the only one who's a pro.
I've been waiting for this.
Oh, let me get inside my mecca, where I host all my ideas.
Please.
Idea number one.
I play as Rebels, so none of this applies to you.
Idea number two.
I only have two health mutations, because don't be a little bitch.
Number three.
Don't get your throne butt, but if you want to, you should get your throne butt.
Wow, that's a pretty...
That's kind of an irrelevant strategy.
Do it or don't.
Idea number three.
We need to get clean drinking water to Africa.
We should innovate in car design.
We should innovate in nuclear throne, but in real life.
And most importantly, remember to have fun and be yourself.
Stop bullying.
I think bullying builds character.
Sure, but what kind of character?
Don't take this in a racial direction.
You're going to break the call again.
Believe me, it's not racial.
It's sexual, not in a sensual kind of way.
But in an inferiority kind of way.
Yeah.
Like you agree, right?
Of course.
DeVoo, on record, you agree with me, right?
No, I don't.
We had different opinions.
I'm going to edit the footage, so DeVoo is actually the one who's saying all that.
And I'm saying no, DeVoo, that's horrible.
Why would you say that?
It's the magic of video editing.
The magic of post-production.
Wait, do you guys have the game Sound On for yourselves?
Yeah.
I have it on very, very low.
What the heck am I doing?
Of course, this game is...
You need the sound to know what's happening.
Yeah.
But no wonder I've been stuck.
Yeah, you do.
That's one thing I do like about the game.
It's one game that forces me to have Sound On because of how much the sound helps, you know?
Yeah, it really does.
That's what I'm talking about when I say this game has good game feel.
Like, have the screen shakes whenever you shoot a bullet, and it's...
Binding of Isaac didn't have that shit.
No, sir.
Well, see, Flambier is like the god of that.
They're like the Sumerian god of creation.
That's what I heard when it comes to good games.
That's what you called chicken.
No, you called chicken a Sumerian god of destruction.
Yeah.
I'm seeing a strange logical through line in your comparisons in Flambier content.
Well, see, I myself am a Sumerian god, so it would make sense that I reference my content.
Sure.
This is going to be the best podcast on the face of the planet.
I was surprised how good it was for the first 20.
I guess it's actually coming out pretty good, given the nature of its production.
There are nugget.
There are definite nuggets in here that are good.
All right.
There's a lot of bugs.
Hopefully, the keyboard and mouse sounds will give people some ASMR.
Yeah.
Not with this microphone.
Just like Funky Kong taking you home from the airport.
Yes.
Everyone, stop watching this podcast or listening to a go watch ASMR Funky Kong.
Caring and supportive takes you home from the airport.
The best ASMR video I've yet seen.
Now, I was going to ask if that's a real thing, but I'm sure it is.
Yeah, it is.
Is it exactly what it sounds like?
Yes.
Okay.
It's much better.
Well, I want to see it.
It sounds great.
All right.
It sounds like a real edifying experience.
I see more characters that are cool.
I guess...
Yeah, let me go back to...
I don't get what it is about the characters that's so great because I don't know anything
about them.
Honestly, the game doesn't give them much personality aside from the mechanical ways
they play.
That's not entirely true, but I agree with what you're trying to pick at.
That does say a lot about the character, but...
They're tooltips, dude.
Yeah, they become...
I get to become them, so that's why they're cool.
Yeah, I guess they have character-specific tooltips.
Okay.
Well, yeah, I have noticed a bunch of character-specific tooltips, but they haven't really told me
anything about Crystal.
Oh, yeah.
That's because they don't like Crystal because she's not cool.
Oh.
I mean, she said something about family, and she keeps...
She says, like, oh, it's not right.
It's not fair.
What does that mean?
Okay, you know the school of characterization where you only come up with a...
You only explain a couple of details, and the rest of it is your imagination welling
up with a bunch of ideas for the details.
Obviously, you can't just do that and automatically make it work.
It has to be...
The couple of details that you do expose it have to be done just right for that to work,
and for me, Nuclear Throne, that totally works.
And also the way that the characters feel together.
If there was a game that only had one of them or only three of them, it wouldn't be nearly
as cool as the fact that they're all together.
And I'm looking at the character select screen, and they're all at the campfire.
They all feel like they're part of the same mission in a way.
They all go out on their own to get to the Nuclear Throne independently, but there's this
moment where they're all at the campfire together, getting ready to get going.
I agree with that.
They are a very diverse and colorful cast, but they're also all very unified in their
design, so I think that's pretty sweet.
I love stuff like that.
Which is maybe why Rebel, I think, I didn't care for her.
Rogue!
Rogue, because she stands out a little.
I'm just...
Yeah, I'm the trendsetter.
Yeah, but I'm with you on that front.
I mean, look, obviously there was probably some bunch of games out there with better
character casts than Nuclear Throne that came out this year.
I just haven't played a whole lot of games this year.
What game could possibly have a more diverse character cast than this?
There's a skeleton from this game?
Did you know that?
Oh yeah, I do know that, yeah.
Which is kind of weird, because isn't it melting like almost a skeleton?
Yeah, but it's not always halfway to being a skeleton.
He's almost a skeleton, that's pretty cool.
I don't really play him.
Almost.
He's halfway in his evolution from man to skeleton.
The natural end point of all life.
Well, I mean, I wasn't sure if you were baiting this response to Voo, but Undertale had a pretty
diverse cast.
I was baiting the response.
Yeah, that had, you know...
Well, what I love about the Undertale characters is the way that they're written in this.
Other than Flowey and especially Sans, those are characters I like.
I think about how cool those characters are independently of the game themselves.
But what I love about the characters in Undertale is how they work with the story and with each other
and all the other elements.
Whereas the cast of Nuclear Throne, obviously the way that they fit with the game is great,
but also their own aesthetic does make me feel like...
I don't know, it's the kind of thing where I could be walking around and be like,
oh man, I wish I had eyes, powers, and I could drag that towards me.
I mean, if this killed me, I sure would like to be able to run around for five seconds
and try to get my life back.
Uh... I guess, I mean...
Whereas I never go around thinking wishing I was a gay fish, like Kanye West or Rondine.
I think that every second of my life, every second of my life, no matter what action...
Why has no one done an undying gay fish AMV yet?
That's a crime.
I don't understand the reference.
There's an episode of South Park where they come up with a joke where they go,
the joke, Jimmy comes up with a joke, the joke is this, do you like fish dicks?
Yes, I like fish dicks.
He goes, what are you, a gay fish?
Everyone in the world loves the joke except Kanye West who doesn't get that it's a joke
and he thinks that people are accusing him of being a gay fish.
Then at the end of the episode, after he tries to get to the bottom of this,
he realizes they must be telling the truth, I must actually be a gay fish.
So he sings a song about him being a gay fish,
and he goes into the water and makes that with a bunch of male fish and then drowns.
And I just don't know why no one has done an AMV with that song to undine yet.
Uh... sounds like a great idea, you should get on it.
Maybe because we're not, we're not, we're above that as a culture.
Maybe we're 2,000 years of culture into the civilization,
and we don't need to degrade ourselves like that anymore to do.
Maybe this is an ancient Rome, where that kind of thing would be acceptable.
Yeah, well, I don't know.
Maybe we've finally moved past our perverse societal need to mash up things with other things.
No, man.
I've been putting on that Biggie Smalls Thomas tank engine mash up every day.
It's like one of the first things I do when I wake up.
As much as I wish I didn't like Space Jam remixes, they never get old.
They have yet to get old.
The best one is the Space Jam theme.
The little John one in Lazy Town, that one I'll never do that one.
Well, that one's only like a minute and a half long.
I like the mash-ups that go on for a while.
Yeah, it is pretty great though.
I better make a pretty cake.
What?
If the way's hazy, gotta do the cooking by the book.
Okay.
No one can do that voice though, that's the problem.
I've gone three disc guns on this one level alone.
I hate disc guns.
Why do they're good, dude?
They fucking kill you.
They die when you use a disc.
I like weapons that are dangerous.
No man, I've gotten to the point, back to actually talking about Nuclear Throne.
I've gotten to a point where I don't even pick up the good weapons
because they're too fucking dangerous.
Grenade launchers, I mean I can mostly handle a grenade launcher.
You're extremely wrong in your assessment that grenade launcher is a good weapon.
Okay, fine.
But I mean the stronger weapons, the more deadly ones.
Explosives basically is what I'm getting at.
I really like the flare gun because the flare gun can't kill you.
Oh my fucking god!
What?
I've never seen a human being so unsophisticated as you.
What's wrong with the flare gun?
It does one damage, ever.
That's not true, I have killed Snow-Mex with it in one shot.
Snow-Mex are way weaker than they look.
That's the weird thing about Snow-Mex, did they originally have more health
and they decided to nerf them?
Because they die so much quicker than you think they would.
Everything in Snowtown dies faster than I expected.
I go in there with heavy crossbows because everything's so big and intimidating
but then I went in with a revolver.
All I need to do is just put rust textures on all the enemies,
make them all look rusty.
Therefore, they would be more weak and easily deadified.
Dentified?
I feel like they do have some rust, don't they?
They might.
But they still look really scary and they just don't live up to that.
Have you ever seen one of the golden snow tanks?
Yes.
Oh yeah, sure.
Good, good.
I've gotten to the snow zone pretty often.
Quite a number of times.
I can't wait until you finally die to an Explodofreak in the labs.
I can't wait for that moment.
It'll be like you've all grown up.
I don't think I've ever died in the labs.
Good job.
I'm sure because once you get past Little Hunter you're in excellent mode,
you're in I gotta not die mode, you know?
Because you're in a rare state of success.
Little Hunter is so fucking easy.
I'm always so fucking terrified when I get to the labs
that I go wicked slowly and peek slowly around every corner
and launch all my bombs ahead of me just because I don't want to take any chances.
To the whole reason, one of the things that makes me really low...
I know why you're not doing well is because you're using Explosive Weapons.
Well I've stopped using Explosive Weapons because I'm too scared of them now.
See, it's sort of...
Because they just kill me every time.
Well not every time.
Honestly, I've gotten...
Oh fuck, Mad Dog just exploded and killed me because I'm stupid.
Speaking of dying and explosions.
No, I'm pretty good with grenade launchers.
But like, yeah, disc guns kill me every time.
Anything...
I got a nuke launcher against the nuclear throne once.
It didn't kill me?
What?
No, that's a good weapon.
That's unironically not misleading, that's a good weapon.
Yeah, it dropped in the throne room and I picked it up and I was just like firing nukes.
I got off like seven or eight of them before I was murdered by green bullets.
I have a gold one of those, say in my loadout screen for YP and it's very fun to get out sometimes.
Because you know, it may be kind of weird that I like this game so much.
I give it like a nine, even though I haven't really gotten that close to beating it.
I'm not that good at it.
But the reason I love it so much is that I can love it without having to be good at it.
I don't know.
I mean, I know what you mean, but I'm not like that.
For me, the whole draw of the game is the tension that it creates between just how badly I want to beat it.
So if I never beat nuclear throne, I will be pissed for the rest of my life.
I mean, up to doing my review of it, my video on it, I was like, there were many play sessions.
I'd be like, alright, time to focus.
But the play sessions in which I try to focus don't necessarily end up better than the ones where I try to focus just a little bit.
I mean, obviously, if I wanted to do a decent job, I wouldn't be doing a podcast while playing it.
Oh gosh.
Well, see, I feel the same way like I can't be laid back.
The thing with video games and getting great at them is that when I get great at them,
then I feel like, well, I'm done.
I can't get quite the same level of engagement.
But with nuclear throne since it always goes on forever and ever,
then I will never feel like I'm about to hit that limit of goodness.
I guess once you get to like, you're fired or something.
The game ends when you get a world record.
That's when the game ends.
Well, no, because the game has to end when you get a world record and then the world ends,
so you know no one else will ever get that record.
Yeah, exactly.
So the real goal, you're saying that the real goal of nuclear throne is first get the world record
and then destroy the world.
Getting the world record and nuclear throne is only the beginning.
But you can only destroy it by building a nuclear throne that will destroy the entire world
and cause the events of nuclear throne to happen.
The goal of nuclear throne is to bring about nuclear throne in real life.
And you'd be so good at surviving in that world because you know.
Yeah, exactly.
So you become like the top.
I mean, I'm sure there's an explanation for this in the game, but I don't know it.
But I guess in this fantasy world, we're creating...
Wait, which level of the scrapyard is the car in?
Oh, one. It's always in one.
Crud, I passed it and I had to screw it over, whatever.
I'll get it someday.
I think it spawns in all other stuff.
No, no, no.
Man, it sucks not having a melee weapon that pulls back bullets when I get to the big dog.
That's the most funnest thing about the big dog is that I can hit all of his bullets back at him.
That is pretty fun.
Luckily, I died by the way.
I'm not really...
Man, it sure feels good to be a man and not be a little baby.
A little baby crystal player.
It's just so...
It's just the shield is just so indispensable.
I got an auto crossbow and bolt marrow.
We have a run, boys.
Oh, fuck.
I never take the weapon-specific upgrades because I don't feel like committing.
Well, see, you always take two in a run.
Yeah, I actually do.
I guess it's like...
What's that?
What were you saying, Munchie?
You always take two in a run.
Unless you are like a melee user and then you have to always take long arms and laser brain.
Why laser brain?
Oh, shit.
You people don't know.
Oh, nigga.
So what were the upgrades you said you had?
How about laser brain?
In four dash...
Actually, they might have changed it.
I mean, I know that there is like some upgrade that you only get if you get two...
Are you going to tell us about that special mutation?
There's a weapon that drops in 5-1.
What?
Yeah.
There's an energy sword in this game and it's the best weapon in the game.
Oh, I think I saw that.
I've watched playthroughs of that.
Man, I want to get good just so I can get those freaking weapons, man.
I think I saw it one time but didn't get to pick it up.
Well, see, it drops in 5-1, I'm pretty sure.
It's not like a late game weapon.
Oh.
Well.
Yeah.
So if you can get that laser brain in long arms and preferably trigger fingers, but you
don't need that specifically, then you won't die.
I do love melee with trigger fingers.
So the laser sword is in level 5-1.
How do you get it?
Well, no.
It's not a guaranteed drop.
Oh, okay.
It may show up all right.
I wish it was because when I saw that I'm like, well, I want that, man.
Oh.
Well, see, the thing is, the reason it's so good is because you can swing so fast.
Yeah.
And so much damage just builds up over time.
And all the high tier weapons are, well, not high, well, yeah.
All the high tier weapons in pretty much every class are energy.
So you might as well be picking up laser brain anyway.
I just want to be able to kill the enemies as fast as possible.
My favorite character for nuclear throne is just to be the dev and just open up the game
file and just hit, just control A all the enemies in the room and hit delete.
Yeah.
That's my favorite too.
A super splitter gun.
Oh, Nick.
Oh, no.
Oh, Nick, are we in there?
Why do the levels load to 101% or more?
Because it's cool, dude.
Yeah, that's pretty cool.
Munchy.
Yeah?
I know that there is a, there's an up, or there's a mutation that you can only get
if you have two weapons specific upgrades.
It's three, actually.
What's up with that?
Oh, okay.
It's heavy heart and you get more weapon drops.
Is it good?
No.
Oh.
Well, all right.
There's no reason for it to be in the game.
I am not capable of focusing on the game enough to play well when I'm also talking.
So, unfortunately, my social tendencies override my game tendencies.
So, not going to be able to do well.
And if I was trying to do well, I still wouldn't do well.
I would still lose to Little Hunter.
So, actually, I'm pretty sure if I encounter him another couple of times,
eventually I'll get him because I understand that it's probably better philosophy to just
run right at him and start swinging.
That seems to have better odds than running, which is what I was doing before.
I'm going to tell you like Game Dude, like Nintendo, like Power Nintendo,
Good, Ultra, Guy Fieri, Power Breakfast, like a tip.
Okay.
Sure.
Pick up the jackhammer and fight Little Hunter.
You know what?
I had the jackhammer and honestly it didn't do that well against Little Hunter.
I don't know why everyone says that.
Why does the jackhammer help Little Hunter?
I remember hearing that, too.
Ben.
Ben, is it possible that you are an escaped mental patient
and you shouldn't be out with us normal humans?
He was...
I kept trying to hit him with it and he would just like jump away
and I would only get like one or two shots on it.
I know, but you'd have to keep doing that.
Well, yeah.
You could do that with other weapons.
I know, but it's safe and easy.
I'm just saying this for DeVoo because he needs medical assistance.
Maybe.
He's fallen.
I guess.
Medical assistance.
I guess I haven't really tried the jackhammer.
Whenever I picked it up, I'm like,
I don't want to use this and I put it back down.
I should give him more of a chance.
Yeah, something about it.
I picked it up one time.
I've used it like once because I knew Little Hunter was coming up
and I heard it was good against him and it was okay.
And once because I was out of ammo on my other gun
and there was a jackhammer there and I was like,
oh, okay, and I took it.
And I don't know, I didn't like it.
It felt like the flamethrower, which I also don't like.
And it just expends a lot of ammo really fast
for not a whole lot of payoff.
I didn't feel like it was doing huge damage or anything.
No, see, the thing is it's not.
A lot of melee weapons aren't weapons and more tools for you to use.
And I feel like the jackhammer's not a good weapon,
but it saves your ass a lot of the time.
Like the Throne 2 just gets destroyed by...
Oh, shit.
Forget I said that.
Okay.
There isn't a Throne 2.
No, why would there be?
Why would there be a new End Boss on subsequent playthroughs?
Are you trying to avoid spoilers here?
No, I don't want to do this broadcast again.
I saw it and I don't want to do it.
Then why is he so aggro?
I'm going to be on the level!
Oh, but I was going to say, yeah, Little Hunter,
I feel like I'm just starting to get to a point
where I kind of have a handle on what to do with Little Hunter.
I think I've faced, I don't know, maybe a dozen times now,
and I'm just starting to not be overwhelmed and terrified by his very presence.
Little Hunter is my BGSM sub.
You're what?
Nothing to do.
Gross.
But it's accurate.
He seems pretty, he seems pretty dumb to me.
Oh, that's what we were saying.
Gotcha.
Well, I mean, see, well, I think the most effective weapon,
and this is probably just the most effective weapon period,
but on Little Hunter, the Super Crossbow,
if you have that, then just shoot him once in his bed.
Well, that sounds good.
Because you know, when I see the Crossbow upgrade option,
I'm like, okay, if I have the Crossbow, I'll always pick it,
because yeah, you know, the one that makes the aiming better,
and then sometimes I'll be like, you know what,
I want to get the Crossbow.
I like the feeling of a Crossbow.
I like the feeling of like weapons that are light,
but do a lot of damage.
Like revolvers in some games are like way more powerful
than like freaking shotguns or something.
Yeah, the Crossbow feels really good.
Yeah, it's my favorite sword and weapon in any game like ever.
Yeah, it just feels really good to like carefully aim a shot
that does like ridiculous damage.
It feels great.
But there's a late game revolver that's like fucking beautiful,
and I love it.
Is it the Super Revolver?
No, there isn't a Super.
Well, I'll just tell you this, I don't care anymore.
It's an Ultra Revolver.
Ultra.
Is that the one that takes rads?
Yep.
Is that the one that you spend rads?
I should do an analysis of revolvers,
and it'll just be my memories with revolvers.
I've never touched a real revolver,
but my memories with games and revolvers,
like playing Clue, obviously.
But my fondest memories of revolvers is in Fallout 3,
because I really, that was like the 44 revolver in that game
was my favorite weapon.
Because again, it's so tiny, but it does quite a bit of damage.
And then when I got into cheats on Fallout 3,
there's one cheat you can get to give yourself a revolver
that doesn't have a scope.
And for some reason, that revolver does over 5,000 damage.
And so, like a super mutant behemoth would come,
and I insta-killed him with a revolver.
And I would just go through the whole game
insta-killing absolutely everything with my revolver,
and it was the greatest time.
So whenever, and I recently played Half-Life,
and so I shot down, like, telekinetic aliens with a revolver,
I don't have to cross, though.
Revolvers are always a special time in video games.
Well, the crossbow in Half-Life is pretty rad.
Oh, shit.
Revolver quest.
Yeah, man.
Oh, this gold scorpion fucked me up.
Oh, yeah, I hate those.
They're dead.
I'm gonna try to try to do well enough to get YV.
All right, yeah, this is no more baby bullshit mode.
We're just gonna go silent.
I guess.
No, man.
That's missing the forest for the trees.
I don't even know what that means.
Oh, right.
At some point, I accidentally dropped my freaking screwdriver.
When did I drop my screwdriver?
So I'm killing a big hunter, I mean, a big bandit,
just by, I killed big bandit just by throwing my wrench
out of a bunch of times as chicken.
That was pretty funny.
Yeah, that is good.
There's a bug in this game where if you have a melee weapon
and you hit big bandit as soon as he charges,
you can hit him 47 times.
Huh.
Well, unfortunately, I somehow dropped my screwdriver.
So I guess I'll have to get it again.
Well, it sucks because I would never get a screwdriver
for any other reason because it negates everything
that I like about melee weapons.
Yeah.
Oh, here's something I like to do.
It's as chicken if I have the wrench as I do right now,
I'll switch between my blade and my wrench
to be able to rapid-fire hit things.
Yeah, that does not sound cool.
That is the coolest.
I guess it makes sense.
I don't know how practical it is,
but it's a fun thing to pull off.
No, man.
You said, I said before, trigger fingers.
Trigger fingering with melee just feels so great here.
Yeah, you run up to something and just smash them
and kill them and then because you got trigger fingers,
you can just run right up to the next one and whack it again
and just keep whacking.
And you guys ever played Geometry Wars?
That's like the ultimate in games
where you feel like you're mowing through enemies
where enemies are grass and you are a mower.
If you like trigger figures, play Geometry Wars.
It's where the enemies will cluster up in a cluster
and you just, your bullets eat into them.
Like it's eating through a wall of enemies
that are slowly being eradicated.
That is pretty cool.
Like that fight against a thousand heartless
in Kingdom Hearts 2.
Or maybe there were nobody to do whatever.
Freaking Geometry Wars needs to come back as a roguelike.
As like a steam-friendly roguelike.
Because the problem with Geometry Wars
is I don't like the level structure of it that much.
The roguelike setup can make the game
constantly challenging and engaging forever basically.
And I'm glad that it's a trend that's catching on so much.
It is a good thing.
I really like the roguelike elements.
So yeah, Geometry Wars needs to come back as a roguelike.
I mean, do we need like a new sub-genre signifier
for like the specific type of roguelike
that Downwell and Nuclear Throne are?
Mystery Dungeon. Pokmon Mystery Dungeon.
No. Procedural Death Labyrinth.
PDL for sure.
Because like Nuclear Throne feels a little bit more arcade-like.
There's almost like an arcade-y feel to it.
Which makes it like the only type of arcade-y games
that I really, really like.
I like video games that are video-game-y.
Yeah.
I do too.
Dude, you just hit my sweet spot, yeah.
Like, yeah, like...
Yeah, like, yeah.
I haven't played Mass Effect.
But games like Mass Effect seem inherently kind of unappealing.
Like, I don't feel much drive to play games like that
that are like about their stories.
Interesting.
Exclusively.
Well, I haven't played Mass Effect.
I mean, I know that's an overstatement.
It is a game and it has gameplay and stuff.
But I don't know.
Something about a game that is all about its mechanics
and the moment-to-moment feel of the game.
It's got a heavy crossbow.
It's really great.
Swapped up.
I love the heavy crossbow.
I don't know how many times I've had the heavy crossbow.
But specifically what's great about Trigger Fingers and Melee
is that it's that feeling that you're swinging faster
than you should be able to
and you have to keep chaining them to be able to keep doing it.
And so like, your window to hit...
Oh, the blue one.
Your window of opportunity to kill the next one is shortened
and you have to jump on it.
It's like you're on the edge of your seat.
It's like this tense thing where you have to chain them together
to achieve maximum deadliness.
Yes.
And your offense, your strong offense becomes your best defense
because you just got to keep killing.
And if you stop killing for a second, then they'll kill you.
Yeah, man.
Okay, the combination of my chicken sword and my heavy crossbow,
I'm getting into that vicious Rambo Mode.
Dang it, I got nothing but crap upgrades.
I have Lucky Shot and I have Strong Spirit, Hammerhead,
and Extra Feet.
Strong Spirit's not bad.
It says prevent death once, but I've never noticed it preventing death.
Maybe I'm not understanding it.
Well, it just lets you take one extra hit, basically.
That's weird.
And Hammerhead, going through a limited number of walls,
I only picked once and forgot that I picked it,
and it threw me off constantly.
It was really distracting that I was eating through walls,
and I was like, what?
So it's nice to know that you can do a whole strategy
that involves manipulating the walls to create your own cover and stuff.
I feel like that's kind of like Crystal's Throne Butt
in that it's probably really good in the hands of someone
who really knows what to do with it.
Who likes to go play the Worms games or something.
I don't know, just someone who has a plan,
who's like, yes, if I can eat through walls,
I would do this for my strategy, but I don't know what to do with it.
Alright, I'm back with a sandwich. What did I miss?
We were just talking about Hammerhead.
Yes, Hammerhead is good.
You think so? What do you do with Hammerhead?
Well, see, I don't use it offensively.
If you get a bad spawn, you can just dig into the wall behind you
and you can use it as a shield.
Yeah, okay, so you can funnel enemies towards you through your tunnel?
Well, that too, but also just make a little cove.
Spawns get especially bad on loops,
where you will spawn in a big room full of enemies,
so you have to make a little bit of a safe space for you.
I'll say, because what I was talking about
was how going through a limited number of walls
made me think that there would be a lot of strategy
involving creating cover for yourself and stuff like that,
where there would be more spatial tactics that you could employ.
One thing that was a little disappointing about Nuclear Throne
is that I was thinking there was going to be people
who would be specializing in careful runs of the game,
but then I look at the top runs and it's all run into the middle of the action.
So I framed that as a positive thing in my video
that it encourages you to go crazy mode,
but I think it would be cool if there were incentives to do careful mode,
and there's no scoring in this game, right?
Okay, yeah.
I think all you have to do is create some sort of scoring system where...
No, there is.
Oh, there is? Okay.
Monchi, should I get the flat cannon?
Yeah, yeah.
Do you have a strike on the shoulders?
No.
If no, don't, then don't.
Well, I'm in the freaking Diamond Spider Zone
for the first time in this podcast.
I finally made it this far.
God help you.
I mean, I usually get here pretty consistently.
I've looped five times since we've started this.
Wow.
Anyway, I think maybe one of the modifications you can make to the game
to encourage careful runs
is that you get higher combos of your points.
Like, your point ratio goes up significantly
if you don't get hit at all.
So there's a multiplier for your points
if you don't take any damage.
That would incentivize careful runs.
I just died on the Crystal Spider.
Basically, it means if you do a careful run,
it will take way longer to get to the top loops, you know?
But then you could do,
you could get more points that way.
That way, your objective in a careful run
would be to get the highest score
rather than to loop the highest number of times
or to beat your speed record.
So yeah, so you could do speed records
versus point records, and one would be careful.
Right, because then you can really get a lot of advantage
out of stuff like running through the walls,
using grenades to manipulate the walls.
That's such a good idea that I just had.
I must preach into the heavens
and post this podcast everywhere.
Let's get Vlambeer in this podcast.
Hey, Vlambeer, how you doing?
What do you think about video games?
I do not speak English.
Does he not speak English?
Where's he from?
He's from Sweden, I think.
Well, good for him.
You know what's funny is that you guys were talking about
how great it feels to have the screen shaking,
like, within five minutes, first booting up on me.
Oh, no. What?
Oh, no.
Please, yeah, come on, it's awesome.
I'll turn it back on. It's not like I was super opposed to it.
I'll just...
You know what put it back on?
Max.
I don't know what level I have it on.
I have it on whatever the default is.
Wow, it's like the whole freaking screen chugged.
Maybe it'll make me better. I just figured it would make me worse,
but if it...
It just feels awesome.
I didn't really get mage to play Nuclear Throne.
I knew she wouldn't because I know it's not her kind of game,
but I was making my case for it
and she went and looked up a video for it
and she said...
and she said she didn't like the shaking screen.
She said it made her feel sick.
And you know, I could see it in a video.
If you're just watching it, it probably doesn't feel good at all.
But when you're playing it, it's so awesome.
Okay, well, I...
The funny thing is...
Immediately, 100% was too much.
So I turned it down to 35%.
And if I can warm up to that, then I'll go higher.
Let me see what I have.
I'm curious now what...
My screen shake is on 100% and it's rad.
There wasn't even going to be like a slider in this game,
but people were literally saying
that the game was making them nauseous.
And so J.W. had to play a slider.
What a bunch of fucking ssss...
Ssss...
Real men play Nuclear Throne.
I wish everything had a slider like that for like the hunger games.
You know, turn off the camera shake.
Those movies would be way better.
I thought you were saying
that you wished the movie, the Hunger Games,
had a screen slider to turn off the screen
so you could just like slide down the screen
to just like make the movie not happen?
No, no, just make it...
Just get rid of the generic...
Get rid of the contemporary movie aesthetic
where everything shakes constantly.
When you tie it into the Hunger Games...
Dude, I got the blood hammer.
I've never even seen the blood hammer.
I would like it except...
I could accept it's blood
and that, you know, I lose my health, so...
You know, maybe Nuclear Throne is the Hunger Games.
Maybe Nuclear Throne is the Hunger Games.
They're put up to this to do with...
By Jon Snow.
Yes.
That's his name, right?
Wait, you know that you don't
lose health with a blood hammer
if your swing hits?
Oh, really? Oh, whoops.
You didn't notice?
I wish I had been...
Well, I mean, I've never actually had the blood hammer.
I just happened to be reading about
melee weapons on the wiki today and I read that.
Yeah, because you see, when I get a weapon,
the first thing I do is I shoot it around a bit
before actually engaging anything.
I'm like, oh, I lose health each time, okay?
Yeah, I mean, I see that.
So anyway...
But that would be terrible if you lost one every time.
I wish I'd been told that one half a second sooner
because then I would have gotten it
before going into the portal.
Well, I don't know.
But it ties to my chicken sword
that I'm not sure if I want to get rid of it, you know?
Oh, oh!
Top strat!
Drop your chicken sword
on the first level,
and then when you loop, it'll be there,
but it will be like a super mega,
like Superman ultra good
Bill Cosby good sword.
Yeah, but he's not going to loop, though.
But Bill Cosby isn't that good.
No, she's kidding. Bill Cosby's very good.
He's like hero.
Okay, yeah, but anyway,
that's true, that's a lie.
Would I ever tell you a lie, Davoo?
I don't know.
Look, there's a bazooka,
and I'm not going to...
I just killed 5 million enemies
with my power crossbow,
and it was the most amazing
empowering moment.
Oh, your super crossbow?
Wait, is there a difference
between the super crossbow
and the heavy crossbow?
Yeah.
Super crossbow shoots like a spray.
Heavy crossbow, that's what I have.
Heavy crossbow is so fucking bad.
My brother has a crossbow.
If you have trigger fingers,
then it's good.
But the reload time on that thing is just so...
I got trigger fingers,
and it's quite good.
Impact wrist,
corpses fly and hit harder.
Oh, that's so good.
That one is so much...
When I heard that, when I read that description,
I'm like, well, it probably doesn't make him fly
that much further, so I'm going to pass.
But then when I picked it, I'm like,
oh, they fly like 5...
Oh, I met a little hunter.
I believe in you, Davoo.
Everyone pray, dear God in heaven,
I love Davoo.
If he doesn't tell a little hunter I'm going to go to jail.
Please don't make me go to jail.
God, I'm a good man.
I love America, and I love everything about it.
Please don't make me go to jail.
Well, I died.
Nice job, dude.
I died, but then killed little hunter,
and now I'm dead.
Wait, so you and little hunter killed each other?
Kill each other.
That's something.
Congratulations.
Basically, I killed little hunter,
but I didn't get past him.
But that's the first time you go to jail.
And the thing is, I did not go into him
with any strategy, because going after him
with a crossbow is the stupidest idea ever,
because if it's really low time,
if you don't have triggers, you're right about that.
Because I just wasn't even thinking
about the fact that I was coming up against him.
Oh, and the other thing that made it really great
is that we were in a very tight corridor
with like, the cops were not on my ass at all.
Yeah, that's the best way to fight him.
Because I just, the location was perfect.
So the only reason I did that well
was that nothing else was there.
Which is always the reason why little hunter
kills me, is because he forced,
he panicked, and I run into everything.
So that's kind of another reason why
I'm not focusing, is that, yeah,
when I don't focus at all, I could die
before I even get to the sewers occasionally.
But that level of like,
crazy, just my mind
can ramble, sometimes
brilliant things can occur.
So I like having
a randomly generated brain at the same time
to make it truly roguelike.
Mmm, that's good.
True roguelike experience.
I have another 3DS 3D
super food tip for you.
When you,
okay, when you get to
5.3, it's a timer
for when little hunter comes.
It's not like how many enemies you kill with big bandit.
So it'll immediately start taking down.
So what you want to do is,
you want to go right up next to a wall
and kind of like walk into it, you know?
And then little hunter will be like,
oh, I'm going to land right on top of him.
So he'll land right inside of that wall.
And then he'll make like a little cove for himself
so he can't really back away or anything.
So you can just nail him right then and there.
Against as well.
Huh.
I want to say,
that I think that the fact that
the hunters pretend to be dead,
I mean that the assassins pretend to be dead
is really cool. Yeah, yeah it is.
Wait, which ones are the assassins?
The purple ones?
You know, like you'll come upon them
and they look like they're dead.
But sometimes you can see they're like...
You mean like they pretend to be undead.
You mean like they play POSSIBLE? No.
Yeah, those guys killed me a couple of times
before I understood their nature.
Dude, they're great.
And then, oh, fucking mimics.
And then they get up and they run at you
but they run in this erratic pattern.
They know exactly what to do and make it really hard
to hit them. And you never even see their attack
because it's so fast. They can also reflect bullets.
Yeah, well, you have like...
They can reflect bullets. Wow.
See, I always love games where you feel like
enemies that have the same movesets
and the same mindset that you have.
That's always the coolest thing.
You know, that's what Undertale's got.
It's got a character who has...
It's basically the same powers as you
that you're in competition with.
Again, this is the sequel to Undertale.
It just came out this year. Toby Fox
shipped it off to some people in Sweden.
He doesn't want to make video games anymore.
He got all this money. He doesn't need to make any more art.
This is all just a front to get money.
And now this is the sequel to Undertale.
Just like Downwell is the prequel to Undertale
because it's about falling down.
The post-cool to Undertale is Shovel Knight
because that also has...
That also has...
All the bosses in Shovel Knight
make me think
if I were playing as that character
with that moveset, I would try to
fight Shovel Knight roughly the way
this AI is trying to fight me.
Where...
Not all of the bosses. I mean, they're not quite that on that level.
But a lot of the bosses
that you fight in that game
seem to be getting the most usage out of
their stamina level and
their moveset as they possibly can.
And that makes the fight feel
way more engaging than most boss fights do.
Where most boss fights are total bozos
who sit around and wait for you to hit them.
And that's why most boss fights are not interesting
to me in most games.
Oh shit, my niggas. Gatlin Sugga.
I think I'm going to be encountering
a little hunter.
Little pizza maker? That's what I call him.
I almost called him little slugger.
Dude, that'd be cute.
Hey!
I don't know how else to phrase this question
other than did you know, even though
I know you don't know, you could play as big dog
at one point.
What takes a big dog? Oh yeah, that big dog.
What? Yeah.
The one that I keep calling mad dog.
It's a mad world.
Wait, why would you play as mad dog?
You can't go anywhere.
I know, that's what was good about him.
Fuck!
That's how you do that.
Shit! Holy fuck!
Fucking ice.
Look up footage of big dog
playing a nuker throne and you're going to like
shit yourself.
Hey, here's the thing.
I encountered an enemy version
of horror the character
before I unlocked.
Wait, which character you said?
Horror.
Which one is horror?
Little green doggo.
Little radiation monster.
Oh yeah, that one.
Yeah, what was up with that?
Will you ignore radiation
for three levels of spawns
and that's how you unlock him?
I got long arms.
This is gonna be great.
Long arms is, you know...
Well, that's cool.
I unlocked him without even meaning to.
Yeah.
Long arms is the most
nice thing for me to have
with a chicken sword.
Aw, man.
Oh yeah, man. If I was chicken, I would...
Well, actually, then again, the chicken sword
is not really that great, is it?
Because it doesn't...
Like, the wrench is not very good.
Like, the wrench is good for the sewers,
but after that it's like worthless.
And if the chicken sword does less damage...
Nice.
And if the chicken sword does less damage than the wrench,
I gotta imagine it's probably not that good.
Yeah, honestly, it's not that good.
For me, I can't...
I just can't quite deal with
the reload time of all the other melee weapons
that are bigger.
That delay,
even if I have trigger fingers,
that delay is a bit too much for me.
I would much rather have to finagle around
doing more strafing to get those hits in
than I would
with the delay.
Davoo, next time you pick up...
Well, the first time when you pick up the energy sword,
you're gonna feel like a Sumerian god of swordsmanship.
Believe me.
It's gonna rock your brain and destroy your dick.
I saw it.
I saw a guy loop like four times with that.
But I didn't get it.
Oh, I was gonna tell you, Davoo,
the world record right now is like a slow play.
So I think you'd like it.
I'll link it to you later.
The world record for what? Score?
I see.
I didn't even know there was a score.
Yeah, it's how many kills you get, dummy.
Oh.
That's why it displays it afterward.
And so it's just your kills,
not any other factors.
Because I would love...
I would be interested if the game had
a really advanced scoring system,
based on lots of different factors.
That'd be pretty cool.
I want to be based on distance, too.
But I think the farther someone's gone
is like loop four, I think.
I'm not sure.
Loop three,
turn things up a bit,
and you get scared,
and you turn into Home Alone.
Because I like that movie.
Yeah, apparently.
What are you talking about?
What does Home Alone have to do with this?
You turn into Home Alone, Davoo.
Don't you understand?
Okay, whatever.
You know, whenever I recover
my life back as chicken,
I always forget that that means
my health is reduced.
You know how to regain your health?
You either have to get
a stationary medkit,
or you can pick Last Wish,
if you're stupid.
Yeah.
Well, unless you want to unlock chicken.
Oh, wait.
Never mind.
I can't believe you actually found that out
without me telling you, by the way.
How do I unlock chicken?
I looked it up.
Who, me?
You told me.
I just looked it up.
Although to be fair,
I wanted chicken because I heard she has
a melee weapon from the start,
and I wanted a character with a melee weapon by default,
so I went out of my way to unlock chicken.
So I looked it up.
The way that I unlocked chicken
actually got to a
point where I had to choose a mutation,
and I was at one health, and Last Wish was an option.
I was like, you know, I actually kind of want that,
just so I won't die.
Okay.
I've regained my faith in you.
Your faith was on the line here,
and I was thinking, you know,
if Ben doesn't say that this was an earnest
take at trying to get chicken,
I might not even like him.
I don't like this person anymore.
Like if I cheated at the game
and just had to say, you know what, Ben,
we're not going to cut a little more.
When I first was playing this game,
when I first saw Last Wish,
I thought of Last Dream,
which is that item in the final
Undertale.
Oh, yeah.
That reminds me of one nitpick
with the aesthetic of this game is that,
I don't know if it could have been done better.
It's Undertale.
It's not Undertale.
That's my own complaint.
It's that the level up
cards that you see
have, I don't know if this could have been done
better necessarily, but the level up
cards all have a character on them,
which is kind of, it makes it
a little confusing. It's like,
I'm not that character right now,
so I just feel like if they had done
other types of illustrations that were more abstract,
then that would have been
better. But again, the way this is fine,
once I got used to it, it wasn't,
it was only distracting when I first began
playing the game.
I don't mind that, but it does make me wonder
if the ones that have
a particular character on them,
if that's that character's canonical
moveset. That would be interesting.
Well, I think my head canon
is that they're all canonical to everyone.
Ever since,
I guess another thing I like about
the nuclear thrown characters
is thanks to Undertale,
where ever since Undertale, I now think
of every video game protagonist as a time
traveler.
See, the thing about this game is that
it takes place in different universes.
That's what Loops is. It's not the same universe.
It's a different universe.
I see, okay.
I just naturally think
of all video game protagonists as time travelers now.
If you watch my Emily as a Way video,
there's a part where I mention
like, so then you go back in time
to do it this way instead.
I've been playing
papers, please.
And I literally think of this guy
as this art stoatskin citizen
who thinks don't go well for him
so he starts over again to try to make things right.
I just think of that way now
because that just makes so much more sense
and it makes every video game better.
So that's part of what endears me to the nuclear thrown cast
is their determination.
And that's why Undertale is the best game in the world.
That is. Because it made all other games better.
When I was playing it, I actively thought
this makes all video games
15% better,
like, approximately that amount.
Hey, what would that number be
if it was 5% more?
Say that sentence again, but have 5% more
on that debut.
Yeah, when I said that I realized,
but I'm talking about better, not like cool or anything.
Hmm.
Well, aren't they the same thing?
No. I don't know.
I would argue so. I got prescription sunglasses the other day.
Oh, very nice.
I've got some.
Prescription sunglasses, did the doctor have to measure
that I haven't worn in years?
Yeah, I did.
It was an arctuous process, but you know what?
It was worth it, because now I look 20% cooler.
Very tidal back in.
So I died as chicken,
but then I opened the portal
and so now I get another chance.
I'm sweet. I have a chance for, um...
Last wish.
No, actually not really. I have a chance for some kills
for regenerate HP and more melee range.
I'm going to go with some kills for regenerate HP
because I want to be able to live.
Dude, that's an awesome upgrade.
Yeah, yeah. No, yeah, yeah.
I didn't make it, so...
Bloodlust is good too.
Bloodlust is my favorite upgrade, I think.
Partly because the card for it looks so awesome,
because it's white and red.
It's like, oh yeah.
The card does look awesome,
and it's wicked good,
because it benefits you for killing
and killing is the one thing you always have to do,
which is why I really like what he shot too,
although I don't think it's quite as good as this one.
Yeah, you might be right about that, but...
I mean, because like...
Okay, it's great if you're having ammo problems,
but not every game
do you have ammo problems,
and if you have a game where you're good on ammo,
it's not a very useful upgrade.
Well, I think having more or ammo
isn't necessarily a bad thing ever.
No, it...
God, please let me live!
God, no!
But it's like...
You only hit...
You only have to think about ammo
if you're running low,
and so if you are running low,
then Lucky Shot's gonna be great,
but if you're not, then it's like...
Well, since I do melee, I never had to worry about ammo.
So did you die, Munchy?
Yeah, when you're...
When you're a melee, it's not as big a deal.
Which is another reason why I haven't been taking Lucky Shot
as much, because I've been doing more melee.
Munchy, did you die?
No, I didn't die.
Yeah, I know.
I can make it out of any situation.
My name's Henry Houdini, and I live inside the universe.
Okay.
Of the game, I mean.
Not in this universe.
It's just the real universe.
You know, one thing I like about,
um, like,
something that this game has made me feel good at
is being able to swap weapons
while I'm in the middle of a thought,
you know?
Because when I was first getting into Nuclear Throw,
for some reason I just haven't played games
or anything yet, where whenever I'm switching weapons
I have to preoccupy myself with the fact
that I am switching weapons.
It's not something that I could just do.
But now I am good at that.
I'll hit you with one bullet of this,
with two bullets of that,
and with one more bullet of this.
It has a...
It's a good, simple...
It has a bit of a...
It has a rubbing your head
and patting your head
sensation to it.
What do you...
What do you mean by that?
That's hard to do.
What are you talking about, Manji?
I'm just saying, like, when you succeed at...
I've never heard that expression before,
ever in my entire life.
You've never heard the expression
rubbing your belly and patting your head?
No.
It's not really an expression as much as
just a description of a thing.
Well, the idea of it is that it requires...
It's like an interesting allocation of brain
that's a little bit harder to do than you'd expect.
And you have to, like...
You have to, like, meditate on it
for a few seconds before you can do it.
And when you do it, it has, like,
this interesting sensation of, like,
it's really satisfying multitasking and stuff.
So, um, yeah.
Davoo, are you
a serial killer?
Answer the question, Davoo.
There was one time...
There was one time
a box of Crave fell for no reason
wasting most of it, and so I shredded the box
to pieces because I was so mad.
And I knew that if any
serial ever did that again,
I would also ceremoniously kill it with a sword
like I did that box of Crave.
What the fuck is Crave?
It's a Kellogg's
serial that is like...
It's like, um...
Ew, Kellogg's? Don't you know
you're supporting the man?
Let's talk about politics.
It's true.
It's on Paul.
No, dude, that's old man Rand Paul
2012.
Then it'll be Ryan Paul
his son.
Good old Ann Rand Paul.
Yeah, then it'll come full circle.
The entire libertarian
circle of life will be complete.
Uh, what kind of...
Oh my god, Rand Paul probably was named after me.
I thought about that.
I don't have the nerve to look it up because if it's true,
it'll be very creepy and hilarious and awesome.
What kind of
social views do you think these characters have?
Like, one by one?
Well, I think they're...
Munchy, have you seen
um, that picture
that's floating around the internet?
It's called, it's Ask Human Tail.
Yes!
Yeah, okay. Well,
in my opinion, all the characters
in Nuclear Throne have
weird and
out there gender and sexual
identities of that sort.
They're all like
asexual, bi-romantic demigods.
Asexual. I remember when
I was looking at someone's DeviantArt pictures
and like,
he had like this one of him and he said
I'm asexual, bi-romantic.
I'm like, whoa, it's an all new type.
I haven't seen, I haven't heard of before.
Yeah, of course.
I was talking to Digi about this the other day
and we just after a long and complicated
process of deep soul
researching, we determined that Digi is
a, is a hetero-demiromantic
hetero-demisexual.
What? That was too mean.
Hey, you know what? I believe it.
What the heck is, what the heck is
demiromantic mean?
Demi is the worst thing ever
because it describes literally everyone
in the world, so everyone who describes
themselves as it is a genius.
I don't understand what demi means.
Being demisexual means you have sexual
attraction, but only for people
with strong connection to.
Oh.
Meaning basically
a normal person.
Well, I guess you need that word.
I mean, we are homo-safians after all.
Yeah.
Like, you know, people complain about
the whole how every Tumblr thing has
like this detailed description of their
gender and I'm like, you know,
when I first was seeing that, I'm like, that's a little bit weird.
But at the same time, I want to know that
because, you know, it's
I know it's kind of weird, but I do
like being able to know the gender
of whoever I'm talking to because it does
slightly affect my etiquette with
them, right?
Very slightly.
On a place like Tumblr,
where you don't know
who you're talking to, I can kind of see
how, you know,
yes, I'm a girl, use this pronoun
is like, it makes sense.
If I know that someone is male or female,
I will talk more
like, I mean, in real life,
you will talk to certain people of different
genders very with a different kind of
different level of tone, you know, just
but
if someone, okay, if someone
let's say someone looks male
but they want
but they don't identify as male
and they want to be referred to by
I don't know, let's say female or
or neutral pronouns
like they want you to call them they.
Um
Am I an asshole for finding
that like a big ask and
like it's sort of an imposition
like it's asking me to go out of my way
to refer to you as something that
is like not
is not how I would naturally
do so.
I don't know what I'm saying.
I think if you look like
a little girl, like
me, then it's
easier to do it.
Like
the biggest qualifier
because at first I was like saying my opinions on this
like, oh, you know, this and that, but like
I don't know any openly trans people.
I don't know anyone who I know is trans
or anything like that. So I know
I can't say because, you know, you get
certain people who are like
these trans guys who then will like
dye their hair purple
and then like not look like a woman at all and it's like
well, that's weird, but obviously
I'm sure many people think this
obviously all the people who do an unconvincing
job of being trans are going to be the ones
who you notice
and all the ones who you don't notice are going to be
the ones who are good at it.
I think if someone
was good at convincing me they were
a woman or a man, then it would be very
natural and easy for me, I think.
I mean, it
yeah, it would be easy and I know
I know one, I know a trans
woman who is
I mean, it looks like a man, like
when I see them, I think, oh
male and I want to say he, and I
felt like I was the only person
in my circle who had any problem
with this and I felt really bad about it
because nobody else seemed
to ever make the mistake and I constantly
did. Is it Nate? Are you
trying to be on the bush here?
It's Nate, it's
the best guy ever
who is now the best girl ever.
No, but
yeah, and like
it's unfair to say that, oh
if you can
actually look like
what I imagine a woman to look like, if
you look a certain way
then I can accept your request to
refer to you by this special pronoun
and if you look another way then I can.
I'm thinking bringing this back to nuclear
throne, I have no difficulty thinking of
I have no difficulty thinking of
obviously chicken as a female, but
I have no problem remembering that
you know, crystal is female
I actually do, it took
me a long time, I mean
I think I'm starting to get the hang of it, but
even after I found out crystal was real.
Like if you have heads around the house you can get good at that
you know, remembering which ones
which genders, you know whatever.
Yeah, I guess you're cool.
I think of people
being able to select their gender like a freaking
vending machine is part
of what makes
life cool where everything can become a vending
machine. Everything that you used to take for granted
can now be an option
and obviously people are going to be
really annoying the way they'll go about
it, some of them, and some people will be
flam
will be very aggressive and
hypocritical about it, but everyone will
be, there was a moment at which
I made peace with all of the LGBT
stuff in its militantism
when I realized everything
gets militarized, everything is hypocritical
maybe that
core has a slightly
larger percentage of
people who are militants and hypocritical
maybe the percentage is
slightly higher, but
because that's the worst thing when there's some minority
that you're a part of and then
if it's like an
obscure one
then people will only have very limited
experiences with that minority
and it'll most likely be
the big assholes who want
everyone to know it and
that's kind of the problem with any group
any group, there's going to be a percentage of them
who are normal people otherwise, then there'll be
a bunch of weirdos, then there'll be a bunch of assholes
the asshole slice of
that pie will leave the pie
and tell everyone about the pie
and then everyone will think that that group
is a bunch of assholes because the assholes
are the activists who represent them all
so
that's what I like to keep in mind that
I'm not going to think of someone
as some jerk face until they start being a
jerk face to me until then
it's like, you know
everything else about the advanced
21st century society
I really like, so
you know, I like the fact that
I can just make youtube videos as a living
that's a pretty crazy notion
that's a pretty crazy stupid thing
that people from the 50s would think
is lazy, but that's the whole
point of
yeah, like
50 years ago it wasn't expected that
you could just identify as a different gender
that would be considered a weak thing to do
that you'd be giving into
what you feel is comfortable for you
rather than manning up or
womaning up and just dealing with life
and people back in the
50s or whatever back 100 years ago
could have had the nerve to just deal
with it and move on
but guess what, people 100 years ago
they couldn't have survived 10,000 years ago
when you had to learn how to build a spear
and fight a fucking tiger
that whole point we invent stuff
and make society better
is so that you can be more comfortable
and be a big baby and live exactly the way you want
without having to die or get uncomfortable
or without having to get hungry
that's the whole point of human progress
is to have every little tiny stupid thing you want
so yeah
ah shit, killed by on
gosh dang, I hate when the rat kills me in this video game
well I pretty much
I agree with all that stuff you just said
thank you very much
there was a
yeah I think in the past
I might have been a little salty and been a little like
you know
being a transsexual is just like
they're just making it up
I don't know about that
but it all kind of comes down to how you define
it all just comes down to definition of terms
some people don't acknowledge
that gender is a
performative thing
when some people say gender
what they mean is
biological
but when other people's tumblr pages will list their gender
and their sex which threw me off at first
but if you feel it's not that way
then fine
yeah yeah but like people
that are trans generally don't use the word
that way so when someone says
oh you know it's not real
you're not really a female or whatever
you're not really whatever gender you say
well that's just a question of how you're defining your terms
I like the colors
in this game
a nuclear throne yes the colors
it's you know it starts off with a desert level
which obviously means that they were
like that's usually level 2
is desert at least in mario
desert is level 2 but they made it level 1
and it's actually
that's because everyone's mean in this game
they all wear big boy pants
and kill people because they're mean
you know I just I wish
I was a little girl
I think that nuclear throne would be a much
better more solid game
if you started in a planes
and level 2 was a forest
and level 3 was a mountain
and level 4 was snow
and level 5 was fire
with the yachty joke
which is just him going
grass world desert world water world mountain world
rock world boss
it's a remix it's every mario game
I have heard
I have heard him say things like that
that reminds me
I haven't watched any zero punctuation
a while ago
I just stopped watching his
episodes like for like almost a year
and then I would just get through them all
but now I'm back to following them weekly
you know what I just realized about
the level color palette is that
the desert level is actually the most vibrantly colored level
isn't that interesting
it's actually the most vibrant level in the game
I don't know about that
maybe the
it's got all this fucking
yeah maybe that but at least for
all the games
well I'm talking like how
overall bright everything is
because usually the desert level is a time
to have a more
reserved color palette where everything is
more monotone and even though it is kind of
monotone it's all yellow it has fewer colors
going on but it is the most vibrant
the most brightly lit so it does
give you that sort of planes feeling
you know of grass feeling where like things are the most
optimistic in a way
because like even though it's a desert it's the most
optimistic because there's so much sun
so that's kind of a cool
way it conveys the level one sensation
that was something that was weird to me
what's your favorite level in this game
by the way
well I'm gonna say the junkyard area
because it's got rain and the rain is cool
you may notice in my video on it
I predominantly use the rain section
that's true
oh Jesus save me a prayer
I'm on the prairie
and I'm a slave
my favorite level
is
I don't know they're also annoying
in their own ways
I just actually love them even more
they all piss me off in
special unique ways
I actually really like the caves
yeah the caves are nice
the caves are really cool
they make me so mad those fucking
laser gems make me so mad
and those crystal
spiders take so many hits they're so durable
so I hate the caves
it's funny that you say that because I'm actually on the caves right now on loop
and gosh dang it
do I hate this boss and how much health it has
are we trying to avoid spoilers
munchie is trying to avoid spoilers
yeah the spoilers
came in like a giant van
should we explain
what this game is
oh yeah so
viewers
nuclear throne
is a roguelite
top down
they couldn't afford it that much guys
they know that much
that was the coolest thing I've experienced
oh yeah crossbow time
when I was watching
Bruce Jenner
by the way I've been
by the way I've been getting worse at the game
the longer I've been playing it
I haven't even made it to the snow
to Snowden in like
I've been getting mediumer
that was the coolest thing when I was watching
some loop play through and the giant
vans showed up and then I learned that the way
to get to the
you're throwing a monkey rich right inside
the asshole right now
there's no way someone is going to
listen to a podcast
Ben, his name is
Ben, he's a chocolate man
and he's listening right now DeVoo
wait I actually wasn't listening right there
did I miss the spoiler
what's the point of spoilers
it's not
I actually appreciate it
I actually like being unspoiled so
well you shouldn't come into a podcast
if you don't want to get spoiled to it
you just have to say things in like
super like extra cool
like terms like say if I want to say
Van I say the big truck man from
Texas he isn't going to come down and run you over
I have seen the van
I have seen the van in a video
there's no way you can
be on a podcast about something
and try to avoid
spoilers for it hey buddy have you
been the throne I thought not
I'm the boss of this gym
he is, he's a champ
well the fact that you said
that there's a throne as a spoiler so there you go
shit
because you know back when I was first playing it
before I looked anything up I was like
maybe there's not a throne you know like
because of the way the game builds it up
but there's a tool tip that says
the throne definitely exists
exactly that's what made me think
that it may not
that maybe it doesn't
I was getting sort of a Wizard of Oz vibe from it
have you ever been liked
in your life yeah by the Wizard of Oz
the Wizard of Oz the greatest thing about
that thing contributes to the world
of storytelling that I don't know if a lot of people
get from it is the classic
act of subverting audience
expectations
because that's what the whole movie is about
is you always try to get to the wizard
but then he ends up being a jerk but then he ends up
just not being a wizard it like
superverts your expectations twice and even
if you're already it's a double twist
it's an old mobius double
it's so emotionally dense
it's so emotionally thick
did you say fuck because you referenced Homestuck
because that's what you should have done
no I love Homestuck Homestuck's the best thing ever
I said fuck because I crystal to deflect a missile
but then it just happened to explode
I didn't know you were a giant dancing homo bin
hmm I have just
what have you ever read
Problem Sooth by the way
yeah of course
we agree that that's better
it's not better
Problem Sooth is better than Homestuck
Problem Sooth is not better
yeah I know the one
what is that
Problem Sooth was the one he did before
I'm gonna get into Homestuck at some point
feel free to spoil it to me though
that's fine with me because I know that
no
I'm not asking
I'm just saying feel free if you want to
if you want to mention something
if you've seen like anything from Homestuck
I see troll fanfiction quite a lot
yeah well yeah
there's the trolls but I mean aside from that
okay what really got me about Homestuck
was it wasn't like anything
about the story which is like it's a good story
it's fine but
what really blew me away about Homestuck was how
just how like
it expanded in scope
not just like in its story
but in like the methods it used to tell it
this is kind of what
it's sort of what impressed me about Undertale too
is like how I didn't expect it to tell
its story so like
just the way that
in a lot of ways they play like a 16 bit
RPG to get around
that sounds cool yeah I know you already know
about that but like the fact that it starts
off as this weird goofy little
comic and yeah some of them are animated
some of them are gifts and whatever and it's got kind of a
weird format and that's fine but then
suddenly these fucking like big like
crazy flash movies start happening
these interactive games and these like
huge set piece moments
it was just
it just man back in the day
when you were reading Homestuck when it was new
and you didn't know that it was coming it must have been like
holy shit
holy shit it was scary
it was scary wait
did you read Homestuck when it was coming out
it's not done first of all and yes
yeah
you would have been like 10 years old
I'm 65 right now
he's
he's like 15
it's not
I didn't read it when it was brand spanking new
I picked it up when
which granted was a long time ago
but
I mean I think that's about when I picked it up too
I picked it up in like 2011 or something which like yeah
it wasn't new but I didn't know about
it and so for me it was new when I
when I got to the you know
wayward vagabond at the end
it was the longest time and I still love him
I remember yeah I remember he was
oh yeah I remember
he's awesome
yeah that first one where his station
like takes off it's just like
it's just so much more than you expected
from this fucking goofy little comic
and I mean I hadn't read Problem Sleuth
before I started Homestuck but I wish I had
me too because I feel like it would have
set my expectations differently
God no I fucking love Homestuck
the best thing ever
no it doesn't matter we're talking about Homestuck
okay
Undertale and
how they're the same
that's the biggest thing
that people need to be educated on whenever they call
Undertale
Tumblr core it's really Homestuck core
yeah that's true
Homestuck had the same
Homestuck had the same criticisms
levied at it for like basic
Homestuck is big enough of a deal on its own to be
its own thing it doesn't have to be Tumblr
everyone hates Homestuck now though
no that's not true
Homestuck ever
no I'm talking to Davoo Homestuck is definitely
got criticized for being like Tumblr
that's stupid you know what's funny is that like
it's funny it's like
the more it went on the more the game
most of the things I've become a really big fan of in the past
three years have been things that Tumblr loves
you know even though I don't love Tumblr
you know my little pony Steven Universe
Undertale
maybe it's just because like that's
the audience that that creators
have to appeal to you know
so like of course that's the stuff that you know
well you know like yeah
well for one thing creators are going to
especially if they get into Hollywood
or something they're gonna be inclined to be liberal
because of the social structure
there
that's my understanding is that basically
Hollywood is
like it's sort of
like liberal
liberal mentality
is inclined to be in Hollywood
because it's kind of a sort of
commune type of area you know
in a way like everyone works together
you have to work in sort of a
collaborative mindset
in a way you know what I'm saying like
rugged individualism doesn't make
Hollywood movies for the most part you know
and a million other factors
there's a million other factors
yeah I mean I guess I see what you mean I think it's
maybe more just that like
the culture of Hollywood is
liberal so therefore
the people that get accepted into that culture
will be other liberals generally
obviously a lot of it is also self perpetuating
but I think well what started it
being that way and I think
there's also a sense of
well obviously people who hate their parents
have a lot of inspiration
to create art you know
through parent hatred
parents are conservative and Christian
so there you go there's the correlator right there
um I mean
I think maybe there's something to that
well I think there's got to be a lot because like most of
I'm the freaking only
person on the internet who I
who I know I don't have any online friends
who come from Christian
conservative households who don't hate
their Christian parents everyone is
either raised by liberal parents
or hates their conservative parents
I'm a Christian but
doesn't everyone kind of hate their parents though
no no you're wrong and I hate people
like you well I hate
okay I'm using the word hate very
lightly I mean like disgruntled
is the proper word you know
I'm not not disgruntled
at all alright well little hunter killed me
I'm fucking disgruntled
listen to me hey Ben have you ever tried
to eat your own body
it's I think you should do that right now so you stop existing
and you like put your like arms
inside of your mouth and then you just chew away
dude I watched one cartoon where that happened
where like a sheep ate itself
that was the coolest thing it just
just shh shh shh shh shh shot everything
Deveaux do you read one piece
nope watch it
awful fucking eats himself
and it's awesome but he does it
to become more powerful
because his his devil
his devil fruit is about like he can
eat things and like take on their
properties sort of it's it's hard to
explain I don't really understand it honestly
but there's
yeah he and at one point
He actually eats himself to, like, reform his body into, like, a new shape.
So what you're saying is that one piece is Steven Universe?
Um, no, it's good.
Unlike Steven Universe, it's good.
You know, one of the other strange stuff.
Yeah, say something about Homestuck.
Right.
Oh, I think...
I'm sure this is, like, literally only me,
but I think Spurb was the most interesting thing about that,
and I wish it just stayed with the kids.
No, I totally agree with you.
And the fact that the game isn't gonna have Spurb in it fucking breaks my heart.
And, yeah, the fact that the early comic is all about exploring the mechanics of this crazy game,
that's what got me into the comic.
Now it's all about the characters, like, you know, resolving their arcs and whatever.
I mean, that's fine.
Are you joking me?
They're not gonna res...
I don't know.
Hustle's all about meta shit, and he's gonna pander to DigiBro, and I hate him.
He's gonna pander to DigiBro.
Yeah, he'd better.
If he wants to get to DigiBump, that is.
Um, no.
No, I mean, I'm reserving judgment on the ending of Homestuck.
I want to see the end so I can get perspective on all the fucking bullshit we've had to deal with.
I know, I know.
See whether it was all worth it.
So long, dude.
I want California to win.
I want that to be the big twist.
That would be meta.
That would be super meta, dude.
Dude, when John went back and, like, saw Caliborn and, like, brutalized him and left him traumatized,
I feel so sorry for him.
I know, he's his character.
Yeah, he's hard to hate.
He's gotta be.
He can't be the same Lord English that is, like, the fucking monster man.
He's gotta be a different dude, because he's too lovable.
Just unrelated.
I don't really like him.
I don't really like him that much.
Nah.
He's too green.
I don't know.
I don't know what it is about him.
I like his coat the most.
I think his coat is, like...
Oh, yeah.
His coat is really cool.
But, you know, I think he designed the coat before he designed the Lord English.
Yeah.
You know, I think that's literally true, actually.
I think it's definitely...
Homestuck induced.
Just, dude, oh, shit.
Oh, because you saw that fucking coat in the fucking scratch in Mission with the midnight crew.
Oh, my God, it was so fucking cool.
That was the shit.
You know, back in the day, people who skipped that are the vein of my existence.
Dude, I didn't...
I think I skipped it my first time through, and I felt like such an asshole when I went
back and read it, and it was so awesome.
Homestuck has allowed me to zone out a bit and made me realize I have the music on, and
that's also distracting me.
I just need the sound effects, so thank you.
You've helped improve my skills.
Welcome, dude.
Yeah, the music is droning.
Yeah.
I think Jack Noir was like my favorite villain for a long time, just because he was so cool.
He's just cool.
He's pretty cool.
I don't know if I'd say he's my favorite villain.
Well, not now.
He's just kind of like an angry...
I mean, he's always just been like...
He's just an angry dude.
I know, but he was...
He got personality, nigga.
He does.
He's got a lot of heart.
So, Munchy, you were talking a little while ago about why you're jaded to this game.
It didn't have the co-op like they wanted.
Oh, it didn't have the co-op, and there's a lot of...
I think just balance issues that they promised and didn't really deliver on just because
of time.
Well, not time.
Well, maybe time.
The way this game was released is they made a deal with Sony.
At least I'm pretty sure it was Sony.
What?
I know that's something to do...
Yeah, it's on the PlayStation.
In case you didn't know.
And we know.
They said they were going to release it by the end of the year.
And the end of the year came.
And so they had to release it, even though they...
Like, this update is extremely broken.
I don't know if you've ever encountered a...
When you go into a Crown Vault, there's a bug where you...
Sometimes it will like turn into like a broken level, and you'll have to like fight enemies
from the level, like before it.
Sounds like some NES glitches right there.
Yeah, it really is.
It changes like part of the walls.
Do you?
It looks really weird.
That's like some...
I've seen it change part of the walls.
That's cool.
Yeah.
I've seen it change part of the walls.
Honestly, I think it is cool, but the problem about that is it takes up one of your...
You can only have three...
You can only enter three Crown Vaults per run, which I think is the most stupidest thing
I've ever heard before.
But anyway, the reason that's not like cool is it like takes away one of those and you
can't, you know, takes away an opportunity to get a Crown.
Wow.
Man, I picked something I don't often pick.
I picked less enemy HP because I'm going...
Dude, that looks great.
You need to prioritize that one.
Because I'm playing chicken, but I have the screwdriver because I want to unlock YV,
which means I'm basically doing all melee, which is great except it takes forever to kill
things, but with less enemy HP, that is not a problem.
Uh...
Oh, yeah.
One of the main...
The scarier face is awesome.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's great.
One of the main things I had about this game is something that neither of you know about
yet, so I can't...
Well, actually...
Yeah, fuck you.
Davoo has like warped my brain.
See, he's perverted my brain into something more sinister, something more dark.
If it's...
If it's not like a...
I mean, I'm probably not going to mind.
I'm definitely going to appreciate whatever you say, if it's interesting.
Oh, well, that's going to be up to you.
When you reach the throne room, and you're going to know, you're going to know what it
has been, and I'm going to ruin this price for you right now, but the generator...
Is it about blowing up the generators?
Okay.
When you get to the throne, you walk up and there are these generators, and from your
guys' perspective, they've always been there, right?
There's never been a time where there hasn't been generators.
Okay.
In order to loop the game, you must destroy the generators and have the throne go super
aggro, and when you kill the throne, you get taken to the throne too, which is, you know,
a baddie, super boss, mega ultra 3D.
Anyway, it didn't used to always be like that.
It used to be you just destroy the throne and you get taken to loop.
Now, this doesn't seem so bad, and in and of themselves, I guess generators aren't exactly
the biggest problem in the universe, but what it implies is what?
Davoo got on the biggest problem in the universe.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, whatever.
The special car is red, right?
Yeah, red and gold.
Sweet.
Yeah, it's a little darker.
Okay.
Everyone stop.
Wait, you died?
I did it.
Wait, did you die?
Turn your follow-up and mute Skype.
Turn your music up.
Turn your music on.
Please.
I died.
Damn.
You're disappointing to me.
Anyway.
But did you get the...
But did you get YV?
I exploded the red car.
No.
No, you're not supposed to explode the red car.
You're supposed to just...
What do you do?
You hit it with the screwdriver and it fixes it.
Oh, and then you get in?
Yeah.
Okay, cool.
It says get in.
Guys, you need to get up in the fact that you're doing a podcast while I'm not paying
attention.
Geez.
All right.
Well...
Next time.
The reason I don't like this is because loops are pretty much integral to the game and making
it any, at least, somewhat interesting.
Because all of the best weapons you get are like level five and up and you're going to
use it for that long if it's just getting thrown.
Yeah.
That's...
Loops are like my favorite part about this game.
Well, obviously the loops is like the whole thing that keeps it endlessly challenging.
So, yeah, the fact that loops is this very specific requirement is, is, uh, stupid.
Mm-hmm.
I can't believe you actually agreed.
I don't know.
I can't have an opinion until I've actually agreed.
And it's a pain...
I said generators aren't that big of a problem, but they pretty much are.
It's just like an animate object you have to, like, shoot at.
And it doesn't always give you your ammo back.
So it's, like, sometimes, like, not even, like, fun to do it or rewarding.
Because, you know, another...
Because, like, I guess the idea is that they wanted to make loops mysterious or something
where, like, hard to get.
No, no, no, no.
It's not that because when you sit on the throne, you get an ending.
So they wanted to make it a cinematic experience, I'm assuming.
I've never even seen the ending.
I've only seen loops.
Mm-hmm.
So...
So they wanted...
But why would they make it...
Oh, killed by a big rat that's never happened before.
Why would they make it to where the quicker...
The actual ending is easy, but then the looping is hard?
That's to make it mysterious, right?
To make it like, whoa, I actually got even further than expected.
Is that the idea?
To make it like, I'm going beyond...
That sounds...
Like, basically...
That sounds like the idea.
Which doesn't work quite as well when it wasn't already like that in the original version.
So you're, like, mystifying something that wasn't already mysterious.
But even in and of itself, something that Undertale very much convinced me of is that that kind
of crazy going beyond the barriers, freaking, you know, like second half of Girl in the
Lagoon type of stuff, should be easy to get to.
It shouldn't be this crazy thing where you have to do three back flips and then you
will stick a bubble gum on top of a trash can in order to unlock.
Because it's the coolest part of the game, you should just do it easily.
Not like automatically, but do it just enough to where it's easy to get to, because it can
still be just as satisfying.
And there's so much content that's like, restricted to loops.
There's so much content that just some people just won't do, because they don't know.
Like, how do you get the whole second half of Symphony of the Night?
Don't you have to do, like, a specific thing?
Oh, yeah.
I forget.
But it's like, I think you have to...
I have no idea.
It's something like that.
You do have to do some secrets.
Yeah, and it's like, you know, you can make that not crazy secretive and it'll still be
really satisfying.
You'll still feel like you're going against the room.
I don't know, man.
I think it's cool.
I think it's cool that it's, like, hard to find.
I think that makes it more meaningful.
I don't know.
That's what I would have...
Something like Nuclear Throne.
I think it might be different, because you have to do it every time.
Yeah, exactly.
In something like Castlevania, if it's hard to do, that's fine, because you just do it
once, and then you got it.
I guess so.
Yeah.
Because that's how I would have used to feel, but the way the Undertale leads you into it
made me feel like...
Because Undertale does have plenty of things that are crazy obscure to get that are, like,
little things.
So I don't know.
Dude, I've got Rabbits Paw and Scary Face for my first two upgrades.
You're doing it.
Is this the run?
I want one of you to be the Throne on podcast, so you can, like...
That's definitely not going to happen.
I haven't even made it to...
You have to understand, even if I get past Little Hunter, I'm going to get to the freaking
labs, and I'm still not going to be paying attention.
The Palace is super easy.
Well, it was super, until they buffed the Guardians.
It depends.
I've gotten layouts where it's really hard, because it's, like, big and open, and everything
is coming at me from every direction.
Then I've gotten other ones where I'm in, like, a little safe corner, and I can, like,
safely proceed through, and that was really easy.
Oh, well, the Guardians are the ones that, like, shoot the orbs of you.
They used to be really easy, because they only shot one.
And they were...
Those ones aren't so...
I know, but...
It's the ones that jump at you.
Oh, the dogs, yeah.
You know...
Go to PetSmart and get a leash, dude.
The thing about doing the podcast in this format that's pretty insane is the fact that we
all do not have any sense of how long we've been going.
Like, we don't see the time code, so we don't ever feel the urgency to stop, which is funny,
because I could just go on forever.
Yeah, I...
How long have we been...
It's probably been two hours.
Oh, my...
I'm gonna cut this down a bit.
Yeah, have fun cutting it down.
I'll take a while.
Well, I mean, I love, like, seven-hour videos, so to me, this is, like, the perfect video.
Yeah, because for me, I always feel like I'm always able to just talk forever, like, literally.
Yeah.
For I...
It's almost always someone else who leaves or stops a conversation.
My endurance knows no bounds, even when my throat is dying.
Mm-hmm.
Like, if anyone...
I feel you, I feel you.
If anyone who's listened or watched my Q&A would know that even if my throat is dying,
I will still just keep talking into oblivion forever and ever more.
And, oh, my gosh, this level 1-3 is insane right now.
Oh, my gosh.
This level 1-3 is insane?
No, no, no.
This particular version of it.
This particular...
Whoa!
This plane flipped this out of the charts!
Is it...
Is there a gold scorpion?
Yeah, there was a gold scorpion before I killed it.
Okay, well, there better be.
But, like, the way the level was arranged was, like, everything was all in a very tightly compact,
like, like, hoop.
It was the most insane 1-3 I've seen.
I'm not saying 1-3 is insane.
I'm saying that particular one was insane 4-1-3.
Come on, guys.
Get the picture.
I get it.
We don't hate you yet.
Yeah.
Much.
I'm gonna play YV because I don't feel like trying.
Yeah, the fact that he doesn't actually die, he just gets bored of the failure.
Is that...
That's canonically what happens, yeah.
Yeah.
You know something, I was taking a swig of water, so an enemy was coming toward me.
That's like Kirby.
Kirby never dies.
He just gets bored.
I'm sorry.
I totally steamrolled him up there.
Don't do that.
I was taking a swig of water, and I didn't pause because I don't like pausing.
And then an enemy was coming towards me, and so I'm like, oh, I'll just shoot him.
And it was a grenade launcher, so I died.
Oh, well.
Holy shit.
Like, 40 ravens just, like, they flock, you might say, onto my screen.
Well, I like them when they...
They're okay.
I don't ravens when they have a wrench.
Ravens with a wrench becomes like a whack-a-mole in reverse.
In corridors.
In, like, tight corridors, they're easy.
In, like, a big open space, they're hard.
Ravens are the birds that come down, right?
Yeah.
When you've got a wrench or any other similarly powerful melee weapon, they become whack-a-mole
upside down.
And...
Wrench is like the worst melee weapon.
Why is that the worst melee weapon?
It goes fast and it's fun.
Well, it's...
Well, it's because it's...
I mean, obviously the screwdriver is the worst.
And, like, the wrench is the worst of the acceptable melee weapons.
I mean, a wrench is serviceable in the sewers, but beyond that, it, like, can't kill anything
in one hit.
Freaking try...
Well, I mean, I'm gonna stick with my chicken sword, though, because I get to always have
it.
No, no.
Like, I look for a wrench, like, I want a wrench to get into the sewers, but beyond that, like,
I'm always trying to get a sledgehammer from the shovel.
There is some sense in that, because I built up my affinity for...
What do you mean there's some sense in that?
They're just way better.
That personally applies to me, because I built up my affinity for the wrench when I was beginning
the game and not usually getting very far, not usually getting, you know, to Snowden.
So, obviously, in the couple of times I've used, like, the sledgehammer in the Snow area,
I was getting pretty good use out of it, because, yeah.
So, yeah, I guess I will start planning around using the hammer.
I mean, I just like to kill things in one hit.
And when you got to get really close, like, in a melee situation, it's like, if you can't
kill it in one hit with a melee, it's not worth meleeing.
Well, I don't know about that.
Yeah, especially in the Snow area, because when you hit them once, then they start flying around
if they're not dead yet, and that could cause some damage, so that wouldn't be good, you know.
There's something I was going to say, but I forgot.
Oh, oh, Davoo, I want to, like, record, like, VHS record for future generations.
Your face when you find the Ultra Shovel for the first time.
Let me think.
I've never seen the Ultra Shovel.
I mean, I've probably seen some footage of the Ultra Shovel.
What does it do?
It's a shovel, but ultra.
When did that become, like, established that, like, the system of Super than Ultra?
Like, that was, like, the way it became established.
Well, Ultras are, like, oh, oh, oh, you mean, like, ever?
Yeah, in all of video games.
Like, in language generally.
Yeah, like, was that a video game invention?
I wouldn't be surprised.
It's my first encounter where there was Super Star Saiga.
I'll bet that there was less of a clear hierarchy between the two words before video games came around.
That's one of the cool things about video games in terms of how they benefit culture,
is that it's allowed people to, like, systemize a lot of things that were very abstract before,
but now we think of them as more...
I don't think it allowed us to systemize them.
I think it just demanded more systemization than we had previously.
It just made us more, what I mean is, not allowed, but it made us more inclined to think that way.
You know?
And I like that, that's pretty cool.
Uh, yeah, probably.
For us, us millennials who play video games.
Finally, I have a year...
Hold on, uh...
No, are you gone, Davoo?
Finally, I have the energy weapon upgrade and an energy weapon.
I almost never have both for some reason.
That's good.
Dude, Lisa Brain is good.
Anyway, what I was saying is I completely fucking forgot and Davoo ruined the podcast.
I never get Lisa Brain because I never really use energy weapons,
because they don't seem to do as much damage as they wish they did for their low rate of fire.
To remember what you were saying, just recreate what was being set up to that point.
Like, recreate the scene.
All I can think is black people.
Um...
Melee, Ultra...
Oh, yeah, yeah, okay, okay.
This isn't like a thing that you people will have input on, this is just a statement.
What do you mean?
Yeah, you kind of people.
Yeah.
Ultra weapons should be called nuclear weapons.
Just think about that.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, I agree.
I immediately...
I don't even have to think about it.
Everything is nuclear in a way, so...
Although, there is already a nuke launcher.
It's like, what would you have a nuclear nuke launcher?
Dude, wouldn't that be cool?
It would be kind of cool.
I mean, since nuclear stuff is part of the world building,
calling stuff nuclear would be a little inelegant.
Well, the weapons aren't nuclear.
I mean, like, the things are.
I think that is cool.
The only thing that I don't think it would work with is with the nuke launcher,
but, like, whatever.
Just give that one a different name.
Who fucking cares?
Call it a thermonuclear...
Thermonuke.
Yeah, thermo.
Thermo's got to...
How about men's gay and I eat butt?
Everything should be thermo.
How about that?
How about that's the name of it?
No.
Well, over the course of this podcast,
I've become very much into crossbows more than I was before.
Yeah, dude, they're really good.
Yeah, I'm a fan of crossbows.
Because doing really specific aiming where you're, like,
weaving in and out like crazy and the enemies are weaving in and out like crazy
and, like, against all odds that Arrow finds its way to the enemy is pretty sweet.
It's just so satisfying.
It's way more...killing an enemy,
killing, like, a salamander with a heavy crossbow bolt
is way more satisfying than killing them with, like, a bomb.
I don't know why.
Yeah, it's probably the most satisfying killing in the game.
Ben, I don't know how you even, like, survive, like, life using explosive weapons.
You know, here's the thing about...
I only came to that conclusion.
I don't know, dude.
Here's the thing that annoys me about, like, all pro discussions about from pros in games
is that if a weapon or an option is not very effective,
then you're called a pleb for using something that isn't effective.
But in the end, if something is very effective
and you're called a pleb for using something that's too effective,
I don't understand.
I'm not a pro.
Like, you've been shitting on things that are too effective
and then shitting on things that are effective,
and it's like, I don't understand.
Dude, you have to be me.
Or you aren't cool.
The...
Shit, I feel like I had something to say to that.
But it's gone.
That's because I was right.
The... oh yeah, explosives.
I get a lot of good use out of, like, grenade shotguns in Snowden.
I don't know, I just, like, fire them down quarters and...
Whenever you decide to do an explosive run,
make sure to always get boring veins so you don't die.
I never get boiling veins because I'm crystal,
so I feel like only the very low minority of the time
am I going to be at low enough health to benefit from it.
If you, like, get hit at, like, HP 9 or something, you know, high,
it'll still, like, make you not die.
Like, if you, like, get with a point-day explosion when you have full health,
it'll...
Oh, will it make the explosion only bring me down to 4?
Oh, that's really good, then.
That's way better.
I thought, I thought if I was at 5 and got hit with a 5 damage explosion,
that I would die.
Oh, that's so much better than I thought.
Munchie...
Oh, that's so good.
That's a good weapon.
And don't let any of those cocks in the big government tell you otherwise.
Never.
Is it worth getting the homing bolt upgrade if you have the secret pistol?
Yeah, because it's, like, way more accurate than what it does.
Like, when you have, like, the normal, like, without the mutation,
like, you can't shoot down a hallway, but when you have it,
it'll, like, lock on to any of these from very far away.
That's totally worth it.
Yeah, it is hard to shoot it down.
Hey, which aiming reticule do you guys use?
The first one, because it's the best one.
What?
You can choose your aim there, yeah.
Well, for me, I actually go with the YV one.
Partly because it's cool.
Yeah, the YV one is nice.
But also because it's a graphic, it's like an actual thing.
It's YV in the shape, it's like YV's shape with the triangle on the eye.
But because it's an actual graphic, it always catches my eye,
and therefore it's easier to pay attention to it.
When I use any other reticule, I just forget it's there.
Partly because it, like, also the YV one is more solid of a thing.
Like, it's more of a shape that, like, really catches my attention.
And so it's, I never forget where my reticule is,
whereas with using any other ones, I will sometimes forget where I put it.
Yeah, I mean, I don't have a problem because I mostly just aim by, like,
I don't even know.
Like, I don't look at my crosshair ever.
I just kind of infer where I am.
I just shoot blindly, like a child.
Dude, when I get the Steam Controller, this is going to be the first game I try it on.
What kind of child are you?
Well, right now.
All of the little kids with their pumped up nuclear thrones.
Chicks, go, run better, run out, run my 2011.
Um, it was a good year.
It was a good year for the internet.
Wait, that song came out in 2011?
Man.
I think so.
I'm feeling 2012, but...
That sounds about right.
Because I remember that was all over the radio when I was in California,
and that's also the year that I picked up Homestuck.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I don't know.
And so you made Homestuck AMVs based on better run, better run.
Just one or two, yeah.
There's a lot of narrative of fucking...
Something.
I don't know, emotional something there, you know?
The most emotional part in Homestuck is when Carcat gets his shoes stolen.
You know what I'm saying?
I've conceived of more ideas for AMVs than I have watched AMVs.
I don't like anime.
Yeah, I don't really watch AMVs.
I guess I don't seek them out.
But there are lots of times where I'm like,
oh man, I could sync this up with that and it'd be great, but...
Yeah.
In high school, I made a Fully Coolie AMV set to float on by Roddy's mouse.
It was before I knew what an AMV was, so it was still cool back then.
I rammed my mic until it was cool.
It was face of a kid today.
He grew a horn and said, that's not okay.
Is that how the song goes?
That's FLC over here.
What's sad is I feel like I'm pretty decent at coming up with improvised parody lyrics,
but then I can't sing at all.
Oh no.
You might as well just throw yourself off a bridge.
I think I'm pretty good at making parody lyrics.
I can immediately sync up all the syllables and make every line different,
but also syncing up with the theme of the original song and the new parody theme.
Davoo, we all think we're good at something.
It's time you just learned to not think highly of yourself.
It's time you learned that no one has anything.
I am way above average good at making parody lyrics.
And that's quite the skill.
Yeah.
Well look, I mean, obviously by the fact that I don't do it often,
it proves that I understand its lack of usefulness.
You know who thinks they're really good at singing?
Christian Weston Chandler.
He has described her voice as having a quote unquote Bing Crosby flavor,
but she's totally toned out.
I mean, I've watched enough videos of her trying to sing.
Wait, she's identifying as female now?
I didn't know about this.
I went to the Sonichu Wiki and I didn't mention that.
By the way, I went to the Sonichu...
Oh no, well they might still call her Christian there,
because I mean, that's how they've always referred.
I mean, I still think of him as Christian.
I still think of him as a guy, honestly,
because that's how I always read about him.
Did you hear about how he got arrested?
Oh yeah, dude.
I mean, which time he's been arrested?
I've heard of Sonichu years ago,
but it seems like you guys really keep up on your CWC information.
No, it's me, man.
I am a fucking scholar.
I am a fucking scholar of Christian.
My junior and senior year of college,
following the adventures of him was my main hobby.
I even tried to make a fan game about him.
I made an RPG maker game based on one of his own games.
And I actually did a shit ton of sprites.
Wait, did you post that anywhere?
I think I remember seeing.
No, no, no.
There are other versions of it that were made.
I never post them.
You see, I can be fascinated by the autism universe,
but then I get...
It's something that I only appreciate in spurts.
It's not something I can stew in.
It's not like...
I was in the chat, introduced me to the new storyteller,
and I was so into him for like 30 minutes.
I did subscribe, but then I unsubscribed.
No, it's not the same.
The new storyteller...
I mean, I haven't watched his videos,
but he just makes ridiculous videos.
Christian Weston Chandler not only makes this ridiculous content,
but he also had this bizarre narrative surrounding him.
Okay, you know Max Landis' video about where he condenses down
the whole story of Triple H?
I could do that.
And I actually think I almost want to do that for Chris.
But you should draw it in the style of Sonichu.
Maybe, maybe, I don't know.
But okay, here's the thing.
The story of Chris is like professional wrestling
in that it's a bunch of people playing characters.
The only thing is that the main character doesn't know it's an X.
June Show crossed with wrestling.
Yes.
I've never described it that way before,
but that's a really elegant way of describing it.
I'm really impressed with myself right now.
Yeah, it's like a big circus,
but the main character doesn't know it's all an X.
He really believed that all these ridiculous characters were contacting him
and that Shigeru Miyamoto was talking to him about getting his game,
his comic license for a video game.
And he thought that Reggie Philzheim and Jay-Z
and all these famous people were talking to him.
And he had like, have I told you about, there was the liquid side where a guy,
yeah, this guy, just for fun, for his own time, he wasn't trying to mess with anyone.
He just made videos where he pretended to be Chris
and put them up for his friends to enjoy.
But people found the vids and sent them to Chris
and pretended that this was the guy who was actually trying to impersonate him.
And so Chris got really upset and challenged the so-called imposter
to a karaoke contest to determine who was the real Chris.
And the fake Chris crushed him.
Wow.
And the story just goes on.
It's like years and years of people playing these roles
and just duping Chris into believing that these outlandish things are happening.
Wait, I need to talk directly to you, Ben.
This isn't directly related to a Christian,
but have you heard of a man named Jace W. Connors?
Otherwise known as ParkourDude91.
No, I've never heard of him.
I think I might have sent you a video of him at one point in my life.
Wait, wait, was he the guy who was like, you gotta follow your bliss?
No, no.
You gotta follow your bliss.
That guy actually knows him.
Oh.
But we'll see, ParkourDude, we found out it was an act.
But anyway, it's a really fucking good act.
And the one that I'm gonna link you one day, it's this guy.
Hey, speaking of, oh man, I got interrupted.
Speaking of really good acts, have you ever heard of My Immortal?
Yeah.
Yes, I know about My Immortal.
I'm pretty sure it's an act, but it's pretty good.
It may have been sincere, like, at first, somewhat,
but it definitely became a comedy thing.
That's probably my favorite autism thing that I was into for a while.
But, Munchy, what were you saying about the...
ParkourDude91 is this character where he's supposed to be a 420 gamer.
That's his character, and he's really into Parkour,
and he thinks he's a marine, even though he's never been in the army.
And he'll say, I'm a disabled and wounded veteran.
I need to keep you with respect.
But all of those things contradict everything else.
Being into drugs, being into Parkour, and being a wounded veteran.
None of those things are compatible.
I know, but see, it makes this...
That's intentional, oh my gosh, that's brilliant.
It makes such a convincing case, because those are all the things
that people who play shit like Call of Duty extensively,
and all that Xbox Doritos culture,
it all culminates into this character this person made,
who continued to be like...
He kept up this for like two years, I think it was,
making constant videos.
One time he flipped his car, and he said he was in a drag race,
and his Prius couldn't perform.
And he got mad at his car, yeah.
In the bedroom.
He's so insane.
I would like to see some of this dude.
I'm going to give you my favorite one, it's called The Hater Hit List.
Here's the thing, I think people who are able to convincingly put on an act like that,
and then keep it up for a couple of years,
they have to also be somewhat insane.
Because that's the thing, anyone who can come up with the idea
of I'm going to play a crazy artist,
and then you will get bored of it immediately, that's what I do anyway.
And I'm just thinking, people who can actually keep up that act,
the lines blur just a smidge as to whether or not you're actually insane.
People who are able to keep doing it convincingly,
and not go insane doing it, to not be bored.
Some like, I mean, do you guys know Froggy Fresh, the rapper?
I know of him.
AKA Krispy Kreme?
Yeah, well, he released these famously terrible raps.
But the thing is, they were just good enough that they actually sounded kind of good,
even though the lyrics were embarrassing.
I mean, it's still an open question.
Nobody really knows, but I am one of the people that comes down on this.
I kind of think he was faking it.
I think that Froggy Fresh is a character.
But no one believes me.
Everyone else thinks he's legit.
And maybe he doesn't.
You know, someone like the new storyteller is,
there's no way that can't be legit, because it's not that funny.
It's not, like, the level of effort that it takes
versus the amount of funniness that it is, is just too diminishing of returns, you know?
So there's no way that's not funny.
I mean, full disclosure, I didn't actually watch any of his storytellers videos.
Brilliant.
I love him.
I think he's boring, honestly.
I think he's, like, whatever.
Well, he's not like someone who you could endlessly come back to or anything.
He's not that interesting that you could just always enjoy him.
But, like, his voice, he has some major speech empowerment.
I really feel like he must have been the inspiration for Bane, the new one.
The way he talks.
Like, I just feel like Christopher Nolan.
Bane?
Dr. Pavel, I'm CIA.
The new Bane.
Like, Christopher Nolan, like, watched the new storyteller,
and was like, that guy is really cool.
You know, I can see that.
Christopher Nolan has a famous taste in what cool voices are sounding like.
You know?
This is a cool voice.
And so is this.
Everyone is cool in my world.
Oh, oh, man.
A snow golem blew up, and I almost died, but I was okay.
I like how we're all still playing Nukia from.
Yeah.
I thought...
I'm actually getting into the swing of talking and not even thinking about what's going on
in the game.
And I'm not doing that great, but, you know, I'm getting better.
Like, I'm actually making it to snow.
I am shocked at how good this is and how this is actually making all of our conversation
better, I think.
Yeah.
It makes me realize that Sam's the noises, not the skeleton.
This is a great setup for a podcast, you know, other than...
Do you want to, like, make this a thing?
I, you know, I've been thinking that.
I mean, I really...
Oh, shit.
I just killed a little hunter.
Good job, dude.
Yeah, boy.
I mean, I think this is obviously a lot less entertaining to listen to than we think,
because any boring parts are, we then start playing the game more seriously
when we aren't talking.
Oh, absolutely.
This isn't going to come out.
That's why I'm saying, like, even though I'm having a good time, I'm definitely going
to have to edit this down.
Like, honestly, we've, honestly, we've spent a disproportionate amount of this podcast
talking about this podcast, and I think I'm going to try and trim some of that.
Because I'm...
I think I'm just amazed that it's not like that, like, it's not, like, incredibly boring
and we're not even, like, saying anything.
Yeah.
No.
We haven't had much radio silence, which is a victory.
Victory.
Dot, dot, dot.
Blood launcher.
Oh, do that.
I don't even know what that is.
It won't hurt you unless you want it out of ammo.
And if you try to shoot it when you don't have ammo, it, like, it, like, will shoot,
but it won't, like, it'll take damage.
Oh.
Well, then I just won't use it with no ammo.
Sweet.
If you get the cannon, it's a much better version.
Well, I can only do what I can do.
Like, the, like, blood explosions that it shoots, it won't hurt you, and it destroys projectiles,
like enemy projectiles.
Yeah, yeah.
Nice.
Well, I found my new favorite weapon.
How often do you guys go in the pizza sewers?
I've never gone to the pizza sewers.
Is that the place with the turtles?
Yeah, I've been there a couple times and I don't know what the point is.
The way weapons drop in this game, every portal you go into ups the tier of weapons you get.
So if you go in one more portal, that means you'll get one, like, slightly better weapons.
Holy shit, that's so cool.
Because I've always been fascinated by the way it'll show the map of levels that you're going through
and how going through a side portal will show a distraction.
Like, I always felt like there must have been some more significance to that.
Yeah, I know.
That is some freaking cool stuff, man.
Now, I'm going to tell you something that will blow your mind.
Okay.
Robot, his, like, passability is that he gets one tier better weapons.
I see.
Now, if you go into the pizza sewers, you go into both of the vault portals.
And since, uh, cursed weapons can appear, like, two tier more weapons.
And, like, say if I get a cursed chest and, like, one-one, I can get a one-three weapon.
So it's like that.
If I do all those things, I can get a cursed super plasma cannon,
which happens on the throne in, uh, two-two.
Or, I mean, in, uh, five-two.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's pretty cool.
So it's great how that works.
Yo, relevant about the pizza sewers, because I haven't been there,
but I checked out the music for it.
And that's the music I used at the beginning of my video.
That's the only weapon, yeah.
I mean, the only music that I genuinely like a lot.
Yeah.
Besides the Venus Mansion music, which you'll see why I like that.
Yeah, I've listened to that, too.
Okay.
I listened to almost all the OST in, um, when making the video.
And I ended up going for the pizza sewers for the first half of the video.
And so, obviously, it sounds exactly like the music for the-
Shit!
God fucking damn it!
The thing-
Did you win?
Damn, it killed by a horror dog.
I mean, thank you, man, y'all.
Hee-hee.
I was on, ugh.
I was in the- I was in the darn.
I was in 7-1.
That was the best I've done so far.
Well, hey, getting better.
I think we're, like, we're training you.
We're-
I guess so.
This is, like, this is the longest I've played at a stretch in, like, maybe ever.
Dude, I play this game for hours on end, and I have no friends.
I-
I have been going in, like, short spurts, which is not usually how I play games.
Usually I fucking marathon them.
But nuclear throne, I've been more like, oh, I'll play, like, four or five games,
then I get bored and I go do something else.
I can't wait until you guys unlock hard mode.
Yeah, there is.
Is there a hard mode?
Okay, so the thing about the pizza sewers music is that it sounds-
I don't know if this is obvious to everyone, like it is to me.
It sounds exactly like the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles NES game music.
Which-
Well, yeah.
That's probably intentional.
Yeah, yeah.
But, like, the thing about that that was so impressive to me is, one, the fact that-
The most impressive thing about that to me is that the Ninja Turtles NES game music
was its own distinct sound.
Which is something that I wouldn't have thought about.
That-
That Ninja Turtles NES game music was a distinct sound.
That could be imitated with a new song.
That was, like, really made me reflect on NES music.
8-bit chiptune.
And the observational powers prowess of Lambeer, whoever made that song.
Like, it's such a specific thing.
I couldn't-
I don't know.
He probably just identified some, like, key riffs in it.
No, like, the way that the instruments are set up, I don't know what the terminology
is for chiptune, but the way that it's done is, like, the way the synths blare out is
similar.
But maybe there's some similar melody going on as well.
I don't know, man.
I listen to quite a bit of chiptune, and there are different types.
There are chiptune.
I'm always fascinated.
Have any of you guys ever heard, like, a chiptune remix that's, like, really low energy?
It's, like, it's almost like a lullaby.
Yeah, I hate those.
I can't stand those.
Well, you know, I hate it when I'm looking for an exciting one and I get a lullaby.
Like, before my body is dry, chiptune is like that.
And it's, like, I do appreciate the unique tone that that gives it, but I want a real
one, and I feel like people are demotivated to make one because that one exists.
So it's, it's, I feel like it's deprived the earth of a proper chiptune.
Don't lose your way.
I feel like pixel art and chiptune, by nature, should be energetic.
It needs energy.
It needs strength.
It needs stamina.
Those do not have the strength.
Don't have the stamina.
Dark souls.
This is pixel shit.
You heard it here, folks.
Why?
I was embodying Trump.
I was talking about pixel art that doesn't have energy, doesn't have the strength or
the stamina to be part of the indie scene.
I saw on the, on the Asanshu Wiki that, that CWC was opposed to Trump.
And, you know, that was pretty, pretty influential.
CWC doesn't have his own opinions.
CWC.
He's a god.
He just, he just parrot, he just parrots things.
It's like whatever.
The only thing you can consistently count on him to do is hate men, mostly gay ones.
That's true.
And without good reason.
I mean, or with good reason.
He has, he has some kind of weird line.
He'll sometimes say about how his like principal in elementary school like molested him, but
I don't believe it for a second.
I think it's some lie.
I think, I think his, I think his dad like made up the story or like grossly exaggerates
the story.
They only molested him a little bit.
Some like weird southern agenda.
Like there, there was one time where a counselor said, where did they touch him?
Where did, where did they touch you?
And he pointed to like some really inoffensive place and like, oh, okay, you can go home now.
That was a pretty okay place to be touched.
I get the feel.
Okay.
Now I'm just kind of going off of my vague memories here, but I'm pretty sure he just,
he talks about like that the, the principal like made him sit on his lap, which is not
necessarily an inappropriate thing to do with the kid, but he says it as though it's like,
you know, this weird gross section.
I don't know man.
The only way that I can follow an asshole and like study them is if they do something
that's cool and I like them.
Dude, Sonichu is cool and I like it.
Maybe.
That's why, that's why I can follow Chris because I can get, I can follow him through
the lens.
Okay.
Like the only person who I study and dislike is movie Bob because I mean like, I don't
know, maybe overall he's an okay person, but there's so many things about them that
are jerky that make me mad, but his reviews are just a little bit too good that I can't
keep, I have to keep coming back to them.
So then as a result, I have to, yeah, he's, he's got you by the balls over the last four
years.
I've had to analyze him to understand why he's like that and he's not, you know, he's
not that big of a jerk.
It's just that like, I think his prop, his capacity to be a jerk is probably not significantly
higher than most people.
It's just that he's willing to let it ruin his videos, which no one else is willing to
do.
Like anyone who makes good videos doesn't want their jerky tendencies to ruin them.
They'll put their asshole in this aside.
I know I do.
I don't know, man.
His videos are all about his opinion.
Well, it's not, it's not the same thing I would have to, if you want me to, I could
go into an in depth explanation, but I don't think I want to hear it like the way he does
it is not quite the same.
But I guess you may have, you may have tapped into the way he sees it though.
I mean, yeah, I'm not sure.
I'm not sure what you want from him.
I mean, if he's, if he's a guy with shitty opinions and his videos are opinion pieces.
Well, yeah, it's not like I've ever told him, like, calm and didn't stop doing this.
But if he'll be pissing me off and pissing me off and I could explain it, but you know,
I don't, I don't want to get into all of that.
I mean, he's not like someone like say Sargon of Akkad, whose videos are shitty and obnoxious,
even aside from their content.
Just the format of them is obnoxious and shitty.
That's part of it.
Like if you were like really tightly written, like the flaws in his writing and the, is
like really the, they're intertwined.
This is like an intertwined issue.
The flaws of his writing and the writing itself are too, are too closely linked to it.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
I do each other.
I don't know.
I mean, I don't really get it.
I don't want to.
I feel like I could go on too long.
I mean, I'm not, I'm not even that big on movie Bob hating.
I'm mostly been exacerbated in it because Digipro has been ragging on movie Bob lately.
So that's kind of amped me up, but being like, yeah, frickin movie Bob.
Exactly.
But I really haven't been mad at him in a while, except for that one time where I watched one
of his videos and then turned it off because I got so mad.
But I don't like, I have a frickin life now.
I don't frickin.
All right.
I picked up the shovel.
I, I forwent, I forwent, I forwent my, my chicken sword to get a shovel.
Now I'm at five one.
So hopefully I can find a screwdriver somewhere around these parts.
Oh wow.
Shovel on five two.
Best weapon in the game.
Munchie.
You're on the West coast, right?
What time is it?
12.
Oh my God.
Okay.
Using a melee weapon to hit the robo snipers bullets back at them is like, probably like
my favorite gaming thing to do in a game of 2015 that isn't in Undertale.
Like, like that is the most, I sometimes I would just sit there for a while and just
do that constantly.
Just, just hit them, hit the bullets back, hit the bullets back.
Unfortunately, I'm a little baby crystal, so I don't have to do that.
I can just shield them back at them, which is also pretty cool.
I like how it's significantly lower than it kills them.
It's like self like worth just by calling him a baby crystal.
Well, but I accidentally triggered the ICC.
Well, I mean, I mean, no, be IPPC, whatever.
You see, you see the reason why is because on, is because on some level I already knew
it.
So when you said it, it just, it just.
Like, if I didn't really, if I didn't deep in my heart know that I was a little baddie
for playing crystal, I wouldn't be bothered by you saying it.
But because I know it's true, it hurts.
Dude, Otto Crospo, Crino.
Oh, it's so good.
There's an Otto Crospo.
Yeah.
Whoops.
Oh, I went, I went into the green portal.
They got to the throne room.
Whatever you call that thing, the green portal.
Oh yeah, the chronicle.
All right.
So now it's time to make a choose here.
No HP drops.
Big age.
PGS more common.
Get curse weapon chests.
Get the cursed one.
Because that's the best.
A lot more curse chests.
Yeah.
Okay, fine.
Why?
Because curse chests are like good.
There's like not a big downside of them.
Like not being able to drop them.
Like if it's a good weapon, why would you want to drop it?
Dude, the Otto Crospo is the new stage of life.
I know.
It's so good.
Do you know what?
If you pick last wish while you have a curse weapon.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's nice.
Because you see, the only problem with Crospo is that they don't have a rapid fire, but
then the Otto Crospo negates that problem.
Oh my gosh.
There's a heavy Otto Crospo.
Well, but then it introduces the new problem that you run out of ammo for.
Well, all you have to do is just not hit the button that often.
Not a...
Are you saying that even three-year-olds can serve their ammo in nuclear thrones?
That big dog.
Oh boy.
Oh man.
How long have you been alive?
Like two months?
Roughly.
That's, you know, that's within two orders of magnitude of the correct answer.
So yeah.
Right.
Now the Otto Crospo and Trigger Fingers.
This is going to be intense.
I'm playing fish right now.
Which do I want, Munchie?
Do I want the regular Crospo or the Splinter Pistol?
Splinter Pistol.
Thanks to my Otto Crospo, I faced right down against the crystal that was aiming its bullet at me.
I didn't flinch.
I didn't try to run away.
I just kept firing my Crospo at it.
I love when, like, you're scared of an enemy, but then you get a good weapon.
You can just mow them down and you just feel like you're like a Samarian god of life-taker
aware.
Oh.
Life-taker aware.
God.
Except I'm now only HP.
So I better, I'm being careful again.
Okay.
What were you saying, Ben?
I was trying to think of a, I was trying to think of a joke.
It's hard though.
I'm not smart.
We all know that Ben isn't funny.
So we just invited him and this podcast just to make him feel better about himself.
I was going to say, like, for example, oh man, I took a, like, I had, I had real severe
diarrhea earlier today.
I felt like a, I felt like a total Sumerian god of taking a shit.
That's what you sound like.
Also, I have a cursed jackhammer.
So what the heck is up with cursed weapons?
What do cursed weapons do?
You can't drop them.
You just can't drop them.
You can still switch them.
Yeah, yeah.
If you find another cursed weapon that you like more, you can switch out cursed weapons.
Oh, that's cool.
I'm going to pass.
I'm going to stay.
Yeah.
Really?
You get a thing called cursed ammo.
What the frick?
Oh my gosh.
Whoa.
I got to 5-1 and it's a mostly open environment with like half the enemies of the level all
right there.
Yeah.
I have paused.
That's what I'm talking about.
I need to take this in for a moment.
That's what I was saying before, like a huge flock of crows just like flew down at me all
at once.
It's the worst.
That's crazy.
It's like most of the enemies.
Grab a triple machine gun.
Big robot guys that slide around.
It's like seven of them.
In my immediate vision, the moment I spawn, I'm still paused.
I need to take this in.
I'm going to go refill my water.
Maybe I'll go to the bathroom.
Well, anyway.
Yeah, whatever.
Cursed ammo, it explodes if you don't get it in time.
Don't get it in time, but it gives you more ammo per drop.
All right.
See you for a minute.
Oh, you mean the item on the ground explodes?
Interesting.
Well, yeah, I have not found a single cursed weapon.
Maybe that's normal.
Well, you need a crown in order to...
Oh, wait.
You only get them with the crown?
I don't like it either, but whatever.
I'm not the maker of the game.
My name's not J.W.
J.W. Bush.
Yeah, George Bush made nuclear throne.
He made it as his foreman.
George Weedman, creator of nuclear...
Edward Snowden, creator of nuclear throne.
Edward...
John...
John Edward Snow.
We could do this all day, folks.
Oh, and we will.
We've already gone for like three hours.
Holy shit.
All right.
This is the run.
Okay.
I'm going to hold you to that.
Oh, shit, my nigga.
Because I've got gamma guts.
And I'm just running over maggots right now, and it feels...
It's filling me with determination.
Oh, that wasn't the last enemy?
Okay.
Oh, and this time, you know where I'm going?
I'm going to...
I'm going to gosh dang...
I mean, young Venus.
Okay.
The car.
I'm going to the car.
Yeah.
You said that the car spawns on 5 or...
3-1.
Yeah, 3-1.
3-1?
Okay.
Have you ever picked up a golden weapon before?
Yeah, I...
Wait, no.
No.
I just had YV's gold pistol.
Well, gold weapons, if you take it to an enemy portal and you start a new level with it after you pick it up,
then it will store and it will always be selected right from the start of a run with that character forever.
If you just take it to the next level.
If you just beat a level with it, yeah.
Nice.
With it in your inventory, yeah.
Okay, well, I guess I should try to do that then.
Well, I mean, the tier 1 gold weapons, which are in the mansion, aren't super good,
but there are ones that are on loop that are really good.
But I still think it would be nice.
Right now, I have a slugger for eyes and it's really nice.
Shit.
I missed that.
Alright.
I'm back.
Good.
Alright.
That's good.
I need to create a battle plan.
I'm gonna switch to my autocrossbow and then run to the right and start firing like crazy.
Whoops, I did not...
That's good.
Now I'm running and now I'm shooting my autocrossbow and now I'm dying and I got my health back
so now I'm not dying anymore and now I'm dying again.
So now I am dying and then I got some health back and so now I'm alive again and now I'm
not dying and now I'm out of bullets and now...
I was not speeding that up in my commentary.
That's how fast all that just happened.
Okay, now I got some more health and now I'm well...
Now I have half health and...
Okay.
Wow.
I kind of wish I'd been filming that because that was the most incredible thing that's ever
happened in my life and now I'm down to one health.
And I still...
You're making it?
No place for cover really.
Oh, freaking health health health health health health health health health health health health.
Oh, I got some health, alright.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, man.
That was...
Oh, now I got some more health.
Aw, yeah.
Aw, freaking...
Now I got more health.
Now I have almost full health and oh, my gosh.
That was...
Oh, man.
I was so engrossed with your story that I actually believed that I was at one health.
Do you want to remake The Christmas Carol with me?
Because...
I
You know that those kinds of those kind of decisions you need we need to think about them carefully
Before we take that kind of step in our relationship
Your gift of gab in your story made me think you're just a such a great
Remake the Christmas carol for a modern audience. What a great story. Oh, I'm dying. I'm alive now. I'm dying
That's the magic
Okay, I don't know what the hell this guy wants. I don't even care
That's the match. That's really that's my chicken right there
Is that I became alive and in dead in the live again multiple times only?
Talking
Munchie, I just shamed myself. Do you know how I died? I
Tried to eat. I tried. I tried to use gamma. Oh
Man
Yep. Oh well. Yep. It was good. I did it and it worked. What do you know? I wish one game
It's the one that it's when enemies touch you they kill you and snipers are the ones that when they die
Yeah, I had to die up a handful of times before on
That's the other thing I like about them. I like about
These kinds of games this you know down well this kind of this sort of new bird age of
I
Roguelikes is that my favorite way to learn how to do anything is to fail five times first
But the problem is that you know fail a bunch of times is really frustrating
So in a roguelike where failing is like, yeah, I get a fresh start
So failing feels like cool. So I get to learn exclusively through failure, you know, like I don't
It is all about learning. I mean all games are kind of like that
But most games try to make you not fail the first time because it's frustrating to die
but in roguelikes you can really roll with the punches and so I died to the
Sniper bots like five times before I finally drilled it into my head to not be close to them when I killed them and that entire
Process felt totally satisfying. It didn't feel like oh when the heck am I gonna get the hang of this?
So yeah, that's something because yeah, I like I really like what the heck I went into the purple portal
But it but I went through the green portal. What the heck happened? Yeah
Well, you can't open the green portal because of Lambert will think oh well
He obviously wanted to go inside the crowd but he just couldn't do that. Oh rusty revolver. What does the rusty revolver do?
Oh
Okay, let me explain that entire chest right there that chest if you put a gun inside that chest
Then in an entirely different run with a different character
You can go to that chest and the same weapon will be in there
So that's it's permanently in there even if I turn off the game and stuff. Yes
That is a cool, but freaking tool brood pub the blue thing but unfortunately
I love my autocross bow a bit too much. Whoops. Oh, okay. I'm fighting these green guys
Oh fighting these green guys from the lab. All right fighting green guys thankfully my
Yeah, big glowing guys. Yeah, wait, whoa, whoa, where are you?
I was I was in a crown room. Yeah crown ball, right? Oh
All right, which crown should I get now?
More drops when it full HP
Ultra I
Mean level 10
Level 10 what the heck is level 10? Oh, I'm at level 7 and I'm halfway through
Don't get destiny if you're close to ultra you most of the time want to do destiny
He's you can just fit like squeeze an extra mutation in there
But since you're not pickups fade fast are worth they
Pickups fade fast are worth more. Well, see most pickups. I do get pretty quickly
Remutation narrow future a lot more cursed things no ammo
You know what? I'm gonna go with nothing because I want to keep things predictable because you know
Yeah, I'll start shaking it up after I've beaten the game. How about that?
Yeah, the crowns. I don't really know what they were. Oh, I forgot. I'm fighting a little hunter
Good luck. Godspeed. Yeah, the crowns don't the crowns don't seem very good. Yeah, they really are
Didn't kill a little hunter. Dang it. I
Died to the hunter. There was even a health pack up there, but I knew that the amount of time
I would take to get oh, man, I might die by the time I get there
That's a that's like a special property that the the snow area has which I guess is probably present in later areas
But the snow area has a tendency to drop health packs way into the middle of danger
So you have to start really counting for your temptation
Well, yeah, because because everything because everything's blowing up in the middle of these giant crowds
So that's where people are done. I'm glad. You know what Deville? I'm glad we both managed to kill little hunter
in this
Thing any but I think I mean are you guys tired?
Almost four in the morning. I can't do this without you. Well, I I don't know, but I'm not tired for one
I can yeah, I could go forever
All right, okay. Yeah, but I
We got a poll we got a cut where you I mean continued. Please please please enjoy
Nuclear throne one of them have a statement done
Yeah closing statement on my cast. Let me just say that I had a great time shooting
Buttholes with you buttholes. Yeah
Nuclear throne is a game about shooting things and I did I like it a lot you should go buy it. It's a
$100
Mm-hmm. Oh, but I don't think we mentioned Monchie that you gave me a copy. I did you
I'm gonna be probably giving Nate one too because I'm getting the physical copy and I won't have a use for another copy of the game
So I might
Why are you getting it? Why are you getting a physical?
Collector, yes, I like
Oh
Devoo your turn. Yeah, I'm sure I'm sure he'll be stopped
Three seconds one two three go
Go watch my video on it. That's a dramatic closing statement on it wall hit boxes. Yeah
Yeah, watch Devoo's video about nuclear throne design elements
Role like how much my video on undertale. It's located on
WW dot Devoo undertale calm slash
Monchie
All right, that's it. Thanks for listening viewers
Oh