My volumetric intake is high and my volumetric output is low.
This is a calorie-rich environment for Mike Swimming.
For Mike Swimming?
Yeah, for Mike Swimming, the best swimmer in the world.
Mike Swimmer.
Mike Swimmer and Johnny just...
He's a Pokemon trainer too.
Yeah.
He has a... he has a Ramareya raid.
He's one of those weirdos who's got like a waterproof thing on his Pokemon Go phone.
Yeah.
He goes kayaking into buildings.
Into underwater buildings.
He crashes into them and he totals his boat.
He has a... a subnautical kayak.
With a little dome, he goes...
He just... he just has like a little like...
He just goes kayaking in like a deep sea dive or like a bell helmet.
Yes.
I mean he just... like he has the little paddle and he's just like... he's just like spinning it.
The way it works is like his... the sides of his kayak have little like him waterproof glove compartments
that you can put your hand in so he can move his arms around like a spaceman.
You feel like after all this important thing that he's like modded into his kayak,
he might as well just get out of the kayak and dive.
Wait, like... like that he's in the kayak.
Like the kayak is around his torso and like his little legs are sticking out the bottom
and he's just walking around in like this kayak.
They're like... no, no.
Okay.
Like he kayaks out to the sea.
Yeah.
And then... but then when he gets there, you know, he like puts on his helmet and like he goes into deep sea mode
and he just sticks his... sticks his feet through the bottom of the kayak
and then just like seals himself shut and just... just submerges.
So I can feel the purpose of crashing into underwater ruins.
What I... I assume you were going to say was he kayaks down and then he gets out of his kayak
in his underwater suit and then the kayak just floats to the top because it's got air in it.
It just leaves him behind.
How's he gonna get out of this situation?
He can't swim.
He's just gonna... he's just gonna put that to the front of his kayak through like the storefront
of like an old civilization.
The ancient Mayan burger place.
Exactly.
Oh, fucking Dave Kayak, you're so interesting.
Dave Kayak and Mike Swimmer.
Twin... twin emperors of New Mexico, Canada.
Very nice.
We will always remember you.
He left us to his suit in the kayak wars of 1983.
Wait, wait, it was... it was Mike Swimmer. Who was Kayak?
Oh, Dave Kayak.
Yeah, Dave Kayak.
That's the fusion. The fusion is Mike Kayak.
He died... he died the way he lived, ramming his kayak into an underwater ruin.
What an asshole, dude.
Yep, he really fucked it.
Okay, let's just play the fucking video game now.
Hello, welcome to the second and best rowdy fuckers cop killers, the movie starring me, Ben Sainte, and...
And Munchy.
And my nemesis Munchy, he's here.
He's here and he's larger than life.
Oh, Ben Sainte, I didn't destroy you last time, but I'm here to finish the job.
I have my guns, I have my grenades, I have all the things that you are weak to.
Those are not allowed in a Pokemon battle.
Oh, no, it's you.
It's Hippo.
And you're here.
I'm the rulesman.
I'm here to make sure it's a fair fight.
Hippo's here to adjudicate our grudge match.
I didn't prepare for this. Oh, no.
Who lives and who dies.
We're gonna settle this once and for all, Munchy.
It's been a long time coming.
You had free reign over this place for far too long.
I'm gonna fucking collar you and shackle you.
I'm gonna put you in the stocks in the front of town of our Old West town.
You're gonna fucking chain me underwater.
I'm just gonna have to burn there.
Yeah, anyway.
Paradoxically, because I'm underwater.
And I can't burn, but...
It's not gonna be pretty.
And the way I'm gonna do this to you is by utterly defeating you
in a series of Pokemon battles that we have decided upon.
That was my one weakness.
I thought that your weakness was guns, but I guess it was just video games.
I'm weak to guns and strong to Pokemon.
So since you started this fight, since you picked this fight,
I get to choose my weapon and it's Pokemon.
But actually, you're probably a lot better at Pokemon battling than me
because I've never fucking done this before.
I have never built a team or fought another human being.
My first Pokemon is Pokemon Goo.
Pokemon Goo?
Alright, the fan favorite of...
Let's go.
Alright, so the way it's gonna work is me and Munchy are gonna have three...
We're gonna have three sets of best out of three.
We're gonna fight with teams that we've...
I mean, I have painstakingly put this team together.
I have done research and crunched numbers and made spreadsheets
and the fruits of my labor.
I wish I was kidding.
The fruits of my labor are here
and we're gonna compete in the three different tiers.
Little Cup is gonna be first and Little Cup is for unevolved Pokemon.
It's for the weak bitches.
And then...
I'm gonna get you good for that one.
I'm gonna steam now. You activated my gamer rage.
I'm like that caterpillar in Mario that turns red.
You just stomped on me and now I'm red and I'm invincible.
You're fucked.
Okay, and then second is the underused tier for the pretty good kind of good Pokemon.
And then third is the ultimate championship, the overused tier, OU,
for the real super strong boys.
Not the strongest Uber tier.
Way too good for any reasonable battling tier.
But like the soap, the good enough, but not quite overpowered tier.
That's how it works for anyone that doesn't know about Pokemon.
Like I didn't like 3D.
I've also made myself a blanket of nails.
I will wrap around my body right now
and I will always have this on the entire time I play to improve my stimuli.
Is that gonna be like your held item as a Pokemon?
Like a nailed blanket?
Increases your Pokemon's suffering by 100%?
Well, see, relevant to nails, you know how you have the Benz Saint drink?
I decided to make my own drink.
And it's called the Munchie.
It's comprised of tic-tacs and nails.
And I blend them together and then I just drink it.
That wasn't the way there was a Benz Saint drink.
The Benz Saint is hot coffee.
Hot coffee and chocolate protein.
Oh yeah.
And you're tears because you're gonna cry once I'm done pummeling you with my fuck you.
I'm gonna kill you Munchie.
I'm not talking about this fight.
I'm not talking about Pokemon.
I'm going to come to your house and murder you.
I'll be waiting.
But let's not worry about that.
Yeah, alright.
Open the damn game so I can look at something.
Yeah, let's get it started.
So, let's have a look.
So Benz Saint, we got Porygon, we got Abro.
We got some little guy from Dragon Quest.
It's a mole from Dragon Quest.
It's Drillber, dude.
And we got Red Robin, Red Breast.
And that guy from an anime.
It's the monster from Undertale.
It is, it's the Undertale kid.
And we got a Kakun with spikes.
And on the other side we have...
Kakuna with spikes.
We have Munchie, he's a clown.
We got another Red Robin, we got another little kid.
We got Star Yu, that's the one.
We got Munchlax, which is his spirit animal.
We got a Kakun egg with spikes and a sword.
I'm gonna kill that sword.
They're all level 5.
You're not even gonna be able to fucking breathe.
Let the games begin.
Alright.
Now everyone knows that the entire battle is decided by who you send out first.
And everything else after that is just a formality.
So this is crucial, this is crucial here.
Got it.
Go, yellow bullet, mark two.
We both fucking protected each other.
We both knew we were gonna send out Farathorn.
You fucking bitch, you're not even cool dude.
Yeah, well I thought you had two steel types, so I thought I'd send out a fighting... anyway.
Yellow bullet, yeah right.
Like you think you're cool.
You're no match for my Juggalo.
They're staring each other down.
That's the only one I remember from Pokemon Stadium.
That's the only one.
I was gonna do more.
I think one of them is these Pokemon.
Whoa, he used knockoff.
And the other guy used knockoff as well.
God, we're so evenly fighting a critical hit, so I'm winning.
Yeah, it's true.
What's he gonna do?
What will he do?
Oh my fucking god!
I can't believe you went for that.
Why was yellow bullet faster than the other guy?
The other guy is cause the name.
Thank you.
It's a bullet speed.
This bird, which one?
Level 5.
What's he gonna do?
You know, I'm...
You're headband, what do you think I'm gonna do?
What do you think I'm gonna do, huh?
What do you think I'm gonna do?
Oh, I can switch sides, yeah.
I can't actually see what you're selecting or hogging over.
I can switch.
Oh god, I don't know.
I just don't know.
Alright.
Egg bullet.
Both of them are bullets.
Egg bullet, go!
The iron barbs hurt little bird.
This little bird is very small.
He's got thin legs.
Will he be able to actually, with the thin legs,
probably attack without getting hit by the spikes?
Oh, you're such a fool, dude.
You're such a fool.
You turn.
Dude, you don't even know who fucking brains are.
Oh, I like that you're a clown.
Do you see my little avatar?
Yeah, of course.
It's Munchie's mom's dildo.
Paralyzed instantly.
What happened?
Thunder wave.
Why can this egg use thunder wave?
It's an egg.
Look at his eyes.
It's level 5.
Look at the intensity of his eyes.
It's so stoned, dude.
Um, fuck.
Nah, fuck you, dude.
Whatever.
That's stupid.
Oh, he knocked off the item, which was something.
Stealth Rock.
I don't know anything about Pokémon.
The fuck is all of this?
Dude, I had never heard of none of the moves I'm using
on any of my Pokémon
I had ever heard of before this shit.
It's fake.
It's not real.
That's true.
Yeah, yep, yep, yep.
So they're both...
They're always getting out of there.
Come on, yellow bullet mark 2.
Show them how to die.
Always getting hurt quick and suddenly.
With bullets.
Drain punch.
Oh, he really drained that dildo
out of his action.
There's one ain't nothing.
Dude, you ain't fucking...
You ain't even heard of my bitch.
It's gonna be you, dude.
Whoa.
Nice.
Mmm.
Carl's junior.
Whoa, Starry has a little thing on his leg.
On the back of his leg.
I didn't know.
I was entranced.
He's not psychic type.
Yes, he is.
He's a psychic type.
He's junior.
You don't know shit.
That's true. Does he have a psychic move?
Guys.
What am I gonna do?
What is he gonna do?
I'm sure.
He's probably gonna use... wait, hang on.
Let's check this.
Psychic is ineffective against...
Put away your dictionary, Ben.
This is a war.
Dude, New World can't know.
Can't know anything?
Can't know.
Good.
Psychic is zero against...
What even is... oh, I can hover over the guy.
He's dark and fighting.
He doesn't look dark or fighting.
He looks like a little kid.
Oh, rapid spin, of course.
Who will I've been?
HB45% possible abilities.
Da-da-da-da.
I could have been looking at information this whole time, but I didn't.
I know what you're gonna do.
Oh, ah, shit.
It wasn't what I thought you'd do.
That's quite powerful.
This yellow bullet is punching like a...
Storm punches...
An old lady.
When she couldn't get inside quick enough.
Knockoff...
What kind of words you're saying?
Knockoff deals double damage against enemies that are holding an item.
So...
That's why it did all that.
Oh, you're done!
I can't believe you're hitting all these.
That's not how that works.
What is the hit rate?
It's 90% hit rate.
Man, this bird...
I know, but that's not how that works.
How can this bird stand up to a fucking jumping slice with a foot?
Speaking of jumping slice...
It's a sword.
It can slice him in half.
It gets you a bad idea.
Because they can punch me and swords are weak to people who have bones.
Oh, it's the little...
It's the mole of my hand.
Dirt bullet! Attack!
Oh, shit.
Oh, I've made a terrible mistake.
Yeah, you fucking retard.
Didn't you know birds can really borrow on the ground?
They're more powerful against ground.
Yeah, man.
That bird annihilated that mole.
He did.
Just like real nature.
What a terrible mistake.
You're fucking done. You are done.
You are done.
You've made the last mistake in your life, mister.
That's not true.
It's not true.
You've made the last mistake you'll ever make.
If he's made the last mistake, that means everything he does now will be a good idea.
Oh, no.
I did it!
I've... I...
Well, you know, I'd like to pretend that I predicted that, but I didn't.
It's Friends General.
I can't believe this.
He's super effective.
What are all these things?
0.67 times speed,
1.5...
Attack, 1.5 defense.
You're done, kid.
You're done. Use curse!
You just... you just sat on him.
That was also good.
Oh, here comes... here comes old yellow boy for backfraction.
Flying kick.
Attack.
Yeah, you know exactly. That's exactly right.
Ah, shit, I knew it.
I know. I know. I know. I know.
Birds can't... can't withstand a drop kick.
Especially small little babies.
You're so fast.
I can't even see his movements.
Yeah, you do got this.
Don't away.
I've got... I've got fucking bones inside here.
He brought a knife to a Pokemon fight.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
That was the only thing I could do.
Using knockoff is really good because you always want items.
Knockoff is awesome.
I am fucked.
And the crowd goes...
And the crowd goes, uh, get on with it already.
Hey, I'm trying to fucking figure out.
He hasn't even used his Porygon yet.
He could use all of those.
He didn't.
Maybe he used it.
Oh, this looks like it's...
It's over for Munchy.
His little friend going to be beaten to death with one of them.
I can't believe you've hit Clyde at all of those.
Uh, yeah.
Well, it means 90%.
Dude, do you know...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's how that works.
You don't know how many times people have died in these very chairs that we sit in.
One point for Ben.
Bing!
Are you in?
Are you seeing my precious neon bullet?
Neon bullet.
Oh, the little leg's going this way and that way.
Yeah, yeah, man.
He's kicking like pretend footballs, one after the other.
That's his intimidation strategy.
Ah, shit.
So we're doing a rematch.
Now we've got Porygon vs. A knife.
Can physical...
Can Japanese steel...
...steal slice a computer?
Fold it a thousand times.
I think I can...
I can't slice a fucking program in that.
I think I've seen this in an animal before.
You just gotta believe...
Yeah, what else people got seizures?
If you mix circuit boards in with your Japanese folded steel, you can slice computer programs.
That's what I know.
That doesn't fucking matter.
I don't care if I move last.
Oh, yeah, you're slow as fuck anyway.
Oh, no.
I wonder what my switch is.
Oh, look, it doesn't exist.
Oh, dear.
Okay, okay.
Ability download? Holy shit.
You could destroy my computer.
If I download something, I'll do it.
You could download a virus so that it looks like Ben won.
Yes.
It's Dirt Boy.
No!
Dirt Boy is worse than dirt.
That's why he digs it.
You act like something's gonna happen when in fact you know nothing will happen.
Oh fuck Shadow Sneak, I'm such an asshole.
You can't escape from the shank.
You can't be fucking gay, dude.
That's what I learned in college.
Yes, whatever you do, whatever you go in life, just please, for God's sake, don't be fucking gay, dude.
Okay, okay.
Will a knife stab up yellow bullet this time?
Will he be able to get the slice on him?
Look at that.
He's not even wearing plate armor.
Yes, oh no.
Oh, what?
I just wanted to, yeah, I got that crit, duh.
Why did you do that?
I wanted you to flinch, but I forgot I went fucking, shut up, dude.
Oh, he's getting flustered.
Now time for Carl.
Carlton.
It is time for Carl.
Geez, I don't even know.
I don't even know what star you is.
Bubblebeam.
Is it a star or is it you?
Don't fucking check me out.
It's like that Austin Powers movie.
With those Asians.
Fuck you, fuck me.
You know?
We're all one big happy family.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck!
God damn it!
Something happened.
Yeah.
I fucking missed, dude.
I saw it.
High jump kit.
You avoid it and then something else happened.
What happened?
You'll never know unless you replay it.
Oh, he kept going and crashed.
That's the stakes of which you do with the jump and hop.
That's the push and pull of being gay.
If you jump up, you're gonna fall down.
But every time before, you can fall.
Of course, friend junior with the fire punch.
Out of the fucking nowhere.
You know what they say?
Fire is your best friend, junior.
Especially if you like to kill people.
Abracadabra?
What are these?
These are not even a thing.
Oh, that berry juice though.
Oh no, it's too powerful.
Big body.
Friend junior is the greatest person alive.
This is going in the complete opposite direction.
The greatest person alive, yeah.
Oh god, I don't know.
Friend junior is just too powerful.
He sent out his computer to fight Munchie's friend.
He tried to attack, but it didn't work.
That's it?
I'm fucked.
You're fucking gay, dude.
That's what you are.
Hey, whatever, man.
I'm so...
This text goes by way too fast for me to understand what's happening each time.
He's using his tri-times, two times.
Oh, he's gonna body slam me.
What? Wait, really?
I can't believe that.
Holy shit.
He could come back.
He could come back at any moment.
No, yeah, this is it.
This is it.
I also could do this.
Or maybe I'm gonna do this, bam!
Oh no, but he didn't.
I screamed.
The little bird, he's a red-rubbin' red breast.
He's used to the winter.
Oh no!
He sliced you, because he's seen many winters.
He knows the ice better than you do.
I'm...
Fuck you, dude.
Oh shit, it's mirror time.
Bird's first birds.
It's bird against bird.
It's a bird-fight bird world.
Uh...
Dear...
Maybe I'm faster.
I am.
Because of your ability, bitch.
Well, don't you have the same ability?
Yeah, it's true.
Oh shit, a bird comes up against an egg.
The next one...
There's a new bird in that egg.
I'm not sure if I have any
meaningfully useful
powers to do here.
If all else fails,
you can slice the bird in half
with a sword.
I'm gonna sweep him.
I'm gonna sweep Munchie's whole team
with bird bullet.
Bird bullet is gonna rip through...
Is a fucking paralyzed
little guy.
Oh no.
Oh no, he had an accident.
He had a little bird accident
and got paralyzed.
Oh shit, he's got times three attack.
That's like more than
about one. I just feel like this is fucking
bad for me. Hold on.
Yeah, it's bad for you.
Yeah, you're gonna die.
Yeah, your mom's gonna be real mad if
your dildos get broken and she can't
do what she's gonna do.
Hmm...
They're staring each other down.
Are you ready?
Are you prepared to die
right now? Oh dear.
Quick use big
fucking hit.
Nah, I think
he's got this actually.
No! No!
It didn't do it all.
Come on bird bullet, please just overcome
your paralysis.
Like Kirito
in that show
that I've never seen
but that anime guy keeps talking about it.
That one guy.
That one Shella.
A knife versus a bird. I honestly don't know
which bird is quick.
If my paralysis
doesn't fuck me over again,
I think I win. Yeah, I think you do too.
Oh dear. Oh my,
oh me.
Oh, I did it!
I'm killing it! There it comes!
Here it fucking comes bro!
I can't believe this!
I did it!
I can't believe it!
I'm the champion of little cup!
He did it! He's the champion!
Fuck! Oh no!
I'm a disgrace.
Swords dance bird bullet.
That's all it took. A little bird killed
your whole family. How do you feel?
Oh well, I mean, I would like
to have my family back but obviously that's too...
It's too much.
Alright, now it's time for you, you.
Oh, should we have a little
interview, Ben? What do you think of that?
I think
that
I was...
I was, you know,
I didn't even try. Everything I said before
about making my team
really carefully
and making spreadsheets and crunching numbers
and doing hours and hours of research.
None of it was true. I just picked whatever.
I just went with what my heart told me.
You know what, paid off.
Are you in on this? Are you in this new fight?
Uh...
Basketball vs. Monotype.
Oh no, Bensate vs. Munchie. There we go.
Basketball?
Basketball and Monotype.
Alright, let's go through this team.
We got, we got
Play-Doh coming out of one of those things.
We got Blastoise.
We got Catgirl.
We got that thing for this.
It's a boy, thank you very much.
Okay, it's the onion from that movie.
We got Big Crocker Boy.
He's gonna bite you, slice you
with very small eyes.
And Snorlax,
because he's fat.
And then, on the other teams.
We got a very tall
Pikachu.
We got
Brunswink.
We got...
What the fuck is that? This is like a slicey moon.
It's like that one enemy
from the moon in Dark Cloud.
You know the one. Nobody knows the one.
Sailor Moon.
Yeah, Sailor Moon, that's the one.
Then we got, oh, it's a bunch of
roses. It's a bouquet.
And now we got two swords.
He's got extra swords this time.
I agree, Florgis.
Florgis is gross.
And we got Crobat, because, you know,
nobody likes Crobat.
Because whatever, I didn't care
about that last slot.
Crobat is actually the key to this
entire...
Oh, I see.
I see.
What do you think?
Which Pokemon will you play?
Will they play which Pokemon?
Go!
Beef Bullet!
I like how you didn't fucking go for it.
What did you think I was gonna go for?
Spaghetti versus
Big Pig.
Let's have a look. We got Bug Rock.
So it's gross.
That's what it is. And we got Ice Ground.
So he's gonna...
He's gonna...
I don't know what he's gonna do.
I got the defense. I got
the offense. I got the fucking
beans. I have the beans in my hair.
Oh shit, this Bug Rock has Hyper Beam.
Don't say that.
It's got Hyper Beam, dude.
Yeah, dude, you fucking piece of shit.
I got a little Bug have Hyper Beam.
Wait, does he actually...
You're not supposed to tell me...
I can't tell you what they have.
I'm gay as written on your ceiling. Did you write that in your sleep?
Cause that's what your concess was
telling you?
Let me just look up real quick
and confirm that.
Oh shit.
Big Pig used Earthquake.
Cause he's...
You fool. You absolute...
You absolute monster.
He actually did it.
Shut up.
Oh god, you...
You need to use a...
What's the moss from Dark Cloud? Dark Souls?
The moss?
What are you?
No, the green moss is not green moss.
It's like purple or whatever.
My game was crashed.
Oh really?
Oh, it's crashed for me too.
Oh...
You wanna just start a new one
and do exactly what we did?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, let's do that.
That seems...
Okay, we'll just get it right back to where we were.
We're doing a big old Swifty Do.
Uh, here's something.
Alright, well let's do the half-time show.
Yeah.
Put in like a little...
Put in like a...
I'll put in music.
And a gif. That'll be the half-time show.
And then we could be the guys in the box saying...
Well that wasn't...
Well that was not a fucking...
Well, well, well...
He passed the ball...
And he scored, but will he do it again?
What do you think?
I don't care.
He is gay.
That's why he's playing football.
Oh...
Football's gay.
Damn...
Damn, you can't just say that.
On TV.
TV?
Internet v...
Oh, no.
Internet vision.
You have it, I have it.
But will they accept it?
No.
It's the onset.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I had to think for a second.
But the seconds are weaknesses.
You see when my mom taught me...
If you told me one thing, it was this.
You always steal.
You have to steal.
And we're back.
There was a technical hip-skilly,
and now we're just re...
We're redoing the past.
Hopefully there won't be any random changes
in what happened.
Now, okay, we're back.
Okay, now we're back exactly where we were.
We got a toxic pig.
We got a spaghetti earthquake...
I hate sex so much.
Spaghetti.
I feel like going. I have to say it.
I hate sex.
Shit!
That reminds me of a drill tweet recently.
It said,
quote,
history will show that leaving the EU
was the right move for Britain.
And also,
I don't believe in sex.
Signed the Brexit asexual.
God fucking dammit!
I...
What?
Ooh!
Coming or coming out.
Black and red, like my friends.
All my friends.
He's ground and dark, he's dark-
Don't say that!
And...
He got hit with a carbon-earthquake
and he killed him.
He killed him, it's fine.
Well, it's not fine for you.
God, that was terrible.
What an awful exchange.
Why do you mix me and want to touch a little kid?
Well, that really hurts my feelings
and also harasses me.
Um...
I think you're probably...
What if you get off to touch your kids now?
Yeah, appropriately.
One time I rub against someone
in the subway station and I'm pretty sure
they called me a Jew.
There we go.
Well, that is a terrifying screech
of a fucking bouquet.
Uh-huh.
It's just like a rosary.
It's like a rosary of evolution.
It's like a rosetta stone.
You nerd.
It knows Japans.
You friggin' nerd, Munchin.
I forgot.
It knows how I'm going.
I forgot how the ground is-
You forgot about fairy types?
The best type?
Oh no.
Big fat friend or...
It's not fucking fairy anymore.
He grew up into normal friend.
Friend was my father's name.
Call me... Jimmy.
Moonbyist.
That's what you call an average attack.
It's sort of effective.
But...
Snorlax has got like a million hit-pins.
Hit-pins.
I've got a million pints, dude.
Oh shit, he's got an item.
What?
Oh, it's the U.S. government.
It is the U.S. government.
I can't wait to destroy it.
I can't wait to just tear it apart and dismantle it.
Who will win? Flowers or authority?
Oh my god.
Yeah.
It's like the 60s all over again.
They put in the flowers in the barrels of the guns.
I don't know what...
Is that super effective or not?
I don't know what Celebi is for.
For gay rights.
Or...
Is for...
In the morning.
Baton pass.
Oh dear, oh dear, oh dear, oh dear.
Oh dear.
Just when you thought being gay wasn't bad enough,
you had to throw in...
Being extra gay.
Extra gay.
The new product from...
Pokemon The Gay Company.
I know exactly what to do.
You are stupid.
No! Fuck!
Shut up!
Did you know I was going to do that?
Yeah, of course.
What else did you do?
Dude, he's going to use an old type attack.
Dude!
You steel ghost.
Son of a fucking bitch.
You set me up, Munchie!
You fucking set me up!
I'm going to fucking kill you, bro.
I'm going to kill you, bro.
He's ready.
I'm going to shoot you with sword bullet, right?
Fucking now! No! How are you so fast?
I'm deceptively fast.
Oh boy.
It's really getting heated.
This is it for me.
There's no coming back.
That's a fiery heating punch.
How can I stop this?
How can I stop, friend?
I killed friend Junior.
That friend is here for revenge.
No!
Oh!
He's burned.
It's leftovers won't do shit now.
They get burned away.
That's not true, though.
No!
All you got to do is start believing in fairy tales.
Because I'm a fairy tale.
And you're about to be my tale.
I'm going to fucking grind you into the paste that you are.
You are a pasty white boy.
And I'm going to rape you.
Because I'm black.
And that's what we do.
Munchie, please. Please.
Just have mercy.
Oh, God.
Aspene, fire punch.
This is a, surely a,
clearly a match.
This is clearly a match.
This is clearly, definitely a match.
It's a match between two people.
A neck?
Maybe you should switch into your ground type.
Oh, wait, he's dead.
That burn will kill him.
But not before
sealing my victory.
Is that, like, a thing
where you're going to bring out a seal?
Ah, shit.
Ah, whatever.
Ah, god damn it.
Spaghetti vs. the moon.
I just want to be, I just want to be extra
careful, so let me just give this to you.
I just want to be extra careful.
Let me just give you this to you guys.
Let me just give this to you guys.
He's going to protect Stovework
and I'll talk to him.
So I can, you know,
you know how it be.
This is an intense battle.
Fucking neck bullet.
Neck bullet.
I love neck bullet and neck bullet mark, too.
How does he shoot his neck
without killing himself?
Well,
he's a long guy.
He is the bullet. He's just comprised
largely of neck.
Where does it end?
It's a girl.
Oh, fuck this.
Why did I like girls on my team? That's why I'm losing.
That's why I'm losing this fight.
You're going for the Pokémon
that arouses you more than the Pokémon
that will save your life.
This Pokémon arouses me just fine. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
He does have a very, he does have
an infectious smile.
Oh, no.
I've made a terrible mistake
over and over again.
That's what life is all about.
For you.
Oh, of course he is protect.
Munchy.
Oh, that burn. That burn will do it.
He's sticky webbed.
He's rocked. He's burned.
He needs a nice hot bath, but he doesn't have one.
No!
Oh, yes!
I can't believe this.
That's what old Hammurabi told me
when he fucking killed me.
It's kind of close.
It's kind of close when she has one extra Pokémon,
but it's already damaged.
What will Ben do?
What will he...
If he's smart, yeah, and if he's smart
then he'll fall right into my trap
and he's a trap.
No, come on, though.
Yeah, you fell right into my trap, buddy.
Oh, shit.
Well...
You can't not psychic a bat.
That's what they always say.
And you're going to try and do what you think is right,
but you're going to be wrong.
Because I also know what you're going to do right now.
Oh, my God.
Are you scaring me?
You see,
when God created me, he said,
all right, I was having fun
with my Play-Doh game people,
and I thought it was going to be funny,
but this prank has gotten out of control,
and I need you to undo my gamer prank.
That's right.
Oh, I see.
That's neck bullet one.
Correct.
It's big Pikachu.
The evolved form of Pikachu.
No!
Oh, what?
That electric wasn't even good.
Time to bring out the...
It's like you think that you're cool.
It's almost like that.
It's a ring around the rosies.
It's almost like that you think you're cool.
Because the rosies are in the ring.
Foolish.
What a mistake.
I can't...
We're just...
There we go. That's all I needed.
That fucking minus special defense.
No, come on.
Don't...
Don't fuck around with me, though.
Yes!
I'll kill you.
I'll kill you, though.
Here, I'm going to keep them for can fodder.
No lie.
Dammit! God fucking dammit!
That's no lie.
He used protect against nothing.
I don't know what I'm doing anymore.
We'll smiley face punch him.
Will he win?
Also, I hate florgas.
Oh, he's toxic.
You're dead, boy.
You don't have anti-dote.
Oh, I'm...
I'm terrible.
This whole battle has just been one mistake after another.
I don't care if Shuckle fucking dies.
Who cares about Shuckle?
Nobody, that's who.
We got three Pokemon each.
It's an even match.
Kind of even...
Digimon.
Here he comes with his big attack.
You fucking nerd!
You fucking nerd, are you serious?
I forgot.
Did you really just do that?
Did you really fucking just use
Dragon Pulse on fucking florgas?
I forgot.
You infinite bastard.
You're a fucking...
What? Holy shit.
You fucking retard. I'm still going to win even though I'm gay.
Maybe I spoke too soon.
Listen, you can't judge someone
just based on their sexuality, alright?
Wait, what?
I can't.
Damn.
You can get most of the information.
If there's one thing I know
it's that being who you are
is not...
It's wrong.
Agreed.
Oh, that special defense is really...
Okay, I know what to do.
Oh, you didn't let me do it though.
Okay, shit.
Oh, shit.
I think it's gonna die.
It's not gonna go...
What even is aura sphere?
Is it a physical psychic?
Or is it a special fighting?
It's a special fighting.
I think you can do it now.
You have faith in me? Come on, bad bull.
Yeah, roost! Yeah, roost!
Oh, keep roostin'!
Roost all the time.
Roost Bolton.
There we go.
Is that what you were looking for, you son of a bitch?
He's bored.
Oh, I didn't mean to do that one,
but it doesn't matter anyway.
Doesn't it?
No, it doesn't.
You're just gonna keep...
I think, Ben,
the amount of healing you're gonna need to do...
No, look at that. I'm making progress.
Oh, yeah?
Don't even fucking try with this dragon pulse.
It could go either way.
Oh, bad bullet.
Bad bullet.
You can do this all day, dude.
I can do this all day.
But you're gonna have to damage me eventually,
and that's when you're gonna die.
Hang on, how much... Roost has 10 out of 16s.
That's a lot of roosting you can do.
Shit, I can only roost 10 more times.
I'm gonna need at least 100 for this plan to work.
Shit.
It's more than 5, sir.
As soon as he gets a crit,
it's over.
Yeah, dude.
You got this under control.
I've been waiting my whole life for this battle.
Oh, man.
That's sick.
Just end me.
Please.
Please put me out of my misery, Munchy.
Alright, now I've had enough.
I've had enough. You got this one.
Okay, I've had enough.
I'm gonna give you this one, Munchy.
Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna let you have this one.
You deserve it.
One point for Munchy
towards this round.
Alright, rematch.
Let's not mess around.
Yeah, let's take this one
seriously, though.
Yeah, for real, for real.
Absolutely, 100%.
Oh, dear.
It started off with a superb effective.
I forgot about moves.
Only you remembered that the video games
were not catered to retards.
Yeah, I wish I could remember that.
I wish I could remember that.
But, you know...
When Shigeru Miyamoto
first swore...
No, god damn it! Why?
When it just happened, it was a shadow boy.
And you got superb effective.
When he first set foot on the moon,
he said, from this day forward,
I will not, if you do games,
will be minority repellent.
Thank god for that.
Oh, no, this is...
Is that what they said in the minority report?
Oh, that's what they said
in, uh...
last week, tonight, with John Oliver.
When he was interviewed.
Are you just gonna have all your guys get damaged
and then go home?
Yeah, sure.
Why not?
This trap...
is trapping you good.
It may be paralyzed and a boy.
And act like you know how things are.
You act like you know what things are,
except you don't.
I know one or two things.
Can beef boy kill the trap?
Find out.
Well, I don't know if you know if you realize,
but he's a trap because it's a girl,
but it's not.
And that's why it's a trap.
I know what that trap is.
You just want to put your doll in it,
and then you realize, where do you put it?
Well, you realize
that there's a wonderful thing called boy pussy.
Alright, take that out of the video.
Wait, no, what is that?
Tell me about that.
I'm wondering.
Take that out of the video.
I'm the one who has the footage.
I can edit it all day.
Both of you look like the coolest guys
with their boy pussy.
Yeah.
Uh, let's...
Let's try something radical.
No, no, you're not.
That's pretty radical.
Shoot that bat with your gun.
It's Digimon.
Oh shit, electric.
Can you Thunder Shock Big Blue?
Yeah.
Maybe.
Amphor off the slowest fuck though, dude.
Um...
Yeah, well...
So...
So what though?
What was that?
It didn't do anything.
It got rid of the stealth rock.
What the hell's the stealth...
Dude.
The greatest commenter of all time.
What the hell's the stealth rock?
I don't know.
I'm here to provide moral support
for me and no one else.
People have laid a clever trap
and megablastoise.
Dude, look at my eyes.
You think my eyes can see?
Fuck you, I'm blind, dude.
How can our eyes be real
if we can't even see?
Exactly.
How can the sea be real if we can't see?
The sea.
That's true.
A.
Don't even fucking try it.
You're stupid and it won't work.
Oh, for God's...
Oh, please. Oh, no.
Okay.
Wait, it's Wish?
That's cute. He wished that his sword buddy
would come and save its own life with health.
And he did.
He's alive.
Oh, that wasn't good enough.
The sword danced.
I've really...
I've really fucked up.
Oh, dear.
Try this one for size.
He's got times three.
Oh, sacred sword!
Ooh, that's good.
No.
No!
Sadistic is not going to work, by the way.
I hope you realize.
Yeah, I do.
I know ghosts.
I ain't afraid no ghosts.
I am.
They are real.
And they're real.
The one time I saw a ghost and I said,
Dude, why do you do this to people?
And they said, I just want to be loved.
And I cried.
And they said, you know what, I'm going to write a story about this.
I'm going to post it on a creepypasta.wiki.
And I'm going to get a lot of updates.
God, I can help you become famous on the internet.
That's what I wanted to do.
My name was Ben St.
And he never got famous on the internet.
And he became a ghost and he went back in time.
And that's who I met.
Munchie, you know what?
Before, I was debating whether I should
Swords Dance or Shadow Sneak.
And if I had Swords Dance,
then that fucking sacred sword would have killed friend.
And I would be home free.
God fucking dammit.
The whole match was decided right there by not
Swords Dancing.
Shit.
You really screwed the pooch on this one.
I sure did.
You guys
are better at commentating your own match
than I am.
We actually know what our Pokemon are doing.
The text goes
by too fast so all I can do is go
eh.
You know?
That's all we need, dude.
I lifted one weight yesterday
and my arm is like broken.
Nice.
Was it one kilogram?
It was one centimeter.
That's very dense.
Just like
someone.
I want to insult someone
but can't decide so
I'll just leave it up to interpretation.
Fuck.
Bitch. Ass.
You act like you know what shit happens
and you don't know how shit happens.
You just know that you are a little boy.
Chomp his neck. Chomp his neck.
You've got the teeth, I think.
No!
God, it read me like a fucking book.
Read you like a
bestseller.
Jesus.
Dude.
You don't even know how weirds are.
Can Kamina eat roses?
I don't think he's a vegetarian.
I think,
yeah, you need that guy.
He is a vegetarian.
Or is he a vegetable?
He is. He's gross.
Find out next time.
On the next episode of
Dagen
Dragon.
Dragon Kid Boy.
You know what's called
Dragon Ball Z
because he went through
drafts
and the first one was Dragon Ball A
and it wasn't very good so he did it again.
Well see,
what you gotta understand about Dragon Ball
that was made by a crazy man.
A crazy man
in a cave and that guy
was just up to no good.
Hmm.
Let me get out the damage calculator here.
Pokemon is
boring.
Right?
I was about to yawn really loud
but then I stopped.
Damage calculator.
A little bit of good indicator of my current feelings.
Just kill the swords or something.
Use your brain powers
and your psychic.
Use the death note.
You can see his name.
No, that's not gonna fucking kill me, faggot.
Yeah, you think you're cool, dude.
God.
Damn it.
See, you just gotta have to
you have to see with your mind's eye, dude.
I forgot my bat boy
is so dead.
Nope.
That doesn't matter.
I'm special.
You sure are, man.
I'm special, though.
You used U-turn.
Which means
Pikachu's here.
Get some nice free damage there.
They're going once.
Going twice.
It's souls to
US government.
Oh, no.
That crocodile's cry
sounds like her beginning of a rock song.
It sounds cool.
Oh.
You dummy.
I've been completely outclassed.
Ah, shit.
Yeah, I'm not gonna...
No.
I like how that was resisted, by the way.
Nope.
Hey, you did something
with your life.
I fucking did it.
Shit.
It's 2 vs 4.
Yeah, 2 vs 4.
Friend
is a...
It jumps really high.
I'm a little...
It's kind of like when you
fall into the flower bed.
You're doing fucking this shit.
I wish
you had knocked off my left over.
She worked really hard on those flowers.
You can't just roll around on them.
So that's why it didn't work.
And it was protected by the mother
of friend.
That's the lore behind that
attack.
So this is what we're doing, huh?
Yeah, this is your fucking
doing.
It's almost like
I'm your parent, so I'm disappointed in you.
I forgot that you had one.
The fact is that you had another Pokémon.
Oh, you got a wish.
And is he gonna do more?
Is he gonna do more health getting?
Was he a doctor?
Doctor bullet?
Doctor bat?
Come to bat? Go to bat with a doctor?
What is he doing?
He's gonna stab you
with his U-turn.
And run away.
I'm not letting
this match go. I can't.
I just can't let it go.
There you
got that, dude.
This fucking flower
is tough as nails.
But not as hard as nails, because it's a
grass and, well, it's not made of
grass, it's a fairy.
But it is made of grass, I think.
But that doesn't mean it's a grass type.
How does it not mean it's a grass type?
I don't get it. But the fuck is a fairy?
We got wings.
We got little
feminine
wings. Damn!
You're just gonna say that about him?
Well, it is a female, I mean.
Damn!
Damn, dude.
What the fuck? In 2016?
Dude, are you higher something, dude?
Well, no, actually,
I am on the second floor, so...
If I jumped out of my window, I could
be seriously hurt.
Oh, what? Shit!
Ah, fuck. Ah, Christ.
It's spaghetti.
Back from already.
It's over is what it is.
It's over!
Yeah, sure.
Do whatever you want, stupid.
More.
Brave bird.
That's not even true.
We're in a rocky helmet, like a piece of shit.
Those are illegal.
Uh...
Those are illegal in our society.
Nah, dude.
Yes.
Oh, god. Why do I just keep...
Why do I keep doing these things?
Oh, bad boys.
He's got webbed.
I think that means you can't leave.
No, it reduces my speed,
but not for Bat Bullet,
because he is, um...
A flying. He's a flyer.
He is an up-and-laid ride, this guy.
Hmm.
Just use kill.
That's the best move.
Yeah, that is the habit.
Munchy.
Munchy reaches into his pocket.
Here, Shuckle. He'd take it.
It tosses a gun into the battle.
He did say he had grenades.
It's possible.
It's probable.
It's Pokemon!
That's the theme.
Pokemon!
Oh, man.
In Verbank City,
Roxy, the gym,
it's like her band is playing on the stage.
And, um...
It's awesome, because the song they're singing goes like
P-O-K-E-M-O-N
Pokemon!
That's the song, dude.
I'm so proud of you.
That's the fucking song.
Finally.
Finally free of the menace of Shuckle.
You got cheerleaders and cheerfollowers.
Foolish.
Oh!
Yeah.
I'm gonna turn this shit around.
You turn it around 360 or 180?
I don't even...
know...
what that means.
Turn it around 360 or 180. Which one?
Oh, shit!
Ah, shit. I'm fucking dead.
I'm dead.
I am dead.
Holy shit, you are dead. You only got one big fat friend.
And he's nearly dead himself.
This is intense Pokemon.
Um...
Will he do Moon Blast? Will he do Protect?
I gotta open up the damage calculator again.
Fire Punch.
We retaliate.
The moves that he has shown he has.
I forget, I forget if friend goes before...
who cable and...
I can't remember.
Wait, I can look.
I know I'm gonna look it up.
What?
I'm gonna look it up in the fucking...
Yeah, we're both damage calculated right now.
Yeah.
Yeah, boot cable it moves first.
I think I got it.
What's the name of your Pokemon?
I'm very confident that Moon Blast will kill friend.
Goddamn it!
What?
Oh!
Why did...
What happened?
Why did that?
I still lose though.
I still lose.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god, I fucking did it.
I can't believe it.
Dude, just because you've won the battle doesn't mean you're...
You're not gonna win.
It's a point for them.
That was so...
That was so close, holy shit.
We're gonna do a deciding round for this round.
This time there's a special rule.
You gotta die as quickly as possible.
Shit.
God...
Fuck.
I can't believe you predicted.
Of course.
Look at me.
Just look at me and you'll see.
You'll see the reason why.
Foolish.
Foolish spell.
That was a foolish spell you cast.
Goddamn.
I know, I know in my heart what I must do.
No.
Don't do it.
I know in my heart what I must do.
Give up.
Fuck.
Digimon.
You should blast his oise.
Blast his oise out of his head.
He had...
He had scald, he had dragons something.
And he had punch.
Yeah, I did have punch.
Do you guys want any?
Because I brought some for everyone.
I would love some punch right now.
I can't be sober for this.
You have punch coming from Blastoise's back thing.
You just spray it.
Yeah, it's Hawaiian punch though.
Eww.
With just a tad of nails.
And battery acid.
Oh, that's okay.
I made just for you, Ben.
Because I know that you're inhuman.
Because no one know my little face like that.
That's what they say when you're having...
That's what they say when you're having sex
is you're inhuman.
Because you're probably in...
Unless you're into Pokemon.
Yes, which I, of course, am.
Ooh.
Okay, you can't kill a bat.
What a fucking piece of shit.
Nobody can kill a bat.
I got my utility out.
Don't worry.
It's all in the plan, dude.
It's all in the plan, Stan.
Impossible.
Could it be that Ben would win this game as well,
and then be the guy
who wins both games?
And then, is there another game after this?
Yeah, yeah.
There's the OU. There's the OU tier.
I owe you an apology.
Thanks.
Nice.
Shit.
What's good against grass?
Nothing.
Fire?
You can't...
Smother a fire with a leaf.
Oh god.
Okay.
You were a dummy if you think
that you're anything other than a dummy.
For what?
The sin that you've just done.
The fucking...
You are a ghoul, and you're about to see...
No, because this time,
this time I fucking know what I'm doing.
I know how to beat you.
Sacred sword!
Yes! God damn it.
Yes, I've learned.
I've learned from my mistakes.
I sliced him in twines.
I can't believe this.
I'm using the sacred power
of being a fucking dick.
I killed friends.
Okay, okay.
What a shame.
None of that look at sword guy.
He's kind of like his two eyes or his eyes,
and then the scarf is like
Zoidberg's lips.
Yeah.
He's really goofy and stupid.
Well, I mean, originally he was just
two swords,
so I don't know how good that design was
to begin with, but...
Well, with that, you could at least
just pick him up and whack him on a guy.
That's true.
Make a move, boy.
Oh god, I don't know. I know you've got Shadow Ball.
I know that's ghost type.
No, I don't. No, I don't, dude.
Yeah, yeah, get the fuck out of here.
He's got Shadow Ball.
It's ground type.
Just make a move, dude. Just make a move.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm dark.
Pokemon, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Alright, alright.
If you can kill bouquet boy,
really quick.
Oh, bouquet boy.
If you can kill him really quick, you win
because he's tough.
There we go.
Oh fuck, I forgot.
I forgot about Shadow Ball's ability.
But Moonblast could potentially counter it
by reducing the other thing.
Oh.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, okay.
Just keep doing the same attacks over and over.
I'm good.
The trap
will sprung.
Sure was.
Oh.
Oh no, did you have?
Oh, I thought so.
Okay, okay, okay.
Let's see.
Defog.
Was that what would happen?
Yeah, I got rid of him.
He was a size shocker.
He was a worst size shocker.
Super effective.
Plus 6%.
That's it.
And then Bat Bull is going to
flap his wings again.
Oh no.
0.75 evasion.
Sometimes special attack is lower than 1.
So he's going to switch up with Spaghetti Boy with this.
Oh, that was a mistake, dude.
No, Shuckle's going to hit him.
Shuckle's not going to know what hit him.
He's going to shoot him.
He's going to get him with his braper power.
You're going to throw rocks at him again.
He didn't let the rocks always critical hit.
That's quite bad for Spaghetti.
There's more rocks.
Haven't you realized yet
that Shuckle is the only thing
that's coming from winning?
Are you saying that when I destroy Shuckle
you'll become more powerful
than I could possibly imagine?
Yes, that is exactly what I'm saying.
Now we can really use the protect
on itself.
Ooh, nice.
Roosting up there with the rocks.
Being a brave boy.
He's coming down with it.
With the sickness.
Down with the sickness.
Protecting himself again.
He's very good at that.
He wears his safety gear.
Really?
Protect stops me from defogging?
What a bunch of bullshit.
Whoa, dude.
That is big. Protect.
This is fucking nonsense.
What's happening right here?
Just defies all...
Oh my god. There's no way out.
There's no way out, is there?
He's just gonna keep using this.
Look how low your evasion is.
Aw, you're fucked now.
Just keep using those rocks.
Just keep using them.
What do you mean, yeah?
It's the weakest part of the one that's gone.
You don't have a...
You don't have a prayer.
Shuckle is it.
Shuckle is your final bastion.
But now it's the rock song.
Yeah, you act like that's gonna kill me.
Eat that fucking bat hole.
But you know what? I'm making a statement right now.
Eat that bat hole. You're big enough.
Here we go.
Chomp, chomp.
No, my black sludge.
You're smarter. You're smarter.
That's a song.
Why are you doing this?
Why'd you stop?
Careful, you're gonna get content in the aid.
You can do it, come on.
Come on.
Man, man, this is it.
This is truly it.
Are you at the end of your rope?
This is the best of times, and this is the worst of times.
Ooh, nice dead.
This bat, even though Ben didn't care about this bat,
is winning every single game.
Yes.
Oh.
Sword versus sword dance.
Can you slice him up?
Slice those onions.
You'll cry, but he'll be dead.
True.
This is intense.
It's so intense that I can't even...
Stay awake.
Nice.
They're doing swords dancing,
but one of them is actual swords, so that one looks better.
Damn it.
He's got times for attack, but no health.
What will happen?
Only time will tell.
I didn't mean...
The time has told.
The time has told me what I need to do.
You can do it.
Now he's got priority.
Oh, God.
Wow, it all comes down to this.
So Ben wins round two.
Wow.
I won little cup and underused.
All right.
Now it's time for the ultimate battle.
The ultimate battle of wits.
Oh, boy.
Let's have a look at these guys.
We got on Munchie's team, we have...
Of course you're using slow boat Munchie.
Of course you're using slow boat.
Hey, slow bro, dude, fuck you.
Oh, shit.
We got...
Huge bird, different from small bird.
Latino.
We got...
Slow boy.
We got big fucking mess of
tangled cables.
Fucking mess.
And we got...
That big guy.
We got a Tyrant Godzilla.
We got Godzilla.
And on the other side, on Ben's team,
we have a little girl with a big
weird jelly underneath.
It's diamonds.
She's a diamond girl.
She's a diamond in the rough, dude.
We got chocolate pudding
demon.
We got
egg with leg.
Egg with leg.
We got that guy.
Slow boy.
We got
Power Ranger, we got Super Sentai here.
Steel Samurai, one of them.
And we got a Latino too.
So...
That's pretty good.
I have not seen these Pokemon
ever used.
But I don't play Pokemon, so...
Well, you're about to see them used
and abused.
They're foolish potential.
Nice.
Foolish.
Fucking foolish, dude.
And we're off with bird versus...
Oh, we're not.
We're friend versus bullet.
Pink friends
attack each other.
Pink friends attack?
So we got...
I've got choice here.
This is an even match.
It's a one paralyze, believe me.
Disabilities don't count.
Oh, now he's paralyzed.
Egg with leg.
It doesn't fucking matter.
Yeah, barely.
I like egg with leg.
You mean melon bullet?
My bro.
My bro melon bullet.
What tricks does this idiot have?
That is quite the moustache.
It doesn't even start from his nose.
It starts from his eyebrows.
Yeah.
Moustache like that before?
No, sir.
What's he gonna do?
It's a grass type.
First grass and steel.
This can only mean many things.
This guy...
He's acting good.
Really, he's just a fool.
There's fucking shit tons of spikes everywhere.
What is he doing with his spikes?
He's trying to random up my ass
because he knows I love being gay.
I mean, you do.
True.
But sometimes you just gotta look inside yourself and say...
What bird?
What pumpkin?
I don't think anything's actually happened yet.
I'm not sure though.
Dude, this is...
I'm totally winning right now.
I've got my spikes out.
I've paralyzed his dudes.
Who gives a shit about any of that gay shit?
He doesn't have a single prayer.
Dude, has anyone used nut type?
Oh, it's chocolate pudding.
Ah, steel type immune to toxic.
Oh no.
Oh yeah.
They're switching out thick and fast.
Trying to figure out the best combo potential
setup movement.
But they're just gonna keep going in and out
with their Pokemon.
In and out and in and out, I say.
That's what they're doing.
Pokemon balls flying like hither and thither.
It's like that one show.
Pokemon.
Yeah.
Except in actual the show Pokemon
had a real battle.
I really feel like all my planning
paid off.
You know, when we agreed to this battle
in like an hour, you were like,
okay, got my teams and I was like,
oh my god, he made them so fast.
He must know exactly what he's doing.
But turns out he's just a fucking nerd.
And I spent like two whole days putting these teams together.
And it paid off.
Listen man, listen man.
All that matters is that I have my pride
at the end of the day.
All I need is my pride.
But you lost everything.
My job.
My wife.
All video games.
Pride comes after and before fall.
Oh my god, he turned into a jet ski.
Misogyny.
Wow.
I didn't realize he could have an airplane.
You didn't know about that?
You didn't know about planes?
Wait, dude, is there a Twin Towers Pokemon?
There is, as a matter of fact.
It's called...
Well, it starts out as...
A single.
A single building.
It did evolve into two.
Yeah, it's awesome.
When given the U.S. Constitution
and traded.
Yes.
It's weak to flying.
Oh shit.
The sandstorm, these spikes, this leash.
Misogyny's having a hard time.
Oh, but he used boom!
And he got like...
Oh, am I gonna get him? I got him!
I've been one the first round.
Yeah, I think so.
Hang on, it's not over yet.
I think it's over.
It's over.
I've got fucking three spikes
and a stealth rock out and he just lost his...
Whoa, that's like all his health.
That's clearer.
Half his health in one big swell.
It does look cool though.
I like that bird.
I think it's supposed to be like a
Kestrel or something.
Nothing.
Or a weirdly waddly
bird with a thing on his head.
A Unibird.
Unicorn bird.
But a backwards side head unicorn?
I can't believe this!
How did you know I would stay in?
Um...
Uh...
I don't know.
I don't need your lies.
I used S.C.A.L.D. because it would
be effective against anything.
True.
Well, I guess except for the slow bro.
Um, whatever.
It's S.C.A.L.D. like you get a boiling pan
and you just throw it at the Pokémon and they go
Ah!
Regardless of what type they are.
Because nobody likes putting
their face in a boiling pan of noodles.
Except for the noodles.
But they don't get those because it's just water.
Oh boy.
That waifu is
times two speed and attack.
I mean, no special.
That's what it is.
Oh god, I was paralyzed.
That was bad. That was a bad time to be
paralyzed. I'm still gonna win.
Paralyze really does occasionally make the game
really interesting.
By preventing anything from happening.
Well, yeah, you're like, I'm sure I can do this.
Oh wait, I can't. Whoa!
You know.
Whoa, bro.
Slow bro.
Pherothorn is fucking OP.
He is insane.
I can defeat him. I know.
Ever.
And you know why I didn't use him on my team?
What? Because he looked ugly.
He's so good.
He doesn't look terrible.
He looks like Metacross.
Why don't you just use Metagross then?
Because it's not a situation.
He was in my first draft, but I didn't like that one very much.
He's got those, that springly, sprangly
thing going on.
He sure does.
These Pokemon cries are weird.
Yes they are.
It's like they're crying for help.
Almost.
Most things do.
I had ridden a creepypasta about this.
Yeah. You turn around.
Oh, they're red with blood.
Oh.
Their eyes went red with blood.
They went bloody and attacked everybody.
The spikes became real spikes.
They were real spikes.
And they shut it on my computer.
Wait, what?
Pikachu paralyzed me for real.
Oh no. It's hyper realistic
Slowbro.
Zoom in on Slowbro's
hyper real face.
Damn it.
Has Ben got all his Pokemon alive?
Yeah.
Wow.
His team
completely counters mine.
We should have used
Vile Plume.
Yeah, Vile Plume's nice.
I gotta do it.
I just need to fucking go for it.
There's nothing I can do.
Just stab him with your head.
You got spikes on it?
Yeah, there's nothing I can do.
No, no, no, no.
What?
Super effective. Not even quite.
Not even at all.
You clearly have magic guard.
No.
Soft boiled leftovers.
I want to
defeat.
It could move.
It's crazy.
No.
Come up to the home stretch,
ladies and gentlemen.
Don't you have two packet men?
No.
Wife who keeps getting beaten like the wife she is.
Oh.
But he could come back
because he's continually healing.
If you sweep with...
Okay, okay, I got him.
No, I can't.
I gotta do so.
Sweep up.
Sweep up with that broom.
Is there a broom Pokemon?
Is it OP? It should be.
Yeah, it should be.
It's abilities and it swoops away all the hazards.
Come on and crit. Please give me a crit.
If now is the fucking time.
Oh no.
It's a battle of attrition.
What does that mean?
I think it's irrelevant here.
You know, it's a battle
for fucking gay people who don't matter.
Like the war in Afghanistan?
No.
The Afghanistan people are just goons,
so I don't care about them.
Gugliayistan.
Gugliayran.
Okay.
What I'm doing right here
is not what I should be doing.
Um...
You know, what would be really cool
is if you two were both recording
and you could...
there would be like onscreen
like what are you hovering over?
Like what are you gonna do?
But instead I'm just looking at
what happens afterwards.
I am hovering really intensely right now.
Yeah.
You gotta figure out what to do
in case you wanna be gay
or in case you wanna be straight.
That's what all decisions come down to.
It's not right or wrong, it's being straight.
You care straight.
Shit.
Damn it.
Oh.
This bell is fucking terrible.
He punched him, he punched him,
he gonna slap him in the face.
But instead,
he's soft-boiled.
Quick, use attack.
That's all I can do.
You can just attack.
These turns are lasting a year now.
Yeah.
Um...
Hang on, what the fuck does stored power do?
It's psychic type, okay.
Yeah, sure, sure it is.
Sure it is.
A melon bullet is used all four of its moves
so I can see all of them.
Oh, pink one.
Oh, I've made a mistake.
I have made a mistake.
Ah, damn.
Super mega.
It sure did grow.
It's got those...
Those little dingley doodles.
Are you not entertained?
Well, you shouldn't be because
this is very interesting.
I might speed up
or cut out in between
nothing happening.
Yeah, me.
But I won't, probably.
Some of this is real important.
Oh no.
What a shame.
Oh dear.
Oh, Nisama.
Oh.
Fuck, Mudboy's dead.
He looks cool.
Oh Nisama.
Taunt?
I mean, you can't...
No, I just, like, I think
there are no different games with taunt.
What?!
Whoa! Is he gonna sweep?
I'm not gonna be able to sweep.
You can, you killed a guy.
No, I'm not gonna be able to.
Just use your grenade.
Just use my life grenades
and start off shotguns.
Sort of grenades.
Yes, exactly.
They explode real good.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Yeah, I know, I know.
I should have done this years ago.
It's Red Ranger.
Use Dino City.
I forgot about paralysis.
But I'm still gonna die.
There's nothing I could possibly...
Oh!
He got his power.
There's nothing I could possibly do right now.
What, is this depressed chi?
Instead of munchy?
Shit, shit, shit.
There's nothing I could possibly do right now.
Shut the fuck up, I'm gonna kill you.
There's nothing I could possibly do right now
to impact this situation.
Okay.
Let's just end the game then.
Alright, well he caught him with a big
swish.
Well, there's actually nothing I could do now.
I'm gonna make you...
No! No!
Oh, oh...
Just one more whank, I mean punch.
God damn it!
Did he get paralyzed again?
Oh, he did.
Yes!
Let's have a look at Waifu's stats.
She's got 10 soft boils left.
So that might be enough to survive this whole match.
What will Ben be doing?
Basically giving valuable information to my opponent.
Well, he can hover over, right?
No, he can't!
Can he not? No!
I mean, I can see some things.
I can see the moves he's used before.
I can see his possible
speed values.
But you can't see how many times he's used the...
Alright.
Yeah, I can see how many times.
Okay, so there you go.
I'm totally in the right.
Oh no, if this were a judge and a jury,
then you would be the jury.
And I'd be the gesture.
I'd be jury Seinfeld.
I like that show, it's a good show.
I've never seen it.
Oh no, I'm dead.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh no.
Ben St. Wins Ding Ding.
Is this the first round of this one?
Yeah, that was the first round.
So how do you think that went munchy?
I hate him.
Ben, do you have any words?
Do you have any words?
I...
I almost fucked it up and let him
his Clefable sweep.
And then...
I got real unlucky with paralysis,
but there was never any chance.
Nobody has any
fucking clue what they're doing
when they face me.
No one. No one has the single clue.
Not one person in the entire fucking world.
Starting off with the Japanese man
versus the Mexican.
Jeez, yeah.
Because he's got a lot of hair, right?
And the Japanese man
is a power ranger.
Of course, of course.
There's my reasoning behind that.
Oh, and he jumped on a bird's head.
That's gotta hurt the bird.
Fuck.
Ooh, he's on burn.
He's getting insulted.
Sick bird's bird.
It's okay, I know exactly what to do.
Are you gonna do
win game?
It's my favorite move.
What the fuck?
Why didn't that work?
Sucker punch. What else didn't work?
Wait. Why didn't that work?
Sucker punch doesn't work.
Oh my god, it's because your priority's higher, isn't it?
It's because you have double...
Oh, god.
You used it twice and it fell both times.
It's complicated.
Maybe you should just lay...
lay off the sauce.
I keep tapping over, but I'm not supposed to
because I'm recording and I hate that.
Lay off the sauce.
That was fucking abominable.
Like the snowman.
That was the worst.
That was the worst B'sharp has ever performed.
That was pretty quick death.
Alright, so we're starting with Munchy getting
an advantage with the Pokemon amount.
But anyways, we all know that doesn't mean Jack.
Oh no.
Oh, it parallelsed.
Oh no!
Why does he use many spikes?
Holy fucking shit.
Three in a row.
Paralysis is like 25%.
So that is
statistically
Paralysis and abominable.
Okay, good.
I like it.
Yeah, you think you know shit.
You think you know fuck shit.
Damn it.
Everybody knows shit fuck.
You know what I'm gonna do.
You know what I'm gonna fucking do.
Something about his skin.
This is not a whole lot you can do, buddy.
It looks like a chocolate eclair
or like a glazed chocolate donut
or something.
I like it.
But he's got a skull face.
I don't eat donuts with skulls.
That's not cool.
Oh shit.
Whatever.
Well what? Flash fire.
He's immune to fire attacks
and if he gets hit by one
his fire gets
stronger.
Impressive.
Two frags in two seconds.
You thought I was gonna
thunder wave.
Nah, I just didn't fucking care about
what bird.
What bird?
Turned down for bird.
Oh no.
Oh dear.
The stakes are never higher.
Oh no.
Never higher than right now.
And he's missing a little bit
of mud.
Mr. Saturday, it's you.
Mr. Saturday.
And it's Mr. Saturday.
I predicted you bitch.
Oh no.
He's hurt by poison but don't worry
because he's about to reek.
It was all just an elaborate meme.
He's going to 9-11
with a meteor.
It was all just an elaborate meme
to get you to get a boner.
That's what you did.
You got a boner.
No.
He played you like a damn
piano.
Shit.
He played you like a damn video game.
It's pretty fun.
Pink buffet.
Bullet, I mean.
Oh fuck.
You're one point faster
than me.
Well you know.
You're one point faster
than me.
Well you know.
I don't.
Bullish.
Yeah, truly.
Boom.
Truly.
I did it. I fucking did it.
Well it is Godzilla.
I didn't realize that when I said it was Godzilla before.
Yeah.
Oh, it got a Gmail
message.
Someone subscribed to my Twitch account
at munchie
at twitch.tv
slash munchie wears tiny hats.
Whoa.
I'm subscribed to you.
Yeah, you're a newly ascended master.
That's what we call our followers.
Newly ascended master.
I would go, but I don't know what you do
on that channel.
What do you do?
Advertise.
Sometimes I play video games.
Other times I twiddle on my clip
and I do nothing.
Which one of those is better?
Yeah, man.
Go on.
Well, if you're
in it to win it, then you know
how to bebop and scat all around
Manhattan.
Yes.
Godzilla dead.
Oh, Godzilla.
Egg with leg.
Comin' at ya with his face.
Spikey though he is.
He has a soul that is very soft
and nice.
He has a hard outer shell
and a soft inner shell.
Hold on, I gotta open up the damage calculator
again.
I gotta open up
the damage calculator.
One plus two is three
damage.
Yeah, you don't know that.
Ah, it dunes.
I think I know what your calculator is.
It's not that good.
I need to blow my nose
but there's nothing in sight.
There's nothing in reach.
I can't blow my nose.
It's just gonna slowly come out and go into my beard
and I'm gonna have to just deal with it.
Meanwhile, in Pokemon,
nothing is happening still.
They're staring each other down.
The waifu is staring at Mellon Bullet
and he's doing a little hip, hip, hip,
hip, hip, dance.
He's not intimidating at all.
It's very cute, actually.
Mellon Bullet is doing a little shakey-shake
because his legs are made of springs.
It's got spring legs.
They're vine springs.
Vine springs.
As actual.
Actual.
And now we got Slowbro who, honestly,
his design is annoying.
You are the worst person.
Yeah, it looks like Ben do, don't you think?
It looks like a Pokemon
that's just like, I'd rather have anything.
Anything else.
Tentacruel is my favorite
water Pokemon, I think.
That's a good Pokemon.
He's big and he's a fucking evil guy
because he's got angry eyes.
Angry eyes are the best types of Pokemon.
He should be a genre
of angry eye to recall.
I completely 100% agree.
Like Voltorb? Voltorb's pretty great.
It's perhaps okay.
I gotta, I gotta, I gotta
put the kibosh on this waifu situation
before it gets out of hand.
Just waifu situation.
Yes.
Oh, dear.
That's more than I
can prepare to accept.
Oh, no!
Taunt ended.
That's not fair.
That can't happen.
That, that can not happen.
What the fuck?
Yes!
That was, that was
alright. I thought Munchy had a chance
but now he only has a moustache
and a guy.
And everyone knows that
a Mexican can't defeat a diamond
in the rough.
Well, it's not that rough.
It's like a park, you know,
bench.
It's like quite nice.
Gigadran.
Yes.
Well, wait a minute. Maybe it's not Mexican.
Maybe it's Jamaican and it's got dreadlocks
and that's a lot of dreadlocks.
Maybe it's not any nationally, huh?
Maybe, maybe it just wants to live
its life just like you and me.
I don't believe that anyone wants to live
their life just like you or me.
I think they have to be different
and identifiable and
ridiculable.
The main quality I look for in people is
You gotta be able to laugh at something
and if you can't, it's not very funny.
Not very worth your time.
Okay, we got friend version 2.0.
Something bit his butt
and he stood up but he didn't do
anything about it.
We got 3 vs 1.
Oh no.
I used healing wish
and I sacrificed plane bullet
to give melon bullet a second lease on life.
Oh, it's over.
Now he's got a leech on friend.
Yeah, man.
He's got a leech on friends life.
The video's over.
You thought I was
cruise?
Roll the credits, bro.
Oh, it's over.
I swept it.
I fucking swept this tournament.
Oh, no.
Swipped it under the rug.
Nobody'll know about it.
Oh, no.
It's over.
It doesn't actually do.
All my planning
paid off.
Oh my god.
Guys, you know,
champion will be out
three days later than it
otherwise would have been,
but at least I've beaten my chief fucking Pokemon.
I would say it was a worthy cause
because you're happy about it, but I don't care.
Cool.
I wouldn't watch this video.
I'd leave a comment saying no.
End it.
It's okay. Nobody watches
Rowdy fucker's cop killing.
Enough of this.
The first one got is like the least.
Oh, yeah. No, yeah.
It has like 2000.
I've still never gone back and watched that,
even though I had the time.
Oh, god.
Now, hold on.
The grand finale is going to be something special
that I prepared just for you.
Wait, there's more?
Just a very quick thing.
Did Ben win every single...
Yeah, he did.
Win every single type of match.
Yes.
You were fun.
I'm the best. Wait, random?
Oh, okay.
I'll do it.
Wait, they're different levels?
Yeah, a little bit.
Well, we got Polirath,
which is a cool guy,
and Zekrom, which is a fucking
dark drill.
Oh, and you can't see the enemy's Pokemon.
Why aren't they all like that?
No clue. It was random.
You're not allowed to know what you have.
Oh, my god.
Yeah, I can see what I have.
Down at the bottom.
Wow.
I don't know what you're looking at,
but I'm looking at some real fucking intense shit
on my side.
You pretty much always get the big guys in this.
I like Polirath's little
little leg crease.
What the fuck is that?
It's awesome.
Oh, my god, I love Kling Kling.
Let's look at...
He's so good.
What does Zekrom turn into a little guy?
It's a substitute.
Oh, god, what's good against steel?
Fighting ground
and fire.
Kling Kling vs. Magnemite.
OTP.
Oh, my god, it's war.
It's why, why?
No, it's not.
It's Zed.
It's the Z Snake.
Shit.
What is one level 81
level 76?
That's kind of unfair.
Are you...
Don't fuck with me, Kling Kling.
Shit.
Oh, no.
Dang, I didn't go that well.
No, yeah.
Not even close.
That fucking legendary
bug snake
friend.
What is it?
Oh, you did it.
Oh, yeah.
Extreme speed on Zygarde.
You did it. You absolutely did it.
Sylveon.
That's just a whatever.
I've seen him before.
Oh, wow.
Does one of you have the god?
That's close enough.
Yeah.
Oh.
I hate Sylveon.
Sylveon always fucks with me.
I don't like it.
We used to use it to accelerate.
What are you talking about? I don't even know what that means.
You need to find your soul and you need to go faster.
Oh, is that...
Is that all that did?
Wow.
You got two legendaries
from the same game already.
Three.
No, yeah, yeah, yeah. From the same game.
We have three legendaries altogether.
Wow.
So much he has no legendaries yet.
As far as I know.
That seems like a bit of a wish.
But he's still
giggle with.
Man, all my Pokemon are so fucking big.
I know, dude. They got big and meaty.
Just like your fucking butt.
Yeah.
Oh, it's egg face.
This is the meme one.
I want to zoom in, but I can't.
I don't want to look at the entire video.
Just one of his faces.
I just want to see his face.
But he's so pixel-y.
I like his dance.
He's a happy fellow.
Yeah, he's not going to be too happy when he's dead.
Come on, Zekrom.
Hang in there.
Oh, God, Leechsea is so good.
Look at this, Zekrom.
Zekrom is a
dragon electric.
Nice job, dude.
How do you have two?
I just do, dude.
How did you have two citrus berries?
Oh, you got harvest.
I just do, dude.
You got harvest.
The rest of my team
is not prepared to deal with Executor.
Executor?
I'm not
prepared for this.
It doesn't count.
Shit.
Well, you know,
you know what they say,
if you can't eat them, beat them.
Well, you can eat them.
He's a coconut.
What?
I don't understand this at all.
You can eat coconuts all day.
It's a ferraligator.
Yes.
There's now Ode his name,
so I don't like it.
Check him a little typey charty.
Yeah.
The news is not good.
But maybe.
Wait.
Nobody will wait.
No, it's bad.
It's all bad.
Okay, I've only got one choice,
and I am...
Oh, my God.
Why don't those two work together?
Never mind.
No!
Oh, wow.
How the fuck?
That was quite the meatier.
Didn't do shit.
Also, why is my...
Why is my...
Why is my special attack not...
Oh, it's because it wasn't here.
No, man.
See?
Ironhead.
What the fuck?
Oh, it's running around on you.
Straight from chuckling to what?
God damn it.
Come on, come on, come on, boy.
Ah, shit.
What is that?
Mellowetta?
I've never seen a Mellowetta before,
but it is fucking cool.
Is that a legendary? I hope it's not.
Yeah, it is.
It's a mythical.
It looks like a little Indian girl,
like a Native American,
with feathers in her hair, you know?
Yeah, a little band.
No, it's me.
No, it's me, too.
Thanks, Dad.
Thanks, Dad, for saying that you know.
Here we go.
Bam, bam, bam, bam, bam.
Oh, that was...
What is it with meatiers of not being effective
and how can people just throw actual meatiers
into the planet
without ruining everybody?
It should be illegal, you know.
Draco Meteor is a special attack?
What the fuck?
Dragon Dance raises attack,
but Draco Meteor is a special attack.
What a broken game.
It is a broken game.
It doesn't even work.
Dude, I unboxed this game
from my loot crate,
and dude, not even fucking...
I'm refunding it.
Yes!
I didn't think that would actually work.
It's 4 vs 3.
Well, Ben has one Pokemon he hasn't shown yet.
I want to see what it is.
I really...
Show it, show it, show it, show it.
Ben?
No.
Come on.
What if it's really good?
I flinched him.
I did it, though.
Show it, show it, show it.
We gotta see it.
Oh, it's Luna.
It's Luna.
I actually like that Pokemon.
It's funny.
It's got a beak.
Oh, I think...
Yep.
Okay.
Here we go.
I don't know what aura break means.
Come on.
Yes, yes.
Can I do it? Oh, no!
Oh, wait, no.
I'm super fucked.
I'm super fucked because your last Pokemon
is whatever name is.
Silvio, hey.
Sephiroth.
Use meteor again.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh.
Da-da-da-da-da.
Shit.
What a weird wish to have.
I wish for more hit points.
Why did you just wish for the other Pokemon to die?
I agree.
Pokemon don't know what's best for them.
Well, this could go
every single direction.
But upward,
because I don't really like that.
I don't like...
I like getting it up
in a sexual way.
Oh, dear.
This is it.
This is the one.
Whoever wins this wins the whole thing.
Doesn't even matter about the other ones.
Only now do you know this.
What are my options?
Oh, no!
Oh, my God.
I have a choice band!
No!
What's that?
I shouldn't have said that.
I'm dead.
I can't believe it.
Then one anyway.
Yeah.
Damn it.
Shit.
I really screwed the pooch on this one.
You want to do another one?
One more.
Random battle?
Yeah, of course.
There's no such thing as not random battles.
Check it out, dude.
It's Goo Goo.
What a Goo at Pokemon.
Nope.
Not actually.
It has been Goo'd.
Ew, it's dripping.
I love how it's dripping.
Yeah, I love how it's 3D model actually drips.
Look at this piece of shit I have.
I'm just going to send it out so I can die.
Oof-a-zant.
Look at this meme.
Wait.
That's like a turkey.
Damn it.
What the fuck is tailwind?
It doubles your entire team's speed.
Oh.
That's cool, I guess.
I don't know if it lasts if you switch.
There's three turns.
It doesn't.
So it lasts through switching.
God damn it, Goodra.
Dude, just gotta-
Goodra, would you please?
Please, Goodra.
Goodra, would you fucking please?
Just work with me.
Goodra, why?
I shouldn't have stayed in this long.
Okay, yeah, it's fine then.
No, actually that sucks.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck, I'm sorry.
He's got extra smooths.
Whoa.
Hey, come on.
That's so cold.
Get it together.
You know, I'd sully this commentary with-
I wanted to throw you off your guard.
Get your act together right now.
Oh, Samorot.
Oh, but I shot you.
Uh...
Die.
I will fucking die.
Sellaby again.
Yeah.
Ooh, Altaria, it's a big fluffy baby.
Correct.
Took me a second and I had to cough,
but I've come to the conclusion that yes, you were right.
Um, um, um, um, um...
We're just looking at it.
It's just so cool.
I've never seen better.
Seen better what?
Seen better what and where and when?
So I can go and I can kill it so I can be number one.
Big, big fluffy wings.
They're hypnotizing.
It's the floatiest ass Pokemon I've ever seen.
Why's it got to be down on the ground?
Oh, shit.
Why did I do that? It was foolish.
It was foolhardy and I should be shot.
You, you, you've, you've done it now.
Check this shit right out, Boyo.
Bam.
Whoa, it's even fluffier.
Look how big.
That's all I have to say.
That is the biggest fluff I've ever seen.
I've...
No!
Don't kill it.
It's too cute to die.
Here.
Oh, thought you would switch.
Yeah.
Why would I, why on earth?
I...
I don't know.
It's so foolish.
Okay. Okay, though.
Alright, this, this battle is for the entire thing.
Yeah.
No.
No, come on.
You can just say I, that didn't count, but I'll work.
This isn't, this isn't real.
Well, of course it's not, because it's a Porygon.
Porygon.
How did, how did they render Porygon to, so...
No!
They just put him inside the computer.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, it's, it's, it's, it's you.
Yeah, it's waifu, dude.
It's clear fabley.
No!
More like dead fable.
That was a fable of a previous time of the past.
In the past it's dead, it's gone.
Yeah.
As in dictionary.
You're gonna be like the history books.
I don't have anything.
Oh, shit, is, won't she gonna come away with a win after all this?
Will he win?
Yeah.
Oh, this is funny.
Syllaby, use rape.
It's super effective.
Super effective.
Against the matriarchy.
It's Armaldo, that's pretty cool.
He's got funny eyes.
Why are all my pokemons slow, asshole?
Like all of them were fucking slow.
They were all super slow.
Is that a fucking emperor?
He's dead.
And Munchy takes the victory!
Get out.
Get, get out.
Munchy for the ultimate win.
We didn't even see the other Pokemon yet.
What other Pokemon did you have?
It was...
Samurai and that, that light fish.
It was, it was some fucking bitch.
And a bird.
And it was another bitch, and it was another bitch.
Ben, it's been great playing with you, but you know,
if you mess with the best,
then you get the horns.
Oh, god.
Well, the ultimate winner is...
is Munchy.
Yep, everyone, press one in chat if I do throw in Ben,
and even though he beat me,
in some battles it's not good.
Everyone, press one in chat,
if I'm gonna seal Ben away in my cage.
My cage is shaved.
Munchy, I work so hard.
Don't take it away from me.
We'll let the viewers decide by their ones.
Their ones will seal you away.
Forever.
You know, Yu-Gi-Oh, that's gonna be you.
Just buried in a mountain of ones.
Just fucked over.
Just fucked over and over by ones.
Guys, I forgot to let the viewers know,
but if I won, then you had to make Vincent real,
so you better get on with it.
Oh, that's right.
The deal that I never agreed to,
but which I will nevertheless honor,
because of what an honorable samurai I am,
is that if I won...
Wait, what the fuck was it?
If I won...
No, no, no, no, no.
If I won, you have to make Vincent real from your comic,
and if you win, then I get to make you
Ben-Saint real,
Ben-Saint real.
If I win,
then you get to make me real.
Yeah, I remember.
Okay, deal's a deal.
Vincent is coming to a store near you.
Not as a product,
just as a guy.
You'll see him in a store.
He'll be buying something.
At one time, the beta uprising
will truly begin.
It will.
It already has.
Our anti-sex crusade begins now.
My name is not important.
One of the important is what I'm going to do.
I was just about to quote that
drill tweet about the Brexit asexual again,
but then I remember that I already did.
I already said the Brexit asexual.
It's such a good...
Okay, I don't know how to end this.
Alright, alright.
I've had a fan...
Yeah, it's been a good time.
And you know what?
I never competitively battled before,
but in the days that I spent training
for this engagement, I got really into it
and it was really cool.
It was way easier to get into
than I thought it would be.
I thought it would take weeks or months.
I thought it would be like League of Legends
where you can play your whole life
and still be a piece of shit.
No, I just looked up some stuff
and figured it out.
Well, it's partly team setup
and then everything beyond that is mind games.
It's just Minecraft.
Yeah.
If you're going to play anything with them,
play Terraria.
It's much better.
I played that years ago.
Get the Pokemon mode for Terraria.
There will be Pokemon.
Yes, exactly.
Okay.
Alright, let's get the fuck out of here.
This has been the rowdy fucking cop killer.
No, the rowdy fuckers cop killers.
Fuckers cop killers
with Ben St. and Munchy Shatsky.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Munchy Shatsky.
Another one.
Full name, Munchy Shatsky.
And Hippocrite.
Acting as...
Orlando, Florida.
That's his last name.
Orlando Blue.
Alright, are we calling it?
Yeah, and from the bottom of my heart,
I wish you a Merry Christmas night.
I wish you a Merry Christmas, Chan.
Okay, goodbye.