Alright, let's turn on the game.
We're free.
Let's just play all the video games, whatever it may be.
Alright, I'm gonna start with Pokemon.
And now!
Alright, I'm gonna do Mabeebley's quest.
Okay, Mabeebley's.
What's this?
Mabeebley.
Should we introduce the video?
Yeah, hey, it's RowdyFuckersCopKillersLIVE!
Live in Ben's room.
Welcome to the indie game clusterfuck.
The game where we fuck all indie games ever made.
Yeah, fuck indie games.
I don't like them.
Nobody really likes them.
We all just pretend to, so we think each other is cool.
If they were good, they'd make a billion dollars.
Look, my favorite AAA game, Undertale.
So, we'll probably switch games at some point,
but I, BenSaintofPatrion.com, slash BenSaint,
am playing Mabeebley's quest,
which is like a Mega Man clone, basically,
by a gay furry on Twitter.
And it's really hard, but it's really good and pretty cool.
Do we get to do the Mabeebley?
You are Mabeebley.
Okay.
Let's do a new game.
I'll start a new game.
I have not actually beaten this game.
I've gotten, like, halfway, and then it got too hard,
and I gave up.
You're harsh.
Well, I'm not going to set up that kind of pushy attitude anymore.
Mabeebley difficulty.
Mabeebley easy or double easy?
Be a true hero.
Easy or double easy.
No, no.
It sounds like it wants you to play Mabeebley.
No, no easy.
Mabeebley.
Dude, Mabeebley.
No.
Would you get stuck on easy?
I think I was playing Mabeebley.
You played Mabeebley, you fucking bitch.
Fine.
You already got halfway through.
God.
Easy.
Ooh, I like it.
Oh, yeah.
Your bullets are weird and, like, drop off halfway through.
What I like about this game is that it has the background,
and it's like...
Oh my god.
Dude.
Whoa.
Very artistic.
You got a fucking dick, you got a dick, suck a dick, suck a dick.
Go, go, go, go, suck the dick, suck the dick, suck the dick.
You guys are pressuring me too much.
I'm feeling performance anxiety.
I'm already impressed by the prevalence of tics in this game.
It's really appealing to my demographic.
Which...
Of most sexual...
The gayden.
Somebody's got to appeal to them.
Whoa, okay.
That's cool.
There's a lot of, like, weird creative shit you've never seen before.
Yeah, you're like rolling out the video game.
It's like game's art.
Video game's art.
Never heard that.
Kill the art.
Look at all this art.
I want to kill that pencil.
There we go.
You shoot through walls.
Yeah, your bullets just kind of...
They don't go a set distance.
They go to sort of the end of the screen,
and then just sort of drew balls.
It seems like, like, programatically it was programmed to just kind of go...
So wait.
If they're programmed to go to the end of the screen,
does that mean if you run with them, they will never stop?
Yes.
Well, to an extent.
It sounds like they sort of detect the edge of the currently visible screen.
Oh, shit.
Oh, you're so fucking gay.
Oh, he got me.
What the hell happened?
He fucking turned me into a...
He hit me with his spotlight and turned me into a piece of art.
I like it.
Such art in this game.
Such art, dog.
This is pretty cool, though.
Art in the truest sense.
It's a metaphor for art.
Yeah, like, I really meant to finish the game,
because, like, there's actually some really great cutscenes and shit that happen
and maybe we'll get to see one or two of them.
And they...
Yeah, you see, you are Mbibli, a creature of indeterminate anything,
and your enemy is Croco-Bibli.
At least we know he's a crocodile.
Do we know that?
Dude, you saw the pipe as well.
Fucking art.
That's how you really know it's art.
Also, the fact that this is called art world.
Max lives.
We did it.
I didn't even need those lives.
This game's the easiest thing in the world.
Is three of the max lives?
Oh, yes.
Don't worry, it gets a lot harder.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, shit.
You're so bad.
No, let's see, I dodged that one.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, no!
Oh, no.
You're blowing it.
That was a devious trap game.
Hey, this is great.
So, how have you guys been doing?
This game reminds me of that one time I went to Las Vegas with no money,
and I just killed people.
So, this is being recorded at Radcon 2.
Yeah.
How are you guys enjoying Radcon 2 so far?
It's okay.
I'd rather be killing people in Las Vegas.
As previously mentioned, it's good.
It's a good time.
Yeah, I would download it.
I would download the DLC.
Yeah.
Well, that is real.
Radcon 2.5 DLC.
We were having snow adventures out in the wilderness today, which was fun.
There's footage of that that will exist.
Oh, no.
Did I miss the main event?
You did.
A snow event?
Yeah, you did.
This is what I fucking get.
I did try to wake you on two occasions, so you were just a check-down.
I can believe that.
I am an indecipherable piece of crappy art, just like me.
What a commentary.
So...
Oh, there he is.
Arch enemy.
Crocodiebly.
I was...
Crocodiable.
Kill him.
He's a fucking Bible character.
See, it helpfully notes that he is Arch enemy.
I do like that.
Oh, God.
Okay.
He has not accomplished much, if anything.
Uh-oh.
Okay, all right.
Crocodiebly.
Just chill a fuck out, dude.
He's such an asshole, dude.
Look at him.
Who would do this?
This is really beyond the pale of acceptable behavior.
God.
If there's one thing I hate, it's pretentious people.
Look at his hair.
Look at him.
Dude, look at his fucking...
Whoa.
Look at his comeover, bro.
You can tell he's bald.
Oh, God.
He's really embarrassed.
What is that?
Wow, look at his fucking...
Wow, real originally, you took some organs out of someone's body that you didn't make.
Wow.
Yeah, God made those.
Yeah, you fucking bitch.
Oh, God.
Okay, all right.
Oh, my fucking God.
I'm in like...
Yeah, I can only move left and right.
That up and down is automatic, but the left and right is up to me.
That's what's happening right now, viewer and friends.
Okay.
All right.
So, as you can see, this is the best game I've ever made.
Yeah.
This is not fucking around.
I just killed his Croco Man already.
I mean, I would.
All right.
I would if you would let me.
God.
I'm not stopping.
Oh, okay.
You're actually doing quite well, Tim.
Oh, man.
He's spraying piss everywhere.
He's shooting at the ball.
This guy reminds me of my...
This guy reminds me of my teacher in middle school.
Was he a crocodile?
I killed him.
Okay.
HP bar is doing things now.
Son of a fucking bitch.
All right.
You know, one time, me and my friends, I was in a gaming club in college and we did a couple
of game jams because I had a lot of game design stuff at the time.
And one of the things that happened was one of the game jams was about like breaking conventions
or something.
Whoa, how unconventional.
And there was a whole bunch of stuff.
I know.
We did it in the game that was made for a bunch of things like this where one of the things
that happened was that if you get too much HP because there are HP pickups, it was a normal
2D platformer.
And if you pick up too much HP health, your health bar extends too far, breaks the barrier
surrounding it and it just drops off the screen and then you're invisible.
Whoa.
It's pretty cool.
Yeah.
It's pretty creative stuff.
Okay.
Enough with the intestines.
No.
Oh.
An immeasurably long time.
Eventually they got born in parted ways.
Well, I guess I won't.
All right.
Yeah.
I'll call that a victory.
That's the moral victory of nothing else.
What?
Oh.
Well, this game sure is quirky and fun.
We're going to see another game I like to call...
Undertale.
No.
You watch there are good games that aren't Undertale.
They're Undertale.
They are all Undertale.
Every time you see a good game, this really reminds me of Undertale for some reason.
This is a really good Undertale you're playing right now.
God, that makes me so mad.
You know, Lisa's a pretty good Undertale, but you know, it just doesn't...
It doesn't really...
It doesn't quite live up to...
I mean, there aren't any fucking memes.
The Undertale is...
There aren't any fucking Skeletons.
You're sad.
Sad.
My dick is soft.
You need to suck it to make it hard.
Sad.
Why are you not in this game as well?
You would be a good addition.
What are these people saying?
They're all just saying really sad things.
Damn, you're ugly.
Hey, fuck off, buddy.
I think the person who made this game has low self-esteem.
It's the Mibible.
The Mibible.
That was the Mibible that I almost reached, but I was teleported.
What's the significance of the Mibible?
Oh, you'll see, but you'll see what the Mibible is.
Okay, what's that going on?
You are hero.
Okay, okay.
You are hero, Gordon Freeman.
Okay, we're teleporting.
All right.
I teleported in front of my own bullets.
Okay.
You ever want to do that in the battlefield?
No.
No, it's...
It's reckless behavior.
God, Battlefield 3 looks so fucking bad.
Battlefield 3 is my favorite Undertale.
Why is this game such a fucking Pokemon ripoff?
Pokemon is a really good Undertale.
Yeah, that's true.
Sun and Moon had a lot of good Undertale traits.
Oh, you're going to die, dude.
You're going to fall.
Am I going to die?
Maybe.
Oh, there we go.
Okay.
But it was a quirky like...
Oh, the force.
Any second now.
Okay, here we go.
Yeah, we did it.
By the way, I started Audacity in OBS, right?
Yes.
I'm almost positive, but I always doubt this.
I really don't know.
Just check.
No, not on this dramatic screen.
Oh, I get it.
They're doing this to kill time while you're stuck in there.
That's funny.
I like it.
That's quirk.
It's pretty good Undertale.
Yeah, it reminds me of that one time on Undertale where they were like,
do you know that we're like a video game?
And you're like playing a video game right now.
I just want to let you know when people forget it.
Yeah, Undertale had a lot of good Undertale qualities.
It was all like, dude, like video games and RPGs, bro.
Yeah, it was basically Control-Alt-Delete, the video game.
Yeah.
It was just all about video games.
Yes.
Is that elephant a good boy?
I'd say...
That's the fucking elephant from Dumbo.
Holy shit, he's fucking here.
Heroine Dumbo drank that shit and he was like,
oh my god.
Oh, wait, what did I do?
Oops, I didn't mean to do that.
Just check your audio while you're...
This is recording.
Okay, we're good.
We're good.
Just kidding.
Game over.
Game over, fools.
Hurry up and get to that rave, dawg.
Hang on, hang on.
That's where the rave is.
The rave is the city.
Wait, was there a bar at the top and bottom before there was?
There was not.
Here, just try double-clicking the screen.
Or there might be an option on the top left
that specifically is like a maximized function of the game
as opposed to the window.
No.
No, you fucking died.
Wait, there might be...
Try like one of the...
First, F4.
Unminimize and try F4 or whatever.
Yeah.
Try some of the other Fs.
F.
F1.
U.
Yeah, choose FU.
Yes, I'm very sick.
I don't know how to do it before.
It makes me want to cry.
Oh, really?
Whatever, just maximize it's fine.
No, no, no.
I really want to...
See, there's got to be a menu because I want to find how to save.
Try right-clicking on the screen, maybe?
No.
That's wrong.
Hit enter, maybe?
And go escape, perhaps?
Escape is how we got into this mess.
On its own, press escape again.
Nope.
Doesn't seem to be doing it.
First, all the buttons on your keyboard.
Let me just tell you, this would never happen in Undertale.
Yeah, Undertale has a very concise method of doing anything.
Undertale is always the same thing.
Perfectly ergonomic.
Even when it's trying to do the deal.
Undertale, I really like Undertale.
I respect it forever.
I respect Undertale for continuing to present conventions
and not breaking them whatsoever.
Because I likely used to say the same.
Although, I mean, what if I die?
I haven't saved.
Is that a problem?
Well, maybe.
I see how I skip...
I buffed conventions and passed the levels.
What about the rave?
I don't know.
I just really wanted to go that way.
That's me.
Sometimes a boy just wants to dance.
Looks like I need three more hammers to, I guess, kill these horses.
Hey, it's Tommy.
You're a ready-fuck-your-cop killer now.
You are officially a ready-fuck-your-cop killer.
Well, it's this.
You will soon.
We're sitting here and playing shitty indie games
that we all love.
Buy yourself a place.
Well, who's gonna be an indie clusterfuck?
We hate all video games ever made
unless they were made by Toby J. Fox.
Is the middle initials J?
No.
No, he doesn't have a name.
He doesn't have a real name.
I was gonna say, the same for Jim.
All that money he took.
Yeah, all that money he stole from me.
Man, go to the rave.
All right, fine.
What the fuck is this shit?
Grind up against a fucking fag, bro.
This isn't a beat.
You know, this game is not as hard as I remember.
No, that's good.
But it does get...
Oh, this is the best fucking level.
Okay.
So the thing about these games, or this level,
is it's DVR inspired, and if you hit one of these arrows,
you don't get hurt, but you do freeze in place
and are shot at, and you can only move
when you hit the corresponding direction or button.
Cool.
It's so fucking great.
Okay, fuck that up.
And I'm about to die.
Okay.
Well, I died.
Okay, don't worry about it.
Never mind.
This is the hardest game I've ever made.
All right.
Does it remind you of that one time in Archeo
where, like, you were at a magical place
and it was like, dude, you have to fucking do it?
I remember that.
It was the best thing that ever happened to me in my life.
Oh, sad!
I feel like I'm a pretty pretty boy.
Mmm, I don't.
Who's that?
Indie games are all...
Indie games are for nerds.
Papyrus.
That's my sense.
Indie games, more like Indie games.
It's time for a woman, Papyrus.
I can't wait to vote for Donald Trump.
No!
Audience, I said this yesterday.
It was literally the funniest thing that ever happened.
Just trust me on that.
I'm still with her, man.
I'm still with her.
I'm still with her, Papyrus.
I'm always going to be with her.
It's her time.
I'm not my president.
I don't know.
You seem to have a few votes to pick from these polls.
Oh, no!
No!
Because he's a skeleton!
A skeleton!
Fuck my asshole!
Because Donald Trump is a skeleton.
So he has bones to pick with him.
That's true.
He's so evil, he's literally a skeleton.
There we go.
Alright, good work, good work.
Keep it up.
So as you can see, the game is really getting...
You're just bad.
Oh, and you gotta get the check marks to, like, progress shit.
Oh, I see now.
What game is this?
It's M'Beebley's Quest.
Well, it's Santa's Quest.
It's an independent funded game.
The best game ever made by a gay furry.
No!
I don't know.
I have played it.
If you lose this game, that means we'll have to fucking vote for Trump.
Oh, no.
Anything but that.
Um, yeah.
This game is the hardest game.
Oh, no!
Did you see how much fucking damage it took before?
It was ridiculous.
Quite a bit, quite a bit.
It was a sin.
I forgot.
Are you playing on M'Beebley's difficulty?
No!
I am playing on M'Beebley's difficulty.
Okay, good.
So you're playing like a real boy.
Ah!
No, it's Mediton!
It's Mediton!
It's Undertale!
Why is this game such a fucking bitch?
That is a Mediton.
Uh-oh.
It's like it's taking out a mega ton of info.
It's very name-based, man.
No!
Shit!
Undertale!
Sin!
It's Mediton, Sin!
You know Mediton!
Shit.
Okay.
Sin, help me clear my semen from the Disneyland Hot Topic area!
Disneyland Hot Topic!
Shit!
Goddamn it!
I think I must goddamn damage that shit.
Oh, Shans!
I love wingmunch!
Sin's real relatable like that.
You know what they say, Shans?
Everyone is a Sora, and everybody else deserves a fuck.
Say it or not.
Say it or not, Shans!
Yeah, something like that.
Are you saying it or not?
Shans!
Where the fuck is Mickey the Mouse?
Shans, why doesn't Donald Trump view me when I ask him?
Shans, why doesn't Trump love gay assholes like me?
He's my president, Shans.
I just don't listen like I love you.
I just wanna help the Trump!
I can't help the Trump.
I love video games, though.
The only thing I love more than Donald Trump is video games.
Sam.
Shans, please.
But only Triple A once.
Shit, no!
Yeah, I only love Triple A games like this one.
Shans, why is Ben Saint to Ben Saint?
Why is he shit at everything?
I am the best gamer.
I play on the hardest difficulties, and my experience reflects that.
Shut up, Vincent.
No!
We're acting like you're a separate character.
It's an autobiography.
Called Tiberius Rising.
Like Monkey Jones.
No!
You guys see Monkey's new autobiography about his school shooting?
Yeah, I think it's more of like a manifesto of future plans.
More like a hagiography, you know what I'm gonna say?
More like a hate crime.
Oh, the next lives.
Oh, fantastic.
Just in time.
Everyone's having a great time.
I love the guys.
Those guys are having the most fun.
I wish I were them.
Are they raving or having a seizure?
It's hard to tell.
They were having a rape.
They don't even have anatomy, so who can say?
That's true.
Oh, dude, you see how with such dispassion and skill...
No!
Jesus!
I'd never say anything.
Please go on about your great skill at video games.
Never ever be good at games.
Perhaps I will.
Shand, I actually pissed my poop into the fighting Nemo's submarine at Disneyland.
Oh, dear.
What are we gonna do with you?
We're continuing adventures of Shand's babysitter.
What's his name?
The Undertale fan 589?
No, the Undertailer 587 or something.
Yeah, some of the Undertailer.
We spent a lot of time perfecting his character.
Yeah.
He's got a rich lore.
We totally remember his name and everything.
They call him the New Cold Corona.
I do have the New Cold Corona on the Undertailer 589.
I have no wonder if this guy is just calling his carer Sans because he loves Undertale so
much, or Sans is actually his carer.
His carer?
I mean, I always vision him in like a Satan orange fur, like praying to Sans to grant these
wishes that he wants.
I guess that was the interpretation of the Undertailer 589.
This is that rich lore we were talking about.
Yeah, exactly.
We're gonna have a zone of psychophedia or dramatic, or we're just like CWC.
Exactly.
There's gonna be tons of fan theories.
The Undertale.
Sans, stick your head down my lemon pipe and suck out the bot flies.
I can't feel my skin.
Holy shit, that's disgusting.
I hate that so much, dude.
I hate that so much.
Highly offensive.
Sans, I opened the umbrella in my asshole again.
Tell me, Sans, tell me.
Get the god and she is.
It's very important you get the god and she is.
Nothing else will do.
You guys see that fucking skill just there?
I did, I did.
Sans, I was almost killed by a creeper in Minecraft when I killed him.
Oh fuck.
Sounds like everything's working out here, Undertale.
Also, my dick is stuck in the toaster.
I love to dance.
You have to if you want to survive that thing.
Oh, I get it.
He's so good.
Yeah, he's right.
Oh god, here we go.
Is it our boy?
It's Flowey!
You know, this is too shape number.
No!
You read time!
It died!
Okay, it's okay.
I gotta concentrate.
You turn into Alphys when you die.
You turn into something worthless.
No!
Oh god, okay.
Alright.
Okay, brutal.
You still got this.
I might.
You're fine.
Everything's fine.
This is the easiest game ever made.
That's right.
That's what they tell me.
Oh god.
Ah!
No!
He's booking it.
This guy reminds me of one of those little kids from Dr. Seuss.
This guy reminds me of my middle school teacher.
Okay, okay.
I got two more chances.
Yes.
Love the dance.
Fuck it up.
Kill that nigger.
Right on the map.
Fuck up.
I hate myself.
Very upset.
We hate you too.
Aw.
Not at all.
Okay, alright.
Maybe you have to be with you.
Yes, this guy.
Oh, like just go under it.
Oh, that's gonna make it way easier.
Yeah, yeah.
There you go.
Alright.
Okay, that's a strat.
Sans, give me the ultimate strat.
I want to be Undertale!
Hello!
Why is Undertale so fucking hard?
I don't even remember this part of the game.
I'm very so disappointed.
This is the DLC, the Greedy Jew, the Tobey J Foxx release.
Tobey, why do you hate Mexicans and women and also the black people?
Well, I mean…
What are you talking about, Munchie?
Yes.
Munchie J Foxx.
Munchie the bitch.
Munchie J Foxx is my real life OC.
He's Tobey Foxx's brother and Andrew Hussie's dad.
Shit!
Oh, no!
I love his beard shape and I just can't even read.
Okay, I'm gonna blast through it.
Okay, alright.
See, I know all the strategies for the level now.
Why does that elephant have to play the game?
See, it's like Dark Souls, you know, they run.
It's like Dark Souls.
First thing off the bat?
Nothing.
Okay, I'm really doing good so far.
Did you guys know that Ben Stain's skill at video games is directly proportional to
how much money he has on paper?
That's right.
Pledge now.
Stop sucking.
It's within your power.
Yeah, I don't know.
Maybe that'll get people to un-pledge.
That was my plan all along.
The quality of the video is directly proportional to how much money he has.
Your entertainment.
Whatever that means to you, it's totally different.
You could just watch a better let's player for free, but when you're invested at this
point, you don't even try to do that.
Wouldn't you rather watch me beat this game and be the coolest guy ever?
Shans.
Shans!
I want Patreon money, but nobody loves me.
Shans, I tried to use my game furry comic about furry gaming, but no give me money.
Shans, I want to play video games, but I don't know how to make money doing it.
Hey, why don't you just call yourself Ben Stain and make yourself a let's play channel?
All Ben Stain.
And change your words.
Oh my God.
The lore is that the Undertale are 5 and 7.
Oh my God!
I was commanded by Shans.
Shans.
And what?
You can't disobey that.
Shans granted you the grace to make you use Shans.
His pupils went all black, and I was like, oh, better do it.
I think I'm real serious.
Yeah.
Shans, why am I so bad at Pokemon training?
Too real.
I don't know.
I bet Shans is too real.
Too real.
What would Shans, if Shans were a gym leader, what type would he be and what would his team be?
Boat.
Ghost.
He'd be ghost type.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Yeah.
Well, sorry for my shitty question.
I didn't even think of it.
It's okay.
You have to promise to never speak to him.
Cubone is rock type, isn't he?
He's ground type.
He's ground, you fucking Marowak.
And Marowak is ground too, yeah.
Well, now it's fire ghost.
Yes.
Which I guess, I don't like it.
I came down on the side and I don't like the old Marowak.
Is he still holding a bone?
Yes.
What's the lore with new fire Marowak?
I don't know.
He's a fire boon.
He's a fire thingies that they use in Hawaii.
Yeah, he does.
But why would he change his type just because he took up a fucking new hobby?
Because it's sick and it has a good typing.
It's a video game.
If something is a new type, he just happens to be able to burn.
Well, except there was already...
I think the thing that sucks is that Cubone isn't also different.
Yeah, that's kind of weird.
That does really suck.
Like, if it was just Cubone, it's just different.
Oh, I already beat it.
I think what they should have done is they should have just...
Every one of the original Pokemon should have had it a little more.
They should have not have been a lazy cunt.
Go watch the good, great video on Hippocrates channel.
Yeah.
Where he says, fuck that shit.
And then you just go watch the Hippocrates video.
I think I just stole your point about realizing it.
Yeah.
But it's not as important as everyone else.
And there's what?
There's like 10 of them or something?
15?
I can't remember.
Not a lot.
What, a lowland form?
Yeah.
There's like...
It's like a dozen or something.
No, there's a bunch.
They're all...
I really don't think there's that much more than a dozen.
Hippocrates.
Yeah.
Has a fantastic...
Fuck!
Oh, I could have easily...
I could have easily...
There's like 16 or so lowland forms.
Yeah.
The variety in this game is really...
I think the biggest problem with Pokemon is that they just...
They kept making like 100 new Pokemon at a time.
So instead of just making 20 new Pokemon and like refining the gameplay.
Yeah.
Well, there aren't some big changes.
I think there's both of them.
Tom, they make like 70 new Pokemon now.
Well...
They don't...
They never make like 100 anymore.
Not anymore.
They should only do like 20.
Why don't they just fucking do both?
Yeah.
They just don't want to.
Yes.
No.
Sounds like they can't make new Pokemon.
Sounds like they got kicked out of the blue bar.
You might wish you might smack one to literally every dish they serve there all day, all week.
They all...
Look.
I'm sorry that I...
Was a normal goal.
Now there's like...
You want to catch 1,000 Pokemon, you need to have autism.
Oh, come on Tom.
That is not fair to be like, oh now there's too much stuff and I don't want to do it all.
Exactly.
Well, okay, but that's why they invented the National Pokedex or whatever that lets you
only...
You catch all the Pokemon from that region, that's like a first tier accomplishment.
But that's not really catching them all.
Like you know that.
Well yeah, but you know, that's on you.
Nobody has ever cared about catching them all except for asking.
You did when you actually could catch them all.
Now you can.
I just...
Tom, you're saying that the game would be better if there was less of it.
No, no, no.
Sometimes that's true.
Sometimes.
I think if the focus was put on adjusting the game mechanics all the time and adding
just a few new Pokemon...
By adjusting the game mechanics, do you mean buffing Pokemon that are clearly shaped?
I don't actually...
Honestly, to be completely fair, I don't know what that would entail because I've never
sat down and actually thought about it.
I'm just saying I think of that time spent in coming up with like a hundred new monsters.
You're so big and undertale.
It needs twenty more dollars guys to get better.
If I don't make it this time, either I'll pick a new game or I'll just pick a new level.
If you're on dot com slash Tommy all over.
Tom, I agree that there are a lot of Pokemon that are bad and they should just fix them
all and that would be easy to do.
But also they should just keep adding more Pokemon because I like new Pokemon.
I like new Pokemon too.
I don't know if the focus on time...
There's so many more now.
Is hurting or enhancing?
I don't think it should be hard to do both.
I really don't get why.
Everyone says, oh they couldn't have made you be able to ride any Pokemon.
They would have had to model all these Pokemon.
Yeah, they should have just modeled all the Pokemon because they're fucking Nintendo.
Well, I don't know how much of that is they were too lazy or how much of that was
they're using a shitty cartridge that doesn't have a lot of space.
Well, both are their own Pokemon.
I will say that if they had less Pokemon, it would have been much less work to model
all the Pokemon.
But they only did one.
You don't fuck out of here.
What's up? What do you got there?
Where are you going to put them?
Yeah.
This means plastic.
Oh, here we go. Here we go.
The Jesse Defense Squad.
This is the glass versus plastic.
Oh, the glass thing.
Right, but glass is good for doing experiments.
You have your beakers to shit because plastic.
And when you drink out of plastic, little bits of butane can get in your water.
What sounds to me what you're saying is that plastic is for cool people and glass is for bad people.
What I'm saying, what I'm saying is that glass has uses and plastic has uses.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Windows.
You could theoretically make plastic.
Yeah, but they're better at keeping them in when they're made of glass.
I'm sorry about heat. I care about plastic.
Well, you know, in Star Trek, there's transparent aluminum.
Do you not have the windows in Star Trek?
Yeah, we're the Rowdy Fuckers Cop Killers.
The most important show.
Okay, let's now officially wrap up.
Also, I'm pretty sure you're really mad at us.
So close the door, come in here or leave if you don't want to come in.
But you can come in. Okay, well, alright.
Okay, okay. Bye.
Yeah, I know what you're doing.
Sam's a little ass full of made of glass and plastic.
So much! Just like my Iron Man saying who I am also.
No! I was doing good at that time.
No, one more. No, one more. I'm good.
Sam's, I was up to Ben St. so much in the fact that he can't do anything right just like me.
Why didn't you go to the cave?
He's a real role model.
Because I want to beat this level.
You guys aren't hurting my feelings. The game is hurting my feelings.
I'm hurting my own feelings by letting myself down.
Excuse me, I sniz.
Quick being a Rowdy Fucker.
You cop killer.
That's right.
Sam, well on Splash Mountain, I puked and peed in front of the people but they didn't notice
because you know like the water was like splashing and I liked it.
Just want to let you know.
You know, I really wonder if the Undertale, if the Undertailer is also, you know, at Drill or Wint on Twitter.
They seem to have a lot of similar thoughts.
Oh my god, I saw that every treat by Drill is such a masterpiece.
They're wonderful.
The latest one I saw was like, adorn your front door with a festive welcome mat or go to hell.
Yeah, that's right.
What a legend.
Does anyone know what his icon is?
It's Jack Nicholson.
Jack Nicholson.
That's what I thought.
I don't know from what.
I really want to know exactly what it comes from.
One day I'll find out.
It's some random movie where he actually is just saying Drill at that very point.
Maybe, maybe.
Drill!
So long suckers I say, revving my motorcycle, making a huge cloud of smoke.
When it clears, I'm lying there, completely dead.
That's a great one.
He has a poetic gift.
He's so fucking funny.
I like followed his links on his Twitter to his website or whatever.
Yeah.
It was weird.
It was some kind of comedy that wasn't that great and there was some animations I think.
I don't even need that potion.
This guy.
This guy fucks.
Maybe I can get it later.
This guy has fucking sex and I relate to that because I also have sex.
Please have sex with the all women in the audience.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Don't listen to him.
He just wants to get your attention so he can shut you down.
If you're a sexy lady.
Don't listen to the same.
And you have Snapchat and Nate Bestman so you can have sex with me in the future.
Yeah, eventually.
All of them in the audience.
Then please message me so I can kill you.
Send me a, send me a, send me a, send me a telegram and I'll fax you my address.
All women.
Please kill you.
Please kill yourself.
Sad doesn't like women.
He told me to kill women.
You're gonna die.
A bunch of dirty bitches.
Frisk is a boy dude.
I'm a mooch out now.
Dude, sense of the all women.
Obviously.
I thought McDowell was a wrestler.
He should be.
Oh, you're blowing boyo.
I don't even know what that thing is.
It's a shame.
How long can you stay in those things?
I don't actually know.
Maybe.
Freda?
Maybe I can.
Maybe a test.
Is there another time to find out?
Oh.
Forever.
Well that makes it easy.
Ah, shit.
Whatever, I got two more lads.
Give me tranquility so I can defeat my foes.
Give me the tranquility to know the difference or whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
To fight my crippling outhaul.
Sad dude.
Yeah, it is sad.
The lore is deep.
The Undertaleers had a tough life, dude.
Yeah.
Why do you think he's come to Sands for coming in his great old age?
He's also 85.
Oh no, in my experience he was like 28 at most.
28, 82, whatever, same thing.
Oh.
Sands!
I just came because my future self didn't say it just completed a level in the video game.
Yeah.
I must have gotten a donation on Patreon.
Boost your finger power.
I got a mighty hammer.
A mighty hammer.
A mighty hammer to fucking brain one of those farm animals standing in the way.
Progressing on my quest.
Hell yeah.
This has a lot of cool imagery.
I just realized that you have a poster of your own art.
Someone sent, when that guy sent Digi like a hundred fucking anime posters,
he sent me one that was my comic and he sent Davoo one that was, I forget what.
Oh, it was his waifu, Annabelle or whatever from Kirby 64.
There was one of the Maya and there was one of the...
That was a weird waifu choice.
Yeah, Davoo's got a weird waifu.
No, waifu!
Anyway, this is a meme.
Oh shit.
Okay, that thing's alive.
No.
This is a meme level because it's all about hats.
It seems that I want to play TF2 anymore maybe.
Yeah I know.
So, I probably shouldn't bother to continue this level, but I will.
Yeah, be the legend.
I don't know what this hat does.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, okay, just, yeah, all right, you got it.
You could have jumped, you could have.
Just go down one at a time, man.
I know it does something.
I am.
Oh, Twitter hashtag, follow me.
Follow me at TheUnderTaylor.com slash forward, fuck you.
We should make a Twitter for the underTaylor.
Yeah, I'm gonna make that right now.
The Undertaylor 587, yeah.
Dude, you should just keep that Twitter going forever.
And just pray to Sands every day.
No, Sands, my fucking dick is, my, my Sands, my dick is fucked.
Sands have my seam is all over the orphans of India.
Hey, everyone, it's Jesse.
You are officially a Rowdyfuckercop.
Yeah, we're all Rowdyfuckercop killies.
We're doing a podcast right now?
Yeah, we're doing Rowdyfuckercop.
We're doing Rowdyfuckercop.
No, no, no, I'm sorry, I'll leave.
Whatever happened to anyone?
No, I can't do this, podcast is too many people.
Sands, I can't fucking suck dick if I can't see my dick.
It was adequately terrible.
No!
It sounds like it.
It sounds like you're all being weaves and fucking
plebes up there at the same time.
You're being something.
Yeah.
You're being a bunch of whiny bitches, is all you are.
I was, I was just sucking a lot of dick.
That's true, I didn't hear you much, which is a surprise.
You gotta love anime, dude.
You gotta love anime.
You gotta love anime, man.
You don't love anime.
Sands, I came.
Oh, Sands.
There you go.
I prayed to you for the orgasm, and it finally came out.
Oh, oh.
You should use words.
Anime is a mistake.
No!
Oh, yeah.
Sands, I shot a big boob in an anime at one point or another,
and holy shit, bro.
That boob was big.
I can't believe how big the boobs are now.
And when I was my age, they were like one or two,
and now they're like 500.
Is this the new awesome possum?
This is Mabeeblee's quest.
Oh, yeah.
This is.
Oh!
Mabeeblee's quest is over.
Don't judge me.
Sands, my future self, Ben St. is dead yet again in Miami.
This is Ben St. found dead in Miami.
Following a series of gruesome serial killings.
I like that, Jambi.
Isn't it great?
The guy who made all the big digi, all those posters.
He made that.
Awesome, man.
Yeah, he's a nice guy.
Yeah, he's a nice man.
Me.
No.
Oh.
That was a good save.
Yeah.
I thought that was done.
No!
You didn't know he was going to be there in time.
Yeah, right.
I didn't.
I was, I had positioned myself carefully before.
It seemed arbitrary, but in fact it was RNG manipulation.
Oh, okay.
You don't have to say that.
Patreon.com says bullshit.
Oh.
See, every time I die, I'm actually manipulating the RNG to give me a more favorable outcome
later in the level.
Yeah.
Really?
Absolutely.
Hey, do you guys know that AGDQ is going on right now?
Yeah.
I'm following them.
Do you want to go?
Do you?
You could be watching that instead of Patreon.
No, no.
By now it's over.
No, don't leave.
Anyway, but yeah, the weekend's over, so it's all done.
Oh, really?
Okay.
Well, they do keep releasing videos on YouTube.
I look forward to it.
Have we done enough?
AGDQ.
Awesome game.
The speedrunning.
Average game's done.
A toast.
Which I love.
I'm all about speedruns.
It's super fun to watch.
Bunch of games.
Hey, so they started watching more speedruns.
I understood why that one time you were like shout-outs to thing, because speedruns always
say shout-outs too, and then they'll name some totally random thing.
Shout-outs to data from something.
But yeah, I like the shout-out fictional characters.
They'll say shout-outs too, and then just say a thing that just happened in the game.
Maybe I did that unconsciously.
I think you must have been there.
I haven't watched a lot of speedruns.
Goodbye.
I'm never coming back.
Shem, I was at the Matterhorn bobsled race, and then when I saw the yeti, I just had to
have sex with her.
No!
Shem!
Oh!
How could you do this?
Shem!
Why would you create me in your image if I was also there going to be gay?
Well, you are not!
Oh my god.
This looks challenging.
No, no.
Does it?
No!
Oh yeah, he's a confirmed trans gay boy sexual.
Trans gay boy sexual.
No!
He's a straight, white male.
He's white, and he's male.
He can't be straight.
He voted for Hillary.
That's true.
He's a straight cuck male.
No, a white cuck boy.
He's clearly gloom gender.
That's true.
Yeah, that's why he's always crying in all his fan colonies.
He's a boner boy.
He's probably what, polyamorous?
Because he's always got a boner for everybody.
Hey, you know who's polysexual?
Steve.
People made a plastic instead of glass.
Polyethylene, polypropylene.
Dude, my dick.
Yeah, I'm with you.
Oh, my dick.
This is my de-sax.
I have gone to the gym now, and now I am powerful.
My dick still doesn't work, so please send help.
Please send more dick juice.
My dick is out of gas.
You told me that would help.
Oh, you've worked it.
You've got to jump really far.
You've got to get it.
No!
I had it!
Shans!
You betrayed me!
That was just bad RNG.
That was just a bad roll of dice.
This time it'll be better.
Shans, when I was a little boy, I saw Megaman,
and I was like, why would I make that game?
I'm not with gay shit, and also I'm a furry,
and it's all fucked up, bro.
Thank you for then making Undertale.
Yes, this is very good Undertale.
Prime cut, if I was to say so.
Choice Undertale.
Oh, no, I'm fucking trapped.
Wait, you can jump on the platform to the right.
I'll die if I get hit once.
Then you're done.
You're a nigger!
You are a nigger!
I can do it, I can do it.
Oh, you can do it.
I can beat the game in every sense of the word.
Oh, boy.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Get that hat you packed up.
Oh, boy.
You didn't get the hat.
Quick a nap.
So you're wearing the hat now?
Okay.
I don't know what the hat does.
It's probably like, at the end,
you probably have to get into a tuxedo park.
Yeah, you have to have formal attire.
Oh, my God, you know what game we should fucking play
on this Clarence's Big Chance?
Literally the best game ever made.
It's pretty good.
Always kind of had ambitions to play that on T-Bat plays.
Yeah, right.
Maybe I'll just fucking do it on Ben Sains.
You should.
I fucking love Clarence's Big Chance.
I actually have completely forgotten why I liked that game.
Because it's fucking the best game in every way.
Well, yeah.
Just shut up.
Just shut up, that's all you need to say.
Well, you know this for me.
No, I'm not saying it's bad.
I'm just saying it'd be cool to play it again,
because I forget what was good about it.
Oh, Shads!
Shads!
Shads, why did you invent death that made me
experience it over and over?
He invented death.
That was a dick move, Shads.
He invented death just for this guy.
Shads!
Oh, Jesus.
Shads, why am I blind in the future?
I'm really shitting the page.
Yeah, by the way, guys, you're sitting on my bed,
which I literally shit in.
Awesome.
Yeah.
What?
I mean, where else would you shit?
Shads told me to.
Shads only shits on the toilet when I'm not looking,
so I don't know what's happening.
What is a toilet anyway?
What is a toilet?
If nothing but a wriggling mess of lies
and fucking that shit that you know when I'm showing it.
What is a toilet but a wriggling mess of lies?
It can't be real if my eyes are real, Shads.
You can't fool me.
Stick this semen down my lemon pipe,
and hopefully I will have two semen instead of one.
That's twice as many.
I can take one person in my town.
No!
I want to go, but I'm busy playing the best game in the world.
You can go if you want.
No, I don't want to go.
Okay.
Wait, can you pick me up? Everything?
Yeah, can you give me a fucking...
Okay, goodbye.
Shads, give me a text.
Shads, give me McDonald's.
I mean, I need a 40-piece ticket, but not Shads.
Shads, we need to be friends.
We're a big baby.
We're a big world.
Goo Goo Gaga, please send me a breast milk shot.
It's the only way.
Get out of here.
You're so fucked out of here.
Let's play.
Yeah, we're doing Mbibli's Quest.
I actually do want some chicken nuggets.
Wait, wait, you played Mbibli's...
Shit.
You played Mbibli's Quest, right?
For like 15 minutes, it was too hard.
Yeah.
Fuck, I want Nuggets, but I don't have cash in my Nuggets.
No!
Oh, wait, I didn't die, but I fucking died.
I want the Nuggets, fuck.
Sick, bro, thanks.
Thank you, Shads.
You know how it is with me and my Nuggets.
You know how much I love my Nuggets, Shads.
They just get everywhere when I go to town with those Nuggets.
Those fucking Nuggets don't know shit.
When I'm in the room with my Nuggets, they get very scared.
They go white like a sheet.
When I eat Shads, I love chicken nuggets because I hate blacks.
No!
Fucking dammit!
That again!
What, Shads?
Take one more person.
I'm not going.
No.
This is very important.
We're focused on protecting Shads!
Shads!
This is the worst place.
You're doing it, man, you're doing it.
Shads has given you what you need and it's done.
I hate Shads.
Hey!
Whoa!
What the fuck did you just say about me, you fucking Kites?
Shads now is the same guy?
You're not Shads.
Oh, God.
You're just a pretender to the whole time.
Oh, you're right.
I was just close, man.
Shads was his own fan the whole time.
Oh, my gosh.
What the fuck did you just say, you fucking Kite?
Beat me.
I'm a robot also.
I'll have you know I served 15 tours.
Whatever the fuck they mean, text us again.
I'm a four years trip for…
I got two one trip kills.
You!
No!
Yeah, jump!
Jump!
I am a!
I am!
OK, man.
What did you just accidentally hit?
more many many hats okay well I'm fucked this is I get one chance at this
boss so yeah you got zero what do you have zero okay I get I get shans help me
defeat the factory man here we go here we go you need to shovel the power oh
yeah all right all right shans use your pixie knowledge that you gained while
you were in the forest and my fan fix and I would wear you wear a forest pixie
please fucking help bro okay here comes this boss actually kind of a bitch
maybe I can actually do it if you go right under the smoke at first it looks
like you're saying well you go under it now people he's doing that yeah yeah
dude that's the best guy ever with the strat that's right that's right
okay there you go there you go yeah all right he's he's he's done yeah thanks
shans well at California Adventure I went on that one roller coaster where it's
a circle and then while I was at the middle of the circle I was upside down
and the rides are done so all the way up into my nose and I came I tried to buy
nose I did it now you get a second hammer and now the three hammers needed to
kill all the farm animals hashtag AGDQ kill kill kill the animal kill the animals
kill the animals save the frames I didn't watch AGQ at all bad not this year
yet but I'm going to watch so many of those I think I want to hear um I love
speed runs I love that yeah um crack like watching them for the way we can get
them elephant get the elephant yeah so your lives oh yeah you're watching them
for the fucking Pokemon race I got really into them yeah yeah right it's
good stuff okay secret level secret level secret level look it's real
mega boo sparkles I didn't notice the sparkle thing before what's what's the
promise of this game you're mabeebley hey did you see the fight against
croco deebley that was pretty big he missed that that part is so fucking cool
your nemesis croco bebeley croco deebley croco deebley is just he's there and
you gotta he's your nemesis so you know go that's that's basically it you just
shans I love to not make original content and I love to just make like
mega man you guys see that fourth wall break something about Simon says oh yeah
oh okay I get it now you gotta hit the switches how hard are these gonna get
um I think you can just like I think you can like lose and it doesn't matter oh
really well let's see okay I think there's some okay let's see here
was it this one again yeah
whatever I knew which one it was I think it's just water okay yeah alright let's
what the fuck dude I did it you know what it is I just got to do the first
two and then the second one I just take a hit it looks like you have no choice
but to take that hit yeah okay that's the bullshit you know what I bet I bet if
you record that are you slowed down I bet you get a secret right and we are
recording this we could go back later watch that footage slow it down you
frame by frame maybe pause the game then I don't want to do it no no I will
play it not now but later on later on I will go and watch this very video viewers
that you are watching right now and determine the secrets he won't I may do
it you won't sons give me the strength to go watch my video okay I gotta get the
next one right this is up left right and then right again I believe it was left
left and then I think right fine right fine right got it all right sweet this
one doesn't matter
yeah it did seem to it seemed to be working when I get the first one I
bet there is a solution yeah I'm good because of how good I've done in
puzzles this is a very satisfying oh don't kill that boy you made it and you
were a super hero type thing take this yeah so I think I don't actually need to
go to the final level of the yeah that's why I'm gonna check it out anyway
you or it's a fucking Lisa monster it's a meal do not just broken glass it hurts
how are we oh there's a secret there's a secret in this level really yeah there's
a secret boss human ebly whoa awesome yeah I want to see it so bad okay so yeah
these they become painful and they hurt you if you hit them once and then I'm
going to go away I can't see yeah it's the best game ever made oh oh oh no yes
yeah that's French French though it says I jack off to Fred French on
exclusively it's Luigi's name Luigi get away it's a bug it's a bug Luigi it's
a stone Luigi you didn't make it fuck you Mario you're a contract you're up
we go down there and you can shoot okay that works too wait you just drop down
there you can shoot from the side you will always storms are named after
people sans oh god all right all right oh dear that's the strongest man in the
world actually what two hits me that way scared yeah wait right seems like I
think I fucked up and there's probably so kill yourself as fast as you can oh
look at all that fucking help dude look at that guy up there he looks fancy you
can probably reach it from the thing maybe yeah be careful be strategic with
your shots you bet oh well now you know I'll see you better fucking got it okay
I'm sure you get up there if you do a little you know do a little one of those
okay delete one more block there you go yeah well whatever they're cocked the
oh yeah here we go here we fucking go thank you so much for my dick I just use
it literally all of the day it's never goes a time because with is not in use
basically
sans I read online that Tupac is being held captive by the Prime Minister of
Israel and then if I locate and save him I will win a free Xbox one sans bye
I'm gonna do that oh my god you're so right oh my god you're so right
doesn't even it's just stupid doesn't even like every video in my mind but
Jace hasn't even played any other tail what don't say that let alone the
original please yeah published by Square Enix no doubt
I don't think I can actually do it that hell well whatever yeah you go well I
don't actually need the help and you fucking good guy wait don't you want to
get the job tank you want the tank I do want the tank oh okay okay shoot one of
those and yeah shoot one of these more there we go there you got hit you got
hit maybe but he's a good game I created death I'm a new character the X
Undertale I hate Undertale well not really I would do I would do well you
well no no I'm the Undertale of the PC floor is getting pretty intense
I feel like we're getting into the King of Hearts Birth by Sleep
yeah yeah great PC birth by sleep yes we were asleep the whole time
hi Papyrus I love you so much it's simulation by sleep
well you're asleep while they were there we go
oh there's boys there boys boys and if you don't get back with my Nugger soon
you will fucking not really anything but please do it soon I can't have it in my
ass without it you know how I get my nuggers no I give up my nuggers and no
nuggers no life okay okay this is where the secret is okay I'm paying
attention but I don't I don't quite remember how to like I know where it is
but I don't there's I think there might be some like setup involved in getting
it okay okay this is it down there you have to go down there or something yes
okay just shoot those blocks how do you do that easy like that wait it's gonna
work seems pretty simple shoot that way just match it bro there you go you get
through now wait wait no I can't I can't quite
oh you can't just drop down it's easy it's crazy no I can't because I'm quite
go down there and shoot as much well he needs to shoot down to shoot one more
block down okay is there anything to do that jump to the left again jump
well and then you brought the big deal no no no no no I can't get the cake the
big dude over at this ledge never right right kill kill what kill like one of
them so you can stand there and how do you propose I do that you do it real
carefully oh why are you okay I can't think there's too much
she went in my ear I've lost all sense
balance and I don't know off my bio
system throw it on my bio rhythm
my embryo that's what I was looking for
it's in jeopardy due to all of this insemination no oh I got shot I got shot
again I got shot for real I got shot I'm gonna die I'm gonna die
and I lost all of my senses replacing with one sense that is the sense of doing
bad things that I do it exclusively to think sans enjoys hearing these prayers
these these these lamentations upon his fair name
take the entire you've on your chair down my limit pipe and let's see if it's new
life wait Ben I think you know what it might be I think I might have maybe I
should have come here without the robot at first and I think I might have
messed it up by like blowing something up with the robot that needed to be here
well maybe not even the robot but like bad guys I think there might have been
some way I actually could have gotten the robot to get here with me but I didn't
do it okay why don't you go I know there's an enemy coming up and the enemy is
supposed to like up please that guy's bullets I think went through when it
didn't do it okay okay I think there's yet it's this guy it's this guy yeah this
here we go that's the one you and you and I pray to you and this is the payoff
bitch it was that pile thing you stand in front of it's just a pile oh okay just
a background thing okay yes yes yes yes I've only got two lives I'm probably
ultimate battle sand for a home of human evil human evil that that water was
really dangerous okay but it's not okay we've seen this guy before he turns you
into a painting is that it is that all you're gonna do buddy I'm sure that'll
come into play in a special way by the way those guys are fucking awesome yeah
they're cool look at him he looks like cold corona kind of yeah he's robo he's
robo-corons you know they remind me of a little bit me
I don't know about who
made Pokemon go but I want to figure out how to make them Pokemon go to the
polls and how do I get them to be convinced to do such a thing I need
here I'm going to cry is that say the one death what death percent death
I'm just gonna play this super save yeah I think you can run those like
teats they do look like teats in fact pretty gay bro I shot oh yeah you're
almost there there it is safety zone oh thank your son okay there's health over
here worth it yes yeah thank your sons for this help even though this health is
fucking poultry and like anything will kill me anyway hey you know what what the
fuck can you do oh I thought he was a pony
the whole time I've been tricked by the a little bit of it
sons did you know that Walt Disney was a hater of the Jewish race I just found
out can I watch the documentary about niggers and why they are bad I saw that
document yeah it was made by Walt Disney oh god it's human ebly dude human
eble I had no idea what the fuck okay he's gotta be he's gotta be he's not lost
is that Ron Weasley it is oh he's fucking sick okay all right all right you
gotta calm it down Ronald your family doesn't even have money and you don't
even have moves yeah oh no it's a ginger bitch let's me a
dispose of him like I do all of my prey with semen I'm glad you gave me
the building yeah so much so much sexual violence stop doing that please stop
doing that oh god I thought I was gonna get hit but in because I'm smart and able
nobody nobody is disabled okay you're you're you're chipping away at him
Shaz while eating Disneyland ice cream I saw a small boy with the clutches with
crutches and I went over I pushed him down and I got the crutches and I
so far my ass now my brain is being affected what do I do get the
Disneyland security I know they know me by name they know me by scent they smell
semen and they know it's me there's exact same scenario with the exact same
human as appeared before in the database I know you've got them on speed dial
no no he's beat he's just gyrating the quarter now yeah so do you get a sweet
outfit now you get nothing all right is that an enemy no just fucking sends you
back to the level all right what is that oh I am sad rock you wear my big
brother awakes he's awake he's violent shans please don't let me die oh look at
me I am Asian undertaker now gookie gookie go I could you could you don't
think that baby that's so gay yeah it's fun
definitely not as good as under there or Pokemon go to the pole level you know I
went to a Vatican City and Pokemon go to the poem oh shit once you get froze
no I think I think it might be possible to not get hit by it really you have to
be frozen for a long-ass time yeah I don't think hitting buttons does anything
oh no oh
sans while getting on the Roger Rabbit car ride and toon town and Disneyland I
it was like a roll up and also I may have dropped a small child in my gaping
ass a while I almost did it okay all I want to know sans is where did he go all
I want to know sans is where the fuck is Mickey Mouse and Donald J Doc Donald J
oh I am a new character I am African undertaker I'm the same character except
I am an African tribal man I sell my own race well while I was at Disneyland in
Africa which ones I they're out at McDonald's right now that's true they're
poor shade I don't know shade might be in his room oh yeah in his room I think you're one
I don't know you just saw a G in the lap or Conrad or whatever his name is
no he's going tomorrow morning that's their friend Marcus oh yeah yeah yeah and I can't
we stop talking about
the african at disneyland
african america
oh yeah yeah you gotta make that
restrictor shat job
good point sands
that is a good point get out of here
yeah
have a good revenge
oh you got a thing
oh i guess you just have to not hit any of those
other bits
i hope that i hope that the fact that
i died to um
violent rock doesn't mean that like the fact
that i beat human eebly is erased
yeah though that may or may not even make
a difference
i feel like that might be possible
considering that like nothing happened
so maybe you had to hear the actual level
of gay pride
i don't think so i think cause like
next time you fight human eebly he has fewer
clothes on because you knocked his suit off
and like i knocked his suit off so i'm pretty
sure it counts
whatever counts he means
i mean you have to make him completely naked
you have to embarrass him beyond
yeah yeah the last time you fight him
he gets a stick out
really
these guys a little tallywack here
that
sexual shat
it's amazing game design
oh shat
the game feel on display
you know what i like in my game shat
let me explain for the viewers at home
it's peteis's semen dick fuck diarrhea
and pee
also bot flies down my lemon pipe
which i have in excess
i don't know how they keep getting in though
i keep cleaning out once every 16 years
consist oh god oh god i can see
money is the root of all the evil
but i don't know what the root of all the root
of all the bot flies
that potion doesn't actually restore your HP
it only restores your lives
oh really
so yeah you might as well get it
even if it won't do anything
is there anything funny in bot flies
no
i don't think so
let me think
robot flies
no
i went through everything
you sifted through the list you keep
yeah
no
oh shit
oh god it's such a garbage
okay i'm not going to do human evil at this time
obviously
yeah
it's not really annoying
those
no not as annoying as these guys
you have to preemptively shoot your parts
yeah you do
oh alright
yeah this robot actually fucking sucks
because you have to point out your shots
yeah
does the bullet always go at the same downward angle
it doesn't go down it just goes straight ahead
oh yeah i guess you're right
whatever
i'm just happy that i got the secret
yeah
me too
we did it sans
sans i'm a video game
no
oh okay
sans
i don't even like video games
i only played Undertale for the story
i played Undertale to get sweet goat poor sans
as real as a lovely little butthole sans
i love his goat tail
i rip it out and then i can see the exposed
aider
oh
oh no
no we too well
i can't wait to upload this or then
i guys are you guys
are you guys fucking hyped to be professional
rowdy fucker
now that we've now that we're theoretically starting to monetize the pcp you guys are all gonna be swimming in it
you guys are all gonna be rolling
after all the right fingers cop killers is the most successfully well viewed thing
it is the least viewed thing
yeah
i think actually that might not be true but it's the first one is pretty fucking far down
that's true
it takes a lot of work to be this bad
yeah
you can't do that
i don't think i don't know we're not bad we're just niche
we're just niche
oh very niche
where josh you're niche
we're a botfly demographic
tell me you don't love the sans like nobody could not love sans
are you talking about real sans or this new sans
well
well midtown sans
midtown sans
our god
could you go along with the fedora wearing ronie papyrus
we have midtown
oh never write off the best
right gotten the fuck
this guy is like i feel like if you
seems challenging
i feel like if you like really got this guy it would be easy to just like understand him so well
that he would never be in any danger at all but that's not me
ooh
alright
i got one chance
well
these week
sans
spaghetti
these linear powers
like shit
oh no
come on
shake it loose shake it loose
oh
if you get hit there's just no way
i think that
shh
speaking of which
oh dear
oh what a sans
you got two hits left
for your murder
fuck
one hit left
oh my god
bensane
it's time to go into the zone like in my favorite anime
i did so good before
well
y'all have a certain amount of skill per day
try just hit him like three times
and then focus on the blue
the blue should be
sans
why did you do this to me samuel
i don't actually need to beat this guy
but i really want to
because i hate him and he must die
okay no one shoot game over
and we have to go do a new game
because that's the entire point of the bush
as soon as i beat this guy
and then find them a bible
pdrall.com
we're about to find them a bible
after this we find them a bible
i guess this is
this game is for finding jesus
yeah this is a bible dude
it's the most powerful artifact
so you're a furry
who realizes the area of your way
to try to find jesus
the bible isn't saying
that shell not yiff dude
it didn't need to
that shell only yiff
that shell
that shell indeed
that shell only yiff
if thy woman has no furry boobies
then she is killed instantly
not even
alright you know what
i hate this game
yeah shut it up shut it up
no no no i'm just going to skip this level
i'm just going to go to the next level
and then i'll quit
yes thank you sans
for the gift of death
thank you sans for letting me fucking die
okay
now let's see what happens over that rainbow
alright alright time
it's time it's time
we've killed all the animals
yes
sans i like
to touch the butt
of all the laundry
i like to vacuum pack
my scrotum sans
it really gets
right in there with all the sucks
it really gets me right in the emotional
squiddly spooch sans
what
did you control all the lights
he didn't do nothing
you guys saw that?
it just crashed
open it up
i hope it fucking autos
look down at your test score
is it? no it's not there
no it's not there
alright alright let's fucking see about this
sans what the fuck
yes sans that's
pretty fucking gay
fucked up sans
he's not you
just continue and see where we are
alright
games great
buy it on steam
or whatever
i think this game is free actually
i think in which case it's
the best fucking deal ever
this game is fucking radical
alright
you go back to the
beginning area
it circles around
oh yeah
yeah
time for some important lore
croco deeble's castle
whoa
croco
shits
you cannot defeat the great croco deeble
that's what you think
we've got three hammers now
i can do that
why are the hammers perfect
i didn't realize this was an actual level
i'll just beat it
because of how cool i am
dammit
me for future me
oh no croco deeble
oh he got you
he got you real bad
we think slow does protest a little
but not enough
why don't you just leave me alone
croco deeble
you're gonna die now bitch
you're pathetic you're so easy to kill
hope it's garbage day because you're gonna be
garbage i'm gonna smash you into a million
different itty bitty pieces
and you're gonna die and it's likely you're not going to
enjoy it very much
i hope you brought some coffee because i'm gonna
cream you
and coffee and cream go together
look at how pathetic you are
you thought you were going to save the world
i'm party drawing thing
trying to save the world
don't make me laugh
saving the world
what an original tale of a story
in fact it's all a tale of a story
i hate you
why would you want to play here in the city
i'm just party drawing thing
again i self respect you piece of crap
and this is why my mind is so long
this is a story of a story
i don't want to read this
i'm not gonna say what happened
you're boring, this is flag
this is all a story of a story
i'm just kidding if i didn't lay the game
i wouldn't lie
i hate to play, i hate to do
in the evening
what is happening
i'm about to die again
this is not gonna stop this is stupid
get alive it is going on
but wait wait
we're going to fight
a little billionaire
sand come on sand
sand
sand help me
help me sand
i'm an undertale hail sand
i'm dying
for my undertale sand
my sand
help me
jesus fucking christ
that was pretty sick bro
we did it we made it
oh isn't this nice 3D kind of thing going on
land that plane
yeah it's a runway
straight to hell
is this undertale hell
this is pokemon hell
oh no
oh okay
oh this is like some weird
thing where i can only
move in certain
my movements
it's an RPG
like i'm not moving right now
it's like one of those ice puzzles
where when you start moving you keep going
a slippy slide
it's what is known as a slippy slide
hmmm
you're delightful
shans i know
you're behind the masacre
in jones town
i have planned
to push your idea wasn't it
you can't hide that
it's even in your name
samsy hook
new fucking card
i want that fucking pie
god stop it
shans after i
was under your influence i realized
that all death is related to you
oh i know how to do it you have to get
oh no no no
wait may you go back you cannot go back
you fucked
i'm picking out how to do it as well
i'm so sorry
i don't know what it does
we just gotta move on with our lives
we have to move on
that would be disappointing
shans
we just gotta go into this video game
shans i love video games
be bread boys
definitely want to be bread
seems like a good choice
wrong character
sexist
i just want to be bread man
maybe
oh
wow look at all this shit
shans this game sucks
took my life out of a lot
shans my
be blaze have become
i have i have a maybe
you can meb
i'm gonna spam fireballs like a champion
that's the way to do it looks like it's working
real well yeah fuck you
crocadebes
crocadebes not one as you can see
having defeated the crocadebes
the quest to save the world continues
makes sense
here we go
stop it
we gotta find them a bible
the bible is here
sounds like you don't know what we're talking about
there's no level involved
i shouldn't have to play another level
thank god
i just need to find which one of these goes to the
i think it's
ALL
home stuck suburb
god
here we go here we go
this is where i was before and then i got teleported away
shans never mind i don't like undertale
i like home stuck
this is my character now i'm fucking
hey daaaave stryder
it's the bible it's the fucking bible
i got it i got the most powerful thing in the universe
aaaaaaaaaaaaaah
what did i do
You got some of Bible press cross see you cross pick up sweet Jesus and you can use it once for level and then you just go
You just go
Sick bro
Shans, I hate you again. Yes. Yes, Shans. Where are my nuggers?
Fuck damn it. All right. Are we we're done
I
Okay, so what are we playing now it quit this game. It sucks. Yeah. Yeah, you're not enough
Fantastic deal for free. How long is it going now? We have been going for an hour and a half. I'm done. Oh my god
Damn it. This wasn't any cluster. Fuck. This was a mabeebley cluster fuck
Yeah, you're right. All right, whatever bye
The words