Routy is the one year anniversary of our fucking video game Endless War, a tech space MMORPG that
you can play in a Discord server.
Today, the 9th of April is the first year since it came online. I believe a year ago and a
couple days was the first time our server went online. I have no idea when the actual
anniversary of that is. I think that's in March actually. I'm going to look at that.
April 9th is the day that the bot went online?
Yeah, the bot went online, yes.
Yeah, okay, so that's in my book, that's the Endless War's birthday.
Also, coincidentally, it's also my birthday. It just became my birthday half an hour ago.
Wait, are you serious?
Yes, April 7th. Yeah, thank you.
I didn't want to tell you, I deliberately hid that information until the show started.
That's so crazy. Oh man, I'm going to have to give you something.
My birthday is two days before that of Endless War, as it happens.
Well, it just still happens.
Yeah.
You're also very close to the first episode or the anniversary of Veryfuckers Cop Killers itself,
because it's on the 11th of April, so April's just a big month. April's a huge fucking month.
It's like, yeah, two days, two days, two days. Also, I just want to say, so I'm here playing
Enter the Gungeon, because I want to hunt that rowdy rat sweetmouth. I hear he's lurking down here,
and I haven't killed him yet, and I'm out for vengeance. He's been the prodigal son for too
long, and it's time to bring him to justice. I know he's down here somewhere, and I haven't
managed to kill him yet, and also I just fucked up, because I shot the water barrel in the fire
place room for it, so yeah, so I'm already behind. I've already screwed up, but you know, whatever.
Okay, okay, viewer. Okay, we're going to premiere this, right?
Yeah, I think so.
Okay, so you're watching this premiere. This is a big event. This is the whole day of
the event that we planned for you, right today. After this video is over, that's not the end of
things. This isn't just like a, oh, cool, like a Veryfuckers Cop Killers episode. I love those.
You know, I can't wait to click, oh, you know, watch right now. No, click the link.
That was that would be taken to an all day stream that we're going to be doing in person.
You may think a premiere is live stream. No, it's not. I don't know how many out. I don't know why
that everyone who watches the premiere doesn't know what the fuck it is. Even still, to be honest,
if you've never done a premiere, if you've never like launched a premiere, I totally get why you
would have no idea what it is. It says premiere. It says premiere on it. That doesn't explain what
a premiere that doesn't explain what a premiere is, though. Well, okay, whatever. We're not live.
We can't see you since Super Chat's still though. Anyway, after this, there'll be a real actual
stream on our Twitch. Well, Pokemon, XT, Gale of Darkness, not to mention. It'll be a bit of a
variety stream. Yeah, yeah. Unless XT just takes us all day. It's going to go from noon to midnight,
Eastern Standard Time. And during that time as well, if you click on our Discord server, the
thing that this whole thing is dedicated to, then you'll be able to play the one of the earliest
versions of Endless War. You'll be able to see what it was like back in the old days. Endless War
Classic will be live, what, today only, right? Today only. Today only. So get in there while the
fucking game's good. Click that fucking Discord link down in the description if you haven't already.
Listen, okay. I know there are some people who watch our FCK and know how to play Endless War.
Not a lot, because frankly, I literally don't understand how that's possible. But if you've
ever thought, like, maybe it may be something to the effect of like, like, it's almost like
like a one piece or a homesick where it's like, it's still, you know, there's so much there,
it'll take too long to catch up in a way. There's so much well-established, like, societal and cultural,
you know, stuff that I'll have to, you know, read or just, you know, listen to or something
intimidated by the vast, deep society that we built for ourselves right now is the time.
Jump in right now, be part of the community, and stop fucking way on the sidelines.
Yeah. Also, I don't even feel like, you know, I think we used to say, I think maybe we used to
say that there was like, just so much. Well, no, I think we, no, we fought this notion. We fought
this notion that there's like so much lore that you like can't, you know, it's impossible to catch
up. You don't need to catch up. You don't need to know everything that's happened. It's not important.
It's all, you know, it's whatever. That's all in the past, and we're looking forward. We're
looking to the future. We are. So just join, you can read orientation, you get caught up in literally
five minutes, and you'll know everything that you need to know. Yeah. Play the fucking game. It's
literally not hard. This is even like a less complicated version of the game than is like,
you know, this is literally just, you press mine and you press kill and you're done.
Temporarily, we're temporarily rolling back that feature creep.
Temporarily. Very, very temporarily. Among the people who haven't played the game are also people
who can't mad when you play the game. And while I don't respect you whatsoever, just so happens
that my interest aligns with yours for a second, because there's just so much to talk about, because
through the last thing in February, in February, that was like a billion years ago.
Was that so like two months ago? Maybe just so much. Yeah. So much to talk about. So,
so we can catch me as much as I would like to. But first, but first, let me crack into,
let me crack into my new, my energy drink of choice. Please, please, God, please, God, summit,
summit gridlock. Oh, Mike. Okay, I'm, I'm fucking rigorously Googling. So just right now. Okay,
summit gridlock. Okay. Oh, somebody's like, yeah, this looks like Metal Gear Solid 3 is what this
looks like. It looks like it's like it looks like a health potion. It looks like Metal Gear Solid
3. This is the most like parkour dude 91 thing I've ever seen in my entire life. Yeah, it is.
It's so parkour. Okay, think of gridlock. It's pretty similar. It's pretty similar to Monster Ultra.
But the thing about it is it's a dollar can for like a full size can. It's, it's, it's only,
it's like only available at Aldi though. So, so get your butts, get your butts to Aldi, I guess.
I'm so glad that we are just like, like rapidly becoming the energy drink duo. I feel like this
is the dynamic that we need to empathize, or emphasize in all of our content together. Because
I, listen, you've heard of bang, but have you heard of rain? I have. From you. But only briefly,
only briefly, and that was a shit flavor. But I am drinking right now rain energy drink,
Melomania. That's, that's um, that's R E I G N. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's R E I G N. Yeah,
yeah, yeah. And I'm about to send you a picture if you can please show it on, on the episode.
I'll just tab over or whatever. All of my, my potions, my various potions that I have today
in front of me. I'm going to be drinking all of these this recording session. I've already cracked
into the Melomania. I'm not, I'm not editing, I'm not editing an image into the video. Okay, well,
okay. Are you recording your, I was just imagining that you would tab over to his court and then
open it. But if you're only recording your game, then whatever, I was supposed to be in the,
okay, yeah, I can do that. But I'm, I'm, I'm killing the, I'm killing the king of,
I'm killing the king of time right now or something. So, well, whatever he's, he, listen,
does he drink bane? Is, is his mental retardation cured? I don't think so. I don't think he matters.
Okay. Show, show me this, show me this, show me this crap.
Right. I deemed it to you. I'm going to be going to taste test. I'm going to be evaluating
energy drink and I'll be telling you how they're rigged.
Okay. So, okay. There is a new monster ultra flavor. It is green. It is slime green.
What? And it is, and it is called ultra paradise.
No. And it is apparently green apple watermelon flavor, which sounds
too good. It sounds too good to be true to me. This is so, you know, you know, Ben, this, this,
this reminds me of a, of a, of a local brand of energy drink from new Los Angeles city,
Akinia, Milwaukee, a fuck energy. I used to drink fuck energy as a kid.
Yeah. Until you need to stop. But you didn't.
Yeah. This, you know, it's like stinky tofu. Like when you eat it, it reminds you of home.
It smells terrible and it tastes terrible, but you know, it just, it just brings it back.
It just brings you back. This reminds me of fucking energy a lot. Anyway, I have right right
here. And as I described to you, Ben, over deems, what a rain con candy was, it was just a watered
down con candy bank. It was just sort of like a, someone saw like tasting bank. I was like,
yeah, I guess we can do that. I guess we can make our own energy drink, but they didn't put
their hearts in the water. However, melon mania, which I'm drinking right now
is fucking de-lish. Have you ever had a hubba-bubba watermelon flavor?
Yes, sir. Yes. It tastes just like that, but it makes you energized and it makes you feel like
you could crush a car between your fucking big toe and your pinky toe. It's absolutely delish.
And rain, I'm giving you a fucking hard, hard eight to light nine. You are doing great,
my friend. You are doing fucking great. Sadly, your con candy flavor sucks. However,
I also have right in front of me the original that rain you cannot stand up to. And that's
con candy bank. So let me taste some of this right now.
Mmm. Rain. Ah, you may taste good, but you're no bang. Bang, bang. That was me shooting rain,
because bang is a fucking literal ten out of ten. This con candy bank is the most delicious
fucking drink I've ever had in my entire fucking life. Nothing can beat it. I have to,
I gotta get me some. I gotta get me some. You've been drooling over the con candy bank
ever since I told you about it. Well, I'm a little skeptical. You know, I'm a little-
Oh, you're skeptical? I wouldn't say skeptical. I would say curious. I'm curious. Like, what
is a cotton candy energy drink? What does that even like? What does it even mean in today's world?
You know, it sounds weird, but the actual taste itself, I don't think is necessarily radical.
The thing about bang is it's, you don't really realize it, but drink, energy drink flavors
are sort of subdued in a way, where it's like, uh, yeah, they do have flavors, and flavors
are usually distinct. Technically, they taste like something. Technically. Yeah. But bang is
like an assault on you. Bang is like the most like, like, it's not that the flavor is better,
it's just that there is more of it. It just is like, they put way too much syrup into it,
and you cannot- That sounds perfect. It sounds like all your sentence.
It sounds like exactly what I want in a beverage. I know, it's- Ben, I'm gonna fucking smuggle you.
I swear to God, I'm gonna smuggle you a melon mania, uh, rain, and I'll smuggle you in a con
candy bang. I have, uh, I have, I have yet to actually, like, check any stores near me. There
could be, there could be bang around here. I just don't know. I'm sleeping on it. I'm sleeping on
that bang. Hey, hold on. Speaking of Boston, next time I'm in Boston. Yeah. Uh, this will be my
first public, uh, announcement of this. Uh, you know Ben, but, uh, the, the, the, the saga that has
plagued me and my appearances on the procrastinators podcast for a while now is over. I got into
Right. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Um, I, I, I'm all- Massachusetts awaits.
Matt, yeah, I, so I've been, I'm gonna be able to, like, RCK will turn into, like, possibly
an exclusively in-person ordeal. Scary. Scary though. How fucking weird will that be?
Imagine having another person in your room ever. Ugh. No, thanks.
Uh, I, I suppose I'm gonna, did he used to record, like, like, like we'll, oh wait,
oh, he's gonna be gone though, I think. Is that official? Is that official? I think it's official?
I don't know. We were talking about this last episode. I don't know. You never know, you never
know, you never know what that guy, you never know what'll stick. Well, it's, it's not even just,
it's, it's, it's everyone. You never know with anyone, you know, you never know who's going
where, you never know what's going on. But what we do know is that me and Ben, we're gonna be
together and we're gonna be able to, we're gonna be roommates. Oh, oh, oh, opening a monkey house,
or sorry, wheelhouse, don't mind if I do. We're gonna be bridesmaids. Hmm, always a bridesmaid,
never a kingpin, as they say. Yeah, I see. Always a consort, never a kingpin. Sad.
I want Tom to fucking move into a monkey house so bad. You keep, you keep begging him to you,
keep saying like, hey, there's a spot open, and he was responsible for that stupid fucking thinking
emoji. He never actually thinks with his real brain. He just lets the emoji do the thinking for
him. Yeah, yeah, exactly. Yeah, I mean, I mean, he's not gonna leave, he's not gonna leave Digi's
place because he's got a, he's got a sweetheart deal there. So, I mean, sure, you know, what happens
with Digi's place doesn't exist. Yeah, I don't, so until, I think until Digi's place doesn't exist,
or is confirmed to soon not exist, he probably isn't even gonna think about it. And at that point,
will come the time when he must choose like, okay, do I live in a real house or do I just,
or do I live in my car? He's not gonna commit to anything until, until such time as that.
Also, you can't see this, but I'm using, I found, I've never used this weapon before,
it's called mutation. And it's just a big fucking glob in my arm. And it just shoots out big, like
Akira fucking flesh goo that like splatters blood all over all the walls. Perfect thing to hunt
the rowdy rat with, I should think. Speaking of mutations, we're gonna be reading the mutations
contest on stream. So, look at that. Oh, right. Well, click it at noon. Click it at noon. Sorry.
Click it after this episode is over. Yeah, yeah, yeah. It immediately, immediately. There will be
no delay. We will plan it out. We will plan it out. We will plan it out. We think you were doing
anything other than listen to RFCK today. You're, you're, you're, you're so embarrassed for you.
Ben, we gotta do this show monthly. We gotta do it monthly. We gotta have an episode out monthly.
We gotta have a stream out biweekly. We gotta get some sort of fucking schedule here,
because we're, we're hemorrhaging slubs, dude. We're fucking no one, no one remembers RFCK.
By the time we released the episode, everyone was just like, huh? Last, last one was when I,
you know, was two years ago. I don't even know who you guys are anymore.
I mean, sometimes I forget.
Ah, that's a nice, yeah. I wish I could forget. Ben, I'm sure you had this.
I'm sure you had this, but I've reached the point in my endless war developer career,
where every single time I go to sleep, I just am like, oh, slime court. Oh, oh, oh,
what weapon rebalance? I just toss and turn. That was, that was, that was me in my brain.
That was me in the first couple months. Yeah. Yeah. Maybe the first six months or so.
Like, like last night, I just got into bed and like for seriously, like two hours,
like not a joke, like I watched the time fly. I would try to close my eyes, try not to think
about updates to the game, fail miserably and start writing down notes in my phone. I would open it
up and I would just like the light on my phone would blast my eyes fully awake again and the
process would repeat over and over again. Here's the thing. Here's, here's the thing about being
mean or probably any sort of art idiot like me. There's too much to do in life, right? You know
what I'm talking about. There's too much to do. I feel, you know, I feel bad that I haven't been,
I haven't, I haven't been as active in the endless war. I've probably been saying this for a long
time because this has been true for a little while, but I'm like, I'm, I check into the dev
discord once in a while. I'm not like actively developing anything right now because I've,
I've sort of taken a step back and I've really buckled down on like my
comics, basically. That's, that's, that's where I'm at. And whoops, should I not save this on the
rfck? Am I being a downer? No, no, no, no, Ben. Okay, listen. All right. Like, what's the most
important thing about rck? Is it making do fucking kill was happy? No, it's being real. It's about
being wrong. It's about saying the actual shit, right? Not the fake shit, not the phony shit.
Yeah. Um, true. And I mean, I'm still like around, like I'm still on discord and everything. Sure.
Sure. Yeah. Um, you know, you know, you know, it's, you know, really, it's the gamers fault.
It's the players fault because we never did hit 100, uh, 100 x's in the secret project.
Uh, we never, we never even hit 50. So, you know, uh, I could blame myself and my own decisions,
but that sounds lame. Uh, so it's your fault. The listener, you're still ahead of type of
recording this. You're still ahead. So we'll see. We'll see how you fare ahead of what, uh,
in, in slime, in slime, in kingpin slime. Oh, Ben, do you remember the mechanics of the game?
Do you remember? That's not what I was talking about. Um, but okay. Yeah. I mean, I mean, I spent
chin up is what I'm trying to say. Oh, I mean, I've been ahead in slime for, I mean, that's,
I'm not even worried about that. The killer's got, got the slime on lock. Um, uh, you're, you're,
okay. I will say if there's one thing, okay, in this war, RCK, the server in general,
is sort of a bad mistake. Yeah, unironically in a way. Wait, wait, okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. It's just
cause the people in it are so, they're so active. They're so active. You, like you miss a day and
you're fucked forever and they forget about you. Yeah. So I, I can like not tune in for like a week
and everyone's like, Oh, another absentee father. Oh, oh, my munchies just fucking gone. Ben, a
munchie. You don't even check the game. Hey, munchie, do you know what the, do you know what the
street race is? Yes, I know. I'm sorry. Like I'm not in literally every single fucking day.
Yeah. Yeah. That's, that's kind of, yeah. It's, it's a fast pace. You know, it's fast.
It's very fast. I mean, there's just a lot, there's just a lot to do. There's just a lot going on
over there. I will say that your presence has, has been missed by many people to the point where
the killers don't like recognize you as the valid ruler or as a entity that exists. Okay.
Go on. Tell me more. Well, no, like everyone says fuck Ben. Oh, that's what I'm trying to say.
Okay. That's a little more, that's a little more than you're, oh, fuck. The thing about,
the thing about Gungan is you really got to perfect the bosses. You really got to perfect
the bosses if you want to make it in this life. I'm really fucking this run up, by the way.
But you're on a let's play show. That's expected. Yeah, true. I mean, whatever, what kind of
attention would there be if I, if I, if I got him first try? Yeah, no. Ben can play this game
blindfolded when he's not talking. Well, I don't know. Well, I mean,
okay. Okay. Were we talking about, oh yes, I am a bad person. Yeah. Well, bad father specifically.
Bad father specifically. Um, yeah, I'll come back one of these days.
I'm still, you know, I went out, you know, I took a trip. I went out to get some jewel pods.
I still haven't come back, but you know, don't give up hope. Don't give up hope. Oh god. 25
slime coin for a rip of that jewel, please. It's more precious than slime coin. Oh god.
You ever know slime coin is fake, is fake Chuck E. Cheese slime bucks?
No, don't tell them they have to donate. Oh, right. Are we going to keep our sponsorship
deal with fucking energy and subsidiary, uh, uh, slime core slime? Yeah, actually slime
corp has made it has, has incentivized us heavily not to acknowledge the obvious truth of that. So,
I'm just gonna, don't worry about it. Don't worry about anything that's gone here. Stop
watching this video right now. Oh, what, okay. What's going to happen when we shit talk their
Chuck E. Cheese money? They're going to stop paying us and said Chuck E. Cheese money and then we
won't have any more Chuck E. Cheese money. And then how will we play speedball? Yeah. Yeah.
How will we play the stocks? How will we earn, how will we earn tickets to buy a little plastic
rings that look like spiders? Chuck E. Cheese is so like, I, I've never been to an arcade that
was actually good. I feel like they've, there's a thing they are, they exist. Like they must be
people like arcades. I mean, you ever been to like the aesthetic of them are cool. But I've never
been to one that was actually good. Can you hear me? Yeah, I can hear you. I'm just talking over you.
Right. Sure. I mean, you ever been to like a David Buster's? Now keep in mind, I would never go to
a David Buster's because it's totally human core and it's like $40 for a play of crazy taxi.
Human core? I don't know if I would call it human core. I would call way overpriced to
overrated, which I guess is also human. Things that are overpriced are human. Those are,
there's so much overlap between those two concepts. Yeah, you know what? Okay, that's fair.
I've been to David Buster's. I don't know. It, that's like, that's like, if you want to go to
Chuck E. Cheese, but you don't want to admit yourself, you're going to Chuck E. Cheese. Yeah.
That's what David Buster's is, where it's like the same thing. Yeah. It's still like in all,
in all ways that mean anything. Yeah. I mean, yeah, it's just adult Chuck E. Cheese, which is fine.
I mean, I don't even think it sucks too bad. Like I went to one once, played some video games.
That's fine. It's just the cost like a dollar per play of, I don't know, virtual fighter or
whatever. It's a nightmare. God. Or at least it did when I went. I love the idea of stuff like
bowling alleys and arcades and stuff where she's kind of like you hang out. When was the last
time you went bowling? Dude, when I was like six. That's an over exaggeration. Like probably like
12. Probably like 12. Bowling is way fun. Also, I died. Bowling is sick as hell. Bowling is great.
I have a fascination with celebration, a.k.a. the most common bowling alley carpet pattern here.
If you, if you start, I think, I think it was like celebration. I can picture it in my mind.
It's purple, right? And it's not like zigzags or maybe blue. No, but you're probably thinking of
one of them. You're probably thinking, I mean, there are multiple. There are multiple. The one
I'm thinking of is this right here. Hold on. This is my favorite pet. Well, you're at tab back over
Discord. Whatever. Yeah, that's close. That's close to what I was thinking of. Oh, it's so cool.
This is my entire personality right here. Oh, I guess I got to show it on screen.
This is your, this is your background for your Twitch or something? Yeah, it's my
background for a lot of things, I think. It used to be like a pretty heavily,
this was a large piece of branding for me back in the day, like when I was first starting out,
but since how much, how much did you, how much did it cost you to license that?
Zero dollars because I work on the internet and
no one cares about you. Yeah, it's not matter at all. God is fake and hell yeah, dude.
You know, I often think how pretty often a lot of the stuff that people do online is like
clearly not fair use and just is. But it doesn't matter. Yeah, but it just doesn't matter at all.
Nobody's going to actually do anything about it. Yeah, so why should it matter?
Yes, I got the cat bullet king throne. A cat throne to hunt the rowdy rat.
Sourpus turns against his master. I think maybe I stole this from Sourpus. Maybe Sourpus
was sitting on this throne. I'm just floating around. Whoa. Oh, it's so cool. I've never had
this item before. God, I wish you could see it. You'd be so impressed. I doubt it. I doubt it.
You know, I just realized I could probably actually adjust the screen, the screen size and get rid
of these borders. Whatever. She would be breaking the fourth wall though. Because we can't do that.
Obviously K is the opposite of a meta of a meta show in every way that possibly could be. That's
correct. By the way, going back to one thing that I skipped over just to talk about how I'll be in
Boston forever now. Get into college. I want to like someone who was received in Oscar or a Tony.
I just want to thank everyone who said good job, Munchy, or said go for it. I also want to thank
Nate because he wrote a letter of recommendation. And I like to imagine some small part. Nate was
responsible for at least 1% of me getting in. So good job, Nate. I know you're listening.
Well, that was pretty nice of him. It was pretty nice. It was a nice, nice, nice thing to do there.
Hey, actually, did you get to read it? Yeah. Because you were in my essay. I had to write my
entrance essay. Oh, geez. Did I ever show you it? Did I ever? No, I don't think so. It was about the
Spicy Bro Pact. You've told me about this, but I haven't read it. Hold on. I don't think you like,
yeah. Hold on. I thought it was like a secret. Hold on. I'm going to read this on the show for
RCK, for prosperity. I'll also link it in the description. Okay. Hold on. That's not weird or
anything. Is it weird? No, it's fine. No, it's fine. I'm joking. It's real small to see. It's really
it's really funny. Let's see here. Six disheveled men sit in front of a large plate of blistering
in the hot buffalo wings ready to record a video of their feast for an audience of strangers.
So they will be involved in a Spicy Bro Pact, elevating their meager friendship with the highest
form of union one can have with their bros. Forge will eat the hot chicken wings available and
preferably crying in the process. Become rotary experienced while sweating through the agony
together lasts a lifetime. Is it for a matrimony unparalleled and sensitive mentality to me? And
I had been nervously anticipating it as much as one would their traditional marriage. Organizing
their cunning supper had been a pipe dream for so long that I can now even hardly believe I fucked
up whatever it was. This gaggle of men in their late to mid twenties had been my mentors for several
years now and I they're young ward. Yes, excellent. Yeah, make young ward a thing. It's already a
thing and I'm glad about it. Oh, it totally is already a thing. Whenever I have an opportunity
to describe myself in relation to the PC guy, always use young ward to specifically offline
That's a yeah. Whenever I describe you, I always say yeah, he's obviously a young ward.
Like who's this monkey guy? He's my young ward, don't worry about it.
It's like weirdly descriptive in a way where you can like it kind of clicks more than it would.
Yeah, I don't know. It's a great term. You came up with it, right?
Well, I mean, it's from Batman, but I mean, I'm the one that started using it.
Sure. Sure. That's what I mean. Yeah. A mixture of online artists, musicians and writers,
all of them especially in niche content. But by the way, the prompt of this was a describe an
experience that has shaped your life. So the PCP is shaped in my life. You see the collective work
body of work includes everything from comics of autobiographical, autobiographical, homoerotic
mishaps in Germany to sprawling medi narratives, dwelling in the philosophical quandaries,
interwoven across poorly edited reviews. Wait, who had homoerotic autobiographical?
You. You. In what line? Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay. It was homoerotic on someone else's part.
Well, that doesn't make it any less homoerotic. You know what? You're right. You're absolutely
right. And I fucked up. Plus it was funny to say homoerotic. Yeah, it's just what could be more
funny. Yeah. Okay. If you're if you're a woman and you're gay, it's not very funny. But if you're
a man, you're gay, it's super funny. It's super funny. It's I mean, it's a little fun. You know,
let's be honest. It's kind of strong. It's kind of fun. Yeah, it's kind of fun. After finding each
other's work over the internet, the band together to create it into a creative force with a totally
unique artistic voice and counterculture aesthetic. Yeah, it's pretty accurate. Though the game of
being a freelance artist on the internet is to appeal to the wider, this possible demographic
to his crew as many donations and patrons as possible. Their work was less concerned with
being digestible as it was expressing themselves with uncompromising zeal to any other person.
This motley, cruel social outcast might have been the subject of ire, but not for me. They were
everything I aspired to be. Oh, jeez. Oh, fucking shucks. You fucking asshole.
Growing up, I was bullied often and ostracized by almost everyone in my school. I feel like there
was no one that could understand me or the offbeat comments I doled in my sketchbooks. That is,
until I found them. Never before I had resonated with art in such an intimate way. There aren't
speaking directly to the part myself which I had to hide on a daily basis. I found kindred spirits,
and so I began to weasel my way into their inner circle, beginning with sending intentionally
terrible pickup lines to various members of the group every single day for months and progressing
to assorted mischievous acts of ironic self-humiliation. You never sent me a single pickup line, you
fucking asshole. Uh, you're right. Greatest regret. Greatest regret. I began to be viewed as some sort
of cartoon character in the creative consciousness. That's correct. It was all working exactly to plan.
Their door to their hearts was shitty performance art. That's too too too accurate. But it wasn't
but it wasn't all post-modern hijinks. For the first three years after discovering the group
were perhaps the most productive my artistic career thus far. I pressured myself to lip to the
work ethic of the group exemplified, which meant spinning every moment I wasn't getting beat up at
school, working on my creative pursuits. No, I fucked up. Did you die? I didn't die. I just I
fucked up and I forgot to save keys for the oubliet. Um, that's fine, whatever. That that been like
that sentence had no effect on me whatsoever. Boy, if you could see this gameplay, you would be so
you would be so fucking stoked for me right now. That's all I'm saying. Okay, continue. Oh, no. Oh,
no, I didn't get the bloopy blop so I could kill the get the gock. That's right. Yeah, pretty much.
How do you know? Are you a pro? Are you an MLG?
Let's just say that I've saved a few frames in my day. You know, back in the day, heroes would
save dames. Today, heroes save frames. Literally gonna make a t-shirt. We should make an rfck
spreadsheet and put that on a t-shirt, not a joke. Yes, that's brilliant. That is a 10 out of 10.
That is, I want that on my person. Click the link in the description. Yes.
Or you're a fucking loser. Okay.
There was a slow burn, but in early 2016, I was officially declared a member of the group.
In the three years I've seen with my mentors, now lifelong friends, I've grown as a person
as an artist. They fostered my strange sense of humor and artistic expression and in turn,
I blossomed into complete freak. Instead of doubting myself, I press on to even more uncomfortable
and bizarre summits, all because of the men who shower on an as needed basis. And so, I demanded
we seal the deal. Theoretically, we could have just eaten wings together in a Skype call, but you
can't see your friends cry over the internet. So, soon we were recording our feast. It's self
another art piece I would edit and release online. Immediately, my cold feet were worn by the inferno
of spice enveloping my entire body. My friends began to wail in pain, cursing my name with every bite.
That's right. I remember that. I remember doing that.
It was great. Though I explained its purpose in depth, I doubt they appreciated the
sentimentality of the dinner as much as I did. Tears ran down from my face from a mixture of
passion and the, I don't know how to pronounce it, it's canine. It's not the word canine, it's a spice.
I have no idea. There's a spice called canine?
Yeah, see, oh, I'm not going to spell it, fuck you.
Spell it, spell it, spell it, spell it, spell it.
C-A-Y-E-N-N-E. Oh, canine.
Canine, sorry, canine. I finally knew what it was like to be loved, to belong. I felt the
compassion of my fellow man and it was excruciating. And that's what got me into college, was us doing
the spice of Ropak. That was the end? It was excruciating was the last time?
Yeah, it was excruciating.
Well, I wouldn't have accepted you, but you know, different strokes, I guess.
You know, one man's trash.
I really do. I'm really happy, you know, I'm really happy I got into this group, genuinely.
No, no, I'm, there were some people last episode that felt like I-
Last PCK episode or RFCK episode?
No, no, RFCK episode in the comments, who I think thought that I was being sort of, I don't know,
mean in a way to some of the other members of the group, because I was a little bit,
I don't know, maybe noided that Boston wasn't going to be the place, wasn't going to be the location.
But I am, I could not express how happy I am to be friends with everyone in the group.
So don't think that, please.
Yeah, well, I don't. So that's fine.
That's fine.
Viewers, get your fucking heads on straight.
And fucking please buy, fuck energy.
And please buy RFCK.
Use the link in the description.
Yeah, if you would be so kind.
I think I'm going to fuck this up.
I don't think I'm going to have enough money.
I thought it's up and didn't get to the ooble yet, and I'm not going to have enough bullets to get to the ratty rats den.
Well, can I click on an audible link so I can transfer you some more money?
What?
You say you're not going to have enough money?
Well, give me an Amazon link and I'll fucking give you some.
Well, okay. Well, I'll click down in the description, obviously.
That's what any good good fan would do.
Now is probably a good time to complain about Oolulia and how he's too fucking dumb to let me make money for him by recording a stupid audio book.
Oh, yeah. Okay. I know about this, but there's a lot of people who don't.
A lot of people who are just thinking like, oh, what, Ben, you couldn't get, you couldn't get Oolulia.
Why am I so lazy? Why didn't I make that thing? I said I was going to make.
Who's the dude who made Tales Control?
Laserbot.
Oh, you let him slip through your fingers just like Laserbot.
You just couldn't get Laserbot on. You just couldn't do it.
Yeah.
Please explain.
Well, okay. So I was going to, you know, I wanted to make the, I wanted to make the audio book for
a legend of the elemental masters.
So I just, you know, a couple of times I contacted Oolulia on Facebook and I was just like, hey, let me do it.
Finally, he got back to me and I actually managed to talk him into doing it.
And he actually was like, you know, it's.
Oh, shit.
Well, you didn't know that?
I, I, no, I, well.
What the fuck? What did you think I was going to say?
No, no, no, no.
Well, okay. I guess I wasn't caught up.
I thought that you had tried for all the time and he just was refusing.
Oh, you're way behind.
No, he never refused.
Well, it was mostly like the first couple of times he was procrastinating actually doing it.
You're, I can't tell if you're like a behinder ahead on this.
There's continue.
Okay. So I, I, he finally, he responded on Facebook and I was like, hey, I want to make,
I will record an audio book for you.
I want to put it on YouTube.
And he was like, well, I'm only comfortable with like the first two acts going on YouTube.
And I'm like, okay, well, what about the rest?
And we talked about it and we said that I could make the audio book version
and I looked into it and I figured out how you do that and how you release it through Audible.
And I was like, okay, well, let's do that.
So I made an, an Audible account, you know, of the, of the kind you got to do to go through
the, the correct channels.
I did all that.
I got him to start making an account.
And then at some point he's like, uh, I think it's, I think he probably had to enter his tax
information or something.
And he was like, okay, I've been working on this for a while.
I will, you know, I'll do the rest tomorrow.
You know, months later, months later, every now and then I'll message him and be like,
Hey man, you ever get that thing made?
And he's just like, I'm playing a lot of Skyrim.
No, yeah, that's the point of the story that I'm at is that I knew that he, he,
he agreed to, and that you were under the, the impression that you would be able to.
Yeah.
It's, and he is totally fine with me.
He just is too fucking, I'm so mad.
I'm just, it's not that he's too late.
It's that he's too stupid.
I'm not kidding.
Seriously, I have, this makes me so fucking mad.
Literally, I literally, I just want to make money for him.
Also, also me, but also him.
You're so connected, but to the wrong people.
Yeah.
It's like, you have, like, you know, people, you, you have contacted and spoken to people
who many others would consider like a big, like,
you've talked to Crixie.
What the fuck is that?
The fuck is that?
Sad.
Okay, cool.
Sick mom, I'm, I'm recording for the internet.
Do you want to say something over the internet?
Hi.
Hey.
Okay.
All right.
Thanks.
Thanks mom.
Good to have you on as always.
Pleasure.
That was great.
Okay.
Anyway, like you've talked to Christian, like that's so crazy.
Like what?
Talking to Christian is a nightmare.
That's so fucking dumb.
And also stuff like this where it's like,
I can't believe you talked to that law cow.
I can't believe you talked to this person, but like it doesn't matter.
They don't, they don't do anything.
They're, they're pointless.
They're, they're fucking useless for a reason.
Like they, there's a reason that their reputation is what it is.
You know, people like Lilia, but like this has made me like not like him.
Like I don't think I even like him.
Yeah, I'm really fucking pissed at him.
I don't know.
Maybe one day if the book, if he lets me make his fucking book for him,
maybe I'll like him again.
But not, not like this.
This is bullshit.
This is some bullshit.
Literally all he has to do is just like finish making his account.
And then it would just be a matter of him like approving the things that I make
and just being like, okay, go through done.
Literally that would be it.
All he has to do is fucking enter his tax information
and then he'll get free money from me, from my labor.
Man, maybe he doesn't like, he doesn't, he doesn't trust you or something.
I can't imagine why.
I mean, there's no-
Do you think it's a little bit too lazy?
He's just, he just literally-
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
100%.
There's nothing else.
What an asshole.
Yeah.
Boy, that pisses me off.
It would have been, imagine Ben saying-
I spent like-
Like, like audio book narrator.
Yeah, right?
I spent like two days recording and editing a demo version of like the first act or two acts.
It's about 15 minutes worth of like book audio for him to just listen to and approve
before I start like making the audiobook proper.
All he would have to do is approve it.
That's it.
And he just, he just-
No, he's kind of busy playing Skyrim.
It's not even, it's not even a new game, it's Skyrim.
It's actually, it's not Skyrim anymore.
He switched to some other stupid thing.
I don't know what it is.
Okay, but just as retarded.
Yeah.
Why are we cursed?
Why are you cursed to only have internet clout to interact with retarded, crazy people?
Maybe I should try interacting with some better people.
You've got, you're a big YouTuber.
You're a big poke YouTuber.
Surely you could throw your clout around.
You, you, you can't get Lilia to let you do his audiobook.
You can't get your vape.
You can't get Ben St. Vapor sold physically.
What, Ben, you gotta make a change.
I can't, I can't do a damn thing.
You can't do a damn thing.
I gotta, you gotta use it or something or else what am I, or else what's the point of
even having it?
It's gonna decay.
It's gonna have life, half life of two weeks max.
And where's the poo video?
Jesus Christ, Ben.
Jesus Christ.
Speaking of, low art has still, you know, months later, low art still hasn't gotten around to
releasing that fucking Poo's Grand Adventure podcast we did.
Don't know, don't know what his excuse is.
I don't even know who low art is.
He's a fucking guy, whatever.
It doesn't matter.
I'm gonna search low art right now.
He, uh, he, he did a bunch of videos about, uh, like retrospectives on Teen Titans that
got pretty big.
I think he's at like 40k.
Cool.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, he's at 48k.
Yeah, and we recorded a podcast together and he just has been months and he just hasn't
released it.
It was the same, it was the same for Internet Dream Lounge.
That was, that's, you know, Mary, Maryweather and this.
Yeah, yeah, I know that is.
Yeah, you know, I was on, uh, his, his cohort had me on his podcast, did an interview with me.
You know, months go by and then he's just like, uh, actually I think the show is canceled.
I think it's really, yeah.
Wait, hey, am I allowed to talk about zone?
Why not?
That thing that you were, we're not gonna do a, we're not gonna write a thing?
Yeah, I did.
You did.
Did it happen?
No.
Okay.
Yeah.
Why are you cursed?
I don't know.
That's so, that's so weird.
It's, it's every endeavor that you do.
Yeah.
Like every, like, you're God.
I don't even like to think about it, but yeah, you're right.
There's like all this shit that I do.
And then I try to like branch out with, you know, it's just, I don't know.
Other people just fuck it up.
Like when you have to work with other people, they just will fail.
Like it will always ruin anything.
Especially something like, like, okay, for, for that podcast, right?
Like it's a fucking podcast.
It's a, there's nothing, there's nothing he needs to do.
He thinks he needs to edit it and he's wrong.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, why do people think they need to edit podcasts?
Why are, why are they so fucking retarded?
Like, okay.
I can see the benefit of it if you want to, but it feels like-
But just don't.
Just don't.
It's fine.
It's fucking fine.
Like the release of it in any way, then there's no point.
It just won't happen.
If he, like, if he continues to think that, oh, I have to do anything, he just won't do it.
Uh, man, I'm getting mad.
You know what, you know what I'm talking about?
I think, I think you're in a hardcore agree with me, Ben.
The fact people, okay, the best kind of art is like slap-dash art.
Yeah.
Art that just is made.
More and more, I finally just fully recognize the fact that technical skill does not matter.
Means nothing at all.
What so ever.
No.
Means absolutely nothing.
It's a liability.
Comic that I love.
It's a My Little Pony flash comic that is clearly not even fucking attempted to be technically
impressive.
It's just, it's all sketches.
But this dude had an idea and he fucking made it.
And it is, some of my favorite art ever.
Something that shit fucking gave, and look at this shit.
Look at this fucking shit right fucking now.
Hold on, there's a fucking guy shooting at me.
It's so beautiful.
You don't need to fucking come up with all these signed documents.
Like fine one.
You don't have to come up with all these fucking structures in place.
You don't have to come up with anything.
Just, if you have an idea, just fucking do it.
It doesn't matter.
Okay, like you might think yourself, oh, but you know, I want to make,
what I make is good.
I don't want to shit something out.
No, no, shut up, shut the fuck up, you idiot.
Don't say that.
Yeah, that's wrong.
It's so, oh my fucking god.
It's better to have loved and lost than never to have loved at all.
It's better to release a comic or anything,
and instead of shooting yourself in the fucking skull.
Yeah.
She's so fucking mad.
There's, like, this comic is perfect.
You, like, if there's no-
Would it, boy, like, I look at this and I just think, boy,
I wish this guy had spent, like, 10 times as long,
like, carefully rendering all the, like, background details.
Unlike these doors.
Like, what, these, these, they're not colored.
They're not colored.
They're not, like, they're not, like, shaded.
They're not, like, delicately shaded.
Like, they're not, like, you know, he didn't spend, like,
an hour fucking, like, doing, like, three-point perspective
to get the room looking just perfect.
I can't read this swill.
I, okay, okay.
Like, the thing about it, what is the point of this comic?
Okay, it's like a character interaction between spike and rarity.
What's the most important thing?
Oh, the dialogue and the facial expressions
and the, the character thing, being good
and easily communicating what they're feeling.
Does it matter what the fuck is in rarity's carousel boutique,
like, in the background?
Does it matter what her doors look like?
No, it doesn't.
I have gone, I have gone, like, I've gone, like, 10 pages,
I've gone, like, 10 panels and there's just been no background.
What the fuck?
Or why are they just floating in, like, a gray void?
This is a nightmare, right?
So fucking ridiculous.
What a plothole.
Okay, and you want, you want to know how I prove this?
You want to know how we fucking prove that doesn't matter?
Go back to the start bin, go back to the start,
go back to the title screen, go to extra, click on extra.
He made some panels in, like, a try to do a show at yourself.
No doubt, like, way less expressive, way more effort.
Yeah.
Not only did he spend, like, eat, like,
I'm not gonna exaggerate, like, 10 times as much effort.
I wonder if he, like, I wonder if he started doing it like this
and was like, this is a nightmare and is stupid
and it will, it will just, will never be done if I do it.
Like that.
I'm sure this exactly would happen.
I'm sure this is exactly what fucking happened.
This thing is really long.
The comic is literally, but, oh, it's, it's super long.
It's 400 pages.
Oh my god.
Yeah, no.
Never would have been happened if you just wanted to do it that way.
And the comic is literally better, better for it.
It's better because it's in the scratchy style.
It's better because it's this expressive.
It's better because he got it done.
It would have been, you know what?
Sure.
Maybe some people would have liked it better
if it was in the flash style, in the, in the track itself.
But guess what?
No one would have liked it because it never would have come out.
It never would have happened.
Yeah.
That's, that's it.
Brian Leo Malley, I heard him say on, on like
form spring or something, he said like anything,
he didn't originate this quote, but I heard it from him.
It's like anything done is, is automatically better
than anything that's not done.
Like no matter how good it would have been,
no matter how like, you know, no matter how perfect the parts
of it that are done are, like if it's not done
and it's not out, it's nothing.
It's, and it's, and it's, it's worse than anything.
It's, it's worse than even the worst piece of trash
that's, that's done.
Wrapping it around to us, the endless war
was not like meticulously planned.
It was not like, oh, we have a grand vision for this video game.
You know, you know, let's start, let's start building the pieces.
No, it just was like, it was cranked out.
It's blossomed into this beautiful fucking
unreal, unparalleled discord server video game combination.
That you can play in your discord server for for free right now.
Click the link in the description.
This never would have happened if like, like, like you,
you, you'd return and clack and like, like crack, like, you know,
let's like spin like a few months, like cash out this game
and then we'll have a big reveal, you know.
Let's get it like perfect before release.
Let's make sure it's absolutely perfect
before we, we put it out there.
Like, you know, let's polish every single second.
No, no thing you, you can improvise.
No, I mean, I, I mean, I knew if I knew,
I knew if I did anything like that with it,
then it just wouldn't happen.
I knew it had to be as bare bones as possible to ever exist.
She's so mad.
You know, well, you know, I don't know.
I don't want to seem too condescending because like,
I know what it's like.
It's like a natural, it's a natural feeling to have, I think.
It's, it's just like, you know, you want your art to be good.
You, you want to have the things you put out be nice.
What I'm saying is not that's like, that you're stupid for thinking that.
I'm saying that like, you have to understand that
that desire will kill you negative.
Yeah, it will kill you.
Instead of you putting out like, you think, okay,
if I do this, everything I put out will be perfect.
Instead, it's, you'll never put anything out.
That's what that means.
It seems like a great idea.
It seems intuitively great.
It's intuitively, like, of course I should work really hard
and make this thing good.
Like, what do you, what do you say?
And I shouldn't do that.
What the fuck?
It's, it's not even about making it not good.
It's just about recognizing.
If you think that, then like, yeah.
I mean, your priorities, your priorities are like,
about what is good, are probably like wrong.
You know, I don't, oh shit.
I don't know if it's like, I can't, I can't say like,
oh, these people.
Well, I mean, about, oh, I can say it, about low art.
Like, I don't think low art is just an idiot who doesn't understand.
I mean, he, he cranks out videos on a weekly basis.
So I don't understand why it, when it comes to this thing, he,
like, why did he bother?
Like, why did he bother like, going through all the effort
to like, do this with me?
If he's just going to like, leave it to language?
I don't know.
It doesn't matter.
It probably doesn't make any different.
Even if it never came out, nothing would probably happen.
It just annoys me.
I don't know what the point was.
I don't know what the, oh shit.
The, the, the reason I get so mad is I'm sure everyone
with a function brain can understand this because I've been there
because I know what it's like and I know what it, what,
I know the exact feelings that you go through and you just think,
well, like, like this is really important to me.
I want to make it as good as possible.
And I, listen, it's, it makes sense.
Yeah, but it's wrong.
It's wrong.
It just is wrong.
You just have to recognize when you think that making it,
perfect and good will often just mean that it doesn't happen at all.
And if you really care about it, then your number one goal
should be expressing the idea you want to express.
Should be making sure that it does happen.
Yeah.
I mean, you know, perfect is the enemy of the good and all that and all that shit.
I mean, I'm sure, I'm sure you've felt that before.
Sure.
All the time.
Um, part of a, I mean, I don't know, I mean, I mean, when it comes to,
I mean, I've definitely improved my speed.
I mean, this probably sounds ridiculous because for so long,
I wasn't putting out vapor's pages, but now that I am making them again,
I can tell that like, I've definitely improved my speed.
And a lot of that has just come from knowing what things are not worth focusing on
and not worth like, you know, devoting a huge amount of time and energy.
In Vapors One, on like the first page, there's like a small panel in the bottom right
that has like, you can see like their room.
You can see like their room in the background.
And I spent like hours, I spent like hours drawing.
Okay.
It's going to be embarrassing because it's not even that detailed,
but I spent a lot of time like focusing on that panel.
It's when they're sitting across from each other.
Yeah.
Not nice.
And there's the dot dot dot.
I spent a long time on the details of their room.
And that panel is so tiny that you can't even see it.
Yeah.
It's a, there's a complete waste, complete waste.
I mean, I mean, something like this, like it obviously comes from passion, right?
Like it's obviously like you want to illustrate this room because you feel like it's important.
You feel like it, like a room can say a lot about a character, you know,
it can say a lot about what these people are like.
So you feel like it makes sense.
But yeah, what, what, what matters more to a character, what their room looks like,
or them like writing dialogue and them having like an expression
and you being able to show that expression to other people.
Yeah.
That, that's really matters.
That is.
And that's, uh, and that's what I mean.
That's what, and Vapors one took like a really long time.
Vapors three has taken a really long time,
but not because I've been spending a ton of time like on meticulous details.
It's been because I've been working on other stuff and putting it off.
Um, uh, different problem.
We're not to say, well, might to some people sound like a backhanded compliment,
but because like that's a societal problem.
That's like people value like perfection.
The abstract ideal perfection way too much.
I like, uh, respect people like a digi so much because they, they are able to put out content.
They are able to just get an idea and execute it without having that,
that perfectionist mindset of having to just like toil over it endlessly.
If I had done that podcast with digi, it would have been out months ago.
Yeah.
Just it would have been out the day.
It would have been out the day.
Yeah.
I don't care what kind of cool editing you're going to put on that podcast.
He's not going to put any cool editing on it.
It's, it's the, that's the thing.
I know that he's not even gonna,
he's probably just going through it to like edit out like gaps or breaths or something.
And he's wrong to do so.
He is, he is un-
I mean that, I mean, that's just ridiculous to, to like, to procrastinate this long and taking-
And I think that's probably what EZK from, um, fucking, uh, uh, Internet Dreamland was doing too.
Gotta take those breaths out.
No one's going to listen to it if there's breaths.
Fuck off.
I think what we're saying here could easily be like miscontrude to being like just shit things out.
Just, just like, you know-
Yeah, that's literally what I'm saying.
That's literally what I'm saying.
It's what I'm saying too, but it just sounds wrong to some people.
And I don't really know how to express it in a way that won't, like,
I think that like, you sort of like, it's one of those lessons you might have to learn the hard way in a way
where you might not like get it right now while we're explaining to you and you might think,
oh, listen to these guys, they're, they're just, you know, they're, they're upset that whatever
projects they were working on hasn't come up and now they're trying to just say like, oh, shit it out.
But I, I am telling you, young artist commenting, you'll feel this one day.
You definitely will.
When, uh, one of your projects takes a year to come out.
Fuck.
When it's taken a week, then you'll know what we're talking about.
That's how I feel.
That's how I feel about Vapors 3.
That's how I feel about, uh, everything.
It's not, uh, arm retrieval.
Hmm.
What a nightmare.
Ben, you want to do a suicide pact?
Hmm.
Do I want to?
Yes.
Will I?
Maybe.
Sell me.
That has to be perfect, you know.
It has to be perfect.
Yeah, he's got to be, I don't want to mess this one up.
Yeah, yeah.
This one, you really, is worth, is worth the extra time.
Uh, hmm.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Hey, I just killed the cannonball rug, by the way.
Yeah, I hope, I knew you'd be happy for me.
Yeah, it's only when you, when you, when you kill that guy in the White House,
you know what I'm trying to say, dude?
Oh god, this fucking mimic.
Chest was a fucking mimic.
Don't worry about it.
It's fine.
It's fine, yeah.
No, I'm not gonna be fine.
A mimic?
What, what, what a ripoff of nuclear throne.
This game is a nuclear throne ripoff.
Oh, but I got a plunger.
I got a plunger out of the deal.
So it's fine, it's good.
God, I hope this, I hope I can buy a blank.
Yes, okay, because I need, I need two blanks to get into the rat's nest.
I'm going to the rat's nest, by the way.
Listen.
Oh, are you, are you gonna kill the ratting rat?
Are you finally gonna do it?
Uh, I mean, that's the plan.
Here's the thing.
God willing.
I, I have, okay, I have gotten to the rat before.
When you get to the rat, there's a two-phase battle followed by,
and I only just discovered this.
There is something else beyond the two-phase battle.
I have died on the second phase of his battle every time, except once.
One time I made it to the, the extra thing, and that was a real fucking trip.
And I'm sorry you're gonna miss it.
It's, it's, it's a sight.
It's a sight to behold.
It, it technically still counts as winning if you just beat the two-phase battle.
Like, but like, I don't know.
I'm sure something else happens if you do the other thing.
And I don't know what it is, but we'll see.
Who, no one knows what it could possibly be.
No one knows it could be.
Um, yeah.
How many of the comments do you think are gonna be, uh,
heavily criticizing your, your gameplay here?
Not that many, because I'm doing pretty good, I think.
That's good.
Ben, you, as a self-employed, self-made man,
who has no obligations to do anything ever in his entire life.
Yeah, true.
What are you gonna do this summer?
Does your life change with the seasons?
Do you feel like it impacts you whatsoever?
Not a, you know, well, not, well, I tell you what, Munchie,
I've fallen into a real funk lately.
And I think it's partially related to the season,
because during the winter I was so unmotivated to, uh, like go outside,
because it was fucking bitterly cold.
But like, I, I didn't, I didn't play, I mean, sometimes I did.
It wasn't like I never went out, but like, especially recently,
I've been, like, I haven't been playing Pokemon Go,
I haven't really been leaving the house very much,
I've just been working a lot.
And, uh, I'm thinking that I should probably take advantage
of the changing seasons now.
I mean, now it's, now we're full on into spring,
so there's no excuse.
Should probably take advantage of the changing seasons or whatever
to, uh, do something about that,
to get out there a little bit more,
get fucking, stop being such a fucking recluse or whatever.
To shut in?
Yeah, anyway, but I think that, so in that sense,
it might have some, uh, effect on me.
Is there anything that you particularly do outside,
or you just want the fresh air, which I think,
I think is a noble goal in it.
Pokemon Go is the only thing that I do outside.
So it's invaluable.
I, I, I, I found a mini-
Oh, it's really bad, I really fucked up.
I really fucked up.
Oh yeah, I ain't gonna get the ratty rat.
There's no way I'm gonna get the ratty rat.
Oh, come on, Ben.
That, you know, one job, one job.
I, that was a complete clusterfuck.
Uh, since, since I'll be living there soon,
I figured that I should, uh, try and come up with some, uh,
you know, things to do in the city,
because, uh, obviously it's fun to walk around
and play Pokemon Go, but, uh, I, uh,
also want to have some sort of maybe, uh,
a thing I, uh, want to go to, or, you know, like a vent.
Uh, I've been getting,
digging the idea of like a, uh,
maybe a weekly or a bi-weekly club meetup thing.
And I found, uh, stuff for, like that for,
for comic books in the Boston area,
like the Boston Comics Roundtable.
I know about that.
I, um, I used to go to it, um, in fact,
I've been meaning to go to it for like a year,
and I just haven't, and I don't know why.
Uh, it sounds, it, it seems like it would be great for you.
Wouldn't it?
I used to really like it.
Again, I don't know why I haven't gone back.
It's like every, I just put it off
and put it off and put it off.
Um, I meant to do.
You want to make sure it's perfect when you go there.
That's exactly.
You want to make sure it's a, it's a perfect occasion.
Yeah, that's right.
That's, that's, that's the thing.
Or some, it's something like that.
I feel like shit now.
Now I'm remembering that I have, uh,
failed to avail myself of this thing.
Yeah, I used to have a lot of fun going to that.
Uh, did it accomplish anything?
No, it doesn't matter.
Got me out of the house.
That's the only thing that matters in this life.
What, when did you stop going to it?
If I, when I, when I moved to Digi's.
Oh, so you, uh, you have a lot more comments under your belt.
I'm sure you'd have a lot more social.
Not, not as many as I should.
Well, whatever.
Yeah.
People will look at you and say,
Oh my God, it's a song to you guy.
And then you'll say, I also draw comics.
And I'll go, what?
Yeah, I guess.
Uh, I guess so.
I mean, I was all, I mean, even before like,
you know, like two years ago when I used to go there,
there were people that,
I remember there were people, there was,
there was like one guy who like knew who Digi was
and was like stunned that I knew him or whatever.
Oh, it's embarrassing.
Cut that part.
I hate saying what I just said.
Cut that, wait, what, why?
I don't know.
It's fucking lame.
What, what, no, why?
Why is it, why is it embarrassing?
Oh, I knew, I knew a famous person.
Uh, that's fucking stupid.
What a, what a, what a shitty thing to like,
make any difference at all in your life.
You know what I mean?
I know, I, you know, so, so it's, it's easy when you're in your,
to get starstruck easily.
I feel, you know, if you like someone,
if you like, if you watch someone's YouTube videos
and you like them a lot and someone says they know them in person,
well, that's, that's, that's crazy.
For a second there, you know, you're like, oh my God, we'll be delighted.
Shut up, shut up.
I get it.
Yeah, I get it.
Um, but it makes me mad and I don't like it.
Fair.
Did I tell you about me going to code for Boston?
Did I ever give you follow-up on that?
I, I told you about what it is, right?
You mentioned it, you mentioned it,
you didn't give me any follow-up on it.
No.
When, when I, I was a bit, part of this,
just wanting to Google search things to do in Boston,
like meetups and stuff, I found this code for America brigade.
And it is a group, an organization dedicated to making a civic code,
which is a very nebulous concept to say the least.
I don't, yeah.
But I was intrigued by it.
I thought, what is that?
Well, I guess I'll have to find out myself.
So, uh, I, I went to one last time it was in Boston before I got a cold
and we weren't able to record Lego Star Wars.
You're wondering why we aren't doing Lego Star Wars right now,
because it got a cold and, uh,
You couldn't record it before it was.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I remember.
Uh, what, hey, when was that?
When did that trip end?
It ended like, more, no, wait.
Did we, did we hung out with once while you were here that time, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Who did that trip end?
Oh God, I have no clue.
I have no clue when that ended.
Sometime at least two months ago, I think.
At least.
Whatever.
Doesn't matter.
Okay.
Uh, but yeah, it sucked and it was a nightmare.
Anyway, I went, I went to code for Boston with, uh, with Ethan.
He was in town, so from our, or from RBCKCon.
And, uh, we went there and, uh, it was, uh,
I didn't really know what to expect because I was getting mixed signals.
On one hand, it seems like it'd be one of those things that's a
similar serious like, you know, we're making, we're improving the community with our code.
We're, we're, we're updating the government to government 2.0.
Literally a thing they've said.
Uh, and so, you know, it's, it's, um, you might think it's somewhat a high brown,
but then also plastered everywhere on the website was come get free pizza.
Come to Cove for Boston and get free pizza, free pizza night.
We come for Cove for Boston.
And I was like, okay.
Give me, give me, give me on a cauliflower crust and I'm there.
Cove for Boston.
Dude.
Wait.
Important, important, important.
Guess who's Keto?
My hero.
It's my hero, Arlo.
Really?
Arlo is a, Arlo is a Keto puppet.
I saw him posting about, uh, low-carb red crusts.
Or, I'm sorry, look, I saw him posting about no-carb pizza crusts the other day.
I was floored.
Famous for that, uh, that, that, that, that thumbnail of a video he made that was sadly
deleted, uh, endless war, boring to shit.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
That's the name of the show.
We mass flagged him and got it taken down.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh, good times, good times.
I can't believe, I can't believe puppets, puppets first of all can be Keto.
I, I replied to his tweet about the pizza crust and I was like, Arlo, I don't know
you were Keto.
I didn't even know you had him a tablet or something.
Yeah.
Um, you know, learned, learned something new every day.
You do.
Anyway, there's, there's two ways that Cove for Boston go.
It's either just like a bunch of hipsters, ideas man, you know, it up.
An eating pizza or it's a real shit.
I wanted to take my chances and hope that it was the hipsters ideas manning so that I
could possibly, uh, I don't know, somehow use it to my advantage.
Maybe somehow manipulate them into a plane in this war somehow.
This actually ties into many things in my life.
I'm going to do a story later about me going up to LA for a premiere of an independent movie
where my also goal was solely to get people in LA to play in this war.
But, uh, that that's basically the only, uh, operated, like the only thought in my mind
is how can I get people with clout to play this game?
Anyway, I go, I go to Cove for Boston, get some free pizza.
And, uh, immediately to my, uh, my shock and my horror, it's real people actually
accomplishing things and my, my, my influence is, uh, worthless.
So, so it's, it's unfortunately just, um, me kind of like it's, it, there's a couple of
rooms each have their own, uh, project assigned to them.
It's a bunch of people.
There's some ideas manning, but it's mostly just people working in silence.
So imagine me and Ethan going there to have, to, you know, just to have a good time just to,
you know, see, see things that just, you know, have, have a good time, party up and code for
Boston. And then, uh, we're shuffled into an office space where people are just silently
coding and somebody asked me, Hey, what are they coding?
Uh, well, one of them is, uh, one of them was, uh, you had to know Python, uh, but also know
the Alexa Amazon API is there making it so you can ask Alexa, like, I don't know,
fucking like, like something about health insurance.
I don't even remember something stupid like that.
Sick. Yeah.
Uh, the only cool thing was, uh, blocking.
There was a blocking Pokemon go app.
You know what blocking is?
Uh, you've told me before, but I don't remember.
It's, uh, it's a combination of jogging and picking up trash.
It's a Scandinavian thing.
What does it stand for?
It's like a portmanteau, right?
Yeah, it's a portmanteau.
It, it, it's, it's some fucking here.
I'm going to get it right now.
It's, uh, some like Danish word, I think with jogging, some shit, some fucking,
some stupid non-English word that I don't even care about.
It doesn't even matter.
But anyway, there was an app for that and, uh, that was, that was at least that one.
There were people who, uh, were ideas manning it pretty hard.
It was pretty in its early stages.
I got to watch them make a reading file, but other than that, it was a pretty boring event.
Yeah. Um, Boston Comics Roundtable.
You know, it, it was, I don't know.
I guess I liked, it was, it was weird.
There was like, you would go there and there would be like, sort of,
people would sit around and like, they would talk about like events, right?
Cause they have, they have sort of a community that does events.
Like they will have like tables at like local conventions and stuff, which is good.
That's, that's all pretty cool.
Um, they, they would just kind of discuss what's going on in their community.
Like sometimes they would have, there was one time they had like a guest speaker
who like spoke in like a lecture hall.
They used to meet at like a, the downtown, a library near Harvard Square.
I don't know if they still meet there, if they've changed venues, doesn't matter.
But they would do that.
And then you would, like before the meetings proper started,
you would post your like latest, like anything you'd drawn that week,
or something you'd drawn that week, you would post it on like a court board.
And then everyone would walk around and sort of, uh,
just critique each other's like stuff for the week.
And it was really cool.
Yeah.
That sounds really sick as hell, actually.
And it was a lot of, um, you know, it was a, it was a big spread.
There were a bunch of like college kids, uh, there were a few of those.
There were, um, you know, there were a bunch of older people,
like, like maybe middle-aged or verging on middle-aged,
people who were like veterans or whatever.
There wasn't a lot, there wasn't a lot in the middle.
There was, it was, it was mostly like those two,
I guess there were some kind of in the middle, like 30 something or whatever.
But it was a lot of the kids there, a lot of the college kids were like really bad.
But everyone was, everyone was polite about it, you know.
You know, everyone offered, everyone offered a constructive criticism,
no matter how good or terrible you were.
Uh, just, you know, that's fine.
What, what, what kind of stuff happens in it exactly?
Like, like, what, like, what is like the, the main thing that you do there?
Is it just shoot the shit and try and network?
It's mostly, you know, you convene about events, shoot the shit, network, critique each other's
work, go out for burgers afterwards.
Oh, burgers, I sold, sold.
Yeah, um, I have, uh, I feel, you know, every day, I don't know why,
I don't know why I haven't done it.
But every day I know in my heart that I'm fucking up by not going back, and I haven't.
Tell me why.
Look in my soul and explain it to me.
You can surely, listen, Ben, I had no idea how like big
Boston Comics roundtable is.
Maybe like 25, 30 people.
You can surely become a sultan there.
I, I, I believe that you have the ability to make people gravitate around you and become a sultan.
I think you can do it.
I was, hmm, I wasn't, I wasn't a sultan.
You could be one now though.
I mean, I was, uh, I don't know.
I don't know.
You know, maybe I'm afraid of, I think maybe I'm afraid that like I'll go and nothing will have changed.
What do you mean?
Like, I'll go and maybe, and I feel like I've been doing this whole comics thing and art thing
and internet thing for like, you know, two or three years since then, and I'll go back and, uh,
it won't be any different.
And I'll think like, what was any of it for?
You know, I'm still just a schmuck.
I'm still just one of these schmucks.
Oh, oh, so you're afraid you won't be sultan?
In fact, you might be a peon still.
Yeah. Oh God. Fuck.
I think that's, I think that's it.
I think I figured it out.
You also, you seem, you seem to have a, you seem to have an insecurity complex about comics, Ben.
You went to mice and you're just like, oh God, I'm just, I'm just a cattle.
I'm, I'm just a sheep to be herded here.
I need to be behind the booths.
Yeah. I hated, I hated not being behind the booths.
What's so wrong with being just another, another citizen of comic land here, of webcomic land?
You know, you'll get your just desserts one day, but for now, but you know,
you got to toil a little bit.
You got to a little bit in the sand before you can ride this to the gate and prekeat yourself.
No, that's not, I don't agree with your framing of the issue there.
Yeah.
Toil is fine. I'm okay with toil.
It's not, the problem is not toil.
It's not like, oh, I have to work and these, and these heroes, these champions, like lorded over me behind it.
It, it was that I, I just didn't, I didn't want to go there to consume stuff.
I wanted to go there to, you know, pedal stuff. I don't know. I wanted,
it's, it, this is not even like a hierarchy thing.
Like, oh, I'm lower on the totem pole, although that is part of it.
It's that like, I was there for the wrong purpose.
I see.
Does that make sense?
No, I feel like what you understand, like you, you were going there not because you particularly like
loved comics in concept, but because these are other comic artists.
I kind of want to rub elbows with them.
And I kind of want to, if not like get people to literally buy Ben St. Vapors,
just talk to other people in the trade, maybe not, maybe not collaborate directly,
but just at least, you know, get in there.
A bit, there's a little more to it.
It was like being, being there as a, as a guest, as a, as a consumer was like,
I wanted to be like, no, listen, you don't understand.
If this is a mistake, yeah, yeah, that's exactly it.
I wanted to be like, this is a mistake.
This is just an accident.
I'm supposed to be on the other side.
Listen, I'm not, I, please, like, don't, don't, don't look at me like these other freaks.
I actually do things like you.
I promise.
Yeah.
Okay.
There you go.
I, I, I get you.
I'm thinking, I'm thinking, what if, what if there are more people like that in that crowd?
What if instead of, well, that's part of it, that's part of the existential horror of it,
Munchie, is that I think probably there's lots of them.
Mm hmm.
And I don't know if maybe they don't feel it as acutely as me or maybe they do.
And we're all equally frustrated to be there.
But, but then if that's the case, then why not turn on each other?
Why, why not, why not find some solace in the fact that there are other people like that here?
And you know, it's just, it's, it's almost as though the, not the people behind the booths
are, I don't want to say luckiness as they haven't worked.
I'm not locked in there with them.
They're locked in here with me.
Yeah, yeah, in a way.
It's, it's not that they're a, they, you are a consumer, like it's a binary system,
either you're a creator or a consumer.
It's just that, you know, maybe you are blending in with the sheep.
You're a wolf in sheep's clothing in a way.
And then maybe there are other wolves, wolves in sheep clothing.
You can interact with them and maybe talk to them and find comradery.
I mean, in your, in your, well, well, it feels to me,
like if you were really a wolf in that scenario, you wouldn't be wearing,
why would you wear it?
Why would you be wearing sheep's clothing?
Like any, any, I don't want to, I don't want to hang out with these pervert wolves that
like dressing up as sheep.
Yeah, okay.
I think our, our metaphor is getting muddled here a little bit.
I feel like the game, I feel like, I feel like they were muddled as soon as they left my
mouth, but you know what, that's fine.
Um, I actually speak, speaking of that.
Actually now is the time for soon anyway.
We'll be the time to register at a table at mice.
So I gotta do that.
Oh, what's the requirement of that?
Is that, is that just to first come, first serve?
And if you're just anyone who's anyone or even just like asked nicely, you can get in.
I, I don't know.
It might be.
It might, I mean, there are problems.
I mean, there's probably some like priority people, like maybe like certain people who
tabled successfully at like previous events or probably people with clout like Casey
Green or whatever, he was there.
Um, like I'm sure, or Abby Howard or whatever, like I'm sure they would be like, I'm sure
they wouldn't be turned away already.
Yeah.
But maybe it might just be, fuck, it might just be first come, first serve.
Let me ask you this bit.
Yeah.
All right.
Two questions.
First of all, would you consider comics to be your main thing slash main Colin like thing
you want to present yourself as the most thing I want to present myself as the most?
Yeah, definitely.
Like a comics artist.
Okay.
Yeah, definitely.
How much do you read or interact with the independent comic scene just in general,
like webcomics, Boston local, just at all?
Almost none.
That's, that's what I figured.
Yeah.
Is that a problem?
Cause I know.
Probably, probably.
Okay.
A lot of, I have been thinking about this a lot.
The thing about online communities, thinking about how I miss the old fandom days,
which I'm like, yeah, yeah, whatever it is matter.
But I don't have a, a interest that I have where I feel like I know what other people
with the interest have, which feel like I have a lot of interest and I know the interest
themselves was pretty deeply, but I don't really know for instance, like for instance,
I don't really know a lot about like maybe the, the homesick community, for instance,
or something more broad.
Like I don't really know a lot about like the podcast community or just things that
like I do and sort of like almost like my livelihood in a way depends on.
I don't really have a sense of like what the community is.
Like, like, like I watch other podcasts.
Do I like know anything about how like other people view said podcasts?
Have I ever been in a red discussion, a forum discussion, a tweet on Twitter?
Have I ever seen anything like that?
You know, no, not really.
I mean, I don't know if there is something like that for podcasts.
Exactly.
Well, okay, well, sure.
But you get what I'm trying to say.
Like, I totally get what you're trying to say.
Yeah.
I felt that way about comics.
The comics, I feel that way as well.
The comics community, as I have seen it, it's really weird.
And I don't think I get it.
It's really weird.
What?
What do you, what do you like?
Well, okay.
What's weird about it?
Okay.
It, it just, you know, I mean, maybe I should try and give another shot.
Maybe, maybe I didn't like it before because I had no like cloud.
I had like very little work under my belt.
And it, and it wasn't like, and that's why it wasn't working out or whatever.
It just, it all feels like people just sort of like buying each other's shit.
Like, like artists all just like buying each other's books.
And like, that's, it's like a bunch of amateurs.
It's like a, just like a bunch of amateurs just like barely keeping each other afloat
with their own money.
That's how it felt like to me.
Well, what's wrong with that?
I hate it.
Yeah.
Okay.
Is that, is that the goal?
Is, is the goal of it to like make shit that like just you and your fellow
members of this community are interested in?
I don't think, I don't think that's why they do it.
I don't think that's the goal.
I think that's a byproduct of them wanting like thems.
I would say almost it's, I think like, I can empathize with a lot in almost like a selfish way
where it's like, I want my comic to be successful.
Not just like monetarily.
I like, I want people to know who the fuck I am.
How do I do that other than collaborate and to like, to mix and mingle with other comic
artists to get their audience into my stuff as well?
But, okay.
What, yeah, I get that, but what if everyone that you're commingling with, everyone's
audience is just the same other people, other people that make web comics?
Hmm.
I mean, sure.
But I don't know if that's, okay.
When you're working on the internet, I feel like that sort of thing is almost like,
like there's no way there's going to be one big circle for like the idea of comics.
Like, like the concept of a web comic, you know?
There's no, there's not one big circle.
There are like several small circles.
I completely understand the idea of wanting to like, just sort of like get the word out.
It's like, I don't, I don't think I'm communicating this well.
Cause like I'm not saying, it's not that I'm saying like, why are these people collaborating
with each other?
Like that's not the problem.
I get that the problem is just like, I don't know that I just, I see people, I see people in
these little comics communities, you know, sort of all it's like, you know, like, like
retweeting each other's kick starters and stuff and whatever.
And like, it feels very insular and like it's not, like it's, it feels very like circle jerky
in a way.
Circle jerky a little bit.
But like, in a way that's like not even their fault.
Like, yeah, maybe they're circle jerky.
It's like pathetic.
I don't want to say it like that.
Like, maybe like, it's like, yeah, there's circle jerking.
But I mean, who else is going to jerk them off?
Maybe, maybe the problem is there's nobody else is going to jerk these people off.
You know, maybe the audience just isn't there.
And that's very discouraging.
And would you say it's discouraging in a way where it like it makes you confront your own
mortality in a way?
Or it's like, oh, if this is all I can ever aspire to is just being like, like other people
also who are commissars liking my stuff.
Is that what you mean?
Yeah, that that one, that one.
Like, I don't know.
I think I said before that I'm not married.
I'm not married to the idea of like, comics being the thing.
Like, if I could do something with like a similar skill set, but in a different format
that would have like a bigger readership be more popular, I wouldn't have any problem
with doing that.
Um, and the web comics community sort of sort of smells to me like one that is very limited
in its readership.
And I don't know if I'm right about that because like there are comics that are successful that
people do read, but also by your own admission, it's you don't, it's not like something you're
fully invested in.
You would like know if like, like, you know, you weren't that involved with it.
That's, I think you're conflating.
I mean, I, I didn't say that.
I mean, I think I know where, I think I know how it works and everything.
I didn't like, I'm not invested in that as like, it has to be this or like, I'm not invested
in the format specifically.
Um, my, my, I mean, there are comics that people read that have like a decent readership.
But they're mostly on, they're mostly on things like, um, they're networks like
HiveWorks.
Actually, HiveWorks is like the only one I can even think of.
But like most, I feel like most comics that anyone actually reads are like on something
like HiveWorks or they're like print, print comics or something like that, or they're just
totally independent and like word of mouth has gotten them around like Ogloff or something like
that.
And like being independent and being known, like that, you can't make that happen.
That's, you can't, you can't manufacture that.
Um, you know, what are you even supposed to do about it?
I don't know.
Getting into something like HiveWorks, well, I tried once and it didn't work.
Um, and I should probably try again at some point.
Um, but you know, I don't know.
That seems like a weird, difficult nut to crack.
And also seems sort of, it's sort of like a, it seems just like a less embarrassing
microcosm of the webcomics community in its own way.
Like it has the same general atmosphere, just like, I mean, there are plenty of comics
that nobody reads on HiveWorks too, um, for instance.
And then print comics, I don't fucking have any clue about that.
I don't think I'm going to get like a, I've been thinking about this.
Um, the idea of like having a job, the idea that of like a publisher like paying me to
produce content on a schedule seems ridiculous, just seems ridiculous, like a, like a stupid
thing to even think about.
Like, I mean, I think, I think those jobs do exist, but I think
they are, they do not, they're not being created.
I don't know.
It doesn't, it doesn't feel like anyone is being hired to do that.
And like professionals say, like, like old professionals say, like these days,
just go indie, just, just kickstart.
Don't, don't, don't go through a traditional like publisher.
Like that's what, that's what I was confused for a second point.
Yeah.
Okay.
I thought, I thought that was like a comment from, uh, Ben, uh, Communism Saint, uh, just
like saying like the idea of the jobs were ridiculous, but you're saying like it's hard,
like, like, they're mythical in a way where it's like, how could you ever land one?
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah.
Okay.
Like who, like who's, who's hiring for that?
Uh, no one.
And nobody wants, I mean, I'm not, I don't have no audience, but I don't have the kind of
audience that like, that like a company would hire me because like, oh wow, this guy's going
to bring in a lot of, a lot of people with him, a lot of readership.
You know, yeah, I, I, I totally get you, dude.
I feel like it's, I, I mean, I would chalk up for me, I don't know if you would consider
this way, but I would just consider it an experience on my part that I don't really
know how the hiring process works for a lot of things.
Like, I, like, I, I mean, I agree with you that I have no idea how like the first thing
to do, but how I would even like approach a like, like, for, like, for instance, like,
like, like everyone who's published a, a, a comic has just like,
uh, well, what am I trying to say?
I'm trying to say that, like, okay, you think about a, a Brian Leo Malley, you think, okay,
how'd he get Scott, Scott Pilgrim published?
Well, he went to Oni Press and he had already had some work under his belt that he'd published.
And so he got, how'd he publish the first one?
No clue.
Like, was he just fresh off the like college or something?
I mean, I, I know, I know a bit about this.
Do you, what, how'd he do it?
Well, he had a comic called, um, Lost at Sea.
Yeah, he had a book.
That one, I, he had like done, okay, I don't know the exact order that these events occurred in,
but he had done Lost at Sea.
I think before that he had done some like strips.
He had done some like comic strips on like some website.
That were sort of the precursor to Lost at Sea.
I don't know what the deal was with those.
He had, I think this was post Lost at Sea pre Scott Pilgrim.
He had a deal with Marvel and Marvel had him draw a like Spider-Man Children's book.
Had him illustrate like a Spider-Man Children's book.
And I, in like an interview or something, he said that like,
that paid really well and like let him like concentrate on like his other stuff.
And, uh, boy, I wish I, I was thinking about that.
I was like, boy, God, I wish I could get paid to illustrate a fucking Spider-Man Children's book.
I'll bet, I'll bet it paid like crazy.
I, I'm sure there's like a clear, I'm just doing, I'm just like looking at his Wikipedia page right
now. It seems like, yeah, he was doing, he was just doing like small, small stuff at like a comics
studio. He was just doing the smallest stuff and doing like lettering and behind the scenes
stuff. And I guess you just have to like, you know, go somewhere.
I mean, imagine, imagine getting a job as a comic book letterer today as like a letterer or like a
fucking, I don't know, colorist. I mean, I guess those jobs exist.
Do, I don't know, do they even exist? They probably exist in some form.
But again, it feels mythical. It feels ridiculous.
I feel like, I don't know. I think we're talking out of our ass.
I like, surely like there's, there's answers to these questions.
I don't know. I've just, I've never looked it up. And I don't know. I don't even think I'm
complaining about it really. I, I, uh, I'm complaining about it.
Oh, oh, Ben, one, one day you'll be behind, you'll be behind the booth.
You'll be behind the booth. I can be behind the booth. Being behind the book is easy.
It was just an accident of history that it didn't happen.
It was a mistake. It was a glitch in the matrix.
It was. That's exactly what it was.
As a matter of fact. Yeah.
Ben, let's go to comics, boss comics round table. Let's like go together. Let's like do it.
Yeah. I mean, I should probably just go like this.
You go, go right now.
Just like, why not? I think they're still on Tuesday.
I'll check right now. I'll check right now.
You only, you won't even have deniability. You didn't, you didn't check it.
Okay. Thursday, 7 p.m. Thursday is okay.
Are they still at that library?
Is it the same way?
They're at Leslie college of art and design,
Lunder hall room 003, uh, near Porter square in Cambridge.
Huh. I wonder if that's a downgrade.
The library they used to meet at was pretty nice.
Open all and all are welcome to matter.
Your level of interest or experience in comics, beginners to experience.
You don't have to give a fuck.
Yeah.
Okay. We're talking about local comic events.
Look at each other's work in progress and generally socialize about the comics theme.
So this is what I wanted.
That's exactly what I wanted.
I just wanted people, ideas, man.
And just being like, yeah.
So I got this like idea about like this comic that like I'll make, you know,
one day when I'm just 30 years from now.
When I, you know, when I'm good, you know,
after I practice a whole bunch and you know,
Yeah. Yeah. After it's perfect.
After I really iron out all the flaws in the story.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Discussing.
Perfect.
Um, it sounds really cool.
I really want to go.
I don't know.
Okay. I feel like I do get what you're trying to say,
but it's a little bit insular, a little bit circle, jerky.
I honestly feel bad saying that because like,
what's the alternative that I'm proposing?
What would be better?
What would I do in their place?
I don't know.
I, I, I get your saying.
I don't know if I, I don't know if I, like if I feel the same way.
I feel like I, I don't know.
Honestly, like I think the only difference is that I have like the PCP and other like
internet stuff as like secondary creative outlets.
Like I'm sure for a lot of these people,
comics are just what they do and that's it.
And like, you know, nothing wrong with that, but I don't know.
Let me ask you this Ben.
Do you think, have you ever reflected upon that effect?
Like, do you think that's bad almost in a way that you are doubly down on one thing?
Yes, probably.
Yeah. I'm, I'm a jack of all trades and a master of none.
And you know, they say that to get, that to become a master,
you got to just buckle down on that one thing and you shouldn't do what I do.
Yeah. You shouldn't, you should, you have to specialize to become great.
And I haven't specialized.
I've cast like a really wide net and you know, mistake.
I think about, especially now that I'm staring down college.
Maybe I'm like, what do I want to do with my life?
Maybe, maybe if I had like done nothing but comics,
maybe I could have made some headway in the comic sphere,
like more than I actually have.
Because you know, I mean, what, what, what like actual comics headway have I made?
Like I had my Kickstarter that did pretty well, great.
But like, I mean, what does that, what does that mean in terms of like other opportunities?
I mean, well, I don't know, maybe it could mean something.
I don't know.
No one's fucking come to me with any job offers or anything.
Is that what they do?
Is that what's supposed to happen?
People email you and say, hey, I got a job for you?
Maybe. I don't know.
How could I know?
I think about a lot.
Like what do I want to do with my life?
Like what, what skills should I be developing right now?
I've had a whole, I've literally themed the year based around,
I want to do more with my life.
I want to learn more things.
I've been learning to animate.
I've been learning to play the trumpet more.
I've been doing a lot of things to try and broaden my horizons and get more skills.
But honestly, like, should I be doing that?
I think about like the skills that I want to use to like farther my life.
What do I want with my life?
I want to illustrate.
I want to, I want to, I want to do visual art.
And so animating works for that.
But just playing the trumpet?
No. Does, does, does having new podcast series?
No, not really.
I guess you could maybe argue that quick draws help with that because it's about drawing.
But that's sort of a roundabout way.
It's mostly my, my actual, like what I'm doing for that is I'm editing a video series.
It's, there's no reason to be doing a lot of things I do.
But it's just, it's so hard not to.
I mean, I think it's, I think most people would say it's a good thing to be broadly
experienced, you know, to have had a wide range of experiences in your life and such.
Sure. I don't disagree and I don't regret anything, of course.
But it's almost just, I feel like maybe I am wasting time in a way.
Maybe I should just be doubling down on, maybe I, maybe I should open up commissions again.
Maybe I, maybe I should just be doubling down on visual art in a way instead of
separating time to, maybe even like, maybe even something like R of CK.
Maybe I shouldn't even be, be trying to manage the community as much as I do now.
But I think about that and I think about like the reason to do so.
And it just feels like my life would be just so much duller if I did that.
I feel like there's such spice to having very interest and to being so,
like, even though it's not good for like, business, it feels good to be multi-faceted,
multi-faceted and like, not really easy to describe in a way where it's like,
yeah, I like that.
For instance, you, like, there's a lot of things that one could describe you as,
but it's hard to kind of like, succinctly do.
So like, you stream sometimes, okay, so you're like a Twitterer,
but you also do comics and, and, and different sorts of comics.
But you also like, do YouTube, but like, what kind of YouTube stuff do you do?
Well, you used to like, Pokemon Nuzlocs, but now you do like,
poo, any of the poo videos, but it'll usually do all this other stuff.
It's like, it's not really, you know,
you're sort of everything and therefore not really anything.
Yeah. And, uh, you know, that has a certain appeal for me, but I think it's, I mean,
I think it's bad, like business-wise, right?
Oh, definitely. Like, definitely, definitely.
Because, because what do you say?
Like, what's, what's the pitch?
Like, oh, Ben's saying, why should I, why should I support him on Patreon?
Well, he does.
And then you do a list of things that have almost nothing to do with each other.
It's like, maybe someone likes one of those things or two,
but what about all the other shit that I don't care about, you know?
Yeah. In a way, it's like, okay, making your business based upon the fact that you are a
personality is such a slippery, treacherous slope where some people can make it work really well.
But I feel they can only make it, they can only make it work well once they've already
established themselves with one trait.
For instance, you look at, you look at, you look at the top of the list, you look at PewDiePie.
That dude could do literally anything and have it be successful.
Yeah.
Because it does not matter what it is or even like the quality of it, it's just PewDiePie.
That's all that matters.
But how did he get that big?
Well, he was a video game, let's play, almost exclusively for a really long time.
Then he started vlogging, started to branch out.
But that kernel of him like developing that one skill of him,
him being in front of the camera and that of him playing video games,
he doesn't even like really do that much video game content as far as I know now.
It's just, he built up with that and then branched out into further things.
But I feel like with you and me, other people in the PCP and just, I mean, a lot of people at
large just are starting with, hey guys, it's me, you're supporting me, do, you know, whatever.
And I don't think people like want that.
I don't want, I don't think people want to like just run off the bat.
Like just now have to follow this random dude who does all these disparate random things.
I feel like our audience will disagree with that because that's what they do.
But I think they're like, you guys are the minority, you know.
Yeah.
People want people to be comic machines or want them to be video machines or want them to be
let's play machines.
They don't want them to be like, for instance, rapping all the way back to endless war,
first year SL version, happy birthday, ah.
Oh, right.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday, endless war, up all the way.
I would go up and give him a present.
But I'm afraid he would shoot his eye laser beam at me.
Yeah, that's the fable ultimate beam.
Mm hmm.
Like this is just not like this RCK.
Like this is an unwieldy mess.
No one wants to play this.
And I understand.
It makes sense.
I don't think the way we run.
I mean, the show is called Rowdy fuckers cop killers.
And I think like I thought about like there are ways we can better monetize it.
And there are ways that we can do that without changing the soul of the show.
But but honestly, like I don't care because I don't want to change RCK in any way that
would lessen it's it's it's like part of the appeal of RCK is the fact that it's very that
it's weird that it's unlike anything else in this war.
Just in concept, this this like the idea on its own of being a text based MMO in a discord
server they can play for three years for free using the link in the description on its own is
crazy.
But the fact that it is tied into this fucking weird avant-garde.
Let's play show is just is a whole nother layer.
It is.
So yeah.
And that's great.
And that's why and that's why it's cool.
And that's why I am you know fucking and that's why I'm a fucking nothing master.
What's the word?
A wasteoid.
Waste wasteoid.
Webazoid.
Go nowhere.
Fucking idiot.
It doesn't have a fucking real art job.
It was just it was just yeah yeah yeah great.
Sorry.
That was kind of that probably sounded kind of spiteful of me.
But like I do think that it is part of like it is an outgrowth of a kind of attitude that I have had
where like I don't care about I don't care about the monetizability of X idea.
I just care about the fact that I think it's interesting and I want to do it
and I'll make something that's not like anything else.
Doesn't appeal to a wide audience.
I don't care.
And um I don't know.
Is that was that a good idea.
I don't know.
Yeah.
I I don't like maybe maybe maybe munchie.
Maybe if I'd made some more maybe if I'd made a web comic about I don't know a little fucking it's
like you know it's like a dark it's like a dark modern take on like Little Red Riding Hood.
But it's like you know kind of like it's kind of creepy but it's cute like it's a cute creepy
kind of like you know it's like a little you know she meets like friends along the way it's
like a fantastical thing you know get that up on Hiveworks or whatever you know chugged away at
that and nothing else for like three years.
Maybe by now maybe by now I'd have like a low level like storyboarding job at like
you know the hub or something you know.
Well well I get what you're saying but I think you're even overthinking.
I think just take what you're doing now.
I mean it's just unpolished is the thing if you just spent more time working on the comics
that you'd already made if you just really tried to iron them out more than than you put them out.
Here's the thing.
I feel like there'd be way more successful you know.
I don't think I agree with you.
And maybe yeah maybe this is ego talking.
I don't think I need to get any better.
Like I don't think I need to.
Wait Ben you are aware that I was making a joke.
Wait what?
That I was saying you had to make the comics perfect.
Oh sorry.
That was obviously bad advice.
You're like I hear what you're saying.
I understand what you're trying to say.
Oh okay yeah you know what I was um that's that's me just that's just the tism.
That's just the tism talking.
Yeah um.
Continue what were you saying.
Anyway I was just saying like well I mean now my I was objecting to a
complaint that you didn't actually make sincerely so.
Cool.
I mean there's like I don't yeah I don't I don't know.
Say maybe maybe maybe if things you know maybe it could fucking maybe it could be like
have built up more of an audience have some fucking storyboarding job at some
animation studio or something uh probably be a lot more it would probably get me more ahead
like in societally wise uh I mean I think I think I have all it's a frustrating because I think
I have all the skills like I think I could easily do something like that that would make me like
much better known much more of like a you know an industry guy like much better connected
much more successful generally um so I'm simultaneously frustrated but that didn't
happen but also I don't even know if I want that anyway I feel both negative emotions
at the same time for conflicting reasons that contradict one another.
We went into productivity as an idea last episode pretty significantly that was a
it was a pretty big section of the episode and I feel it like related to this and and and sort of
like picking what your what what you want to do with your life I feel like having clarity
on issues is something really big that one can easily lose sight of when they're freelancing
and they have so many options before them and it can feel I think we've talked about this before
me and you but like it can feel like you're doing so much stuff but like you aren't you aren't actually
doing that much when you when you sit down and actually analyze what you're doing it can seem
almost like you aren't doing anything in a way uh it just feels like when things are undefined
they feel more uh what's the word they they feel more oppressive than they are actually
when you have vaguely defined work it can sort of feel uh like there's so much of it when in
fact it's it's not that it's a lot of it it's just that you don't really know what you're
supposed to be doing exactly at a good moment and the reason I bring this up is because I feel like
when we have varied works like we do now uh me and you we have so many different things that we
could be working on we could be working on in the store we could be working on quick drive
can be working on the pcp we could be working on our own individual stuff you have like a thousand
different things you could do and it that can be very paralyzing that can be very very like well
and the thing about me is that I'm prone to paralysis yeah it's just realable palsy yeah I'm
I'm serious I'm heavily prone to to paralysis and stuff I completely understand yeah I I uh
there's been some developments in my life and I've sat down and I've tried to cut as many
things from my life as humanly possible and I've sat down and thought myself what are the things
I care about doing online I just went I just went through and thought that the things that I want
to do with my time what do I want to do with my time and I've come back with a very simple
short list rck endless war quick draw the pcp and personal art like commissions and stuff like
that those are the things I care about doing and before it was sort of like yeah I mean obviously
right like those the biggest things in my life it's not like I have another project that's running
but even just the the the sort of vague like should I be making a new podcast series right now
should I not be just even like the the the the vagueness even in an abstract uh like potential
way of like maybe I should be doing something more was causing me to to have paralysis in a way
work paralysis and I also cut down stuff like discord servers and I've tried to leave as much
as I can and just try to I haven't been spending a lot I haven't spending a lot less time on
discord lately yeah uh I uh I haven't been on social media long since I've deleted all that
to my friend I'm just trying to listen your brain is always gonna want to do stupid shit your brain
is always going to want to uh do stuff that's easiest and that requires a little amount of work
so you have to construct the world around you to be make it impossible you can't okay you know
you have twitter on your phone you say yourself I will go on twitter um I just won't go on twitter
anymore uh you're retarded that won't ever happen you need to have actual systems in a place to
incentivize that behavior because if you're not changing the system then why would you think that
you would get a different result you need to either you know like delete it outright which is what I
did or at least come up with like a different like like come up with different ways that your brain
wants to interact with twitter maybe do it at a specific time when you've deemed it's valuable
or just you know like you can't just say things will be different that's not self-control that's
cowardice and retardation yes my two favorite things
so I found it very very eye-opening and helpful to just sort of like define what I want to do with
my with my work and be able to think you know there's not actually that much to do you know
there's only a few projects I want to work on that's not that bad maybe I'll work on quick
try today well maybe I'll work in rck today I mean it's part it's part of the reason I haven't been
as active in in rfck is because like you know I I mean I don't want to talk I've said this a lot
before but like you know I realized like I really had this fucking vapor's three thing hanging over
my head for a long time time to fucking time to fucking put things aside and deal with that
just for my own sanity's sake I'm interested I'm interested at the same thing that I've done
would benefit you in a way because again you have a thousand you have a thousand different
things you could be doing is there any is there any ones that you think that you should be spending
more time on are there any like you think you would benefit from like removing some of the gunk
from your mind and just trying to streamline the process of okay I'm going to re-evaluate
what I'm doing I'm only going to be working on these this this and this do you think that would
be helpful for you well it already has been oh oh have have you done that or what what ones
was it just vapor's three that you're yeah that's the only that's the only thing I'm focusing on
these days um which is the right thing to do and I should have done it a lot sooner
and I think it's this way it'll be and I think do I have a sketchbook no a schedule like not
and I don't mean the sense that you uh regiment every single hour of your day I just mean uh do you
have like do you have a bedtime do you have a wake up time no I've taken it was been very very
motivating in this way uh that he's sort of uh made me think he he too has a bedtime and uh I
thought it was very appealing and I've finally actually done it uh I've got I've given myself
a bedtime which I'm sadly going to be breaking to record this show but you know it's the break
yeah rules are meant to be broken exactly but I've actually uh it feels weird to wake up
in the morning yeah it feels very unnatural for me but uh also very good because it feels like
oh my god it's two o'clock and I've been awake for like an hour already oh my god yeah yeah yeah
yeah I know I know that feeling the feeling of like I got up early my day feels so much longer
but the possibilities are endless um yeah yeah yeah I mean okay now this might not be the best
but it's been working well enough uh I have no bedtime I have no schedule or anything I have
just kind of been like I'm just gonna stay up until the next page is done and I'm just not going to
sleep until it is I mean I don't always get a whole page done in the day or anything it's I've
been getting maybe like one every two or three days lately um but you know they are getting done
under that system so give me give me an overview of the of a day in the life I've been saying
like well like well like what's what's the overview look like uh you you wake up do you
immediately just like get on your computer and start drawing or yeah well I'll get on my computer
and I'll either start drawing or I'll like I don't know play some Gungeon or something okay um and
it's pretty much I mean it's pretty much just alternating I mean it's pretty much just alternating
between like playing Gungeon or whatever game du jour uh you know looking at like social media
stuff and and drawing and like I just I get bored of one and I switch to the other and the cycle
repeats forever until until you collapse or until you get a page and you're finally allowing
yourself to sleep yes that's right that's that's it that's it that's pretty much it's all there is
to it do you feel like social media do you feel like social media impact like is bad at all because
I doubt it I don't I don't actually spend that much time um on social media really I mean I'll
like I'll scroll through my Twitter for you maybe like once or twice a day uh oh it's
funny huge I mean well I used to I used to be on discord more and I would spend more time you know
scrolling through that um not as much anymore that that discord was more of a time sink than
like Twitter was by far yeah uh it feels so good I I I can now see every server I'm in just like I
don't have to scroll I can't scroll anymore I still have to scroll but I just have tons and
tons of notifications that I'll never read Jesus yeah there's so much like you rck is terrible
that side servers yeah there's just so much shit you have to be in yeah yeah there is there's some
stuff that like you want to be in not even just rck but just in general I mean I'd like to in a
perfect world I'd be in everything sure but like it's like there's a lot of the servers where it's
like yeah I wish I posted there but like I'm not going to realistically and it even being here is
just another decision that I'll have to make to go in there or not to go in there and just another
like again going back to streamlining just another thing that could possibly lead me to just having
the choice overload just like literally like like there is I think a noticeable difference or like
like impact on your life just even just having one more choice like a discord server I think it
makes a genuine impact on your life to have clutter in the form of like your room is messy
or like your your discord things are messy and it can just feel like uh again there's just so much
to do uh you aren't uh you aren't fully dedicated to even just a few tasks you can just feel like
you're you're if your room is messy your life is messy it's my motto well my room's a fucking
disaster so yeah mine too lol well um well I don't know I'm thinking about cleaning my room
lately uh probably could do that um I'm cooking I've been cooking a bunch
ooh have you that's very human cordy bin that's a that's a that's a betrayal of your character
I don't know I don't know if it is uh well maybe a little bit um I mean my cooking generally is
about being as efficient as possible um it's about you know getting getting the right macromutrients
um you know fat specifically doing that doing me and Arlo you know doing our keto thing yeah yeah
two together me and Arlo should go on a keto day oh dude bins oh well now that's a guy who won't
let you down you you say collaborating with people is always a nightmare collaborate with Arlo and
do the keto podcast and you'll be fine oh you can come with some pun for keto kermit or something
that effect the the only the only show dedicated to puppets and being keto keto kermit yeah yeah
yeah I mean that's a very niche audience but I think it's one that's been crying out yeah well yeah
it's it's um it's um like like the the silent majority you know yeah totally um okay I'm probably
going to die to this mimic I'm really fucking up I think they're still not killed or the rat I've
only gotten to him once um come on Ben oh and I yep I died I died to the mimic okay yeah it's hard
it's hard it's a lot harder to play when you're talking but that's fine um okay what was I gonna
say oh yeah I make uh I I undertook a project the other day and I made a cauliflower crust pizza
and it came out pretty good um yeah but it took forever okay the real problem was that I don't
have a food processor all I have is a blender and it was a nightmare blending the cauliflower into
like like ricing it in a blender I I don't think I will even though the results were good and I was
pleased with them and it was a great pizza um I won't do it again because I without a food processor
it is a it is a nightmare yeah like blending it's it's just not made it's it's just not made to do it um
sad sad I I've been dying to cook again but my kitchen for like two months since before I left
the last like to go to Boston last trip and since I've gone back my kitchen has been
fucked and like it like it is it's there was mold found during a dishwasher and some sort of
inspection and now that we just haven't had any stove the only thing in the kitchen that's worked
is our fridge and it's just been a complete like uh construction wasteland for literal months
and I haven't been to cook and I've just had I've just had to eat fucking Chipotle every day
oh what a nightmare I know it is it literally is what a disaster um let's get those keto bowls
let's get those lifestyle bowls no no no no no I listen I'm overloaded on ketones as it is if I
have any more than I might brist that's the life that is the life god I just want to swap keto
notes with Arlo that's a that's a that's a perfect day for me I don't know if I told you but you uh
you've you've you've scored a victory uh a long time ago actually uh I haven't I even I've canceled
my hello fresh a long long time ago even before my kitchen broke oh was that why because of me
no not because of you of course not yeah I don't want to any of your advice
sure uh why it's it's it's because I I've outgrown it I know how to cook on my own I don't need
anymore it's like I've always said it's it's it's a beginner's it's a crutch from when you first
started out okay well fair enough all right well good um that's good then I guess you got something
out of it I did uh but unfortunately I didn't get enough out of it because my fucking kitchen's broken
god damn it you know a real man can cook without a kitchen real man just lights a fire in the back
yeah it's room yeah it's a room yeah real man just uh a real man just uh just burns like a fire in
his trash can and just like roasts roast hot dogs over him man god you know hello fresh might be
too human core for me but instacart is the best uh instacart I just I don't I don't gotta go shopping
I feel like one like 90 bucks 90 bucks one time for a whole year of like I never have to go shopping
it is that's pretty good it's so good do I feel bad because uh for the poor people that have to
like actually deliver the groceries for what I can only assume is a complete shithole gig economy
style job with no benefits and probably just getting just exploited the fuck right out yep
but you know what it's not my problem
open oh oh oh uh open I mean it's not like if I I mean it's not like if I didn't do it
it's not like if I didn't engage in this hideous system known as capitalism that these people
would be better off because they don't have me getting them to go out and buy my fucking groceries
for me thanks um so whatever don't even worry about it just don't even worry about it just close
your eyes just don't think about it they love it they want it I'll give it to them free
I mentioned earlier uh I was asking you about about if the seasons impact your life and those
is very very very specific reason they ask this because this summer you're shaping up to be another
year or a summer of pain as it was last time you mentioned this yeah you said that I'm not too
on a recent pcp you said this was going to be another summer of pain uh and uh it's it's fully
locked in that I'm going to be traveling all over the place and I just came back from a trip up to
la now trips at the la for me are not anything particularly special in it other than the selves
uh it's you know I go up to la somewhat regularly but for this was for a um very special purpose
you see as I alluded to uh before um talking about code for boston uh I was I was given an
opportunity where I thought if I can somehow finagle if I can get some some people with social
clout to play in this war then uh then all would just be fucking golden uh and and this the opportunity
came to me in the form my mother asked me to attend a world premiere of a independent movie in
los angeles and to my honesty I don't really know why I thought I was gonna be able to talk to anyone
who would want to play in this war but to me the calculation was simply people in one place
they like movies so they might be nerds maybe I can somehow talk to someone uh who would uh
just like be like hey it's me I'm a big I'm a higher up at EA and I'm attending this la uh yeah
this this uh you know this this event and then I can be like well well mr EA I tune a video game
and would you for a chance want to play me for an afternoon or two and hopefully he would say yes
but anyway you know he's not fucking yes yeah yeah you yeah listen EA I feel like our business model
is very similar to what EA would have demanded of us you know it's completely ringing our audience
cash in this war is the most profitable thing we've done in our entire lives
and I wouldn't have it any other way uh as soon as that bottom line as soon as the bottom line
falls out of endless war it's canceled um yeah I I uh I so so I go up there and it's a fucking
arduous four-hour drive as it always is because LA is shit traffic um so I know by the way LA is
like the worst city on earth like no one lives in LA I'm just convinced that it's like a joke or
perhaps I'm sort of like prank people come out and like like say that they got me after a while
you approach LA there are no roads there are only highways there's no like you know you get in there
there's some surface streets but it's all just they all just lead in highways you approach the city
there's just a bunch of drab gray buildings in the distance they're just sucking life out of you
sucking all the color out of life as you approach them there are no lights on you pass by apartment
after apartment there are no people in those apartments they're just they're just out there's
some sort of like building quota they have to keep up so it's like it's like the town of city
yeah exactly um it's it's like that one north korean city i'm a dmz that there's no one in but
they just want to make it seem like there are people there so the so people in south korea will
affect and that there's actual people living in north korea uh it's complete far since i've
been real is that a real thing that sounds like a real thing you just it is a real thing yeah it is
okay yeah excellent uh it's a fucking nightmare and i hate LA uh but that's that's that's my impression
of you but opposite uh got him so so we're inviting this premiere my my friends are my mom's friend
my gay friend not relevant to the story it's like that would be nice dude yeah that's really
normalizing it um we go to the chinese theater i will speak of gay people i just want to once again
say public enemy number one in new los angeles city pete budigich who has declared that went if he
gets elected president yeah he will wants to put a stop to endless war we can't fucking have it
we can't he can't believe that someone had the audacity to say that oh actually bernie said
something similar i saw it really well kind of he me i just saw him on twitter um like yesterday i
was looking at twitter as i sometimes do and one of his he said uh i think his phrasing was like
we spend too much money on endless wars oh and that was very offensive to me um well hey funny
funny thing i'm going to a yang rally really you are you are on the tenth yeah i'm going to so
the day after you viewer hear this fucking follow me on twitter it's also ugly maybe i'll
tweet something about the yang rally yeah please do um well it's anything like the burning rally
it's gonna be really boring you're gonna wonder why you went yeah i'm i'm prepared for that um
speaking of that burning rally by the way some follow-up on that um while i was in line they were
like hey there there's some uh volunteers there and they're coming by telling everyone like say
and they were they talked to me and said hey did you did you sign up online did you um did you uh
rsvp or whatever and i was like uh no i did i rsvp i fucking rsvp a a uh and and and uh
and they were like would you like to and i said i'm already here what well i have to do like well
like well like like they just wanted like numbers i assume they just wanted people to be on their
newsletter yeah and they're like no no no no it's no it's fine just just just just put your name
here and it'll be fine and i'll and i say okay okay so now you're on the burning mailing list
yeah and on the burning mailing list of course i'm the fucking burning yeah yeah of course of
course of course i am i got the point where they put in my email and i was like oh are you gonna
email me and like no no no no no we we we you know it's just to get it it's just to get the data
yeah i was like and at that point we're already looking at me they were they were already they
were already looking at me we just want to see we just want to sell this to google we just want to
sell this to google yeah yeah and i was like okay okay now if you can't trust bernie then can you
trust and of course i can't put down my spam email which is what i want to do because my spam email is
legendary to legendary poop for 2069 why can't you put that down on the burning rally why not why
not well yeah i wish i did because i get texts every single day now hey anthony did you see our
first text tomorrow night tomorrow at midnight we'll close the books on our first official
it's like it's like it's like getting messages from your from your parents like hey did you see my
text why don't you why don't you ever call anymore yeah hey anthony it's samuel with burning 2020
it's time to get work organized and make bernie our next president i i don't i didn't want this
this isn't why i came to the bernie rally yeah this is not what i signed up for even though it's
literally why i signed up that's what you get that's what you get for getting involved in your
community fucking idiot it is it's literally disincentivizing it's literally like i won't go to
another one and i'm gonna have to find out i'm just gonna i'm gonna say i'm gonna say hey listen
i'm gonna i'm gonna say to him right now please please stop i'm just gonna let me just get bernie
on the horn real quick hey bernie baby uh stop i'm i'm literally gonna say please stop period
that's all i'm gonna say isn't there a thing at the bottom like you know no reply to the email to
get taken off the list there's nothing like that and also i this is probably naive of me and this
is probably like obviously not the case because why would it be but it seems to be like okay there's
there's stuff like did you see our it was do you see my last text there's also like hey anthony
it's me samuel so it might be like a dude it might not it's probably not it's probably a bot
but i don't know fuck sorry i'm possible it's a real person
is anyone ever really a real person does he he does he did he pass the turing test did he
did he pass the turing test he didn't catch the best steltet you've done i was talking about
bernie it's not even trying to talk about it he's not talking about um he didn't pass the
gang or other women oh god i'm not the dunning kruger what's the fuck what's the test in blade
runner i've never seen blade board void blade comp i think it's a void comp test
is to determine if you're a ref void
you're looking you're looking for a magazine you're looking for a magazine you come across a
you come across a picture of a naked girl mr. deckerd are you asked are you is this to
determine if i'm a replicant or a lesbian mr. deckerd uh kane is his name deckerd kane
whatever sorry okay sorry to sorry to turn this into a blade i don't even care about
blade runner i don't want to make this a blade runner cast okay uh what were you talking about
don't care what uh are you rally shit gunjan uh i'm doing decent this round uh but i'm low on
heart so i might die um my weapons are pretty oh i was i was saying that i was going up to a
film premiere to this shit fucking movie okay right yeah yeah was there more to that yeah oh
ben okay i haven't even started with this movie uh i know so we go to the chinese theater ground
chinese theater sure little in fact the theming of it being a chinese theater stop starts and stops
at the entrance yeah it just it looks like a mall i'm the inside yeah uh it sounds about right
uh a nightmare uh we go and we get our seats uh the the the the attendant at the start says uh
if you gotta go back and go to the bathroom now uh it's a long movie and uh i listened but i thought
how long can this movie be really long yeah really really really really really really long
how long uh it is often said by by me even uh me especially i often describe things as nightmares
yes and and well that's you know it's easy to do they pick that up from you who picked that up from
did i say that too i i i i think maybe you from me i don't know doesn't matter okay anyway it's
a very common thing to say i guess and i'm tempted to say that but i would describe it more in a
literal sense it wasn't a nightmare and since it was bad like overly bad even though it was it was a
it was dreamlike in a lot of ways you know how dreams have quote unquote stories but it's just
sort of one long continuous your brain is constantly coming up scene after scene after scene
there's no beginning middle or end it's just one like like like it just is continuously going along
it's almost like an improv comic in a way yeah it just is just it's just continuously developing
in weird haphazard ways that don't connect to with one another and just seemingly endlessly until
you wake up and you wake up in a cold sweat that's what this movie is like genuine it's
wait so the movie was like yeah this is what the movie was okay i wasn't sure if you were
describing the movie or your experience of going to this theater no no the the movie itself though
i guess it could be said for the overall experience for going to the theater because in itself it was
a nightmare but i'm going to uh i'm going to uh say the the movie title was the turnover and it's
on imdb right now you can go you can go to turnover is it about is it about the pastry indeed um well
it's sort about the pastry oh what you have to understand is that okay this is a it says on
here that it is uh two hours uh it felt like it was way longer so i like to the point where like i
don't believe that this could possibly be true like it can be like oh well i just thought the
movie was really long but it's so it felt so long to the fact that like i like there's no way it was
two hours that feels like it's impossible with the amount of time that i was there watching it that
you just there's no way that you possibly compute but um even though it is two hours which is long
on its own it felt like it was longer in the editing bay and it was cut down to be two hours
so there's so much that's like implied to have happened or to be a character trait
for instance i'll give you the part of the movie in a second here yeah but it's about a restaurant
owner and at one point the restaurant owner rebrands his restaurant and one of his employee he
renames it and he gives it a new logo and one of the characters the waitress um says i thought i
threw that design out implying a lot of things implying she's an artist implying she might have
you know she might be perfectionist in a way she might you know she might be down herself and might
not think that her good enough and and there might have been a scene where the restaurant owner
pete finds a design in the trash or something and it has a you know a moment where he's like
this this girl's too hard on herself i'm gonna i'm gonna make things right i'm gonna make sure
she knows that she's cool um literally not mentioned once the woman is an artist never
mentioned again not even like just so many things are just like implied to be you know
it's taken for great like yeah you know this girl draws i guess i guess that's something she does
this can be said for every character every plot point every just aspect of the story just like
things are supposed to be just you know you just get it like a dream there's no explanation for
things it's just like i guess this is how things are i guess this is just like what is happening
right now um sounds a little like the vapors honestly
ben why would you say that about yourself well i mean there's not a lot of like explanation
about stuff stuff it like vapors is just like a series of things that happen right that they're
all around a central idea okay maybe maybe i'm maybe i'm not maybe i'm not getting what you're
saying because it doesn't this doesn't sound like a bad thing that you're describing maybe it doesn't
sound like a bad thing in concept but it was a very confusing film in a lot of ways i just i don't
mean to imply that it just because it was a goon coonsverk and that everything didn't lead back to
a central theme it was bad or that because it was like a sort of sliced life in a way that that was
bad yeah it's it's that it felt like it didn't know what to like what it was or what it was trying to
accomplish on the surface of it it's like supposed to be like a character study in a way of the
restaurant owner pete but it's just you know i almost want to say that you just have to watch it
and you would understand what i'm trying to say sure and uh it's it's just you can't was it just
didn't accomplish anything it did not accomplish in making me like any of the characters having any
memorable dialogue it did not accomplish having even like the semblance of a storyline or the
semblance of stakes in any way that you just felt like sort of an arbitrary series of things that
happens exactly exactly where it's like it didn't feel like one led into the other it didn't feel
like it was uh progressing in any way the the vapor is like sure it doesn't have it like a story
per se but and well understand what's happening and damn it yeah okay so was it just like confusing
were you just confused what yeah that that is the afterwards that is the afterwards that it was just
confusing in in every way i didn't get what it was trying to do i didn't get what the characters
were trying to do uh i didn't understand the point of the fucking movie at all um to get into
more specifically i will read the indb cafe owner peter at least his disgruntled manager
henry to take care of business instead he hires a crew of misfits peter returns to an
unrecognizable business but soon learns of the value of camaraderie with his new team
it's about family it's about family literally literally it's about family okay he's sick yeah
i mean i love camaraderie personally maybe i'm maybe i'm this movie's target demographic
yeah you just don't care about family or camaraderie that's that's your problem
so what i'm going to describe the movie and you may think that doesn't sound that bad
yeah but keep in mind i am heavily condensing things because i don't want to be here for an hour
explaining each scene that just happens and there's no rhyme or reason for it and there's no
like it adds nothing to the structure of the film it just is like a plot point that just
you know just happens for no reason so the gist of the movie there's this old dude named peter
who owns a restaurant and a twink named henry who is who is his affiliate
partner in crime partner in crime i suppose in a way not incredibly well defined what's
going on there he's like the waiter and the chef and like the like everything else as well
he just like runs the entire business sure um and uh he's disgruntled for for because he doesn't
feel like his potential has been lived up to so he forces peter to make a uh a new franchise
yeah well and he is the manager of this is wait what kind of a restaurant is this that's like
a little cafe it's like a french restaurant it doesn't really matter okay um it uh and and and
so peter agrees by the way this entire movie wants to treat peter like he's an asshole and
peter's the main character right yeah peter's the main character he's the old dude yeah and they
want to like the entire movie like the conceit of the movie is that like it's a character
art he's a character study of peter and how he learns to accept his eventual crew of myths
fits for who they are yeah and it he wants to portray him as stubborn he's not portrayed that way
as all except for in dialogue where people are belittling him and berating him like saying like
don't be some stubborn peter yeah and he and he's like oh yeah i don't know like i'm sorry i guess
you're right sorry and okay oh shit oh fuck okay yeah i could see uh you can see how that would be
annoying that's just one of the many things where it's like yeah it's implied in dialogue to be the
case but it's it just isn't it just is not the case you're on team peter oh oh i'm white dude
i could not be more on team peter unfortunately it turns into a pussy later but that's you know
that's it you know sweet yes um then his evil ex-wife comes into frame his ex-wife is a frequent
character but each time she's a completely different person so for her first appearance
she is unbelievable like corolla de vil evil yeah um and comes in what did she do um okay i'm
going to get to it um but she also introduced like else in that scene is introduced my favorite
character in the show all right in the movie who is peter's son and peter son is played completely
straight like he's on the andy griffith show where he says to flake ah gee pops like can i
go to my friends huh can i can i completely isn't a child actor he's like 13 he's not even young
okay he he's like a teenager who is like pops i'm so happy to see you again i'm you know you
know dad you didn't talk like that when you were 13 um oh wait i knew you when you were
13 wait did i know did you did uh i think you knew me when i was 14 at least yeah yeah that's
what you were that's what you were like don't you remember oh gee whiz oh gee whiz did you golly
uh beautiful and it's like that in every single scene by the way this is one of the scenes that
don't matter and isn't uh you know like like um expanded upon it anyway so i'm just gonna mention
it here at one point he's rocking back and forth during a conversation with uh between peter and
his ex-wife um and he shot almost like a horror movie fourth and just cut between him rocking him
back and forth with a knife in his hands and them talking and then eventually he falls out of the
of the chair and stabs someone else on accident and then like that like peter just takes the guy to
the hospital and like that's the end of the scene like he's just fine no he's like he just like stabbed
someone and that's like not a plot point wait just stabs someone why does he just stab wait with
what i'm sorry i was i was see i'm being attacked by a beholder right now okay i understand um can
you can you repeat can you repeat some yeah yeah they're just in a restaurant they're in
peter's restaurant yeah uh peter and his ex-wife are talking his son's rocking back and forth in a
chair with a butter knife in his hand and i'm dead okay he falls out of the chair yeah and he stabs
a patron one of the staff with this butter knife he's bleeding and like that's like never brought
up it's just like he starts to bleed peter says i i take him to the hospital he takes him to the
hospital and like that he stabs him on purpose well not on purpose but it's a mishap and he says
oh gee i like i'm really sorry okay well so it's like oh wait i you haven't seen the room i was
going to compare it to the scenes did you know that in the room there are like not one but two
scenes where they're just tossing the old pigskin around and someone just falls on someone else
for no reason is is that the case yeah there's i think they're tossing the pigskin and but there's
a lot of pigskin tossing yeah is that the term they use as well i don't think so but they might as
well there's one where mark just like they're just they're just like laughing and then like he just
like from no reason just falls on another guy like just from a perfectly balanced standing
position yeah yeah yeah yeah um and there's another one too i don't remember when the second one
happens but there's at least two okay so okay so it's just a weird accident just it well let's
think about let's think critically did they just not have a was it just a way to end the scene
like did they just want to end the scene and didn't know why didn't didn't know how to do it okay it
in in okay i think it might okay okay the only thing i can think is that setting up the idea
that there's a hospital in the city for later oh good okay see that's world that's a way that's
world-building look it up sometime that's the only thing i can think because later the hospital is
relevant but completely unrelated to the incident and that is not important does he like meet a
character at the hospital when he goes to drop this knife no wound victim no okay okay um not no
not at all uh but anyway back back to the back to the chronological order see um evil wife demands
that this literal child is the manager of the new franchise for his restaurant instead of Henry
this literal 13 year old g whiz who's Henry Henry is the old manager yeah yeah he's the
tweak manager who's who's disgruntled and feels like he should be behind the booth instead of out
there and you know at mice like the proletariat yeah okay i'm with them i think i'm on team Henry
yeah everyone post in the comments are you are you hashtag team peter hashtag team Henry um don't
be don't be team pete because pete bootages wants to bring an end to endless war oh i can imagine i
think i think is i have no idea what his name is his name is something like something stupid like
like pete pastry or like pete pierre or something in the fact no his name is not pete pastry it can't
might as well be can't possibly might as well be pete pastry um and and and so that's like a name
that like jk rowling that's like a jk rowling name but like the laziest jk rowling character ever
um so okay the scene is like the the the start of the entire plot and here and the wife just says
like make Henry or i'm sorry don't make Henry the new manager make our son who's a literal baby
the manager and peter says no i mean why and then the scene ends uh also to emphasize how how evil
the x y face she says that she like he'll never see the sun again if he doesn't make the sun the
the man how how would that work which i don't know so and so this is obviously leading to like like
then you know the plot of the movie comes in and she there's like a custody battle or something
you know obviously no okay no no all right uh and so like pete just he is on vacation now i
don't want to emphasize the fact that he like it's not like pete says like oh i need to break from
this i'm on vacation now there's that scene i just described smash cut to him in a sailboat
looking at the sun gleefully smash cut back to the restaurant and like it's only revealed later
that he's on like vacation and for like an extended period of time he's been on vacation this whole
this whole time is what is what you're saying no no i'm saying that like he starts vacation
just not announced to the audience that what he's doing or for like a reason
really it's not like he's particularly in like hot water right now or he wants to get away
it's just like again like again it's just so confusing like he okay smash cut him in the in a
sailboat hey he's on vacation right now he could just be sailing i don't know why i would imagine
that he is now like off of work for like a week and a half like what is actually happening
or why i'm just expected to know that but anyway the ex-wife just tells henry that peter agreed
and so peter or i'm sorry now now henry takes it upon himself to hire a bunch of literally
mentally deficient people and minorities in order to make the restaurant go belly up in
order to spite peter that's the plot of the of the of the story is is henry just now is like
full just like like listen if i can't be kasey green i'll kill kasey green because my thoughts
exactly um yeah okay wait so this is like supposed to be like the actual like plot of the story
is like you know again it's a story about family it's a story about you know peter coming to
determine with this class of misfits that that henry hires this is like an hour into the movie
okay good yeah yeah yeah all right i'm with you he hires two what's the problem like like mentally
disabled people unironically yeah um an old lady just a girl who i guess is that yeah even the worst
of all yeah yeah yeah yeah and and a black guy and a mexican guy and like that's like that's like the
crew of misfits that he's acquired here that's the crew of like like it's it's what a what a color
what a colorful cast of characters i'm sorry you're not allowed to say colored anymore yeah um
just like like normal people basically yeah okay um by the way i'm not about to send you a picture
of of henry just like you know what he looks like um this is you in about uh 12 years ago
no yeah no all right i'll show it there it is yeah there's me there's me
he's super killer he's such he's such a killer yeah not enough killers wear cowboy hats
um we gotta do something about it so the next couple scenes are frankly indescribable
henry leaves the misfits in charge of the restaurant and like bad things happen question mark
yeah literally describe it i literally cannot describe like some people come to the cafe but it's
like oh by the way this entire movie is shot indoors it's there's never a scene of them outside
except for that aforementioned shot of the hint of peter outside sailing
literally not a single shot outside good wait yeah uh hmm i mean i want to clarify it's the same
building and the building is a small cafe so just feels like you're in the same place over and over
again every single scene as you are that's a nightmare did you die again no i didn't die
i just i fucked up and i don't have enough keys for the ugliet the ugliet is a side level
by the way i okay one in one ear out the other okay fine um you know what this might be i might
be able to make up the difference uh and you're fine and finally kill the rat like you've always
been destined to do i mean maybe that's the plan possible that's that's that's that's the plan
um all right i want to speed this up because i won't be talking about this movie forever
anyway there's just a bunch of scenes of the of the of the new crew just fucking up and being
stupid uh in ways that are confusing and ill-conceived and also not really well portrayed in the audience
peter comes back and is just like like upset that his restaurant has been turned upside down and like
it's been on the twist turned upside down yeah and none of these people have any experience in the
restaurant uh scene uh and this is treated as peter being unreasonable and everyone in the
all the crew is like for instance there's this one line that's delivered when peter comes in and
says like guys like what's going on here like you're supposed to be making french cuisine
and then one of the misfits says i'm sandal i'm i relate to him thus far
uh there's a lot you don't know about around here peter there's a lot you don't know about around
here it's his restaurant wait what yes yes he says you're supposed to be making french cuisine
and the response is there's a lot you don't know about around here yeah okay yeah yeah yeah yeah
so this gun so this gun that i'd have it um it just summons sharks from the ground
really yeah like it it's it shoots out a little like shark fin that sort of like floats along the
floor and then when it hits an enemy just a giant fucking jaws comes out and eats them
it's sick okay that's just i just want you to know what's going on for the audience i've literally
by the way viewers in case you couldn't tell i can literally cannot see bin screen he doesn't have
screen sure on and i don't care it like it's it's better this way fuck i miss the key fuck i miss
the key god damn it okay uh yeah this is the way it should be this is the way it should have always
been uh anyway there's there's like an arc where pier has to learn to accept this new cast even though
the new crew like can't do anything right according to the movie but we're supposed to
like them anyway and want them to succeed um and uh eventually uh his ex-wife shows up
now like a sweet woman who like is like reasonable did he like do something to like change your
attitude no no okay but but he's about to do something that could theoretically change her
but she's already like this before the scene yeah where uh peter uh wants to uh help his ex-wife
you know come to terms with it and you know show that he's moved on by inviting her and her new
fiance to a banquet at the uh the the now renamed eclectic cafe which is uh where i that's that's a
new sub-zone of the rye rough house eclectic cafe um of course this is uh of course uh
it's it's it's to honor all the different heritages that are at work in this in this incredible
cafe you understand and then it's like no everything's going to verse like oh because
there are a rowdy band of misfits and we gotta acknowledge that yeah yeah so they're eclectic
yeah eclectic cafe is it about pete learning not to be racist is that what you've done here
okay it's it's about shooting on pete for like two hours and then him being the exact same thing
and then uh everyone but like everyone likes him now cool yeah he's been through a lot yeah he has
been he believe me he's been through a lot he's been a lot more a lot more than you fucking idiot
um so well they throw a banquet the the uh uh uh the new fiance is there uh he he's italian so
that's how you know he's evil his ex-wife's new fiance yes yes yes yes why why is he
invited why is he invited why is she invited i don't get it well the peter's throwing it for them
to show there's no there's no ill will he's throwing it for them that's like a like a wedding reception
thing oh god it's like that song it's like that song about when the guy he's trying to call
his like ex-girlfriends and like her new boyfriend or whatever to like you know just a show there's
a show i will become the blow learn to take it well i only wish my words could just convince
myself that it just wasn't real but that's not the way it feels good song anyway go on i'm gonna
have to hit the road it's by peepootage it's a big hit by peepootage in a past life
uh i you know i i bet the reason he hates in this war so much is because when he first rode
into town in the scorch home to find some nematodes over in toxington he never found one he just
got cancer instead yeah you know tails all this time um okay okay so while at this banquet the
fiat the the the wife's new fiance go like rance about how like the the restaurant uh crew is just
like a bunch of like weird freaks about how he hates them for being different no no it was henry
that made him higher than new guys yes oh henry's just out of the movie henry's just out of the
movie he's just not even here why what happened what did she do to him what has she done with henry
uh henry's just like like after he screws up everything he's just gone for the rest of the
movie okay well that makes sense i guess and and uh you know i guess he just got gunned down
somewhere like maybe maybe in glocksbury and he hasn't responded he's just stay dead now
yeah um you know after after trying to raid killer uh ready territory anyway there's a fist
fight and a food fight at the scene and uh peter just starts beating up the fiance and they start
throwing blows and everyone's just throwing food at one another goes to shit and then peter has a
stroke and a heart attack and then they go and this is what the the final act of the movie is like
i thought this this quirky food fight was gonna be like the end of it and like peter has grown
up and he's like learned to stand up is the new fiance like younger than him yeah okay is the
wife his age or is the wife younger or what the wife is hmm hey you there why now i'm here
okay sorry you cut out you cut out but you're back okay cool yeah um and then peter has a stroke
and this is like the rest of the movie is what it's about it's like it's completely shipped away
from it being like about learning to accept people who are different it just is like help peter not
be like mentally disabled anymore like help him recover from his stroke really and then yes i'm
not joking and then the most emblematic scene of the entire movie takes place imagine this imagine
a scene in the reception like the you know a a a um uh inside a hospital talking to the receptionist
uh and the misfits want to see peter they want to you know they he was taken by him i mean who
wouldn't after after all they've been through together of course so it's it's it's the scene
that keeps getting cut back between the mexican chef this gun is so fucking good i can't believe it
yeah demanding to see him the where the receptionist saying we don't have him on file the mexican chef
just saying find him his name is peter cutting in between that and the waitress uh millennial
goth girl nice talking to her mother who is a nurse and saying the following which has not
been established whatsoever the the the goth girl meets her mom says mom i have a job now the mom
saying you're not old enough to have a job and then the girl saying i'm not an exciting experiment
i'm not your creation i know about the sperm donors italian top of the class at i'm t uh
you know top of the class uh you know the smartest person on earth you bought me you you you bought
you bought the the sperm that made me who i am so that i could be smart so that i could be successful
you you you try to create me i'm not your science experiment i have my own person
yeah and then the mom says the mom says you're so right i'm so sorry that i treated you this way
i'm so you know what you know what daughter i'll let you make your own decisions from now on
and and then and then they hug meanwhile it's still coming back and forth in between each line of
their conversation and that's insane his name is peter we need to find peter oh god oh god i'm sorry
can man is here can man is here he's on my fucking tail oh god oh god oh god oh god it's a red skeleton
it is it oh god oh god oh god oh god it's a red skeleton it's the scariest thing in the entire world
he wants he wants you to pay back that debt he wants you to pay back that debt do you yeah well
guess what it's not happening he's he's tired of a frame trying to start as a frame say he's just
went to the source he's went to his boss i have never i have never seen this before i have never
seen this creature he's there's some name for him but he it's like the fucking ultimate fucking you're
gonna die now you're fucked um well guess what i sincerely doubt that i'm gonna be taken down the
ratty rat uh this time oh come on come on but you know what i'm gonna i'm gonna do my best i'm
gonna fight the beholster um we're gonna see how this goes the rest of the movie doesn't matter it's
just them nursing back period of health it's like an hour though so it's a nightmare oh god he's here
he followed me to the fucking boss room he's followed me to the boss room he's on your tail
forever now yes oh my god and the beholster is cursed oh my god the beholster is cursed oh my
god i mean i mean jam he's not cursed he's jammed two different things uh it's just that scene of
just it's so dramatic the entire thing just completely just out of nowhere this girl has
hang ups about being like like the child of like a sperm donor thing and she has hang ups about that
apparently yeah and then it's immediately resolved and there's no point to it i don't understand what's
happening movie why they just never brought it up before but then they just have a totally
unearned emotional scene where she confronts and gets over her mother buying her sperm from a sperm
donor yeah do i have do i have the do i have the right the idea yeah okay cool i was probably
really buoyed for everyone in the audience for me to repeat that but i'm still not over this
like this was like like three weeks ago yeah still thinking about well hey you know
the movie made an impression so maybe it's actually a masterpiece you know what you're right yeah i know
you know i i i would recommend if you are able to do so watch this movie don't watch the entire thing
because i'm not advocating suicide but i am advocating that you at least understand what i'm
saying because i guarantee you if you watch this then you will uh you'll understand what i am uh
you'll know your pain you'll know my pain yeah you'll know my pain it's as i said i went to like
the premiere so uh it's gonna be a a while before this thing is even on dvds it's gonna be a while
but this this is going on the rck museum it's going the rck uh animals of history and uh i'll
let you know about updates to the turnover i went to a movie premiere at mit a few years ago
i don't remember what the movie was i don't remember like anything about it might have
been a documentary i can't remember but i think i remember that like the xkcd guy was there and he
like gave like there was like a q and a with him it was like him and the directors i don't know what
the i don't know what was up with this i don't know why this event happened or what if anything the xkcd
guy had to do with it um but that's the true oh my god the black hole gun i got the black hole gun
and i don't know what it does but i'm gonna find out probably choose a black hole i had to give up
all right i gave up my key i probably won't be able to get to the ooble at this round but that's
okay i'm gonna try without it it's worth it for the black hole gun i should mention by the way
i started out with the saying that i wanted to rub shoulders to people in uh in in LA yeah immediately
after the movie was over uh everyone who worked on the movie uh uh like just like left like they
all just like like stood up and then all went like to like every like a party that only they were
invited to well literally we just rolled up to watch the movie which was a nightmare and then
drive home and that was it i didn't get to talk to someone at EA at all i didn't see you didn't
you didn't even see um cliff blizinski yeah he didn't even make an appearance
sad if there's i i wanted people who worked on turnover so badly to play in the swore i wanted
i just wanted it more than anything and it didn't work it didn't work man i'm sorry bra maybe next
time maybe next movie premiere you can meet those EA execs yeah yeah well don't worry this is not
this is not dissuaded me from going to every single movie premiere that i can go to possibly to
get the the word in there oh no the black hole ate my key god damn it i'm sorry i haven't you're
not having any luck the black hole ate my key i'm uh livid i'm just livid i need i said i needed
okay how am i gonna fucking kill the rowdy route without a key you can't do it don't tell me you
can do it how like like how hard is it to find the right right because it feels like we've been
going for like a billion years i found him i found it once i found yeah i found what finding him is
not hard um i don't know i just you know i'm not fully focused on the game so i'm taking some bad
damage here um i'm i'm gonna i've tried i tried to find him so i can visualize him is it is his
canonical name the resourceful rat it is the resourceful rat but he's pretty rowdy he's definitely
rowdy he's definitely rowdy you know what okay i'm gonna restart i'm gonna take this really seriously
i'm gonna do it really seriously um because i just true this i just been fucking around i just
viewer i just been wasting your time this whole time you know what don't worry about it um and
that's the end that's the end of my story hey hold on speaking of people yeah i've tried to
chill myself dude did i tell you about that dude on reddit that i do know catfish on behalf of the
pcp to try and get some uh social cloud no um for i think i've talked about this before that i was
going on reddit a lot more to try and uh to recapture some of uh uh the old tumblr days
the tumblr is dead i broke uh and i was on oh there's another one there's another water barrel
yes okay go on i was i was on r slash boston as i was just it was having fun and there was a reddit
post uh saying like hello like like like are there any uh podcasters or internet influencers
that operate the bot like any local boston podcast honestly that sets off red flags for me
yeah does it why well i mean my immediate thought is that this guy is may he's probably a
podcaster himself and he and he wants you know he wants to he wants he wants to get plugged
not on the gate not at all okay completely completely wrong ben uh for you see he was actually
an app developer who wanted us to uh to you see he i'm logging right now so i can get his full
conversation but anyway uh his post is local called local uh boston uh podcasters internet
influencers uh please DM me so we can work out a deal together and i think yes i'll do this on
i will take any deal yeah i love even though um they don't call me munchie day trump because i
don't like deals even though we aren't local to boston um i could have plausible deniability
there you know it's like you know it well it's not true that's totally no that's totally fair
that's totally fair yeah mm-hmm so i i i DM him and then started back and forth uh and uh so i'm
gonna get the first thing here uh uh boss okay okay so so first thing um i say like hey i'm part
of a local boston podcaster and um like need an analyzer group uh in the boston area and i'm i'm
interested in your app uh so please let me know you know you know you know he's developing an app
yeah he's developed he's part of an app development team or i mean what's the app
the app is first question okay well that was my first question too it took him a while too it was
kind of i wouldn't say he was like not he was like shady in a way but he wasn't forthcoming over
yeah he was not forthcoming about it okay um so he's the i i say like i am what you're asking for
and he says i would love the opportunity to chat and pick your brain please let me buy coffee or
lunch so we can spend some time talking about it will you be available next week are you located
in boston sure and so i'm like oh shit i have to tell him that i'm in san diego i'll tell him
that i'm visiting san diego and so i do that i continue to lie to him yeah but but but also
please tell me about your app so he he links me as his app after i i try a few messages of me trying
to ask about about it um and then he explains it uh what does it matter if i name the app i don't
fucking care i don't think so yeah uh uh it's worth t or worthy t um it's pronounced worth it but
it's it's it's just the word oh got it got it yeah worth it yeah yep okay um he links me he links me
like a youtube trailer and here's what he says uh it is a you know you remember form spring right
then your form spring i never used it um but you know what it is remind me it's you have an
account and people can ask you questions it's purely for questions oh yeah yeah yeah right sure yeah okay um
this but it's it this is that however you have to pay money to ask questions um
okay i i get it yeah sure so it's like super chats but only like no video it just is nothing
nothing but yeah you know that makes enough sense yeah i can i can understand i can understand the
thing there sure got it and and then and then uh he says we'd love to get your feedback on it um
things such as if it if it's something you in your community would use what you like or we don't
like about it etc uh please let me know um and i get that message and i pull a bin saint super hard
i read it and i think and i think that's something i should really i should respond eloquently to
i should put a lot of thought into me responding i'll get i'll get i'll get back to that yeah yeah
i'll get back to that way hardcore yeah um smash cut to a month later i'm like oh
shit i forgot about that yeah uh and so i respond super apologetically uh and i explain like it's
it's a cool idea i suppose i'll try it out maybe and i'll let you know um i said that i would pass
on to digi which i i'm not going to or had any intention to it was a straight up lie uh um
and and uh i was just like um yeah uh you know it's it's interesting i'll give it a shot
and then he spawns another thing uh and he's he says something effective um like like can you
tell me more about you and your group and i'm like ooh like here's my chance to explain who i am and
maybe he can scratch my back in some way well it's a free it's a free uh rpg you can play on your
yeah and uh and and that was uh two months ago yep i haven't responded uh well you know
i mean whatever who gives a shit i i i i'm i'm always i'm always trying to find ways to
shill endless war that's that's not it's never working it's never it's never ever in what way
is that a shilling opportunity what what do we possibly stand to gain literally nothing yeah
literally nothing yeah but but but you see it's it's it's it's like um fuck it's like it's like the
animal part of your brain that wants you to have sex and procreate it's like if i can just even talk
about it then i'll i'll have some way to tell something to gain if i can literally just mention
it to anyone who's willing to listen i don't i don't feel that way at all yeah for me it's like
why bother mentioning it to anyone okay as as it's obviously clear from everything i've talked about
like the multiple times right so i got my intention here is to show my product and all three times i've
mentioned on the show have been completely like there's no way they could possibly happen
i'm aware that like the ways i'm doing this are completely like wrong and there's no rhyme or reason
to believe that the things like going to this meeting with me are going to go for boston or
respond to this guy who wants to develop an app in any way could help me i understand that that's
true however it doesn't stop me from wanting it to be the case it doesn't stop me from just wanting
because like what do i have to lose to respond to this guy and like he's he's asking for for
podcasts in the boston area whatever i'll just fucking lie to him just here but tell me what you
can offer me but i don't know yeah but the answer he gave you an answer and it was nothing um yeah
you're right and that's sort of why i stopped responding yeah okay good i just want you to
understand that like the problem here is not oh no why did i stop responding the the the the end
goal is here is so naturally i stopped responding the end good end we made it oh well yeah i'm not
trying to imply that i should have kept responding after i realized that this would not work for the
our fans in any way i mean uh i mean yeah well i mean even if it did even if it did it's not like
it's not like knowing this guy who made the app confers any benefit on us whatsoever
we would just have access to the app like everyone else right true uh i don't know i don't know maybe
there's there maybe you see we could get we could get we could i feel like i'm uh i'm i'm lucy from
i love lucy and i feel like just knowing famous people will get me uh it's not a famous person
this is a nobody who's making some app but but he has he he's developing an app and he never
surely must know pewdiepie are you okay all right all right listen i i know i know it's irrational
i completely understand don't get it but i'll get a little but listen i just listen again any chance
i can even say the words endless war or pcp my brain shoots up and i get a dopamine rush
the moment the moment anyone says that to me at all what why don't you take that nervous energy you
got and put it to some use like impossible even like instead of fucking contacting a random app
developer why don't you why don't you send a fucking press send a fucking press release to the gaming
journalist or something you know because i saw his post on okay listen i saw his post on r slash
oh i'm i like okay you know what stop defending yourself you're right i should stop okay good
i'm glad we figured it out we found we found the solution if only if only if only he reversed
what you gotta get on the app we gotta get on that app if we gotta get on it it's uh
i mean it's not a terrible idea but we're not famous enough i think i made an account and i
did i like i i think i linked it on my twitter and i uh i never checked it again you linked it
well you linked your okay worth it yeah worth it strange name why do you think it's called that
like man asking this question was totally worth it uh no idea i know who i was looking i was talking
to too there's a list of a good team it's kenny it's kenny lee i was talking to
he is fucking mainlanders but he doesn't even believe in ghosts uh well i was asking
that's what i'm gonna dm him i'm gonna say hey listen before we go any further with this what do
you think about ghosts yeah you guys have ghosts on the mainland because we got ghosts in space if
we don't have ghosts but i don't know if we're gonna be able to work together just ask him hey
question you guys got ghosts on the mainland no context context is the enemy
fuck you see this is why i want to go to boston round cable is because i'm just so eager to
collaborate like collaboration at any cost talking to other people at any cost no matter
yeah in any form um i mean i should probably have like the opposite problem
we're like i i like don't i like don't talk about it unless i'm sure that like there's some
like tangible benefit to doing so and other other than i'm like i mean you know what's the point
bring that up you know whatever like that's just the thing um i you know i'm casting a wide net
bin i'm talking to literally everyone and eventually there has to be someone who actually cares well
sure well here's the thing even if they cared so what you get like one guy to join the server
that that guy that guy could tell other guys or or maybe it's not like like i'm trying to sell
that person like i'm not like i'm not trying to get like that one guy but i'm trying to get people
some that guy who maybe has a platform to share it yeah sure sure um hey let me let me bring it back
to the round table yeah let me ask you so like i think they do like a i think they do like a
newsletter or something and like people contribute like comics to like the newsletter uh
i'm just curious if like that's something you would want to do because like i never ended up doing it
but i thought about it like oh maybe i just you know draw some shit and like put it in this
fucking like a zine basically like a zine like they kind of have their own zine yeah so well it's
it's what you're describing is just that like it is like they have a newsletter and you can just
like draw like a like like a like a like a um a funny in the local paper pretty bad like a
like a garfield strip i think uh yeah i think maybe they they took like full page ones as well
but yeah pretty much more or less um well uh no but not because of the underlying idea of it
not that like it's just like work to do to get my work seen by people in any capacity
which is something i'm into i don't know if i have a particular want to do that type of work
though i might not be understanding it completely well i think i got a glitch oh yeah yeah a corpse
just turned into a pink rectangle oh come on developers come on sad sad uh but sorry state
of india games with all these days oh wait it's gone i think it faded okay whatever i i i do like i
think i think zines are cool in concept and i don't have a i don't have a any issue with doing it
just in like the abstract though i think just maybe like like if it is indeed like a garfield funny
i don't know if i want to do that no i don't think i mean i think it can be whatever you want
okay like it's just you know did you make a comic are you do you are you in the boston comics
round table put your comic in the round table newsletter because that's what we're about
well then okay yeah if it just is like you can like like have like an ad for your comic or something
i don't just like your comic i don't think it yeah i don't think it's like they hand you off a script
and are like here make this or anything well yeah sure i don't think so but i i i thought i might have
been like like you remember comic strips from the newspaper we should have those but for our
newsletter because it's like quirky in a way kind of no i i think it's just whatever you
want to make pretty much okay well then yeah i'm not actually sure i'm not actually sure because
i never actually did it or really look much into it i knew that they did this sort of thing i think
they do them like maybe every couple months or something um i have no idea what i would do but
yeah i do have an interesting i think i think that could be cool yeah i i told you about that one
homesick sign that i signed up for but i got rejected for yes you mentioned you mentioned it
uh yeah it wasn't an official thing though right uh it was pseudo official it was like
endorsed by will pumpkin it was made by fans but like what pumpkin like supported them in a way
okay yeah was it canon was it technically technically i'm serious i'm serious was it like
no no not at all i mean i mean it wasn't like a story it just was pictures of homesick people oh okay
lame dumb uh i'm almost glad in a way that i didn't get selected because uh that that whole
operation was a huge shit show and uh very untrustworthy what do you mean untrustworthy
do you think they would have not followed through just like low art and and uh and uh
oh liliah and all these other losers that i failed to collab with it it took them 10 months
to select a a like like the roster for people who were doing art uh weird yeah very weird
when they said it would take them like a like a couple like a week a couple weeks 10
that just speaks to like some weird priorities or something by the way my quest my sub quest this
round is to i have to drop i want to drop this weird egg into fire and hatch it into a serpent
that's my that's my that's um that's something i want that's something i want for myself
mm-hmm yeah wait wait so so why did you say that you just didn't happen to do this newsletter
thing or that you didn't want to for a reason uh i think i was just like
what's the point i was just like eh you know that sounds kind of neat maybe i'll do it but
kind of lazy eyes i'm not even gonna worry about it you know i just like didn't really worry about
it imagine if you had like a like one of the like like the first vaporette but it's in there
and it's just like a small interaction i mean that just seems like why wouldn't i do that
i gotta fuck i gotta write some vaporettes because i am trying to hopefully do the
fucking vapor's three vapor's two kickstarter sand i need some fucking vaporettes for that
i want to do another one and don't worry i won't try it all this time good good as we discuss
trying is the trying is the path to failing my vapor is sick though yeah um kazi wants to do one
i told her she wants to do one vaporettes are cool i told her she could months ago
like months and months ago and uh sometimes she makes fun of me i still haven't given her one
to do because i haven't written anything oh i mean and that's fair you know whatever yeah i mean
instead of writing vaporettes you should be writing real vapor's which is what you're doing so
yeah yeah pretty much um i
one you know
i don't know i haven't thinking about like thinking about like uh money and like my future
uh oh uh oh i know right i'm just thinking like in the absence of some kind of hard to foresee
event where like i gain a lot of exposure very fast you know like i don't know if my audience
i don't know if like my my audience is gonna grow like i you know i've been wondering about
my growth potential like i did the poo videos kind of because i thought it was like it would
might be a good way to grow and reach new audience uh turns out no um i don't think the poo audience
is that big i mean do people know what poo is i don't know i thought i thought it'd be interesting
tom is telling us about that that video series the digi i think i think he did it i think for
fron games did you retrospective of the tales of series yeah that's a good video i actually
really like that also i mean i think i'm in it sort of wait were you i don't know but he
mentions me by name because one of the characters he named one of the characters after me and he
reminds of me that's that's cool yeah uh but like like that was to like capitalize on like it was a
series that like not people have a lot of people to talk about maybe there wasn't a quote-unquote
community for but like a lot of people like it and remember it so it might be a good thing it was
it was like that where it's like maybe like maybe it's not like a poo community per se but it's like
you know everyone knows like people are nostalgic for it people remember it people are interested
to hear about it that's i don't know that was the idea it didn't work out and i don't know why
but whatever um so so you're afraid you're stagnating you're you're plateaued well
well i mean in terms of audience in terms of reach sure like what's how like how do you get big
how do people how do people even fucking get big i think the way you get big is what we were talking
about earlier you focus on one thing do it a lot i don't think that's true munchie because i see
people that do that and don't get big example i could name a dozen people in my fucking twitter
who make comics i'm not doubting i'm first of all i'm not trying to doubt that that like that
is possible or that even is not the case i'm just saying there might be something they aren't doing
correctly like like like like i don't know if that necessary like there are a lot of things that go
into like someone's success online and i think that i don't know just because there are people who
are doing that but like but not succeeding is the case because there are people who do succeed
that do do that you know i think those people are the exception well then what do you think
or they are doing right does is luck do you think it's luck yes yes basically basically
a hundred percent okay yeah i mean maybe that's a little pessimistic well it's not a hundred percent
i mean but like i mean okay like obviously you have to be a certain level of talented
think about that lots of people are that level of talented i think people don't really talk about a
lot it's you do have to even if you're not talented in the way that we would think if you're not
interesting or something no matter what it like i'll take being a youtuber uh yeah to be
my same here no matter even if you're just like a shit boilerplate uh like like an analyst you
still have to work hard to put out videos yeah it's not yeah no listen talent and hard work are
necessary but not sufficient okay and i think the last thing is you just have to get lucky
and some people do and some people don't there's nothing you can do the only thing you can do
about it is keep trying and and not give up and like let let it just just keep hoping i would say it
depends i don't know i don't know if that's i mean i think there did you ever do you ever do this
do you ever like find some content or a content creator and just look at like you know a little
sample of their work and then try and guess like hmm what do i think this person's making on patreon
you ever try never play that game no i don't i play that game yeah is it only would you say it's
more or less or just just fluctuate it's just a fun thing to get i got it a long imprisoned
serpent it looks hungry but wait hello can you hear me yeah can you hear me yes i can hear you
is it is higher is it lower than you expect or is it just fluctuate no the thing the thing is
that i'm pretty good at guessing and i get pretty close a lot of the time and i don't know what that
means like that i can just like sometimes you can just look at someone's work like what kind of videos
they're making and just be like i bet i bet i know what this i bet i know how much this person's
making on patreon and like i get pretty close and i guess that means that there is a correlation but
like you maybe it is like predictable and like gameable and it's not just luck because like if
you can predict it based on what they're making then like clearly there's a rhyme or reason behind it
i don't know if there's ever a patreon that i feel like it doesn't make sense for the person
that it makes that that that means like in the sense that like it's either way more or substantially
less i'm trying to think if there's a patreon that doesn't make sense in the sense that it's
either way more or substantially less than what i would imagine they're making i can only think
of anyone that doesn't like fit in a way but it might just because it is what it is and i haven't
really thought about it till now so it just makes like like of course it's that that's what's always
better
uh i don't know you like fuck oh dead i'm just i got the fucking serpent i got the
fucking serpent but i didn't feed it enough price you you come across people online that you think
should be making way more than they are right that's not a weird thing to observe
yeah mostly me well it's mostly it's artists like artists and well sure well i mean the thing
like the difference is hard you mean like visual art is that what you mean like specifically yeah
yeah yeah like the difference the difference in skill between like a person who's making thousands
of dollars and a person who's making like tens can be like nothing and it makes me so mad
just thinking about it and if you want if you want to make money as an illustrator online
you gotta do porn yeah and you can't and i don't get it i don't get who gives you money for that
uh they just want to do well make their we go hard
by seeing so many ways to do that there's so many ways to do that why do you need to give
your money to this specific person to accomplish that aim i don't i don't get it
uh you like dart style i i guess yeah sure i mean i would never do it it's it's never something
i would want to it's it's always so disheartening though to see someone who you think should be
earning a lot but then just they aren't it's so weird okay i well i mean i i mean i am one of
those people so i have no pity for anyone uh i found this channel that i really enjoy called
j foreman and he's like a he's a british dude who makes videos he makes video series talking about
um for instance he has a series where he talks about like unfinished public works projects in
london talking about like very specific i know like like unused train lines and stuff like that
and like plans for highways that never got built that sounds like the kind of thing that is not
interesting but could be made interesting with the right sort of narration style he does he does yeah
yeah um how and and you think this guy's gonna have no views but he's extremely popular well
maybe not extremely but he's way more than 100 100k followers 100k subs no dude almost 400k wow
wow okay god damn yeah he doesn't break a million on any of his videos but he gets
sort of close sometimes and is usually usually on like one of his main series he gets like above
500k um pretty good so he's doing good youtube wise but his patreon is just like a thousand dollars
that's not bad that's not bad that's nothing to complain about it's nothing to complain about
however i don't know it sort of feels disconnected from me from his subscribers and his views to his
low for 400 you know you know 500k for something so for something so like weird and something that
like nobody else is doing that's the kind of thing that i would expect to have a disproportionately
high patreon yes exactly that's what i'm trying to say it's like yeah i don't know how this has so
many views but so many not people who resonate with it it's not like these are like particularly like
boilerplate videos at all i mean even just by their subject matter they aren't popular i wouldn't
imagine like there's a guy called um there's a guy called krug smash who makes like he makes like
narratively focused dwarf fortress let's plays they're really good and he does art for them and
stuff and they're he's he's he's got some really that's some really great stuff but he makes like
i think he's only gotten the tens of thousands but he makes like uh he makes like a like like three
or four thousand dollars a month on patreon or something like a relatively small audience um
because it's niche because it's niche and nobody else does it the way he does that's the thing like
how can you watch these videos be one of like the like almost a million people who have done so
and then like and like subscribe to him but then like not care enough about this weird niche
interest to like patron him like why are you watching this it just feels weird i don't know man
maybe it's not it's not the fact okay it's not okay if it was just like he was getting
shit views and his patreon that was that i would understand yeah yeah exactly it's just that he's
getting so much views like it's it's just that his views are weird to be this seems like the kind of
thing that a small group is really passionate about and you would think they would be like you
know really eager to support him yeah that's that is that is what i would like think but instead it's
weirdly mainstream and no one really cares enough well i i i don't i don't want to care
rise his patreon is this it's like it's like uh you know it's not a wasteland yeah yeah yeah
but you get what i mean i get you yeah hmm i mean who's someone else who's got like 400k
i mean i'll bet i yeah in g question mark let me tell you no he's like three he's like less than
three oh he has equal amount to him so he's at 375 and the guy i'm just like oh literally the
exact same 375 both of them no shit yeah i should also mention by the way that this guy's been on
like the bbc and stuff so like he's like really popular in the uk i suppose or at least like the
london area question mark hmm maybe it's a demographic thing like maybe british people don't
patreon as much or something you know maybe aren't we lucky to be in america and every and all
art is catered towards us yeah i think the answer is yes it is i agree i mean it's convenient i don't
know well i mean would i really care if like every story i read was set in england no that wouldn't
bother me i don't know if that's i just mean uh well it's not the fact that just it's it's set in
another place but just i don't know like our the culture we have is so ubiquitous in everything
ranging from like narratives to like the like just settings of narratives to just like like anything in
art is made with like the americans might want to watch this unless it's like something super niche
like anime or something count counter argument i mean that yeah american culture is pervasive
but not just in media just in general so like well sure other places kind of have a lot
have pretty similar cultures anyway so like if american media is made for an american audience
an audience with american sensibilities that is actually a lot of the world beyond america
because there's so much like cultural lead over um i don't disagree with all i don't think that i
mean i mean i think that's true i i also think that if for instance you live in a vastly different
culture you the like the sort of stuff that might appeal to you like well okay well actually
let me rephrase that it might be that you kind of maybe not are forced to at all but just like
you know a lot of art is you know for like american sensibility and uh it might not be based around
not like the overwhelming majority of things might not be uh it's something that you might want to
partake in as a member of a different culture kind of talking about my ass right now dude i love
partaking in culture i hate it you know what you're right sorry uh the why i'm looking at
patrons right now you've got me interested uh did you hear about try and get play the game
try and try and like when you find a content creator and you see they have a patreon it's
trying guess it's trying trying to do that do you know about patreon pro no oh ben i don't think
you're gonna like this hold on a new update coming to patreon uh they're raising the cut of how much
they get they uh uh they get or they take from creators uh and they're having it scale
with how much money you make wait what explain yes so okay you can go to patreon.com slash uh new
creator plans uh literally do that literally do that right now i i don't i'm trying to find the rat
you're never gonna do it then no i got a good feeling about this one so they're doing sort of
like a twitch affiliate thing almost kind of what youtube does where when you're a small patreon
and you're starting out you don't have as many tools available to you so there are gonna be three
tiers of creator there's going to be picture on light patreon pro and patreon premium oh my god
okay and when you start out a patreon you can't have multiple like tiers of of like of like um
like like donation okay so uh so you can't like for instance if you just start out a patreon
you cannot have like five dollar month patrons get this one dollar a month patients get this
ten dollar pensions get this you cannot do that now if you just start a patreon
but like old patreon old patrons won't be effective um no they won't okay ones will uh
well i don't why i don't know what what what do they what do they gain from that
well let me read their blurb yeah sure oh okay like they say new creator plans then immediately
they say in bold no change for current creators on patreon so like please don't get mad at us if
you're already on patreon like if they okay so clearly they know this is like a bad and unpopular
thing why do they want it okay let's see patreon has grown in our community of creators has grown
with us we now serve so many different types of creators from a painter with 100 fans who created
business with 100k fans and a staff of 25 this allows us to tailor our offerings to different
types of creators we're also introducing a new payment processing rates for our future creators
including a new low rate of payments for three dollars or less um so basically wait i'm interested
in that part because that actually might make me more money um well they they're they're having
a tax in the rich scenario i yeah exactly explain um okay so okay this could this could be good or
bad for me um i'm trying to see uh with new low rates for smoke okay future creators will choose
one of the above plans uh detailing light probe premium and we'll have new payment processing
rates including a special low rate for small pledges pledges of three dollars or less we'll
use the micro payment rate of five percent plus ten percent for successful payment wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait five percent plus ten percent plus ten cents okay oh okay so it's not
it's not by how much a creator is making it's by how much the individual donation is
yes oh that sucks that's fucking stupid okay so here are the rates for new um
patron things and this does affect you yeah uh uh okay okay so if you're a light user so it means
you just start a new a new patreon get five percent which i believe it is now wait no no
stop stop hold on i'm very confused because it sounded like you were just saying that the
the rate depends on the pledge not based on the creator and how much they're making
that why i just described the three dollars thing i was just talking about previously
that it only affects small pledges that affects the pledges that people make we're not to explain
now is related to the patron thing they're they're not related they are just they're just changes
that are separate but they have to be related because that that doesn't make any sense but the
the the amount that they're taking the the amount of cut they're taking
has it can't like those those things those things don't exist in a vacuum like yeah like the pledge
has an amount and the creator is making an amount and if the amount of that they're taking in fees
depends on one or the other it matters which is no okay okay it's not that they're not related
but it's okay it's like um okay the base rate if you're a light member of patreon which is like
the lowest tier is is is five and when you go up the leaderboard and you get to a pro status
once you have more patrons it goes up from five percent to eight percent but if you have people
who are still pledging like we're pledging you even though you have a higher percent or you have
more patrons and you are a bigger patron and you are a pro patron user if they are doing smaller
pledges they they still have the base amount they send you so five percent do you get what i'm saying
no okay well it makes sense okay okay okay okay let's say you're let's say you are a creator
you are a pro creator
and you and the baseline every person who pageants you uh patron takes a eight percent cut
let's analyze two patrons of yours one person who does one dollar and one person who does twenty
dollars the person who pledges twenty dollars will be affected by your higher rate of eight percent
because that's what that that's the base rate for your patron your your patreon now okay but small
pledges are affected at their own like smaller amount yes okay you know what that does make
sense i i got you okay okay um so it goes up to to eight percent uh but for you it will stay five
percent just so your grandfather did uh for premium users it goes up to 12 percent if you're new
and nine percent if you're old so so this means my rate's gonna go down so that's good well oh wait
um i guess yeah okay you know what you're right it will well but but if you will write but but but
if you grow more then it will go down uh well yeah but i'd be growing more uh true so worth it
well this actually sounds like a well i mean i'm gonna have to look this over
but it sounds like another thing to mention is that features are are gated behind
other but but not for me because i am already having a count no they will be gated for you
still like what um i don't think anything that you might care about but there are there's stuff like
um you can have let me here let me see uh there's there's there's some bulletless here uh dedicated
partner manager which i'm not really sure what that means merch for membership which i believe
is some sort of like patreon built in merch store and a team account which might affect
i i don't know if we were at a higher level that might have effect pc yes not this sounds like none of
it affects me um well also also by the way um hold on hold on wait actually let me see
i guess it would be bad if it affected the pcp
as well that would affect me indirectly no i wouldn't affect me directly actually
i'm trying to read it's kind of hard to parse something here okay premium is the best for
creators that expect to make at least 2500 a month on patreon so the 12 percent fee equals to 300
dollars a month do you have to like opt in or is it automatic no no no okay then what's the
point of saying it's best for it's like it doesn't matter we're forcing it on you
fucking god i i hate patreon i hate their attitude
this ensures our costs provide the services to premium yay i got it okay so they're saying if you
make over 2500 a month of that they will take uh 300 dollars in processing
um what percentage is that about 12 percent oh yeah okay well uh okay so that's a little more
because i think they take like nine percent now no they take five percent they take five percent
wait they take five percent now yeah oh what it was more than double i thought they take nine percent
okay well in that case then it's only bad so we so all that's happening is that they're just
taking more from big creators and taking the same amount from small creators yes uh unless you are
i think in your case if you were to have created a a patreon uh after these changes are implemented
and you are a new account they would have been charging you more like and you had the same
amount of money that you're making if you just had a new account and you didn't you didn't have the
grandfathered in rates then you would then they would be taking more from you because you were
like a medium fuck um hmm all right well sounds well awful bad okay stupid um
um um what's that other patreon alternative subscribe star subscribe star yeah maybe i should
make a subscribe star but it has a bad name been it has a stupid name yeah but well look i mean i
haven't looked that deeply into it but i mean i complain about patreon a lot i'm sure i'm sure
that i'm sure there's at least one nazi on there though so i think we might have to label the entire
operation uh stephen molyneux on there uh i don't i don't like that i don't like that guy yeah
we got we got to do something about him uh we got to be black warming insert poorly edited uh
youtube poop of the end of star wars episode three where obi once says you're supposed to
destroy this if not join them yeah but anakin's face is replaced with the old patreon logo
you should make that you should just make that and it would probably go viral on you know what
literally literally it might yeah literally it might uh oh if i had been like literally the day
was announced i i fucking to shit you not that probably would have literally gone back the day
that this announcement was announced yeah yeah yeah well you fucked up yeah i guess i did
well doesn't didn't dick masterson make his own patreon alternative he did but like it's uh
you know i you know you he has to like personally accept you right it's not like just anyone can
sign up for it and like apparently he just like does it like from his own like bank account
uh okay so i'm sure he isn't looking to like you know make it a huge platform with tons of
because like you know so i'm sure it's just going to be like for a couple of people that he thinks
need you know the patreon alternative he's like wants to personally endorse or whatever subscribe
about star please change your name it's so shit um yeah i mean i don't know is it too is it that bad
like how bad is it i think i think it's pretty clunky i think it's pretty stupid and clunky
subscribe star yeah it's pretty it's not it's not it's not great patreon is a lot more it feels
like off-brand like like something you would like like it there's it's like um it's like it's like
an off-brand soda it feels like it feels like mr. pibb to to do patreon i mean are you sure you
would continue to feel that way if it became something that a lot of people used or is that
just your bias is that just your your currency bias or whatever recency i don't know whatever
i don't think that like the the thing itself is i just think the name is like that i don't i
i i think the actual thing itself i know what you're saying i'm just saying what if people like
what if it caught on and it was big and everyone was on subscribe star would it still sound like
like bargain bin patreon i don't know i don't think it's i don't think it's too bad it's not you
know whatever i'll take it i'll take it yep there you go subscribe star i love you don't ever change
please don't adapt ever no
look look look look at it they got um they got the lighthouse project um okay definitely know
who that is yeah yeah yeah yeah they got um um military the history visualized cool sure yeah
what why not uh shon fits jerald uh that's just a household name it is yeah um yeah don't you
know don't you know about scott fits jerald i'm sorry shon fits jerald he um he made that one thing
on youtube oh i love that one thing i got a patreon him love i'm sorry subscribe i'm sorry i love that
one thing i want to go to the boss and i want to go to the boss and college and table really bad
right now by the way i'm just depressed that i haven't gone it makes me so sad it's not that hard i
know that's the point and i don't know i don't know why i didn't i have like no reason not to
and i just didn't do it been i'm gonna set an alarm shit for you to pasture you Wednesday night to go
isn't it Thursday i know that's what i'm saying so the night before you know what yeah it'd probably
be good for me uh i'm saying this up right i'm i have been i mean double-edged sword i have been very
i've had very little in the way of distraction i've gotten a lot of work done on vapors on the other
hand i've had like no social life um so you know that's that's that's it that's the thing i i i could
foresee this being somewhat well okay i mean it obviously depends you might go there it might be
just like shit and make you depressed and feel like no one's ever changed like you described earlier
yep but i don't i don't think it's unlike i don't think if you were to bet if i was a gambling man
i would not bet against the fact that you might even it might be useful to you to just even just
to be around other comic people and not even just necessarily show your own thing but though obviously
that would be an official name but uh to do what i was describing earlier about like i don't know
i i kind of feel like i'm losing out not really knowing what other comic people or what other
youtubers are up to i feel a little like i'm losing out in that way yeah totally i don't know i you
know i've thought a lot about that like about my feelings of like complete and utter disconnect
from the like comics community as a thing and and just like i i feel like maybe i this kind of
come it's sort of related to the whole like you know don't spread yourself too thin you know master
of one and all uh like you know maybe i should have tried harder to get into that whole thing maybe
i would be maybe i would have a better like network or something if i had like quoted that more
in some way but i don't know i just don't know i don't even know what i think about i don't even
know if i think it's good i i mean i'll tell you this bit yeah you go to bostoncomics.com
and you you you scroll down in boston comics round table it's just bostoncomics.com as the
is the urinal they have um and they have a promotional image for lgbt comics from the
boston comics round table and it is this image of presumably all of the lgbt comic authors all
their characters and like a big group shot and this just screams to me like people who go here
are connected they know who each other are yeah and it is a very clear community that has formed
here and i think because it's so close to you and it's so related to your work and it's not at all
hard to go to i think there's almost no reason not to attend this thing i almost no reason not
i just you know again i have known for this whole year that there's no reason not to
do i'm just like i just find you know i just find excuses if if hold on i'm i'm gonna i'm
gonna link to find excuses not to do the thing that i want to do unequivocally
all right okay boy what boy i'm sure would suck to go do that thing
imagine vincent and magna here it underneath the being true pride flag i can't for you the lgbt
conica it's just too it's too good to be true i you put but you know what maybe i should dream
bigger look look at this shit look all these varied characters you could be one of them
let me see hold on look look at all these very these varied characters who all look like they
were designed by someone who just got out of college and they just are a person
why are you showing me this what you're so are you supposed to be encouraging me
no what okay that's so boring it's so it's so fucking dull oh wait i remember
i remembered why i'm not involved in the comics community or go to any of these things or or
or care care about this at all is because i'm a big fucking elitist who turns his nose up at
everyone else's shit the things that's retarded yep that's what and that's what i'm doing that's
doing okay but whatever that image does not fill me with confidence was that drawn by erica
moan was that drawn by erica moan it looks like it was drawn by erica moan but it probably wasn't
it's i don't think she lives here was that drawn by so that person that i hate i don't hate erica
moan do you know who she is no i have no clue she's the ojoy sex toy lady oh i hate only joy six
toy i walk out do you there's there's no reason i would i would understand it looks ugly yeah i
don't fuck you know i like i've said this before i really liked erica moan as a person on strip
search um all of her work is dumb and bad and bad well i mean i'm not interested in it and i don't
like it um which is a shame it's like all of her work is the autobio stuff it's like an autobio
like like like a diary comic that's one that's one big thing she did uh it was oh she did like a
story comic about like a kid finding a lost bicycle and like having to team up with juggalos or
something which sounds really wacky but it's actually totally pedestrian and fuck i shouldn't
have killed that guy with a cape um he's actually like a bonus thing you're supposed to collect
whatever i i thought that's that that's what the child juggalos did during oh no no no that's
whatever anyway that one was fine but it wasn't that interesting wasn't that funny it's just
whatever and then she did ojoy ojoy say after going on strip search uh robert coup advised her
to go in a direction that ended up leading her to ojoy sex toy which naturally was a huge success
for and made her a billion dollars not really but in comics terms it did and uh everyone hates it
also what the fuck's the cup what is that is that what it's called what the fuck yeah what the
fuck yeah what the fuck's the cup oh god it's you know it's pretty funny i don't i don't get
anything out of ojoy sex toy yeah but whatever you know follow follow your bliss i guess
yeah hey let me let me talk about my let me talk about my sour grapes let me talk about my um
ben i was unaware that there was any other aspect of your personality other than sour grapes okay
so i was listening so i've been um i've been listening to so i was breeding alone in my room
late one night as i as i often that goes without saying um like in just like layer that on top of
everything else that i say um i was um i've been listening to the uh fucking i don't don't
ask me why i'm doing this i've been listening to the like penny arcade like a dnd podcast that they do
um like the c team for example mostly the c team which has as one of its players
erica or not erica amy falcone um who was on strip search and actually everything i just said
is unrelated there's um okay but there was another thing i saw i saw like an interview
with amy and um oh god who's the one that did last halloween she was at mice i'm i'm i think
she also amy whatever the one i did last i'll wait these two contestants that were on strip
search i saw an interview with them and so the interview is asking them a bunch of stuff
what because they because they moved in together they briefly became roommates they're talking about
that and i think one of the questions was something like where would you be where would you be if you
had not been on strip search and they both like laugh sort of nervously and say like oh my god
like my life would be so bad if i had not been on strip search and i leaned back and i realized that
ben saint who is not on strip search and living in these two people's personal hell
um what do you think about that i think okay so so you're you're saying like they've made a big
and they're like they're they're economically big and embarrassed to even consider like like
like their idea of like oh god if i if i wasn't famous god if that if that hadn't happened like
everything would suck yeah like like i would just be like toilet in the way just like like
kind of doing stuff in the void and no one would be reading my stuff yeah and you feel
like wait a second that's me that's what's happening to me so i i am the failure i'm the bad timeline
yes that's right well you know what the solution has been you have to be on strip search
you say that like i don't think about that every single day of my life you fucking
wait okay is it actually still running no that's okay no i would fucking
god pester them relentlessly let me i mean this is fucking i've talked about this before it's
fucking sad whatever i'll say it again uh like i saw strip search and i was like this is the coolest
thing ever i want so bad they and they said they were gonna do another one i was like i want so bad
to be on to be on this to be a part of this um so what i'm gonna do so like i'm like it's for
me to actually i'm gonna fucking start drawing you know like more than i did before this was one
of the things that got me like to start taking it more seriously and i was like you know my like i
boy like i hope that like maybe by the time they do strip search too i'll have like you know
i'll hone my skills i'll have more of a following you know maybe it maybe it could make it happen
season two never happens and and well and what did i get out of nothing it was all worthless
it's it's you know what what like what what's a person to do literally what's a person to do
how do you get ahead in this fucking doggy dog world if you if you can't be in strip search
what can you do uh i mean i guess you know i mean i guess i'm being kind of a little baby
about this because like i have the pcp most people don't have the pcp i have the pcp that's
pretty good that's something it is something i mean yeah um but it's not strip search everything
else is inferior nothing else matters even even a little bit um then what anyway anyway this
thought really depressed me and that's it that's the story what would you say is when would you
pinpoint the exact moment when the upward momentum of the pcp died and we uh became the worst people
on earth you know there's a lot of directions you could come at that from do you mean like morally
creatively uh influence wise well all of the above different discussion for each one but i
have to piss really badly i actually have to too um i gotta kill the cannon ball rod
are you kidding me right now dude like get real like get real right now don't you know about
who he is he made my favorite fucking pinning arcade god it's been insane just alone in my
fucking room again for the last time why fucking penny arcade why are you so cruel
only i was if only i was taiko yeah i would love to be taiko i sit alone in my room and
i grew it about how much i wish i had the penny arcade guys lives okay listen okay imagine okay
forget like ben saint strip arch a u imagine ben saint and poker night the inventory imagine you
talking to the heavy i don't know what that means oh oh do you know what the inventory is no is it a
team fortress two thing no it's it's okay it's a steam game that um was like like a game i have no
fucking clue how it was made it is a poker game where you play against you play in a game of poker
with max the rabbit from i forget a serious name but you know you know you know max the rabbit
sam and max uh i mean sort of you know who he is you know what i'm referring to right i
generally yeah okay uh strong bad from home store runner the heavy from team fortress two
and taiko from pinning arcade okay yeah sure of course um gotcha i'm picking up what you're
throwing down okay yeah all right i'm gonna have to link you an image check check all these disparate
art styles imagine your your taiko this scenario um why are they pointing guns at
he said something wrong what what did he say wrong was it the was it was it the dick wolves thing
listen they've apologized for the dick wolves thing okay there's there's nothing to be done
now there's nothing to be done they're gonna kill them and that could have been you and
and then in the in the fable timeline that could have been you uh
jerryford k horkins aka taiko just spends his entire life just fucking around
bro bro his room saying god i wish it was been saying it was on the fucking pcp no he spends
his entire life just fucking around like running d&d campaigns with his friends making raps about
his oc in said campaigns just having a fucking time of his life every day that's what i want
but instead i'm fucking i'm fucking bound by the human condition unlike that
unlike that living god jerry horkins taiko living god do you know what you know what he looks like
right like in real life yeah yeah good living god
what what what fuck you what what do you want well you see i can't resonate with you because
because because i i shot an aim and landed my entire aspirations to be a part of the
horse your crew and i fulfilled my destiny and now i have nowhere to go well sorry munchie some of us
some of us have real ambition in this world some some of us know what's up yeah impossible
okay i am i am entering i'm entering the lair of the rowdy rat by the way really really yeah do you
think you can do it i'm uh i mean yeah it i wouldn't say it's impossible i'm pretty good i got full
health so it's five hearts that's decent it's not terrible malax this is what you get for
fucking trying to kill her i've gotten i've gotten the opposite of that actually i've gotten both of
the uh chamber like health upgrades so that's that's i'm on track
i actually have to pee um i don't want to i don't want to do this distracted do it together come on
there he is there he is i don't know where his horns went maybe it's like his cousin or something
i don't know been pissed together come on dude all right fine i'm going all right i'm going right
now all right let's go all right let's go all right all right pee break everyone pee break
so
hello i'm just having back yet back from the pee break all right well that was got here before
i won got here before you anyway as i was saying jerry jerry jerry and mike just they they got
they got so successful off the backs of like a stupid gaming webcomic they continue to do out
of sheer pseudo creative momentum that they can just do shit that nobody cares about except them
like the fucking irwood nobody gives a shit about the irwood but they're just all about it and they
love it they have the time of their lives i hate them
okay there has to be something practical we can do here we have to turn this anger
in to some sort of like all right how did they get my my guan stones are fucking glitching out
like crazy right now your jio crystals yeah that's right that's right that's correct you did it
you know what okay i've always been a big proponent of like you know i i feel as though you look at
like the top youtube creators or the creators in general and like well sure there's luck there and
you can say they don't have a lot of talent in the way that we would describe it there's obviously
hard work there yeah but i'm trying like there's obviously like like like uh purified and get where
he was by just being idle and just pure luck no not to say that luck is not in a factor you'd never
say that you know if you retarded to say that but um there's obviously something actionable there
where don't you live with don't you know we live in a in a meritocracy month you don't
know that under capitalism everyone always gets exactly what they deserve um everyone has the
exact same starting uh like like everyone starts the exact same level in every way yeah and and
they're rewarded proportionally to their you know to the value that they offer to the world 100%
of the time fuck fuck okay i'm fuck sorry i'm i'm fucking up uh hold on wait one second i just
find okay hold on one second i'm never never mind actually i'm retarded never mind i was i was
going i was going to um say that uh i found you google search pewdiepie one of the first thing
that comes up for me i have no idea why is a video from this person named no life shack
pewdiepie bitch lasagna reaction first time hearing and i was about to say that uh
pewdiepie is so famous that even just reaction videos by no one get a million views but this
guy only has 900 or 900 and one views so i'm now just baffled on why google gave this to me
and why this was one of the first results when pewdiepie came up same so uh cool great
what a mystery it the answer is gotta be just like you just try hard right that's gotta be
how the world is i i want to believe yeah but it's not you just no yeah but it's wrong it's wrong
though it's the only problem there no it can't can't be yeah no sorry it might be i guess
yeah uh and it's very discouraging um
you know it's such major ass i don't know i'm not convinced that i like it can't be manipulated
um i mean it's not that it can't be manipulated it's just that it more it gets more of a chance
there it's just yeah that and there are just um i mean there are ways to manipulate it but not
all of them are possible for everyone and you know there's only so many there's only so many ways to
do it sure you know to to game the system one way or another you have to quote unquote sell out
and i guess it's just a matter of personal preference whether um any of the ways you might do
that are palatable to you and i guess the key is finding a way to do that that is
hmm but but okay like the most influential art on my entire life home stock yeah i wouldn't say
is like a selling out product or is like super almost not at all yeah yeah and that's super
popular you know it's not popular enough and it makes me mad every day that um homestuck is
remembered as anything other than a than a brilliant masterpiece that like anyone says anything bad
about homestuck now i hate them they're cowards what what what bubbler okay wait okay what what
what do you mean that like it's not popular enough it was really popular it was really popular
like people don't like it anymore people talk shit about it that's what you do like you when
people say homes when people say homesuck nowadays they don't mean anything good by it
but that means that that's really determined on who you talk to there are many people who like
everything about homes okay many people many yes i would say the majority fuck fuck fuck i didn't
die i didn't die but i'm going to um
oh god i got him and i oh man i landed on a i landed on a mousetrap but as it so happens it
was in the cutscene okay um okay here to conclude that thought uh i just i think that the zeitgeist
about homestuck now is that it's just sort of an awkward embarrassing thing i think that's
i think that's the general opinion and yeah i know it's got its fans i know a lot of people
still love it and look back fondly on it and everything i don't think that's the majority
opinion it makes me mad i'm mad thinking about it right now i can make
i can make two mistakes i can make two mistakes in this next battle or i'll die
if i make any more of that it really depends on who you talk to
like i'm trying to think about like the homesick community okay okay well okay first of all
the zeitgeist and homesick like faded of like of course like it's nowhere near as popular as it
once was nobody had about that that's fine i just i think people remember it generally people's
big like say it with like a roll of their eye
you know what i actually think i agree but that and maybe not the same way because okay
fuck i think i think that was an easy one for people to fuck god damn it like this is it that's
it watch this video oh you're fucked up you died yep yep well i got further than i did before i
got to a second phase it's uh it's um it's easy for people to watch this and who have
watched armor shield will be like yeah homesick fucked up but it was good in a lot of ways which
is my opinion that it's my favorite thing in the entire world and it makes me mad when i think
about certain aspects of it but like what i want it to not have happened because it makes me upset
in some ways of course not homesick is the best art ever made yeah um but i think okay i think
the majority opinion knowing what i know about the homesick community which i wouldn't say that
okay i'm in bro hold on hold on hold on hold on if we're talking about the homestuck community
specifically i mean obviously it's going to be fondly remembered you know there uh i'm talking
about like the world at large i mean who like i don't mean the homesick community as it like
it currently exists i mean like like like seeing the the the dialogue of it transform over the years
and like people who used to be in homesick who aren't into homesick anymore taking them into
account i don't mean like just like like r slash homestuck okay i mean i i do mean the world at
large i think the general opinion well well to me the world at large includes people that never
read homesick okay well okay we just like have an opinion of it because like they don't like cosplayers
of it yeah hmm yeah okay i can i can see your point i would say okay all of the people who have
read homestuck i would say doesn't just piss you right the fuck off the people have the
fucking the people think they have any right to be like home stuck right uh yeah i completely
understand i would like that sort of thing because it's like they're like the fans are annoying at
homes or at the conventions i feel this way about steven universe two they're not even they were they
were a couple of times you know people who are like steven universe or are like undertale like
you know like that that thing fucking sucks like that's so stupid uh why oh the fans are bad
please like listen yeah i'll help you just kill yourself i'll help you i let me help you let me
help you with this problem you have in your heart yeah like a gun a knife medicine just there's many
way i'll help you i'll get it i'll get it for you we we have we as a society have come up with
solutions for this oh god damn it whatever okay yeah that that does make me really mad yeah okay
then i mean that's that's what i'm saying that's what i'm sure sure okay i get you i get you
i'm fucking up this run but not in a way that is gonna like permanently fuck me in the fight so
it's fine for now i just i took some bad damage but i can make up for it later
i'm i'm heartening i'm heartened that i made it to phase two i would i would just really like to
see phase three how long we've been gone like three hours uh we've been going for like yeah three
hours i think um i can't i can't see it what time do we yeah whatever um actually more like four
sick good that's on brand that is definitely on brand nothing is more precious in this digital age
than the brand there's so much content right now we're making so much like content for like our
fan base it i mean i mean you're not wrong you're not wrong my friend uh why am i saying no that's
fine that's good it's good to make a lot of content oh yeah it's my birthday well
also endless and it's when we're recording it's my birthday when you're hearing this it's endless
war's birthday and wait what was the other thing that happens on the 11th the 11th is the anniversary
of our reference cop killers is let's play yeah yeah yeah and shut up dog a few days ago from our
perspective was the anniversary of the rfck discord server what's the date for that the fifth of
april yeah they come in they come in two this should be like a holiday week and on the 13th of
april it's homesick's birthday which is basically like an endless war spinoff pretty much yeah yeah
i mean it definitely rolls in there the face and altar is terrible i'm not buying it okay uh oh uh
oh i think someone's gonna walk in the door i think i think my uh my disgusting family is here
getting there it sounds like it someone's there some shit's going on some shit i'm getting robbed
some human core shit some human involved like human core ak just involving people in any capacity
that's right that's correct god look at them howl
listen to the howling mob of blackheads in the street
i took a picture with leopards and the whole town's on its feet
he is dangerous ahead of its time does it have you know who could have predicted you know who would
have known they would have they would predict the rise of the unit and the uh and the gig economy
tyco won't you listen to me i've been your right hand man all along but every comic you make today
gets twisted around some other way you don't even plug my patreon this is you know next to you
seeing that tyco you're the judas to his jesus i wish i wish you know maybe the maybe the grass
i mean he got a whole movie about him um maybe maybe it's like grass is always greener it just
it just seems to me right from an outsider looking in right outside of looking in perspective
it seems to me like you meet the penny arcade guys under any circumstances you make them like you
you become their friend and from then on your whole life is just a fucking it's just a fucking
it's just a fucking it's just a no he fucking broke my water barrel idiot quick restart and from
then on you just play d&d and fuck around for the rest of your life and you just have a great time
well okay well actually okay i want to say something because i feel like it was too obvious
and i didn't say it because it was obvious but i actually feel like it might not be obvious
so i should say it please uh it's the the way to accomplish things is how the way that we have
accrued our success which is tied into what everyone else is doing that's collaboration i don't mean
like in a nebulous sense i mean uh like like i described in my college essay it's weaseling
into people's inner circles it's just it's 100 percent trying to be a no good weasel and just
trying to get people to like you you gotta wait what you're a star fucker munchie i am a star
fucker um by the way um i've shown that our fngr video to people like my like offline friends
obviously have no idea who fngr is or i have like a vague notion that like i make youtube videos
sometimes and so to them just like imagine like one of you like your friend like imagine like like
like little john just comes into your room and uh it's like hey i there's someone make a hit like a
hit video on me and he's listening it's just like a slimy fucking snake star fucker like like
mongoloid like munchie like or john like i hate you with all my heart and you and you will be the
downfall of everyone in in your life yeah and how jarring that would be oh that's it's great it's a
great experience it's um well what do they what do they say about it i'm curious they like can't
believe it or also are extremely confused they don't understand what he's saying half the time
because he speaks in such a way i mean that's just that's just fngr for you yeah um so okay
i don't know i don't know how much we can learn from that specifically but anyway okay so think
about like like that's that's very interesting if you didn't like just mention the fact that you
like digi in that one episode if you didn't become the tbap q and a yeah the tbap q and a or you know
with the other guys you wouldn't have a nearly the same audience that you do now yes the pcp would
not have happened and so on and so forth yes so i mean it's the answer is somewhat obvious it's
just a manner of how to in the brody community so small i bet so i so and yeah it's easy to think
if define people to like you just like and and express the fact that you like them and whoops
today isn't your best friends now it there's it's so easy to become a big fish in a small pond
and stuff like that whereas when you're dealing with like the idea of comics like the the comics
community that ranges from so many different things it's so hard to get into quote-unquote
with with when you're in a fandom it's so easy to be on the same page just watch the
latest episode of a show read the latest update of a comic you like that you can now discuss it
when you're you need to be in like the comics community it's like do we have to read all
comics now i don't want to do that no how fucking how could you um i've been thinking about this in
in with respect with respect to the whole round table thing it's really it's really actually
pretty surreal that you like brought up the round table on this episode because i had
been like thinking about it personally a bunch lately um i mean i have as well since i plan to
go there as soon as i am able to yeah um wait pause pause no okay um
oh i fuck what was i talking about i lost my i lost my train oh oh i was i was thinking about like
i don't know you want you want to get out there into a community to like make connections
right and like make friends make associates people to collab with or just be or just people
to like that you like and you like spending time with you know i think that's what a friend is
supposed to be uh if i if i if i recall my uh my latin um so you know you want you want to you
want to get out there in the world and do all that but like specifically with regards to like
making connections networking um i just have listen i know this is wrong i'm just i'm just like
afraid to like waste my time on people that have no i i know i know how that sounds and i'm
i don't mean to say that like oh like i see everyone as like a potential business connection
and if they have nothing material to offer me then i don't want anything to do with them
that's not even what i mean but just in in the in the i mean look i did this podcast with low art
i tried to make this i tried to make this book with this audiobook with fucking oh lilia
they i mean low art might still come through eventually but these guys they oh lilia might
too if i fucking pass through him for another who knows how long but the point is you know
people flake on you you waste your time you you invest your time what do you get back for it
you know usually nothing um and i mean i guess you just gotta keep chugging away at it
but it's just not a very it's not it's not very exciting to me doesn't sound great i
i talked about this on the pcp and i and i don't want to harp on it more but it's
a derid rate for this conversation since it's relevant i have been craving the fandom connection
for a while now and it's hard to get into because i don't know what i mean by the
fandom connection uh sort of what i just described a moment ago where it feels like
i don't have any connection to people like i don't really have anything to talk about with
other people because my entrance art shows where it's easy to communicate with people on a forum
or on tumblr or on a subreddit my interests are more abstract now like for instance i don't go on
the homestuck subreddit because while i like homestuck they don't really interact with it in
the way that i want to and i don't really know if i want to spend my time in that particularly
but sure i i just i felt like again i think a lot of this is like nostalgia a lot of this is no
depth like i just want things to be the way they were before but i do think there's so you know
things aren't the way they were before you wouldn't even recognize me anymore not that you you know
what i'm doing it's linkin park lyrics munchie linkin park get fucking educated um i've never
seen the room anyway i uh i i think there's something real there where it's like when you're
a part of a community and you're a fan of something it's so easy to make connections with other fans
of that specific thing for instance okay like you listener you fucking you you whoever the hell you
are fucking a frame yeah you are specifically yeah yeah um you bedfellow card card god koonrat
cheeky chicken crypto coin lever dolphin boy madish rampage marco boko uh deviated dr plague
frame matt uh steel viper arrow it's yeah you guys uh you are what i'm talking about i think
a lot about this and how it relates to endless war think about how great it would be to be an
endless war fan you have all these people uh based around this really small community
and it's not a lot of people but because it's not a lot of people and it's something that you
care about a lot it's so easy to make connections and to make fans to make friends i hear you yeah
imagine how yeah yeah you know imagine being able to like endless war instead of having it
just be a ball and chain around your ankle you know what i mean literally yeah yeah yeah fuck yeah
i i feel like like i envy that a lot i really do i really envy just being able to like
make friends and do stuff and like i feel like i've made friends a lot with the people in here
this is a thing that that wraps into what i'm you know yeah when you're a fan of something
right you're passionate about something you want to you want to share that passion with others you
you want to you know the community whatever the fuck you know um i just want to say by the way
that i want this like just to be a fan again i want to have that because okay before i cut down my
discord list i was in like 30 different servers all of them combined like the amount of unique
users was less than 100 probably yeah like in what in what in what in what in across the
discord servers what i mean by that is that like i was just surrounded by the same same people over
and over and over again who i talk to on a daily basis but fans of the pcp i communicate exclusively
with people who like know all there is to know about me in a way i and who are like fans of me
in a way and that doesn't like i don't think that legitimizes our relationship in any way but it's
just well i kind of want to be anonymous in a way sometimes maybe that's a little bit of a harsh
statement but like i just want to like exist i mean i can be anonymous of that context i mean
i can be anonymous in real life anytime i want uh i don't know i think there's something to be
something i want to be a part of a community where the community is not about me yeah i just want
to be a fan of something else again and be able to meet different people i feel so stifled by the
pcp audience i don't want to sound ungrateful at all i don't want to sound like so i have so many
fans but like it is a real feel that i have or i just i want to have different connections this is
this is kind of related who the cheat trigger finger do i want that i think i want that do i
have the money for i don't know okay what you're saying it's kind of related to what i was going
to say but you're coming at it from like a different angle the community angle i don't
have a i don't feel stifled by um you know a community well okay then yeah i just want to
say real quick i think i think the distinction here is to be frank you have your own identity you
have your own content that you have a you have your own unique sort of brand i i don't have that
i don't i don't i don't know if i'd say that i mean i understand what you're getting at
it i mean is what you're saying that like your identity is more tied to the pcp specifically
than mine yes yeah okay well that that might be true um
um
to an extent i mean i don't think it's as dire as all that but okay whatever i go what you're
saying i'll at least begin um my what i was coming at it was not the the problem of like you
know the community or whatever whatever um my my problem is it's it's it's it's i i would kind
of like to be a fan again i know i get i get you but like what am i passionate about
and you know it i don't know if this is like narcissistic but like what i'm passionate about
is my stuff like to the almost to the almost to the exclusion of everything not to the exclusion
but like to an extent that dwarfs everything else like i used to i used to go to like parties
or something and i and people would be you know oh everyone's a nerd there everyone's a geek you
know they're all involved in the geek culture and they're all excited they were talking about like
you know marvel movies like talking about lord of the rings talking about stuff that they liked
and i mean god i don't want to sound like an elitist because i don't judge them for that
i don't think that they're stupid for liking those things i i'm just i'm just i can't do it
you know then i completely agree with you and it's the subject of much personal strike
yeah because i i too like i don't play video games unless it's specifically with another person
and i can kind of justify in the sense that like i'm doing it with another person it's a social
experience i don't read things television shows fucking terrifying me i could never watch like
two seasons of something that you're joking me every million yeah i feel i feel maybe once every
like a couple months maybe dude yeah okay you get it you totally get it okay no i told i totally
get it then when i wake up i just think okay what do i want to do with today what art do i want to
create today to like the absolute like complete detriment like like what have i consumed in the
in the last week literally could not tell you probably the same games i played a thousand times
together for like maybe 30 minutes i can't think of a new thing i've watched oh i recently started
watching you know you know this is somewhat personal by recent started watching orange is new black
with kazi but like i had to stop because i got literally too intimidated by sheer length and
i was just like i just can't watch this i i can't watch a tv show that goes on that long
mmm it's just it's so much time i can't do it i can't watch television shows what's like what's
like i can't justify it what's like this i would like to have the experience of having you know
having something that i'm passionate about something i'm a fan of right and then like
becoming like having a community centered around that thing and like you know meeting people through
our like shared love of this thing yeah yeah yeah and okay but i'm i'm so sort of single-mindedly
uh uh devoted to like my own shit to the point that it kind of hampers my ability to engage with
other things completely agree and i hate it and i'm i'm so much like that but like and that might
be fine that might be fine if but like my like for that for that to fill that community void my
fan base or if you want to call it my yeah like my the community centered around my
shit would have to be bigger and it would have to be growing faster it doesn't there's not
not i don't have if i had like a vast following that was like way invested in like
like if ever like tons and tons of people talking about like oh what's the next chapter
gonna be oh what's the next thing he's gonna make whatever like i'm i want to talk about it like
like i could probably just engage with that and it would be fine but it's not enough i don't have
enough of a following that that fills the void for me do you know what i mean not not at the rate
not at the rate at which i produce content which based on which because of the format i produce
content in is just not that fast i i just think about how every single day like like all i do
is think about what i want to create and what i like like you know i think about in this war
updates i can make i think about like ways i could implement it and it techniques a quick draw
and it's so draining in a way not like i don't want to sound ungrateful i love the fact i love my
fans i love the fact that i'm able to do this i'm very privileged and it's fun like i would not
be doing our unless it was literally just fun for me to do and i'm sure i would be doing it
regardless yeah it's it's just that like it's like where am i gonna find the time to do other things
never when am i ever going to like wake up and there's a distinction here that i want to make
where it's like if i'm hanging out with friends which is something that i do somewhat often but
by that i mean like you know i'm paying them calls with people i can sometimes you consider watching
something or playing something though honestly not even that often i can't think of a single
fucking scenario where i would be at my computer and not at least thinking about my art i might be
absentmindedly consuming some media like like youtube videos i find no community or any sort of like
like i don't feel part of like a youtuber's audience or anything like that no whatsoever
yeah i might be doing that but there's never a moment where like i'm seriously like watching a show
watching a movie reading a comic and then like i want to discuss that like i cannot imagine that
and it's stupid it's dumb and it's bad for my art it's stifling me creatively i feel like i'm so
insular just like like it's it's bad for my art it's bad for my like my mental health i think to be
so like i don't have that barrier of people interacting with me yeah it's just bad but i
can't stop all i want to do is make suffer endless war all i want to do is do that because i'm just
fucking dumb i guess um boy uh i'm it's not that i didn't think you would understand but i am
surprised at the extent to which you are articulating the way that i feel about this kind of thing
you know then it's time like these where i where i remember that i think i think you're my friend
i think that we have we have similar elves on life and that's why we talk to each other
is that canon is that canon though i don't know if that's i don't know i don't know i i think i
think i'm still gonna command my child's soldiers to destroy your child's soldiers there we go that's
what i thought that's what i thought the deal was but i'm glad you reminded me of the deal i wouldn't
by the way buy fuck energy from slime corp dot com uh buy and bulk thirty eight dollars per uh
four pack for some you know energy yeah from fuck city um yeah yeah oh maybe this sounds
fuck city anymore i i like to call it once in a while just to throw people off yeah it's like the
big apple that's like calling new york the big apple um uh maybe this sounds weird to people
like to the to the kinds of people who are listening to this right now it probably sounds weird
right to that okay i wonder i wonder constantly to what extent
what if what if like everyone what if everyone was like me what if everyone who was like
listening to rfck watching endless war was like me listening to penny arcade
shit or or or and not not even fully engaged with it on a level where i'm like i'm like this
but like to a large extent of my fucking brain processes is like
like coveting you know what i mean
and we're so fucking pathetic we should be wiped off the map oh no what i mean we should
despawn we should fucking despawn wait we are you saying we plural yeah we plural do you know what
i mean do you i i of course i know i just want to be here you say that i just want to be here you
know i i of course i i feel that i feel that way about other people completely unjustified
yeah i feel that i feel the way about other people in the pcp completely unjustified and i wonder
well i mean it makes me wonder how many people are listening to this feeling the exact same way
about me like like like to me hearing amy falcone say if i hadn't been on strip search my life would
be shit and i think i have been on rfck my life and i yeah and i think i'm living i'm living her
personal hell and then someone listens to this and i and and one of us says like yeah if we hadn't
like formed a horseshoe crew made the pcp my life would be shit and they think i'm living their
personal hell and this and it's just and it's just hell all the way down it's just it's just
hell within hell i i i want to iterate to our fans that don't mistake the meaning in any way
i envy you i wish i was you so badly i don't you're nothing you're nothing i i want like
can you imagine if i like if i found in this war and how much you would gel with me because i
created it sure you know well yeah like i mean i mean it's not gonna it's not going to appeal to
anyone as much as you or that would be like a miracle if it did yeah yeah yeah yeah it like
i i i can imagine this would be frustrating to people you're gonna talk i i yeah totally they
don't get it and i don't want to sound like i'm imagining listening i'm imagining listening to
like amy falcone say this kind of stuff and i'm and i would be my reaction would be
be fuck you you are so fucking privileged you have no idea like what what i what i wouldn't
what i wouldn't have given fuck what i wouldn't give to have had the opportunities that you have had
die i i think this kind of goes back to this is what that's a lot of things in my life i i i'm
really like even though it's like it's fun it's funny the fact that i feel this way i feel like
weirdly like a camaraderie now yeah yeah yeah i want to talk about it and i want to
edit it because i'm ashamed of it and i don't say i express it and i don't express it um you know
like this it's funny that i say it's funny that i think this about these people specifically these
are not like famous people these are what the fuck okay sorry i'm mimic just attack me and it's
sorrowing me a little bit like these like these are not like huge person amy falcone has like
four thousand twitch followers this is not this is not like a fucking i think that might be you what
maybe maybe because like it's like it's closer like it's more tantalizing and close like i don't
like i'm not going to think about like what if i was what if i was a Bradley Cooper what if i was
yeah i was gonna say ninja but like you know whatever someone same thing someone huge well yeah
i'm not like like oh man i could have been like um i don't know who's fucking giant i mean i don't
want to say pew yeah pewdiepie yeah that's right um insane should be your new intro that's right
you're correct uh well yeah you solved it you cracked it you know we're wondering how do you
grow how do you grow your audience you just say the things he says yeah that's it you just say
pewdiepie that's my god i got my new catchphrase it's pewdiepie subscribe oh the youtube algorithm
will detect that you say pewdiepie i assume that you are pewdiepie and then recommend you to all
pewdiepie subscribers that's how you do it that's how you do it you gotta trick the algorithm
it's not about it's not about making appealing content it's about tricking a computer to promote
you it is though for real that's true a few things in my life yeah uh just ties into me
wanting to streamline my time this ties into me wanting to go to college and sort of almost
okay i don't i don't want to sound like a drama queen i don't want to sound
brash but sort of rethinking the way i've led my life in a way and sort of re-questioning
if i want to continue my life in the way that i've been living it in a way yeah where i think
streamlining my content has or a streamlining like like the way i think about work is not so
that i can work on my art better which it is but i want to try and force myself to socialize the
people who don't think of me as like a person they watch on youtube you know yeah i i really
want to try i have not done this whatsoever this is going to be a complete failure so far of me
trying to streamline my my life and my work and just try and socialize in general this is one of
the main tenets of of the year of more which i wanted to accomplish year of more i've not
described this uh it sounds familiar but i don't remember what the year of more is well it is a
yearly theme that i've been talking to for this year that i thought up in i think February or
maybe january where it's uh i have a theme for the year which i'm trying to live my life by and
i'm trying to uh accomplish oh you're trying to live moss i'm trying to live moss um say
he's speaking of live live live moss one of kazi's roommates won the talk about live moss
scholarship and she got college for free because she because just because you live because you
lived moss yeah because she lived moss and she is currently living moss right now that's that's
cool that's pretty cool um so i live moss that's that's fucking
okay this is gonna sound negative and normally it would be but i don't even think it's bad in
this case it's a little dystopian the live the live moss college scholarship yeah yeah yeah i
if you look something from idiocracy it does it totally does yeah but i like it but you know
but rarely in a way that i like and i'm totally behind 100 yeah it's it's really sick it's really
fucking sick yeah i wish that i got to live my scholarship i mean of course that's that's literally
the only reason it exists is so that people that don't get it would wish that they did yeah increase
brand awareness okay but anyway i've been trying to branch out my life in a lot of different ways
i've taken the the the the the word more i mean a lot you've taken the pepsi challenge and you
want the pepsi i want to do the momo challenge and i'm failing spectacular i think i'm afraid i might
kill myself soon well uh okay all right we'll keep we'll keep up and you never have back
me did did you win the momo challenge did you survive um listen i i have i have i have i signed
a contract uh that's uh i'm not allowed to say i'm not allowed to reveal the nature i just you
know like don't don't ask me these questions don't ask me these things i'll i'll be i'll be revealed
in in due time uh this was one of the main things i was thinking about in february or whenever i came
with this and i wanted to branch out more in like art as well as in social life and before you say
you want to live moss just keep saying i want i wanted to live moss in a lot of different ways
what the fuck what oh sorry i gotta i have a familiar i have a uh sick familiar now um
neat what would you look like well he is his sir junkin he's a piece he's like a dirty paper bag
and he's currently wearing a knight's helmet and if i upgrade him i can turn him into like an
angelic crusader that's cool that's really cool i that okay that's my new goal okay i got him i
just got him a shield okay am i new giving up giving up giving up giving up yeah just give up
well no no i can pursue them both in parallel okay okay so i wanted to animate more i wanted to
animate which i'm doing and it's great and i almost you know the way tom describes things where it's
like 3d clicked with his brain in a way that other art memes didn't uh i feel the way about animation
i fucking adore it and it's great i feel that way about drawing in general that it just clicked with
me in a way that like i got decent at it in like like faster than i think most people do
and it just made like intuitive sense to me in a way that i think it does for a lot of people
i feel that way about animation i also want to do code more i want to illustrate i want to do all
these things and all the art like i had a lot of like art goals and they're all coming along
swimmingly but one of the goals was to branch out socially complete failure have not changed
for a while there i was going on reddit uh you know i was going on r slash box you know i did
mean i did meet some lifelong friends uh from reddit meetups fuck dammit okay okay i'm not reset
no we're cool cool yeah we're cool no we're good no we're good um i got sir junkin you know it's
fine your carol live my scholarship um okay but yeah i was saying yeah i meant i mean were you going
to like reddit meetups or are you just on reddit no i was just on reddit well i mean that's not
enough that's not good for you well i mean i literally stopped going on reddit i could not
like it was such a fail i couldn't even continue to go on reddit or continue to go on website
on websites just any yeah what do you mean you just stop what do you just stop going on
websites what do you what are you talking about are you are you are you smoking crack what what
i mean is i just stopped going on social media like one of my goals was literally just to go on
reddit more which i failed at well because i got bored and i didn't want to stop well that's a weird
goal like going on reddit is not socializing i mean i guess in a way it is but no more than like
being on discord i don't know i disagree because the sort of socializing that i would be doing on
reddit would be completely different than the one i would be doing on discord on discord as i said
before all of the discords i could possibly talk in are ones that i am like like i made in a way
that like are like fan discords of me and that would not be the case on reddit
oh i have i have a magic fish munchie i have a great great ben i have a no i have a magic
fish that will show me what's in chests this is literally a game changer okay just okay you know
yeah that's it okay cool um sick do i want this to be yeah so it would be way different to go on
on reddit and like i wanted really a part of that community the fandom feeling that we were just
talking about that that was my goal was to talk on reddit and try and and other social not not
just reddit but i this was a concert effort where i wanted to go on tumblr more i wanted to go on
reddit more i wanted to do more stuff like that try and go in on the chance more uh failed i don't
go on any of them it's out of my thing you know i if you know if you feel like that is um like
where you would get a sense of community that you're looking for fair enough i don't i have no
interest i have no interest in that um i don't i i don't i don't think that would do it for me i
want you know i want to like i like being on i like talking to people on discord and stuff you
know i want uh i don't know i don't want to talk to people on discord though is the thing
i mean i don't want to never do it well okay sure me neither um uh i don't know i i i also
i also don't think reddit is like or going on social media is the end of it this equation that
was sure this was like a baby step situation yeah sure um okay um so you know what i think i
think i just remembered i think i just realized another thing that keeps me from that has kept
me from going to uh the round table and that is that like in theory this is funny because i've
been there and like i i used to go there so i should know right like i shouldn't even have to think
about this but i do like in theory it is the perfect thing it is it is in in theory the the ideal
solution to like every problem that i have but what i just mean like like it is because it's
it's like a community that is centered around like creative endeavor of the kind that i am
you know focused on almost to distraction from everything else right so what so like
so what if i so what if i go and like it sucks you know what if like what if it's not it's like
it's not enough and i'm like oh why did i bother then what then what do i have left what do i have
left out after that i've exhausted all my possibilities so in a way it's almost like
you want to keep that option open and not capitalize on it so it always feels like
there is another option almost yeah actually yeah you said it you said it perfectly um
you gotta go you gotta go i know it's fucked up i know it's fucked up i know it's wrong
i know that i'm bad
i mean that that's why i mean it like i if i can't go like if i can't even do
the babyest thing in the entire world that's just find a fucking subreddit that i want to go on
if i can't do that then i'm like i've just basically embraced the fact that i'm going to die alone
that's the only thing that can be derived from this yeah yeah naturally naturally um well
what's the solution is there a solution do we even want to solve this is this even a problem
nobody knows nobody knows i i've been thinking about how i've taken it for granted that my life
i will have a picture on i will be an online creator that's just what i will do like why even
analyze it but more and more i've i've found the idea of having a job that's not like a
office job one that pertains my interest ones that may maybe you know oh working in the arts as a
uh but having like a clock out time having just your job be well your job not your
fucking life as it is for me uh that consumes every waking moment of your entire being
yeah just having something that you can just go to and then come home from well not wanting to
die while you're there well that's pretty appealing okay kind of but like
but then like i mean the yeah when you when you say it like that when you say like that it
sounds pretty good but like second like what are you actually doing there like is what you
are doing there something you actually want to do or that you derive meaning from i i understand
and maybe i'm really young and i don't yeah i would have to like see for myself
but thinking about it thinking about it critically i thought about like me personally
and what i derive pleasure from and i've said this i've said this before where it's like what
i enjoy about the work that i do is a lot of the time like the busy stuff i'm talking about art
specifically where it's like i don't know if i particularly there's a few comics that i
would like to do in my life but that don't really call to me like narratives don't really call to me
in the same way the drawing the drawing itself the drawing itself yeah that's what i care about
the most and i can understand that i don't know if i am entirely in the same boat but i get it
you know okay so i feel like i am in a unique situation where it's like i don't really like
as long as like just am drawing for whatever purpose i may be or am animating or you know just
as long as i'm working visually i don't i think that i would be fulfilled i don't know i don't
know if i would be completely fulfilled creatively but i would have a job that i wouldn't hate and i
would have off time to sometimes do my creative work or just live my life and be able to actually
watch a television show you know i'm gonna i don't know if this is walking back i'm not
fuck no no no what i don't know why i didn't just die i don't know i don't know i don't know i also
want to say by the way that i'm not computing internet creative work or even saying that i will
not it's i'm simply saying it's appealed to me more than it has before in my past i mean i have
been thinking it's it's it's creative like doing creative work on the internet is in my life it like
is in my blood i've done it my entire life it's something that i stop i don't think you know uh
he totally um i mean like hippo right like hippo's fucking big boy job i fucking i covet hippo so
yeah i love it him hippo's big boy job or approximation thereof you know has made me think
and i've thought like i mean you know what i was saying before about like jobs lettering jobs
like inking like those don't exist those can't possibly be real like what like what are you talking
about um that is a gun i don't want it okay i thought you were referring to the jobs like
that's a gun that's that's just impossible no i mean i mean like but it can't be true right
like i am a god i have skills i have skills that are not like totally fucking worthless
right sh i mean i don't know i guess i guess any feel that i might like i don't know the
pokey the point is i've been thinking every every once in a while i think about like what if i like
what if i like what kind of a job even could i get like i would i would be fine to you know
to an extent i would i would be okay i would be okay doing creative work for an employer
as long as like the hours were reasonable um and all that shit um
i mean i've never had a job like that before i'd like to try it at least like maybe it would be
great you know maybe it would provide structure or whatever to my fucking waystoy lifestyle
who knows i crave i crave structure like i i i crave structure right now well i've been thinking about it
and i guess i'm just like um but how would i oh my god i got the pig i got pig i got pig
you don't understand you don't understand about pig bitty you don't understand it from my perspective
when you're just talking and then like yeah so this really serious thing happened oh my god
the fucking squiggly dude i got the pig activate my bingity bomb do i got a pig this is a game changer
just like last time this is a absolute game changer um i think i want this armor please
okay look it's a pig it's a pig it's a pig deal that's all i'm saying um
um
what the fuck was i talking about i got really distracted by the pig that's all um
do you do you remember do you remember what i was talking about um i i got
distracted by the pig you just saying the pig oh was i saying oh is this the thing i was talking
about like hippo's job big boy job maybe it maybe it would provide so oh yeah like lettering but how
would i even how would i even go about getting a job like that like like with hippo like i feel like
well a fan of his just just so happened to be like one of those people and like yeah just like
offered him a job that's what i think happened hippo feel free to clarify if it's if it was more
and and that's also i want to just say that's not like a like a judgment on him that like oh
just one of his fans just also if you're listening if you to that to that person uh hi uh thanks
no no no that's not me that's what i'm saying is hi no shut up just call me call me my my
no that's no i was saying hi because um she patron me again like like last month and thanks
it since since we're talking about her yeah well yeah that too sure well actually actually i asked
hippo no after me a job please well listen this is when you'll be interested i asked hippo like
i mean are they hiring i that's interesting and he said uh you probably have to move to
london and i was like oh damn but uh so there you go um how much is living in london probably a lot
i mean how much is living i mean uh i don't know i mean it's probably it's probably a little more
than living where i live now not probably not by too much but anyway you know whatever it's not
important um the important part is like i have thought that maybe like you know i've got like a
a not insubstantial internet following right based off of my art and creativity and i thought like
well maybe you know that being the case i'm sure that would be like a strong like foot in the door
like i'm sure that would be like a good thing and maybe help me but i i have like not recently but
in the past i have gone onto like craigslist and stuff and just look for like you know creative
jobs and just be like oh why not and like send out applications like let's just see what happens
it has never borne fruit or even come even close or even like nothing has ever materialized or even
looked like it could materialize from it and i don't know what the fucking problem is um and by
is i mean was because this isn't the thing i've done recently at all sure and and i don't know
what to think about that um it makes me think that maybe everything that i've spent my time doing is
totally inapplicable to any other field of work and if i ever wanted to get a more traditional
job then it's impossible and and and it's just not just not not with how i've spent my life uh i
don't think that could that can't be true uh but it feels like it is
what a fucking bummer yeah sorry uh no no not you just the just the whole just life just the
way the life is well yeah i'm true um i mean you know i i i guess i don't know maybe maybe i'm wrong
and um because yeah i have been thinking about this i have been thinking about like what could i
i mean you know thank you to patrons like i really i appreciate so much everyone who
patrons me but you know i mean in terms of like living off of like like the money that i make
from patreon is it's a it's it's a meager amount to like live off of and i like we all know this
this is obvious this isn't gonna blow anyone's minds um as i say this um so i've been thinking
about like well what if i what kind what kind of a real job what kind of a real ish job would be
palatable to me right because i just don't want to fucking you know pound the pain i don't want to
look back on my this is a cliche but i'll use it i don't want to look back on my deathbed and be like
wow look how many years i spent doing some stupid shit that i didn't care about you know that's
that's fucking horrifying to me um and that's what a job is right i mean you trade your time for your
money you trade your time you spend doing some shit that you don't want to do but maybe someone
else wants you to do it and they give you some money if you if you do that you make that sacrifice
fair enough you know i get it um but it's a it's a fucking you know it's a shame
you know okay i want to give voice to what i think people could be thinking right now
and and like to play devil's advocate a little bit to what we're kind of expressing right here
and uh for some reason when i'm imagining someone constructing this argument which i'm about to
relay i imagine it's just Nate for some reason yeah uh i just imagine the Nate will say something
which i kind of agree with in a way where it's like okay we've been talking a lot about productive
talking a lot about how we don't have time for anything else and it's just us doing our art
and i think that someone could say well you say that but is that true yeah how much art do you
really put out dude yeah like are you really spending every waking moment just
you know you're completely just absorbed with your art and you know what you show for it well
that's not like yeah yeah i i can definitely see someone thinking that that's not what i'm saying
that's not what i'm saying yeah i don't think yeah because it's not i mean i mean look i mean only
recently have i really got back into the swing of drawing again and that's on me and it's to my
eternal shame um and so and so on and so forth um what i don't know uh die die die die die die
okay okay um yes eternal was i saying about eternal shame um that you haven't been drawing
yeah yeah and i'm and i'm only now kind of recovering i just want to add on to that yeah
that like like we've been saying that we don't have to make time for other things in our lives
but like and this people could say that they could see that like or say that like you know
we aren't producing you like unbelievable like homesick levels of art surely you can make time
and this is in your hands and like you know it's your fault and you can be better yeah yeah i know
yeah i hate myself yeah yeah obviously like obviously yeah this is our fault naturally
no 100% agree um the thing is you know because now a lot of this a lot of this past like
while or so you know there were times when i was it wasn't on comics there were times i was productive
on endless war there were other times when i was kind of fucking up and was not productive maybe
those times i would have been better off working a job uh maybe maybe i would have more to show for
it in the long run possible whatever um yeah the point is right it's not it's not that i'm
it's not that anyone is just working 24 hours a day it's just like drawing 24 hours a day
writing 24 hours a day i don't think i mean maybe andrew hussey did that maybe he maybe he could
manage that for a while um but you know it's it's it's it's it's in your brain it's in your mind
it's that you're you're thinking about it and even when you're not doing it you're thinking i could
be doing it and it eats you up inside i think something that's very hard for people who aren't
in our work to like conceptualize yeah especially if you're working exclusively a wage job yeah like
when you clock out of work you're done with work for the day you go home and you you you
snuggle with your wife and your children and you watch tv um when you do what us you're never
clocked out yeah because there is no schedule there is no like a time you're working and time
you're not working there's just time you should be working and it's 100 of the clock it's time
you should be working and time you are working yeah and i can't i can't maintain uh i can't
maintain focus on on creative stuff uh you know 24 hours a day i don't think anyone can uh
um where are we going with this uh just fucking bitching and moaning yeah um
someone give me a job but like a good job like an easy job that's fun friend makes a lot of money
again yeah that was the plan all your caro rfck
we got we got it we got to live moss and that's what i'm gonna do a realistic scenario
you're walking down the street and uh a little dog comes up to you but it's gross gross i fucking
kill it it's not just any dog it's the owner of millie your picnic and he says your caro
what yeah sure all right what do you what do you do he says your caro ben sainte-vaver what do you
do i say fucking talk talk talk to my agent i say how much you got on here what'd you say
yeah i don't like it no i don't i don't like this i don't like the scenario i don't like the
slide of questioning i don't yeah i don't like it i don't like the base your base assumptions um
okay well that thanks for your question that's all the time we have for today five
yeah exactly um all right ben all right here's the idea all right yeah you hold the news i hold
the gun and then we let go at the same time wait so what do they die of and wait nothing
we just put down our arms and live a happy prosperous life we just lay down the weapons
and who are we who's news who's gone who are we our own our own now there's no that's interesting
are you wait are you saying there's a way out i never i never thought i can fuck i can escape
there's always my way out i say mimicking of the haunted house from disneyland what put down the
fucking crack pipe excuse me why can't i been literally why can't i just like steven universe
like all of it and just be like super into steven universe i'll tell you go on tumblr and then
like just talk about how much i love steven universe i will oh that's a good one oh yeah heavy
bullets yeah oh yeah steven universe no listen i will tell you why there's a good reason um
it's because it's not gay enough yeah i think i've talked about this on the pcp yeah uh um
steven universe gets away with having its cake and eating it too by being quote unquote about
lesbians but with all these qualifiers that make it like not really like they're aliens
they're not they don't even have bodies there aren't any men in their species like that's it's
bullshit i hear people say that it's no it's not it's a weak shit it's it's clear like it's
cleared that like those are things about them that don't like are you trying to say that like
they are gyms are not female presenting and like oh they're like they're exactly bodies of light so
like oh like oh they're not actually female like no no i mean of course they're female presenting
obviously but like none of them aren't so what does it mean for them to be quote unquote gay
it doesn't mean anything because there's no alternative it but the reason people want
well a reason a lot of people want representation is so that it's normalized in our society
not so that it can necessarily explore those themes in the show itself but just so that
people can see yeah they are gay or lesbian or whatever they can see themselves in just
represented in media whatsoever yeah so so while they might not be dealing with the same backlash
that a real lesbian real lesbian couples would doesn't mean that it's not impactful i mean like
we recognize them as you know as humans do just because they aren't like technically a gender
doesn't mean that we don't recognize them as such you know that's a that's a good point
that's a good point you make there i'll i'll buy that mm i mean five million nine please
i'll i'll yeah i'll i'll fucking i'll fucking count out of your sgw agenda that that'll be that'll
be one rip of jewel please no no no no no no my pod my pod is oh god my pod's almost empty
what the fuck do i do your skate pod yeah i stuffed it full of orphans
but then i i had to i had an empty amount so i could climb in instead and they could stay on
the exploding death star uh yeah well actually i stuffed it i stuffed mine full of general grievous
and uh he uh why would you boy that was a terrible idea he's a he's a be he's a mean man
well he kept talking to me stuff he told me stuff about the jq and about how we
should solve it i just thought he started making a lot of sense and i felt like he should
continue on without me mm yeah he you know grievous had a lot of good ideas not saying
everything he did was right but he had he had a lot of good ideas oh general grievous is so killer
and also a nazi oh oh dude okay are okay are the nazis rather or the or the nazi is a killer oh i
think they're totally killer yeah definitely 100 100 look at them well yeah they're fashion sense
totally killer a briefcase of cash dude i just received a briefcase of cash from this idiot
what do i do i'm talking about your patrons yeah that's right
patreon.com slash that's insane all right you know what
mm-hmm what do you think i feel i've taken away from this conversation yeah you know
i sort of feel like even though like there's been nothing said that's convinced me we've
talked for a long time and said basically nothing yeah yeah yeah um there's nothing that's like
convinced me of this so i don't know why i feel this way specifically maybe just i've like i've
talked and therefore my brain has worked it out itself yeah i sort of feel like
i should just stop doing all the stupid things i'm doing only do things i really care about yeah
what yeah yeah stop doing the things i'm just doing smart things in this war and then just like it's
like like that's almost it basically and then just double down on the other thing they want to and
that's just draw yeah i should just do i should just fucking like stop spread myself even a little
bit thin and just completely fucking like hammer down on like trying to network trying to push
this art aspect of me and just do that yeah missions just do that sure harm you feel that's
that way uh doesn't sound like uh that's doesn't sound too wacky um i'm i'm fighting a giant snake
by the way um so i'm a little distracted um and really really important that i not take any damage
here like it in real life you're doing this yeah oh god oh god oh god the snake is a symbolism for
his uh sense of regret for not being on penny arcade i did it i fucking did it i killed the
ammo i got no damage um why am i oh god i must have failed to get the health upgrade in the first
buck okay that sucks something's gotta change something if i don't change something because
of this conversation yeah i'm just retarded i'm just i just like even if i've articulated it with
someone else something's gotta fucking change or else i'm just gonna kill myself one day
yeah i hear you actually have you ever been like actually suicidal like actually for real
um not really why yeah well just wondering because i have been and it's like it's like
sort of weird it's hard to explain because it's suicide is like stupid yeah that's what feels
like oh people who want to commit suicide just like what's you know even what's going on with
them but like it's a weirdly like i have been i have been weird at the moment it doesn't feel like
when you're when you're in that mindset it's just like yeah you know like if i was dead i wouldn't
feel bad so like if i don't want to feel bad like maybe i should just kill myself sure you know i mean
it's logical in a sense right uh there's a certain certain logic behind it i mean i've been depressed
to the point that i've been like man i should probably like be dead that would probably be better
i've been i but i've never been like to the point that i'm like seriously considering doing anything
about it you know i mean i almost jumped out of a car once i was about to but literally my mom held
on like like like grabbed me and because she was way bigger than i was she was able to well
well no no no i i that that that was i don't know why i said she was way bigger than me because
that wasn't the case but just just because she would like held on to me with a vice grip i didn't
uh that's the good stuff that's the good stuff right there and i continue to live morse ever
since yes ever so yeah i you you all that on that on that day you almost lived manos
whoo what what what about endless war uh what what even what even is that what what is it a text
command like what the fuck hey he's wants to rehab any good i never have it because it's not low
calorie okay so i don't know but i think i mean it's not carbonated so probably not i don't think
it's my scene speaking with the teen girls are your scene you sick fuck yeah sure yeah why not
yeah why the fuck no what are you judging get out of here hey i i posted it i posted some
avalanche ravine songs in the killers like killer themes chat and they all made fun of me and they
said they wasn't killer which is completely inaccurate they are i don't know where the
fuck they stood i don't know where the fuck they went to killer college yeah um but it was the wrong
yeah come on guys that that is yeah no killies love afril avine and fucking show me the man that
says otherwise and i'll show you and i'll show you a fucking corpse you know it's just like when
it's just like when dug funniest dad said show you show me a man who resorts to violence and
i'll show you a man who's run out of good ideas there you go that was a lesson i'll show me an
nematode and i'll respect you and he never did i'll show you a god and said he says shooting him dead
dude i've still got this pig i'm in hog i'm literally in a hog heaven because i have this pig
i'm not joking you don't understand you don't understand the context of pig
hey hey hey funny hey hey hey saint show me a nematode and i'll let you in strip shirt
i don't like your girlfriend no no hey whoa think you got a new one hey hey you got a nematode
you got a nematode hey hey dug dug i don't like patty
no way no way no way no way i think you should think you should date sketer
he's black he's not easily embarrassed
can't dance can't dance
well well that's our show everyone it's not though because i haven't killed this rat yet
but this time you okay no irano no irony here feeling real good about this run because i have
the pig um and yeah that's pretty much it i have the pig ah god bless i got the pig and i'm just
looking for rats i'm just looking for rats baby um um hey well let me pivot okay now sure i have um
been thinking and mulling over right i've been fucking for some reason honestly i think it was
just a lack of a lack of healthy alternatives i started falling down this like dnd podcast um root
you know sitting there and and and you know sitting there and just coveting right and coveting
this lifestyle and oh fuck fell down a hole sorry what
wait oh my god the fish saves me the fish saved me munchie the fish i have the fish
everything it's gonna be okay i got the fish and the pig and it's made all the difference
okay okay look got the toad all right so um i mean coveting this lifestyle and and i keep
bringing me keeps bringing me back to thinking like how can i do this right i keep having the
idea of how do i run like a game oh i want to play in a game i want to be one of these people
i want to play in a game and and have that be content that people consume watch me play in a
fucking game watch me have a character run through a story tell a great story have a great time very
entertaining um you know i mean no one's gonna do that that's not gonna happen the only alternative
is that i have to run one and that's a nightmare but maybe i maybe i'm so desperate that i'll do it
anyway and um i mean that's what it is that's a that's a healthy way to view yourself i mean
like i'm so desperate i'll do a thing that i know isn't a good idea just for a sad just for a
taste just for a taste of the reflective glory um i don't know you know i propose i propose doing
one set an endless war that's a maybe i was thinking i was i was actually thinking about um
like the other day i had a i had an idea i actually really liked it and i mulled it over
like for the rest of the night while i was doing other stuff i think i might run like i could i
could run like a game i could run a game set in the champion world i actually think i could i
i actually thought of like oh i have an idea for a story like i have i i have like a concept for
like a story that would take place there and it would be like it would fit cleanly into like a
one-shot thing it has like a thing behind it the thing is i don't know any i don't know if people
that play these games right like like if i got like maybe you or hippo right to be in this thing
with me like you guys to have like it would be weird you'd never played it before and it would
be weird to have it be like your first exposure to it and i thought maybe i could have maybe i
could come up with like a more like like a more simplified like sort of rules light variant do
i really want to fucking spend the time like coming up with a whole system for this or like
maybe i could find a simpler system and also it could be like it's like yeah like me and hippo
are in it but like doesn't that just mean like it's the same audience that you would have already
in a way it does it does mean that um i mean i wouldn't i mean it would work like because
i have like a story idea for it it would work for it could work regardless honestly it might
play out differently depending on who else was there but like it could work with anyone um it
would be fine um honestly i mean this isn't even like this isn't an audience building thing this is
a this is like a man i know i was just i was talking earlier about how it's a bad bad thing
to like diversify and not just focus on one medium but at the same time i like i like being a
diverse i like that's why we do it that's why we do it i like being multimedia i like the idea
i like the idea that like like i mean man i almost never even think about the fact that
i made a whole fucking game for the champion like yeah that almost never even crosses my mind and
yet it is an indisputable fact of some importance i think probably um oh that's a fucking stupid item
but you know what i want it anyway um okay so i don't know i like the idea that like the story
could would be a multimedia thing like there would be you know a game there'd be comics there'd be
these fucking like rpg like tabletop games like set in the universe um that stuff's really cool to
me and i really like it um it's super cool yeah that there just is a video game for this comic
yeah like that's undeniably great and cool i'm very proud of it it's and i actually made it really
fast like that's a weird thing about it is i actually it only took me like three weeks to make it
like like maybe less i okay another thing i want to i want to mention um okay two things actually
number one i was just a broad thing i feel like no matter what even if it's not a
thorough podcast to ever there's always just gonna be stuff in your brain that you can't
articulate it and like there's always some like asterisk to everything you say in a way
where it's like you could always like articulate your point it's like a little bit better and then
like if you when you don't someone's gonna comment it um you mean are you talking about this like
game idea thing or are you talking about no no no i'm talking about in general i'm talking about
in general okay not i'm saying i'm talking about like like me like right now during this conversation
we're having right now sure sure yeah yeah yeah um where it's like like you know there's there's
things i'll say which might to some people require context for them to fully understand
where i'm coming from in a way but just i can't think to do that for every single thing or else
i would just be talking for an hour and saying not really anything just explaining everything
that i'm thinking and all the all the nuances that i'm sort of leaving out to save time so that
that i feel like you can already respond to so one thing i i want to mention one nuance and
clarification i would like to say that like i don't think that like uh like that like being good
is bad for business uh and i feel like people can like say that like all you do for instance like
on youtube is follow the algorithm and feed the algorithm and that's like if you just do that
well you have to you you do that but you like i mean you have to be confident at it right like
yeah you need well yeah you i mean you need a certain base level competency and some people
don't have it but it's not that uncommon either like you know lots of people could oh god i almost
okay um like lots of people could um do it you know not everyone but a lot of people
and that's probably why it seems not special just some you know it it's also like i i think that
there are things that exist that are successful maybe not as successful as someone who is competent
slash either good maybe who is strictly trying to follow the algorithm and just is doing that
specifically and like with intentionally to get paid but there are definitely people who are good
who've succeeded on the back of just being good and there are people there are you know fine success
so i don't i just want to clarify that that is possible and i don't think i think we can it's
easy to get wrapped up and just like oh like like like you know i want to all these things which are
good like you know but like i there's not worth it business wise um i think that is
like it's not that that's wrong i don't think either of those thinkings are wrong that just
like you should just like follow the algorithm on you or something and be a bit competent and you
can do it i also don't think that if you wanted to it's impossible for you to not follow the
algorithm we'll still make quality content and making stuff that people want and like there's
no way to get popular that way well i don't know i just think it's it's harder in some senses and
that's what we're discussing currently well it's like i think yeah i mean i mean i mean if you're
finding okay go on go on i would find it very plausible that there's some like maybe making
that game was not like entirely like the best use of your time in a way that like um well i don't know
yeah cranky now like like uh like uh like like you know a lot of pages i mean the game
theoretically made me zero money yeah exactly and and honestly it probably literally made me zero
money because like nobody talks about it like after it came out like nobody talked about it
and i don't know of anyone who was like wow i saw that game you made and i was really impressed
and like i i check out all your other stuff because that that might be true for this but
this sort of thing in general that's like not strictly for business but you do because you have
a spark of inspiration and you think it's good you think it's a quality idea and it's just creatively
fulfilling i think that thing can feel it can like work just in a business sense of it being like
part of why people like you is that you create content which they enjoy and i think it's i it's
often like almost understated in a way that the masses aren't like stupid they like good things
and when you create stuff of quality they enjoy it often yeah so well maybe that video game in
specific did not generate you money and i'm not complaining and i'm not complaining about that
yeah i think we mix together like stuff like that and maybe endless war which we've said before is
not really made us a lot of money almost at all in the sense uh like i still think that just is
good to do because people will like you more and people will be more often to support you
oh no i'm please please please please yes ah okay i just i was terrified because i realized
i was out of blanks and i need two blanks to get to the rat's nest uh but luckily the store
had some so we're good don't worry about it okay sorry to interrupt you but well no no hold on
also by the way i just want to say that you've said this before but i didn't notice and i thought
you were exaggerating but now like really paying attention to every single panel the halftones
and the vapors is like ridiculous in chapter one the halftone in oh sure sure you mean the dots
yeah the dots yeah you mean the dots what is the halftone yeah um uh it is yeah it is very i was very
meticulous about it too meticulous in fact yeah yeah you know with with vapors one with
vapors one in specific i was very focused on the idea of like replicating the look of a print
comic i used the halftones because they are very print comic e uh in two and now in three i mean
i didn't stop using them but i definitely use them less and i only use them in cases where i
thought they were necessary um there were a couple of shots like the one of vincent like coming
through the door dramatically that looked like the halftones and that looked really cool i literally
as you say that i was i'm looking at it yeah that that's that one's really good um and sometimes
halftones are good but like generally i'm fine with just using like you know gray because like
yeah like the format that i printed can print gray like the reason they had halftones is because
they couldn't print in gray back in the day well you know i can so whatever um yeah um
oh no now i feel now i feel bad now i feel like maybe i should use maybe i should use
more halftones maybe i abandoned something that was important and added value to my work
law i don't know um you were gonna say something i cut you off was i i mean wasn't i just mad
because i had thought that i didn't have blanks to find the rats nest no we were talking oh god
i'm retarded i forget what we were talking about but you were definitely gonna say something
and we're gonna be oh oh we were talking about um how just like inspiring goodwill by creating
quality content is a method to but that is not like inherently goes against the idea of doing
something for a business purpose where it's like doing something that's good for business
core code is described is not necessarily mean just like gaming things or like like
cynically i mean that's that's what go ahead and yeah i mean that's what i always wanted to do
right i wanted to be like okay i'm not i don't want to be like super commercial i don't want to
make shit i don't i don't want to make shit because the algorithm favors it uh you know i just want
to make cool stuff and if i just work really hard and make cool stuff people will see it
i'll see that it's good and you know just sort of naturally you know by just just by on the backs
of the quality of the shit that i make people will find it and appreciate it and that has happened
to extend yeah uh you know not not i mean i'm very poor right so so that's you know but that's
not necessarily a failing of the ideology um that's not that's not a what am i trying to say
okay what am i she helped um blah blah blah live moss um yeah yeah yeah strip search um brood god
is is that is that ben sain in the flesh is that really by the way also looking at vapor's one
right now by the way i've realized that like the way you draw magda while she's in her i don't know
how you describe her her grim bark her grim dark state yeah sure um is literally the way i draw you
in r of ck are which i didn't even realize it look at this literally it's the exact same classes i
did not even notice yeah that's that's a little bit ridiculous it's a little bit weird but that is
the case really funny that's really cool i love it i love it um um i i i get what you mean it like
it's uh i i mean i think the goal is always to just do what you find creatively fulfilling
and if you could do only that and be successful like like no one like okay me and you said this
a thousand times before our goal is not to become the richest people on earth oh that would be a nice
spiritual outcome slash ben sain uh yeah it's i mean it's it's it's about doing what you want
well here's i mean pop it's about it's just about being a guy you want to be not for like
strictly a monetary sense but just in the sense that you want to be able to make your art and not
have to do shit that you don't want to i mean here's my i mean i've said i've said this before
this is sort of my philosophy if i were rich um what i would do with that is i would use the
fact that i don't have to work anymore to just like work on my shit that's what i would do with a lot
of money maybe if i had a whole lot of money i would like hire assistants right maybe maybe that
could help you know grease grease the pipeline yeah yeah that's that's all i would use it for
um uh maybe and if i were famous if i were super popular all i would do with that is
use it to make money so that i could do what i just said i would do with a lot of money
uh yeah ben yeah hmm how do i say this okay your god question mark i'm i'm on i'm on saint
tomlicks.com right now right now which you can too viewer if you click the link in the description
right um these these are genius what are you talking about these why are you talking about
these comics that's bullshit no man i suck remember no you do suck because you make
fucking Winnie the Pooh videos yeah you make you make youtube videos to be fair i was kind of
interested i was kind of personally interested in in like no sure okay no okay in Winnie the Pooh
i'm i'm personally a big Winnie the i'm personally a big Pooh head um it okay there's like a
weird disconnect in my head like like i said this before like i asked you if you felt this way
sort of like in like an abstract like questioning just like sort of um you know do you feel like
ben the saint the comic guy and ben saint the the twitch stream or whatever i just can't people
and i didn't really like like i didn't really notice but i feel that way i don't really often
think about like how i'm friends with ben and you have created the vapors it seems like
the vapors ben couldn't have made the vapors yeah right the vapors is the best thing ever made
no come on now you just yank me you just yanking me no okay you crank yanking me
also it's really cool it's but like i mean i don't think about you that way i mean you know
you know i don't think about myself that way enough and that's that's my problem that's one of my many
problems um and like oh okay i fell into a hole but it's fine um one of the things that i want to
do you know i want to i just you know i spread myself thin and it wasn't even just about you
know i just got out of the mindset right like it's about you know you know the secret is
bullshit obviously but like there's something to be said about like visualizing you know what you
want to see and then like and having it come as a as a consequence of that like just by virtue of the
fact that if you're focused on it you will sort of naturally take action to bring about that
reality and you know when i'm thinking about streaming when i'm thinking about you know
fucking editing doing fancy editing on the latest pcp when i'm thinking about you know making 10
paces draw like really good i'm not thinking about yeah being a comic sky getting my comic
sun getting my yeah work done yeah yeah yeah um uh the the it's such a it's such a because it's not
like okay well okay i'm gonna speak i'm gonna speak like like strictly as i want to say a viewer
i want i want to say this to the view okay no go on okay to the viewer i'm sorry i found it okay
i have been running around the same level like everywhere just looking for the hatch that leads
to the rat's nest and it took me forever but i finally found it so okay uh disaster inverted
okay what are you saying um i just want to say for like i'm strictly thinking as like a fan of
bin saying like i wouldn't say that like just like just only do comics now because like i like when
you do other stuff yeah it's just it's like it's kind of like like you're just fucked like no matter
what you do uh just die in a way it's like i guess like i like the vapors more than other
thing everything else you do but like it's almost like again like i don't i can't recognize out of
the fact in my mind that you've created the vapors i don't i don't get i don't what are you getting
at now i'm getting at i'm getting at that like i like i i don't even like when i think about you
i don't think about the vapors at all really in a way i see um so it's it's almost like i can't
even imagine a world where the vapors or you know any video comics are like the main thing you do
even though i think that would be like the best in certain aspects
like i just can't imagine it this is the thing there's no what's what's the elevator pitch for
ben saying there isn't one yeah it's like 14 different things oh god oh god oh god um i just
a bad room i got a bad room uh there's a there's a demon the grim raper is here
the grim raper is here that's it fuck part part of me thinks that like i like like like as as like um
i guess like as like like a backseat a comics artist in a way like a backseat gamer but like a
backseat uh just like fan of you if i were you i would double down on comics and just try and
throw myself into that community and just kind of focus on that just because i don't know
that seems to be what i like the most of you but like but like i mean i think that's the most
unique i think that's the most unique thing about me definitely the most unique definitely
but like like would i like with that like would i say like you know like i'm comfortable never
seeing another uh like another twitter like ben stream again i'm comfortable never seeing
like stuff like that or his appearances on on pcp or just anything else like that like no no no
no yeah that would be that would be a big loss yeah it would i i think so definitely i don't
want to do i don't want to do nothing but like i don't really want to be someone who does nothing
but you know whatever thing i don't i mean that sounds boring definitely maybe that's maybe that's
my problem maybe that maybe that's my problem and maybe if i were cool for example i would be like
i would be totally okay with yeah i'm just gonna sit in my room i'm just gonna do nothing but draw
forever you know i mean that's how people get i mean that's how people succeed as artists is
they fucking do nothing but it and they become super good at it and they're prolific and they
just put out a ton of shit fuck damn it oh i've got just fighting some orbs just fighting some
real nasty orbs right now um um what's the solution i don't know yep yeah yeah agreed
what a fucking what a shit show fuck shit i say it nothing in particular yeah um
i really hope that i did this sequence correctly because like in the rat's nest you can you have
to go through a yes got it okay you have to go through a specific oh but i lost all my armor
oh that sucks you have to go through a specific like sequence of uh like runes that is unique
to every game and uh i just you know okay there was a chance i was gonna fuck it up there but
i didn't fuck it up it's okay um it is a shit show um um you know i've been i've been having this
idea i've been i keep coming back to this to this run a fucking d&d game as a podcast idea in fact
i've been talking about it for like years like i think i thought about it at like the first radcon
jesus christ yeah but like you know interest interest is like kind of like you know that's
generally the level of interest like if it's gonna happen i need to like push for it and and am i
confident enough in it to like push for it vigorously answer no um there you go
great cool that's that's the answer um
i am i'm i'm at the rat it is time once again really it is really it is time once again to
face the rat yeah i'm thinking i want to call then no no what i this this might be the last
rat attempt yeah okay i'm i'm good with that um well all right here here we go um this is gonna
be a lesbian yeah okay all right if we don't defeat the rat uh that means that we're gonna
stuck in our pitiful lives for the rest of eternity if you destroy the rat there's hope for us yet
there's hope for us yet oh god i don't like i don't like these odds okay well now this is the only
thing standing between us and living my i knew it i'm living moss dude yeah i got i i just want to
live moss please sweet mouse please i just want to let me live moss why won't you just let me live
moss fuck okay took some bad damage oh my god i just realized i have the i was so excited to get
those heavy bullets um upgrade and they are a complete liability and have fucked me up and
have ruined my entire life fuck bad damage bad damage okay i can make three mistakes uh which
is slightly better than the last time but i also don't have a blank god damn it i forgot to use
i forgot to use my trigger item so that's a loss i probably took like at least two hits that i
could have avoided um all right i'm at a second phase oh god i believe in you you can do this
maybe okay i gotta take a swig of my gotta take a swig of my gridlock
god damn all right here we go i'm watching a highlight of drawing yet another page of vapers
three six days ago right now oh yeah oh on twitch yes on twitch there we go
twitch.com slash uh don't you wish that he has professional professional twitch streamer
insane new ninja look out why not why not you laugh one good reason
come on flip moss okay i wasted my okay wasted my trigger item um well not entirely but mostly
fuck okay i can i have two health left okay one more one more mistake and i'm nowhere near
winning i'm nowhere near beating him i'm completely fucked no no okay i lost yep there we go
i can't beat him well one time wait no the pig oh my god the pig he saved me the pig saved me
my Jesus is there hope for us yet i'm literally going to i'm i if i make this if i if i do it
it's because of the pig i actually might make it the cop killer living only due to the palp of pigs
ironic life life is stranger than fiction you can't you can't rate you you can't make the
shit up okay um i shit i'm out of i'm out of my good gun switching to bad gun
what the fuck he's got minions get the fuck out of here little fucking ninja turtle looking ass
hey punk i've been saying i'm an artist slash cartoonist slash youtuber slash podcaster slash
ex physicist slash death cult leader also streamer now that's a great that's a great elevator pitch
you like that yeah i do yeah i do that
fuck i'm pretty close what the fuck
oh i use my i use my trigger item i use my trigger item to great effect
oh my god no no no oh my god no you die i didn't have to i could have won i just didn't
realize that i was on fire you're dead yeah i was so close i was so close well then it looks like
it's uh a long eternity of mediocrity for me and you it's curtains it's curtains i was i could
have done it i could have done it i'm fucking so then if only you had spent that life a little bit
more carefully if you had just sort of you know mulled over your options a little bit more if it
was more of a perfect run you could say yeah then i think everything could have worked out
out pretty well in the end but i think you might have just rushed it out and uh instead of
getting out a good run to the people you've just shit out a bad one over and over and over again
and really what's the value in that
boy it's a tough one it's a tough one to answer
shut up this fucking show good night fuck this it's over