Starting now.
Routy.
Fuckers, top killers.
That was so bad then.
This is such an inauspicious start.
The start of the new era that is
RCK is exclusively live action now.
I'm in the room with you.
I'm tucking your leg right now. How's it feel?
I'm on the inside of your leg right now. How's it feel?
Can you describe what I'm doing to you?
Oh my god, can I stick my finger up there?
Oh let's see.
You made me scream and that's bad.
It's bad and rude.
Listen, we gotta start this intro right.
That's by cracking open a new energy drink.
To ward off all these serpents.
I just want to say that Rockstar Exdurance
is one of my favorites.
And we found, we're at the store.
And we found
the new marshmallow flavor.
Which fucks me right up.
We're opening up marshmallow.
And I just want to say what you said.
All of these have the exact same caffeine level.
My worry.
My worry is that it's just going to taste like cotton candy.
All these have the exact same caffeine level.
But this is exclusively the marshmallow flavor.
We want to emphasize the fact that it has
300 milligrams of caffeine
for some reason.
There's a hand.
Holding out a little crystal skull
from behind us.
There are various thoughts lying in the room right now.
We have to ward them off.
By handing out some of our...
No do this.
We're all going to take a shot.
No wait.
I don't have a glass.
Whatever.
One, two, three.
It's like nerds.
It is very much like cotton candy.
I think it just tastes like nerds.
It's bad.
I wouldn't say it's bad.
But I don't like it as much as the cotton candy.
You know what it tastes like cream soda?
It does.
I like it.
I don't like it as much as the cotton candy.
It's very low carbonated.
It's very soft.
It's vegan.
Sure.
What does that mean?
No.
I just got a little bit of a bitter aftertaste.
I'm going to pour some more for the thoughts.
Dude it's vegan.
Do this.
You gotta hang out every time.
Drink some.
No, it's for her.
I had some.
Are you done?
Rockstar X-Durance.
I really like the can design.
It's all white.
It's all start white except for the X in X-Durance.
And the giant 300.
As in 300 milligrams of caffeine.
God.
I love graphic design.
Why does anyone even bother with drawing or making art?
When you can just do graphic design
for literally no effort and achieve 100% of the effect.
You know what I do like?
There are some energy drinks
that are more of the high end variety
of the less just straight up.
Oh we're playing cookie clear by the way.
But that doesn't matter.
It won't matter if the entirety of this.
In fact we won't even commentate on it at all.
But I like some of the energy drinks that are more like
soft to drink.
The more refined, less just straight acidic
bubbly carbonated to hell.
There are more like
I don't know if science was like that.
I was in Michigan the other day.
I was eating onions energy drinks.
And they were very very
refined drinks for like a sophisticated
man on the move.
Guys you can't talk
when we're recording an audio only show.
You can't just pretend as though
the audience can't-
I love to like that.
You out.
Get out.
I totally cook gonna give cookies.
I was literally trying to get her to stop talking.
I'm not kidding.
But we can't be having parallel conversations.
That's why I said, shh.
I closed that shit.
You can come back later.
No, you can't.
You can.
No, I think your guys are welcome.
I can't sustain an entire show on my own.
Well, I'm leaving in half an hour.
So I can be on the first half hour of this episode
and then leave.
Why are you leaving in half an hour?
Because I want to make dinner and do some work to do.
OK.
I'm fucking around like you guys.
Listen, this isn't fucking up.
This is a historic moment.
This isn't fucking up.
This isn't going the wayside.
This isn't, you know, veering off God's path.
This is exactly what's in accordance with God's plan.
Ben, it's crazy, right?
God's plan?
Dude, I love that wisdom.
I'm here.
I'm here in Boston.
I will be here forever.
I've moved here.
There's nothing I can do.
I'm a surf shackled to my land.
I'm legally bowed to my land.
I'm not able to move away.
I'm going to die 30 feet away from where I was born, Ben.
That's the system we live in.
That's the dream.
OK, how do you feel about all that?
Great.
Doesn't that feel like just yesterday?
Did you just get mad at me if you're going to college?
It feels like it was such a far away dream.
But now things have progressed so fast.
I mean, I'm just, we've, OK, PCB HQ, right,
talked about for like literal years.
I mean, depending on how you want to count it,
PCB HQ could be its first thought of a prelude to it.
It was just going to be Tom and Digi.
Like 2013, 14 at latest.
Like fucking so, like a half a decade of the promise
of that kind of group of getting together.
Me and you, we don't give a shit about any of that.
No, in fact, I hate them.
We're RFCK and we don't need any fucking one.
We don't need anyone.
Let's, we're going to burn all the bridges.
This is going to be a repeat of Ben's stream from yesterday,
temporarily, late to us, however, not related to you.
I have no idea this is going to come out.
That's what I do, just shit on everyone.
That's my thing.
Everyone sucks.
It's, it's glorious.
It's literally fantastic.
Hey, you know who else we saw?
You know who else sucks?
Well, you and me.
Well, well, the combination of, you know,
who else, and also who we saw in person early
when we were at Burning Con.
All of you who are listening to this, probably most of them,
a little bit of them, we've got such a spirit.
Our entire audience was there.
It felt like, didn't it?
It felt like we had like a mass of people.
Sit back a little bit.
You're, you're, you're noticeably louder than me.
Okay. Well, then I will get back.
So we can fix that by just you not leaning in.
And I think it'll be fine.
Okay. It felt like at Burning Con,
like just a tidal wave of people showed up
that we're just coming over to see RFCK.
People I didn't genuinely believe were real.
Yeah. There were a bunch of people like from all,
like across the spectrum of like old veterans
who you would like, you know, you hear the name
and you shudder and your ass whole quakes
and you just want to receive back in the recesses of your mind.
You're too scared of the girth and impressive mic
they may have and like fucking, you know, literally who's.
That's right.
And it was a great time.
It was so nice. I want to shout out.
I have them right here.
I want to give Levy Jevy a shout out
for giving me these sweet communist pins.
I haven't had a chance to wear them out in public yet,
but it'll happen.
I don't know if this is like private information,
but you know what? I don't care.
Slimehouse, which is what the Airbnb was called,
where all the RFCK guys hung out,
all the RCK fans hung out.
Quote unquote.
Quote unquote fans of quote unquote RFCK.
They're thinking about like moving here to Boston as well,
like getting a house together to live together.
Boy, how wacky.
That would be insane.
Like it would be insane.
Everything related to RCK.
I've said this before,
but my house is literally that.
My house was,
my house that I live in was formed by a bunch of guys
who knew each other from an internet forum.
RCK is just like PCP, but good.
That's all it is.
That's all it's ever been.
That's all that will ever be.
The absolute astonishing raid that has gone from like,
you know, just like these fans,
like just got so like into RCK
that they were able to, you know,
convince themselves to go across the country
and wherever they fuck they lived.
Go to Baltimore to go to Bronicon and to live together.
And now they're still like submitting
with the idea of living together
from like a fucking weekend.
They're just like actually thinking about moving here.
We smote them.
And this isn't just like a ha ha funny idea.
I mean, obviously it might not happen.
You know, nothing's been signed.
Nothing's official.
But like they're looking at houses.
They're genuine about it.
They're genuine about their interest at least.
And it's fucking crazy.
You leaving?
Oh.
Am I leaving the house?
Oh, I thought you were coming in here to say something.
No, I just came in to see what you were talking about.
Oh.
Do a slime house.
If you live in a hellhole and you hate it.
Yeah.
Then leave.
Then do it.
You have people.
Try just being richer.
Have you tried?
Have you considered picking yourself up
by your bootstraps, you fools?
Who seems like they could like support,
they can help support you.
Not like you're mooching off them.
But who seems responsible?
It's not your parents.
It's not your friends.
It's not your church.
It's AJ Xu.
Yeah.
You should definitely leech off of AJ.
It's AJ Xu up in a frame.
You can't get the door open.
We're screaming.
You can't do this.
Sorry.
You could close the door.
Yeah, you could.
Can you talk it?
She's going.
No, that's AJ Xu up in a frame.
I trust you.
Okay.
Not me though.
I don't.
Who we trust?
We don't.
That's not our endorsement.
But it's just so crazy to think that like,
it's magical, right?
It's fucking magical.
I don't want to have any reservation, my voice.
I want to have anything that is an absolute hubris.
RFCK is like the best thing to happen to anyone.
To anyone's life.
To anyone that, it doesn't even know where RFCK is.
Their life's just been tangentially benefited
from us existing.
Think about all the, okay, listen.
People like Conman, they're going to shoot up a school.
Listen, they were so impressed when they met RFCK.
They were so like on the verge of so,
like they were like acceleration-ness before they
went to New Los Angeles to be educated and Milwaukee.
Where it's all, things have already been accelerated.
Yeah, it's the end of history.
Yeah, the philosophy is not even needed
because it just is the case constantly.
You put it into practice.
And we made them normal.
And by normal, I mean bloodthirsty,
slime-thirsty gangsters who roam the streets
looking for children to kill.
It's incredible.
We've done so much good for the world.
Dude, we fucked that shit up.
High five.
Dude.
High hoof, bro.
It hurts.
It hurts me.
Dude, BronyCon was so cool.
It was pretty good.
Hanging out with, you know, okay,
I've said before I've said it again,
RFCK has like the best fan base,
like I've ever been a part of.
Like, out of like, out of like, even real ones too.
I mean, a part of it is like-
Which I was a fan.
You know what?
How good would it be to like sit back and, you know,
do nothing coast on the victories of me and you, Ben,
and just, you know, pretend as though they have
some semblance of ownership to the game.
Oh, they populated, they talk a lot.
Nah, they'd be so fucking easy.
Sad.
Literally.
Disgusting.
Sounds like the life.
But anyway, again, I fucking, like,
part of the benefit of RFCK is that it's so like,
small of like an endeavor, right?
So it's like you're almost forced to like, be cool,
or also be expelled and cyberbullied
for how bad of a person you are.
And it's great.
It just breeds like, genuine people who I think are like,
I would actually consider my friends.
Be like a coffin of frame.
Like, I love those guys.
Like, I actually like them, you know?
They're cool and I like them.
So, Bronecon, like everything related to Bronecon
was a nightmare and I kind of like hated it
and it was a nightmare.
But like Slimehouse, just like going away from the con,
you know, not dealing with like whatever fucking,
you know, autistic shit was happening over there
and not having to walk around in the blistering
Baltimore humidity.
Just being able to go back to Slimehouse,
hang out with people, talk, you know,
maybe party for a day, maybe just real talk for a day.
It was glorious.
It was absolutely incredible.
And I've never felt so at home in a community.
And you know what?
It's beautiful.
And I'm really, I'm really ecstatic.
I'm so happy for RFCK, like in all the ways.
I'm so excited for the future, Ben.
I'm so like, we're together.
We're together.
I can't believe it.
It's fucking gay too.
We've overcome like, like, listen, you know,
the Revolutionary War, that's like pussy shit.
I could do that in my fucking sleep.
We PSP HQ, fucking throw it in the trash.
It doesn't even matter.
Who do we need other than me and you?
Who am I gonna talk to Digi about?
I don't even think it's like, it works with you.
It sounds like a disaster.
Not that I wouldn't have liked him to be here,
but you know, other plans, you know, whatever,
it doesn't matter.
The point is, is that like RFCK is the only thing
that I can think of where like being in person
would like, like benefit in like a real way.
Cause you know what?
RFCK has always just been about like,
not being like, you know, overly,
what's the word, produced, you know, not about quality.
It's not about being.
In fact, it's about the opposite.
It's not about being fucking, you know,
all prim and proper,
and about being like a real funny less way.
Like, oh, ha ha, did you see that funny?
Did you see, wow, these cookies?
Well, what's the deal then?
Why, why, why do you, when you click a cookie,
do you get more cookies?
Ha ha, that's so strange.
It's about being real shit.
The interpretation you should have
is that you're literally right here next to me
and Ben right now.
And it's been a long day.
We've been fucking talking all day.
And now we're just sitting down
to play some video games late at night.
You know, the ideal circumstances of you listening
to any of these episodes is late at night,
you know, you want to go to bed, but like, ah,
but I like, I drank like a fucking bang or something
and I can't go to sleep.
Shit, I just drank a marshmallow ex-durance.
Oh, God, I just had, I just had a spike energy,
which is actually just a supplement.
And I'm going to puke up my 15,000 times
by a daily dose of vitamin B. Oh God.
I am, I just can't get over my disappointment
with marshmallow rockstar.
It's just not, it's just not quite there.
It's exactly what I feared.
Frankly, I think you're like, the look on your face
and like the sheer shock when you were at the Korean store
was like, there was no way I could have lived up to it.
No, no, it's just, there's no way.
The promise of the can, the promise of,
the promise of a can that's pure white.
It's like, this is like, like you thought you knew
rockstar ex-durance before.
This is a pure white can,
promises like the apotheosis of everything
that the product here too far was meant to be.
That's what it screams to me.
And I believed it, like the fool that I am.
You know what this is?
Levy Jevy, going back to Bronicon,
every time we go into a convenience store,
he would look for like a stay dead bang.
He would look for like a very like, you know,
ghostly energy drink.
I think this is it.
I think the marshmallow ex-durance.
Absolutely, it is white, black and red.
What's more stated than that?
It absolutely is.
Yeah.
I don't think it existed like a week and a half ago.
Wait, how long has it been since Bronicon?
Oh God, what, like a week or two?
God.
Wait, has this been over a week already?
Yeah, man.
Oh Jesus.
It's a 13.
Is it Friday the 13th?
Feels like it.
No, it's perpetually Friday the 13th, you're with us.
Oh, okay, okay.
My entire life, this is like,
it's gonna be like the most like first world complaint
like ever, like ever since I've been like,
I just like this summer,
I knew it could be like my last chance
to do a lot of stuff with like my friends,
my offline friends at home,
and like a lot of chance to do a lot of things.
You know, I'm gonna be in fucking college
and we put on my nose the grindstone doing that shit.
And like basically my last chance to do a lot of like,
even just online stuff.
Like, it's not like I'm quitting the PCP
or anything related to that,
but like, you know, just the mechanics of
where I'm gonna find like a place
where I can record and be loud,
not my dorm probably.
So I'm gonna be decreasing my internet presence.
So this summer is gonna be like my last message
of a lot of the things I have become accustomed to
for like literal years previous.
Like, you know, the ease of being able to like,
call out my friends whenever I want to be like,
hey, you wanna hang out?
Like I would do so much for granted
that like I didn't do it,
even though I liked my friends,
it was just so much of like a,
ah, I can do that whatever.
And you know what?
I regret it because this summer was so nice
because I was enforcing myself,
like do all the things that I was taking
for granted and not like doing.
And so I had so much jam-packed,
like action-packed fun,
that like my brain is like fucked right now.
Like it feels like, it's funny, right?
Because we're doing, or well,
things are happening in the city outside of our control.
And it's very strange that things seem to be progressing
in almost like alternative reality experience.
You know what I'm talking about, Ben?
You know, that smile that's just wrinkled
on your dimples and your strength.
You'll be a lost being.
I'm afraid I don't follow.
But anyway, and that's been like kind of going to a crawl
and so people will be like, oh, what,
what have you been doing?
Fucking sucking in your own dick.
And yet it's great you ever tried it.
But yeah, I've just been-
I don't kiss and tell.
I've been going all over the place with like,
I've just been fucking going from Milan to Minsk,
if you know what I'm trying to say.
So totally, dude.
We've all been there.
And it's been like, it's been great.
This is really the only way to like,
into something like this, like an error of your life.
Because for like, I don't know why I'm
feeling like a mile a minute right now.
I haven't like, been able to say anything.
This is fun.
I have nothing to say.
Okay, I'm just going to bounce off you
whenever I feel the need to.
You'll have to excuse my enthusiasm,
because I'm just fucking ripping and run right now.
And I'm like, I feel like not screaming,
because then Ben's roommates will want me to die.
They already do.
Wait, wait, Ben, why do you have an image of cough
on your desktop right now?
Oh, well, he asked me to, he said he wanted a,
what do you call it?
Like, he said he liked my color filter on the stream.
And then he was like, I want to make one like that
of my face, of this picture.
And then I was like, I'll fucking do it for him.
Retire.
But then I did.
And like, by the time I had done it,
I think it was Connor had already made him one.
But I think he liked mine better.
Mine had a brighter pink, so get fucked Connor.
We should be on that guy.
We should kill that guy.
What was I saying?
Oh, my entire life proceeding this summer,
and I guess sort of to a lesser extent last summer,
but like for the past like couple of years,
I'm sure I've talked about this before,
but like after middle school,
some like personal shit that I don't really want
to discuss because I'm important to the story went down.
And I started going to online school
for like my high school life.
And it was fun.
It was good because I was able to like pursue
a lot of online stuff and I was able to become
the man that you see before me today.
And I don't regret a moment because you know,
when you regret life choices and you're like,
oh, I should have done this.
Ah, well, you, you would have been a different person.
Well, it doesn't matter.
Point is, is I lit a very stationary life.
And in a moment, I thought it was fun and cool.
Because you know, I was hanging out,
I was rubbing shoulders with a Digi Bro
and it was really nice to be cool.
Can you imagine?
And I was doing this very show
where I was working on this one.
I was doing all these sort of things.
And it was a gale at the time.
But, oh, is that a frenzy?
Oh.
Oh my God, my brain, like why even have anything
that's not this game?
My dopamine is just rushing through my body right now.
Couldn't tell you, dude.
I'm like pissing out dopamine.
I have too much of it.
Like it's, I'm just letting it go to waste.
The thing about, the thing about cookie clicker
is that like 100% of your cookie production
comes from frenzies.
Yeah.
Like everything else is stupid and doesn't matter.
Have you ever done, you know, cookie clicker strats?
Do you know any?
Yeah, I know that the, I'm deliberately not doing them.
But I know that the actual strats are download an app
that tells you what the most efficient next purchase is
and then download another app
that automatically makes it for you.
The most efficient way to play cookie clicker
is not to play it.
But, oh yeah, but I just been living such a stationary life
and such like a fucking like, oh, I'm in my room exclusively.
And that's been one of the things I want to accomplish
with like going away, you know, going to a new city
and having to deal with all the ramifications
of going to college and doing that.
It's just cause I want to like, I don't know,
to fucking live because I have never done it before.
Basically, you know, I,
Ah, pathetic.
You, you've been, we're such a huge inspiration.
I mean, not just in this way, but in a lot of ways,
but it's specifically like,
you going on your fucking like adventures across Europe.
I mean, that's crazy.
That's crazy stuff I could have never imagined
before like this summer where like, I, you know,
I've been to more places and I've been way more independent
than I have, you know, in past my life.
It's felt so exhilarating and great.
And I'm now at the end of this long line of fucking God,
okay, all right, listen, all right, listen to this, Ben.
This is crazy.
In 30 days, I went from San Diego to London, to San Diego,
to LA, to Monterey, to San Francisco, California,
back again to San Diego, to Baltimore, Maryland,
to BronyCon, to Michigan, to Boston.
Oh, and New York City is also in there.
New York, we spent like three hours in New York City.
That's right.
And we got McDonald's in Times Square.
And stuff like that.
And we smelled the track.
We smelled the scent of the gutter.
I'm so privileged that I was able to like,
even like afford to save up that much money
to do something like that.
And like, I was able to like, you know, be able to,
it's a privilege lifestyle, obviously.
And I'm super thankful for it.
And it's just such a, it's indescribable,
this feeling of just sheer like,
a crescendo of so many things that have been building up.
So many like ideas that have been fostering on my mind.
The ending of so many like things
that I've wanted to do online.
Like like this, this slime score of stuff
that's been going on lately.
You know, a lot of people are finding, you know,
don't really care about it.
And a lot of it hasn't really had the impact
of stuff that's happened previously in this work.
That's fine.
Cause it's something that I've wanted to do for a while.
It's something that I've been really like excited to do.
And the idea of it, it's not like over or going to be over
by the time I start school.
But like, that's like the last vestige of my old life,
of my old like thing that I'm gonna be doing.
Obviously I'm gonna keep doing it this morning.
And keep coming back over here and do R2K with them.
But like, I've done all these adventures,
I've done all these travels.
I've said goodbye to all my friends
that I've known all my life.
So goodbye to the town and the city
I've said goodbye to all of it.
And I'm finishing up all the work that I've wanted to do.
You know, obviously there's still projects
I could have done, but like all the ones that, you know,
I actually wanted to, you know,
slime corporate is actually started working on this for,
doing all these new things I have done before.
I mean, just early today, even though like I'm really bad at it,
it's really embarrassing and sucks.
I've been working out with you,
which I've never done before in my entire life.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
Sick and cool.
Should we talk about getting swole?
Dude, we can't.
Should we talk about Baramunchi?
We can't talk about Baramunchi,
but just to finish this off,
like now I'm away from all those trips
and I don't want to go on anymore.
I don't want to get another plane forever.
And I'm here in a new city.
I've all, like it doesn't, part of me is like,
it doesn't feel like anything changed.
You know, I've been to Boston so many times before.
I've been for so many extended periods.
I've been in this chair before,
doing Arpsichia live with you before,
but now it's just the beginning of so much more.
And it's so weird to say,
because none of the ramifications of this
will be felt by like the people watching this, right?
Like there's been so many, like in the PCP,
there's been so many like, oh, okay, new shifts.
Like, you know, Hippo has been doing his new,
or not new necessarily, but like been doing all the way,
but it feels like a new era of Hippo goodness.
It feels like a new like rejuvenating of things.
Nate's been starting his, you know,
he went full-time YouTube.
He's doing that for a while.
There's gonna be new things happening in the PCP right now.
And as for me as well, but like,
none of it is gonna be like,
oh, new things that you can produce.
In fact, it's gonna be like the exact opposite
where I'm like, no longer here, you know?
Hell yeah, dude.
Hell yeah, that's what everyone wants.
But yeah, you're gonna pull a Jesse, just disappear.
Uh, that will be kind of,
I don't know what to expect honestly.
I don't know what things will be like with my schedule,
because it's not like I will want to do it any less,
but like it will just be like,
like I can't do it almost.
Like, I'll be able to record with you
because I'm here in your house right now, right?
Like I can come over on certain days
and we can record together and we'll be fine and good.
But like, I'm not gonna like, like, hey, Ben,
I wanna be in the next PCP.
Can I come over with you and we record together?
That would be, the answer would be no.
Yeah, yeah.
Get the fuck out.
Oh, dude, you're watching Defuntland up there?
Yeah.
Defuntland's so good, but pull up,
which one are you listening?
This was,
I just kind of have the playlist going.
This is Disney's best coaster,
Space Mountain from the Earth to the Moon.
When did you get into Defuntland?
Oh, I mean, I knew about them before.
I mean, I've seen them before,
like as of probably like two years ago
or a year and a half ago.
And I don't know, I just,
you, that feel when you just,
that feel when you just need something to listen to
and you just listen to the entire fucking playlist
and then it's done and you're like,
well, still need something and you just start it again.
Defuntland, like riled up in something to me
that I had never like felt before.
And I got into Defuntland like when they like
first kind of blew up.
Like, I forget what video it was,
but there was one video that like went viral
and then like it was like one of the very first ones
and I got into it there.
And it was cool.
I feel like they've got like pretty overproduced now it is.
Like they're pretty like,
there's like a bunch of editors
and like there's like two writers now I think
and it's like a lot of like extra blow
and I don't think he adds anything.
And he's sort of just become like Wikipedia guy
where at the beginning I feel like he was like,
almost like personally enraged by a lot of them
as opposed to like,
What do you mean by enraged?
Tell me about that.
Because one of the things that I don't,
the thing that I don't like about it
is the sort of inherent way
that it like fetishizes commercial endeavors.
And sometimes I don't feel like that.
Sometimes it feels like he's mocking a thing
and I like that.
But sometimes he'll get like a little sentimental
about something being closed
and it makes me feel pure disgust.
That's the, that's where I want.
That's the reason why I want,
why just because like it's Disney
and you don't think that anyone should be,
you know, attached to what they create.
Yeah, absolutely not.
It's horrible.
Like, like these things are just inherently evil.
No, they're inherently evil.
They are. That's insane.
These things are like, these things are wild beasts.
These things are behemoths that will turn on you
and kill you in a moment
if it will profit them even a bit.
Hi.
Hey, let's go ahead.
Don't, I'm not here.
I was just...
No, come on.
You guys, you guys, come on in.
The one condition of you being in here
is no parallel conversations.
Yeah, that's what I was trying to avoid last time.
Okay.
But that's not, that's not to say that,
it's not that you can't talk.
Okay.
Okay, yeah.
No, my bag's downstairs.
Okay.
What's going on?
Hey.
We're playing cookie clicker.
We were talking about defunct land.
This guy doesn't think that there's any artistry
in like a theme park.
I didn't say it.
That's not what I said.
Yeah, you're right.
That's not what you said at all actually.
I didn't say there's no artistry.
I said that it's evil.
Well...
Oh, you want more?
Do you actually want more?
Yeah, I like it.
Wait, I want to see what color the liquid is.
Is this just clear?
It's clear.
It seems like a bunch on manufacturing, I would imagine.
Did you like it?
What do you think of it?
Yeah, I like it a lot.
I like it?
It's just that the cotton candy
is like the same thing, but better.
I don't know.
Does it kind of taste like
if you mix melon soda with grenadine?
I don't taste melon.
It kind of just tastes like cream soda.
No.
I taste it a lot.
Now that you say that.
Wait, give me a second.
No, it's cream soda.
It's just cream soda is what it is.
No, it's not just cream soda.
There's more new ones to it than that.
It's got a whole flavor profile
that you're just ignoring.
It tastes like something I've had before my childhood.
It's cream soda.
I just realized it's cream soda.
Close that door, but we can continue.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, wait, what time is it?
I gotta keep an eye on the time.
Well, I set my alarm to go off before the bus gets here
and before I have to leave,
so I can hear what time it is.
I have no idea what time it is.
Oh, it's almost 10.
Okay, I have to leave in a couple of minutes.
It's because the bus comes at 10 o'clock and I
have to get out of here at 10 o'clock.
Ben, I don't even disagree with you.
I need your reaction, which didn't need to happen.
Then I thought you were saying that you weren't.
Why don't you be like Neil deGrasse Tyson
and be purely logical?
It's a giant corporation.
It wants your money.
It's evil, but it's also, art's also artistic.
There's multiplicity in art.
I mean, a lot of, okay, I will stand by this
till the day I die.
And a lot of renaissance, at least.
I don't really know a lot about early Disney
and I'm sure there were a lot of varying stuff.
I don't really know all about Walt personally, honestly.
But I know for a fact that in renaissance Disney movies,
there was genuine passion from a lot of people
who genuinely wanted to create a good artistic product.
And I think they did it a lot of the time.
There was definitely, like it was not just
a soulless crank out for money.
Obviously it was obviously Eisner wanted money, obviously.
This is not to my point.
No, I know it's not.
I'm just saying.
I become a profitable thing in a legit career move
that people's parents and family didn't ostracize them for.
To be an animator for many, many years
was just like, what the fuck are you doing?
Like that was like the mom on the YouTube
were now of like, you know, what early...
Did Snow White make a lot of money?
Oh, dude, fuck yeah, yeah, I did.
They went on the massive debt first, though, didn't they?
Well, yeah, they did it for Cinderella.
Or was it Sleeping BlueDee?
I think it might've been Sleepin' BlueDee.
Sleepin' BlueDee.
Oh wait, Google search reconorder right now.
No.
Google search recon...
I'll look up reconorder.
You leaving?
She's getting her problem.
All right.
The problem is not.
My problem is not that the artistry of these things is bad.
My problem is not that they are not artistically crafted.
My problem is that whatever else they might be,
they are commodified.
Yeah, okay, you're not wrong.
And I have no problem with that.
And I just really hate it when a little bit of...
I hate it when sentimentality creeps into the way that like...
Defunctland isn't really that guilty of it,
but like Company Man is way more guilty of it.
When sentimentality creeps into it,
when they're talking about a commercial venture,
as though we should pity or hope for the best
for these entities that absolutely would not do the same for us,
these things would fucking slit our throats for a nickel.
Well, okay, hold on.
I cave that the door is open.
You're right.
The reason I think there's a difference there
is not just the host of the show being different.
Company Man is very like...
Company Man is a very weird person.
He's a very weird host.
I think that...
I mean, I don't know about the guy personally.
I think that it's somewhat inevitable
because I feel like when you're talking...
You have to make an emotional arc.
Yeah, it has to have an emotional arc.
You have to make a story out of it.
And the protagonist of the story has to be someone
that you feel something for.
So you have to anthropomorphize these behemoths.
What I was going to say is exactly what I was saying earlier,
just about...
Company Man talks about a fucking target,
which is nothing but business.
It's not as though that's a controversial stance,
like it just is a business.
It's what it is about.
Cassie Snap is leaving the building.
Bye.
Sorry to interrupt your conversation.
That's fine.
If Company Man, if Defunct Land made a video
that was about Disney, the ups and downs of that or something,
about the ups and downs of Disney,
that would be stupid too.
But it's not about Disney as a company.
It's about these specific rides,
which, while the infrastructure of the music part
is solely a business,
it's like these rides, again, have artistry in them.
I'm not saying that you're not saying that.
I'm just saying that he gets attached to not like...
It's weird to get attached to Target
because what is the experience of Target?
Like you pay money for items that you get and then you leave.
But the experience of riding, especially at Disney theme park,
there's a lot of levels there and a lot of artistry
and a lot of things to appreciate in it.
So it's not just like,
I'm sad that I can't give Disney money more.
It's like, I'm sad that this piece of genuine history
is not being preserved in any way.
The experience of a roller coaster, or any museum park ride,
is the exact same thing as like a stage musical,
where it's so finite and limited of a thing,
even more so than a stage musical because there can be the reruns.
But the original production of a musical,
in the same way as a music park,
just happens and then leaves and gone
and there's no way that even can experience it
in the way it's meant to be.
You can record it, but it's not the same thing.
It's not the experience of being in there in the theater theater.
There is something particularly tawdry to me
about a roller coaster as a commercial object.
In the way that it is like literally just a mill
where people line up to be loaded into it,
run through it, and then ejected,
there is something like particularly...
Okay, well...
And I get that like, yeah, you're paying for this.
It's about the experience.
Like, it's not the...
It's not that I don't even understand the appeal.
I do.
There's just something...
Like, if I...
Okay, I kind of want to qualify this.
Like, I could probably go to a theme park,
pay some money, and have a good time.
I'm not saying that I'm incapable of that.
I'm just saying when I see it, right?
When I see it in a video of like people like,
oh, look, a load of like 30 people
is being loaded into this thing and chatteled around
and then spat out.
And then like the worker is just like sad
and just like doesn't care.
Then they're talking about like,
oh, yeah, like fucking, you know, four million.
Change this to Benson.
I miss the...
I miss the cookie.
I'm so fucking...
Change this to RFCK.
Okay.
Did you forget like what?
I'm trying to think of something good.
Bennett goes to look at his keyboard,
looks at his keyboard for like a solid second.
Like his hands hovering over the keyboard,
like unable to spell RFCK.
Polly slime.
Wow, that's...
Didn't even capitalize the C, dude.
Yeah, that's right.
We're off-brand.
That was the worst experience of my life
was watching that happen.
Cool.
Well, you get ready for plenty more.
Plenty more of that came from.
Okay.
I don't even like have anything to say
to what you're saying,
because I get it.
Like I don't viscerally get it,
but like there's nothing I can say to it.
Keep it down a little bit.
Sure, sure, sure.
There's nothing I can like say to like comment
in order to I really want to,
because it doesn't really matter.
But I will say that like,
I feel that more worth like,
the artistry and display is almost never,
like in a Disney amusement park ride.
You know, you're talking about artistry.
I don't know.
I know that like, okay,
technical skill goes,
I have a hard time seeing a roller coaster
as a work of art.
I really do.
Ben, okay.
I'm actually gonna say exactly that,
that it's almost never a roller coaster.
Imagineers, the people who make Disney rides,
ha ha, funny name.
We'll always say that making amusement,
making roller coasters is always the hardest thing,
because the experience on a roller coaster
is exclusively like you go fast,
and it's fun because you go fast.
And there's very,
like if you look at side by side,
it's something like Thunder Mountain,
as opposed to like another ride,
like the Haunted Mansion,
way less theme and way,
not less effort,
but like way less of like an overarching artistry.
In the Haunted Mansion,
it's not a go fast thing.
And this is where like the sort of stuff
where like Disney artistry really comes into play,
because it's not just like they've spruced up the queue,
and then like the roller coasters painted a different color.
That's not all I'm talking about.
I'm talking about how the meticulously,
how they went to every step of that ride.
That's such like a weird,
like I don't describe it like multi-media ride.
It starts with a walking session,
and then there's like an elevator sequence.
Which ride are you talking about?
The Haunted Mansion.
Have you been on it?
Oh, I've been on the Tower of Terror.
Not completely different.
I'm not sure if I've been on the Haunted Mansion.
I've been to Disney World a couple of times.
So I feel like probably, but I don't remember.
But like, it's not like a fast like thrill ride.
Almost none of like the truly incredible artistic rides
are usually thrill rides.
Those are very hard to make.
But the Haunted Mansion,
just this like meticulously designed and crafted house,
just even the exterior of the ride being like,
like that you have to perfectly recreate.
I'm not talking about Disneyland right now
because I'd never been to Disney World.
But like, and also it was first,
the lawn that they have to maintain
and like the outside, they have to perfectly met.
First of all, make it fit in with the surrounding areas
of New Orleans Square.
The section of the park it takes place in.
And then they have to make it look dilapidated inside.
And they have to do all of these things
in the queue, in the ride themselves.
I mean, if you were to just like,
Google search Haunted Mansion right now
because you'll see that it is like, okay, fine.
But it is like a very like,
I mean, I would describe it in another way,
like just meticulously crafted artistic experience
that you would have to be,
at least somewhat passionate making.
And I know that because there's interviews with the guy
who may not ever get his fucking name because he's famous.
I don't disagree with any of this.
I know that it's all about crafting an experience
or whatever.
And it's not, it's not just like,
how do we make this the funnest thing?
Like there's like lore.
There's like heaps of fucking lore for a ton of rides.
There's like genuine like, like intrigue
with like the creation of rides.
And there are some fucking rides that didn't get it.
What do you mean?
What do you mean by lore?
What do you mean by there's lore?
Okay, okay.
Well, I mean, I know that certain rides
have like a sort of narrative to them that like,
you know, you're waiting in line and you see stuff.
And then you get, yeah, I get that.
I'm talking about like genuine fucking like,
you have to like environmental gameplay
if you pick up to understand some things.
I'm gonna talk about one that wasn't actually made,
but like was like the magnum opus of this idea.
And it sort of spread to the part
of the most emblematic thing.
The idea of, are you trying to...
Gay, yes.
I'm trying to think about how to explain this.
In Dingland, in Frontierland,
there is a section where you can ride
a big Thunder Mountain, which is a roller coaster.
Is that the one?
Does that end with like a water flume?
It does in like, do you mean in Paris, I think?
Okay, then I'm not sure if I've ridden it.
I haven't been to Disney World in probably like 15 years.
I've never been to a world.
I want you for the bad way.
Oh, I've never.
Right, you're a fucking West Coast slime ball.
So I'm talking about Disneyland.
Yeah, I've never been to Disneyland.
I've only been to Disney World.
So okay, yeah, there's definitely gonna be rides
you've been on that I have never been on.
Oh, they would have the Haunted Mansion,
but anyway, it doesn't matter.
Probably.
What was I fucking saying?
Oh yeah, okay, Big Thunder Mountain.
There was gonna be a plan, because historically,
there's always been one big spot of Disneyland
that has not been used.
And it's always been a question like,
where are they gonna put that?
What kind of rides, what kind of land are they gonna put there?
And so there's, I think it's Tony Baxter.
No, that's an animator.
I'm retarded.
Tell me about James Baxter.
Oh yeah.
God, what's this fucking,
I can't remember, it doesn't matter.
A famous Imagineer was going to make an entire section
around Big Thunder Mountain called Big Thunder Mesa.
There's gonna be a bunch of rides there
that will all tie in to this one central idea
of this Wild West town that would be made.
And there was gonna be lore about,
there was a really wealthy owner of a mine who died,
and that would tie in to, I think,
the Haunted Mansion in some way,
or maybe it was gonna tie into Big Thunder Mountain about it.
He was a spear that was compelling
via the mine carts to go out of whack,
and that's why they're really fast and stuff.
But there was just this large, elaborate fucking section
of land that was gonna be plotted out to foster
this narrative of this town, this Wild West town,
that was gonna be meticulously made,
and just like the craftsmanship on me
that would have to not only just the technical skill
of achieving the rides that he wanted to,
but also just like the sheer imagination
that he would have to have come up with
in the first place in some of the rides.
There was just gonna be a whole bunch of shit
that was gonna go in there.
There's gonna be fucking, again, more lore.
I can't write it off the top of my head, but.
You're Google.
Hold on.
No, no Google.
Okay, fine.
What are you doing right now?
I'm grabbing my fucking boomer pills.
Boomer pills?
Yeah.
What?
Wait, are these like memory pills?
No, no.
It's just caffeine.
Oh.
There's some right here too.
Sick.
Oh, is there?
I mean like, okay, I'm almost out.
Oh god, wait, it's a frenzy.
Oh my god, I gotta capitalize.
I gotta capitalize on this frenzy, dude.
Oh, do capitalize?
This doesn't sound very insane of you.
Shut the fuck up, I'll fucking kill you.
I mean, I have to seize the means of this frenzy.
But yeah, anyway, stuff like that,
where it's like, this one guy has an idea
for like an entire fucking simulated town
experiencing what he wants to manufacture
in this theme park with all this well-thought-out things
about the people who would live there
and the sort of people who would affect it
over the course of it, it's like a fantasized reality.
Like, okay, strip away rides,
like rides not being experienced,
like not being a thing that exists.
Disneyland is still an artistic marvel,
just the way that it uses sightlines and smells
and sounds and visualizations of like,
just mainstream, just mainstream USA,
about this crafted experience that Disney wanted,
Walt Disney wanted to make from all the things
that he had experienced in his childhood,
all the good vibration that he had seen
living in like rural America.
He wanted to bring that to this theme park
and he like sculpted these fucking buildings
and they look incredible and they look masterful
and he used, people always like, are like, ha ha, oh dude,
Disneyland uses smells, like hack your fucking brain
and brainwash you and they're like thinking
what they want you to think.
And they brainwash you into thinking
you're enjoying yourself, but it's just a trick.
It's like, that sort of thing is genius.
They're like, they're like completely crafting
your actual, this isn't a video game,
this isn't anything like that,
you're really there in real life.
There's a crafted experience, it's incredible.
Yeah, I mean, you're not, you're not wrong,
you're not wrong.
I forget the point I was making.
Yeah, I guess I love theme parks now.
Me and yours point was like completely separate
and it wasn't even related to one another.
Yeah, it wasn't even like a discussion,
it was just you said something and I said it too.
I'm just like, isn't capitalism bad?
And you're just like, yeah, but isn't creativity cool?
Ha ha ha ha ha.
I guess, maybe there's a room in this town
for the two of us.
Ha ha ha, never mind.
I was watching the, you know, I said on the PCP,
you weren't on this week's PCP, right?
You didn't.
No, I was.
You were.
Oh yeah, I was talking about,
I was talking about defunct TV.
And I said on that the defunct.
Oh, I don't remember that.
I brought it up, I brought it up defunct TV
and I said that defunct TV is just a series
about the Muppets.
Turns out I was wrong.
Most of them are about the Muppets,
but some of them are about other TV shows,
most of which involve puppetry of some kind.
I don't know if that's deliberate or just a coincidence,
but, you know, it's like a good,
like informative narrative about like the life
and times of Jim Hansen, right?
Like it's cool.
Jim Hansen's pretty good, I guess, and stuff,
but I just can't get over,
I just can't get over that it's all funded by capital.
It's all in service of capital, it makes me mad.
It makes me fucking mad.
Isn't that all art?
Like all that?
What is it?
Yeah, isn't it?
Like any TV show, any comic book.
All art, you say.
All art is funded by capital.
Not literally all art, but like almost all mainstream.
Commercial art, mainstream art, yeah.
Sure.
It is.
And I hate mainstream art, I hate everything.
Do you feel that way when some talks about like anime shows?
Yes, absolutely do.
I hate it.
I can't fucking stand any of it.
It's all fucking poison.
It's all corrupt, it's all evil.
It's all in service of devils.
Oh poo.
No, not oh poo.
Oh Ben, why can't you just,
why can't you just lighten up?
Why can't you just lighten up?
Just turn your brain off.
Just learn to enjoy it.
You don't have to turn your brain off.
Yes you do, I literally feel like to ignore the fact
that everything in this world is corrupt and evil.
You have to turn your brain off.
You don't even have to ignore it.
You can think about it while you're talking about it
constantly, but like it doesn't mean that it's,
like the art that itself is any less valuable
or that it's any less.
I kind of think that it means that it's less valuable.
Hot take.
That's my hot take.
It's just, I don't know man.
Just hate everything.
I can't stand it.
I can't stand existing in this world anymore.
Well, everything's bad.
Everything's bad and corrupt.
Listen, it's Cougar Clicker version, the current year.
You know, I mean, this game's pretty good.
Cougar Clicker is the only thing, like simulation,
it's similar to being like a robber bear
and like lords over the people.
I'm like Mav's mind.
Yeah, but I mean, it's all in good fun.
You know what I'm saying?
Everyone's gonna say there's something.
Oh, oh, defunct plan.
Fucking, Cougar Clicker doesn't matter.
Go back to defunct plan.
Go back to it right now.
All right, fine.
Go to the channel.
What about it?
There's a podcast that he has.
I got defunct plan and I got way like fucking coolated
into like the entire theme park YouTube sphere
with Rob Plays and fucking Disney and Dan
and yes to world like everyone.
I get like, oh, people are right over there.
Ha ha, that's funny.
Here's the point.
Here's the point, I'm trying.
It's like, sure.
I know that like to enjoy anything,
you can't think about this stuff, right?
And like by being mad,
by being mad that all commercial art
is created in service of capital,
I am hamstringing my ability to like engage with
and enjoy like most things.
My question is, is enjoyment of those things even valuable?
Is it valuable at all to be like, boy,
I'd sure like to go to Disney World.
Boy, I'd sure like to watch newest seasonal anime.
I kind of think I'm happier
just like dismissing all those things out of hand.
I kind of, I don't want any of it.
I don't want these things that are made to make me happy.
It depends what you mean by that.
I'm fine, I'm fine without them.
Thank you very much.
It depends on what you mean by valuable.
I mean, there are certainly going to be like TV shows
that you would enjoy.
I mean, depends on what you mean, what is it valuable?
Not with my mindset, you know what I'm saying?
There could be, if you were to, yeah.
There could be, that it wouldn't be like,
I'm trying to think about how to phrase it.
Like it just, it wouldn't be a matter of like,
you have to like calculate like,
oh, is my enjoyment of this like equal to the morality?
No, no, wait, I was-
It's not even about morality.
It doesn't mean, it's not even about
the material consequences.
Actually, I don't care, I'll just talk about it.
There's a podcast that you do, Rob Plays,
Kevin who runs to Funkland,
which has my favorite expression
of like a person, like, okay.
You know that experience when you're in a group,
a somewhat secluded, you know,
sort of not ostracized group, but like a very niche group.
And you come up with all these fanciful, funny ways
to in-fight with the people who are very close to you,
but just not cool and niche enough.
Let this in-fight in a little bit.
That's correct, yes.
It had the most astounding version of that,
like embodiment of that I've ever seen.
Oh, lucky, lucky, lucky, lucky.
Oh, God, okay, well.
I've ever seen Rob Plays and Kevin are talking about,
it's a debate podcast, and they're talking about
like the merit of removing rides over preserving rides
and like how, you know, removing rides
allows for new rides to be made, which can also be good.
And Kevin's like, oh, no, you gotta keep
all the history, blah, blah, blah, blah.
The point of that doesn't matter.
At one point, Rob, who's arguing to, you know,
get rid of rides as long as new rides take its placement
are also equally as good.
Kevin, this is something legendary.
So, Rob.
Kevin is the defunct leader, Kevin Perger.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, Rob, you're not really accounting for theme
in a lot of these debates, you say that just
pure enjoyment is a lot of what it comes down to rides,
you know, you're fine with replacing rides
that may have historical, you know, thematic relevance,
but you know, as long as the new rides are fun,
you're fine with it.
So, in a lot of ways, are you saying that you're not
a theme park YouTuber, but rather an amusement park
YouTuber, the employment that amusement parks are like
dirt cheap e-fucks that are just like purely like four,
like the enjoyment, like your brain.
Hold the fuck on.
Yeah.
This is a, this is a lot, right?
This is some galaxy brain, yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, you're right, this is a lot.
Yeah.
I don't even know how to.
Okay, no, it's so good.
I guess it's so good.
It makes sense, it makes sense in a weird fucked up way.
Well, I have some questions.
Sure.
I guess I never considered it, but like.
There's a difference, yeah.
So I guess amusement parks and theme parks
are not exactly the same thing.
Okay, so is what makes a theme park, then,
the fact that it has a theme?
Yeah, that it has a theme that it's,
and I imagine it's a very nebulous term that like
the parks themselves would use very interchangeably
because it doesn't really matter to them,
but like on like a nerd level,
like what determines a theme park is how much I think,
you know, yeah, theme is put into like what it's described
or what is inside of it,
and also maybe the level of artistry
would be sort of a nuanced way to take it.
Like, for instance, Michigan's Adventure,
I think no one could argue, like Google search it,
is anything but an amusement park,
because there's no theme to it other than the fact
that I guess it's in Michigan, it is the theme.
There's nothing to it, it just is a series of rides
that all, you know, it just is rides,
whereas Disneyland has very police of rides.
I mean, so none of those...
No, that's right, it's folks, right?
Because they have names that have like...
Some of the rides might have themes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Does the theme, does the park itself overall
have to have a theme?
I think it would, right?
To have be a theme park, to have be a theme park.
Yeah.
I would have to think so.
Because like, because I mean like,
we go back to like the dawn of amusement parks,
and I think all rides have like a name.
Yeah.
So I guess, I'm guessing that all theme parks
are amusement parks,
but not all amusement parks are theme parks.
Yeah, that's a way to put it.
That's a way to put it, I would think.
But like, okay, the fact that he's so disparaging
of amusement park YouTubers as like a lesser class.
Like, they don't have to use their brain,
they're intellectual,
but they have all the artistry on display
with theme parks.
Dude, you fucking Kevin Bacon or whatever your name is,
you are a mere amusement park.
Like, you traffic in tawdry.
You traffic in cheap disposable schlock.
I am an art critique.
Listen, when I go to Disneyland,
I don't even ride the rides.
I just spend five hours in the queue
analyzing all of the various lore they've hidden
in the tapestries that is the wall
in Pirates of the Caribbean,
that has Johnny Depp's hideous facade
just etched in in stone on the side.
Well, I smell inside the bizarre smells and perfumes
that Disney puts into their rides,
which entire companies have tried to profit on
by selling perfumes that are scented
like Disneyland wet rides.
That's a real thing, look it up yours.
Disneyland red wide perfumes are a real thing.
That's something Jenny Nicholson would wear.
That is pretty fucked up.
And it's totally fucked up.
That's pretty fucked up a little bit.
It's a little bit like crazy.
Yeah.
But dude, it's great, right?
Like, whenever I wanted to spare it to my friends,
which I want to do all the time.
Yeah, of course.
What are friends for?
You're acting like a real amusement park YouTuber right now.
Like, I don't think you really have like the complexity,
the clearness of thought to understand what I'm trying to do.
Try appreciating nuance sometime, you fucking rude boy.
Like the cool, okay, please.
Make like a virgin Chad meme of like the amusement park
YouTuber versus the theme park YouTuber.
Like the idea of a theme park user, theme park YouTuber,
be like an absolute literal like brain dead maniac
who just like, I love to go fast.
I like when the rides are big.
I like to get flopped around on a fucking metal chair, please.
Like smash cut to like a man, like a dark oak,
like burning like a library in his fucking Playboy velvet
of Bathrobe, you know, smoking a cigar
and sipping champagne, you're like, hmm.
They're updating the queue for Tower of Terror soon.
I wonder who, what imagine they're going to apply to that job?
Like, will the new queue videos,
like will they finally shed light on like the origins
of the haunting?
Like when exactly did the bite of 83 take place?
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, it's incredible.
Boy, so.
It's incredible.
You may have a distinction like that for R2K fans.
We didn't have like, we already have gameplay goons.
So we didn't have some sort of like other equivalent
for like the cultured thematic community member.
Yeah.
Like instead of players, it's community members, right?
Where it's like dirty, filthy community members.
No, no, no.
Nurses players like, Oh, you just played the game, dude.
You don't even engage, you aren't even inspired by like the setting.
You haven't even made a contest entry?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
The Virgin player in the Chad community member.
Yeah.
That's perfect.
That's pretty good.
Uh...
Dude, were you talking about Jenny Nicholson just a second ago? You mentioned her.
Yeah, hater.
Bronycon.
I've just, lately I've decided, you know what? I'm just gonna go whole hog.
I don't really have-
Just hate people for no reason.
I don't really have a solid reason, but like, why mince- why- why go half ass with it?
I just fuckin' hate her. I just- garbage. Terrible person.
I- why? I don't- just a feeling.
It was so funny at Bronycon. Like, there would be so many times where it's like, we would just be talking and be like,
Yep. Like, I hate- I hate Impossible a lot. Just hate her.
Yeah.
Just like, mention it out of the blue.
Yeah, and then you know what? All my preconceptions were confirmed when I actually talked to her.
Dude, okay. And she was the worst.
We talked about a few stories on the PC, but there were a few choice ones.
Dude, let's have another frog fractions where we just dunk on Brony people.
Dude, oh, that's what this is right now.
Yeah.
Uh, dude, okay.
Please, regale us with the story about how K.P. could try to get her- you into her discord.
Because it's insane.
It is insane.
It is- I mean, it's not as insane as the story.
It's as insane as the stuff Jesse said that she said, but I can't confirm the veracity of any of that.
Well, it's not like, eventful, but just like, the gall of it.
The unmitigated gall of what she's trying to like, do.
It's just a shitty way of fucking being.
It's- oh, oh, god. Is that a frenzy?
Oh! Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh my fucking god.
Dude, this is what I want. I want that temple, dude.
I wanna buy that fucking temple, my other thing or my fucking-
I hope it's easy to MopUp come from your floor pit.
Cause I'm afraid that it's just been so-
Nothing could be easier.
Do it a-
Do it a- or more reward.
I do it for fun, honestly.
I'm afraid I'm you're gonna have to carry this stream for a minute because I'm fucking focused on clicking as hard as I can right now
That's fine. Listen, I understand the clicking frenzy
But it only comes down once a moon that you may be into dude. We got the timer
We've got more than half of this frenzy. I'm gonna get the temple dude
I'm gonna get the fucking temple.
The burning hole is so great because it was able to just like be so like it
It was almost refreshing and a bizarre like twisted sense
Which is like the human brain loves to have like like adversaries because if you don't have like a goal like something to
Like do or people to hate then like your brain doesn't know what to do and it feels like bliss like oh enjoy me like just pure pleasure
There's something wrong here. I'm not I'm not nature right now doesn't sound yeah. No. Thank you. Wait wait straight
Yeah, so like it was a bizarre pleasure being around people who you hate like exclusively
It was a weird like wow like it's a me against society
It's me against the entirety of everyone around me right now. Okay frenzy's over. I can I can discuss
It was it was weird just being around like
Just a sea of just insane people insane people's only can describe it. Um, oh yeah, kpk
So all right, so we're it's like the very end of the con
This is like right before closing ceremonies and we're just kind of making one last walk around the the vendors hall and we walk by
Some table somewhere and kp is there just packing up stuff
And uh, I don't want to talk to her
nothing
There's nothing I would less rather do
Um, but hippos like I'm gonna go say hi
So he just goes up walks up to her. I'm pretty sure he reckoned. She I'm almost positive. No, no she did she did
Yeah, yeah. Um, so, uh, and he says hi and she she like she turns to our group right me and uh, I think
Kazi was there. I think was me Kazi and hippo
I don't remember but she turns to like our whole group and she's after hippo says hi and she's like, oh, hey guys
You want to buy anything last minute? Which is you know, yeah fair fair question
And I think we're just like no we're we're no we're just you know
Just saying hi or whatever and she's and she's just like uh jumps right to uh, are you guys in the fan discord?
You should join the fan discord like
Not doesn't even want to talk to us. Just wants to shill her fucking fan discord
This is why this is why I knew it was a bad idea to engage
And maybe it was I don't know. I know I know it's not a big deal
But it's just like uh fuck this person. It well, it's a very like weird and like presumptuous thing
like
Oh, no, you know, I I think it's possible that in her in her mind like
The horseshoe crew and then you just like don't really matter don't really factor into her perception of humanity
Why would we yeah, sure
And so I think to her probably just like, you know, just another person just like oh, hey
You're you're someone who would be at brony con. Okay. Okay. Watch my stuff. Yeah. Yeah, I understand all that
But like the fact that like that's her fucking thing. Well, it's bad. Yeah. It's bad. Yeah, it's yeah
I'm not gonna excuse you because oh, well, like I'm just a peon. I'm not an I'm not an important person
So why would I expect her to fucking engage with me like a human being? Sure
It's fucked up man. It is fucked up. Dude. I cannot believe
The disrespect that brony con dealt to us. We didn't get a panel
Everyone treated us like we were fighting too big. I wasn't surprised. I wasn't surprised to not get a panel
Except that all the panels that I did see were such shit
And but like they were like literally who it's weak shit, man. I don't understand like why were these people allowed
To to exist. Why were they allowed to present their vision?
What's fucking lame we could we you know what we could have done it
Straber milk would have made the first public appearance since the frog fraction
I mean
I do you think maybe someone just dropped the ball like maybe someone meant to get back to you and then just like
Okay, I wonder sometimes but like like I did like send multiple emails
But I wonder if like I should just like really just fucking like
Pressed into them if that would have done anything like
If I just really should have just like stuck with it and just been like, hey, we're still here. Please respond to us
I mean
Surely someone would have read it and like well, I mean I'm sure there's someone already did read it and like you know
I mean, you know, maybe persistence does
Make the heart you'll find something is different sometimes being persistent like that can can get results
I mean, maybe it's possible that someone did in in fact intend for us to have a panel and we just slipped through the crags
I don't know. It's weird. It's really weird
Dude, you know who we did meet though was past analysis. How crazy is that like that guy?
I mean, is that really that surprising he was there? Well, okay, not surprising that he was there
But from my perspective, it was and he like mentioned like he like
Like played into this weird interpretation. I had with events and he also had it which was funny
I did not really talk to him at all. I just kind of sat high to him once or twice
Uh, it was funny these last
To quote wreck it Ralph from that one uh commercial where where they couldn't hire jc riley
To actually like a rip fries his role of a right Ralph
So just some random guy who didn't sound like wreck it Ralph to quote him last we spoke
Uh, me and past analysis were on like equal footing. He like far more
Culturally relevant in everyone's mind's eye than I am what back in the pony dance back in the pony days
Where me and we and me and him were both like, you know
Jokey and Lee referred to as the horseshoe crew CMC, you know, we were like just peripheral wait. Were you was that a thing?
That was a that was a real thing. Yeah, I totally forgot about that
Yeah, the real thing it was funny and me and him were on like, you know, just equal footing in that regard and then like
We like I see him now and I'm it's so desensitized to that idea of like, you know, it's just it's just it's just those guys
It's just the pcp who would even care
That's right. That's correct. And then he and then like one of the first things is
Everyone on one of the first things like, you know, we're talking and he's like so like how would you get in the pcp?
Like how'd you do like, what was your strat bro? How'd you do it? How'd you do it?
I was just persistent and they had no standards. That's right. There's no trick to it. You just have to keep doing it
There's nothing that they know is really no trick. Well, I'm gonna piss but I want to talk about how weird I am
Oh god, am I gonna have to carry it? Yeah, you're gonna have to do some work actually
I don't have any energy. I've sapped all my I was I told you I was already fucking
At zero energy before we we lifted and now we've lifted here. Oh my god. Is that a frenzy?
No, it's a bunch of you talk about how good your deals are from Aldi and how they
Dude, Aldi's got the best fucking deal on
Here's my here's my here's the here are the things viewers that are the best deal at Aldi that I buy
heavy cream
cauliflower
sausage
bacon
gridlock energy
avocados
chicken breast
ground flags
and mayonnaise
Now on the contrary here are the things that are the best deal from costco
And the theme of these is generally that like things you can buy in like big bulk, right?
Like things that you get in like a large amount at a time
So peanut butter get like two of the big jars like
Tape together in like a fucking a lot of things from costco or like two containers taped together
This is sort of a thing. This is true of peanut butter and the second thing on the list
mozzarella bags of shredded mozzarella also big blocks of cheddar
bags of almonds and my favorite almond flour
Which is what I used to make my legendary keto pizza
Which everyone agrees is the best on the block and then finally
The things you can get from
Wegmans, which are the best deal the list is short
francs
And pepperoni now the pepperoni is the best deal because they sell these
Giant ass bags of it and all this is is um
In terms of like cost per unit cost per volume, right?
So pepperoni Wegmans you think costco would do it, but they don't
Wegman sells the biggest cheapest bags of pepperoni by volume the francs
They sell these this this kind of hot dog called bar s
At Wegmans and they are dog shit. They actually have they have carbs in them. I don't know why they're fucking made with like
They're made with some sort of like wheat germ fucking runoff or something. I don't know they're crap, but they are the cheapest
It's like a buck 20 for a packet of hot dogs great deal
But they're a little too carby
They have there's an all beef variety, but those aren't as cheap and it's a fucking tragedy. Hey munchie. You're back
I'm back. Did you just feel it just get about how could your deals are now you mapped out?
I was just I was just informing. Yeah, I'm reading off
I have a list pinned to my wall of like what the best deals are and where to get them
Is that wf Whole Foods?
Yeah, and and nothing is not yeah, I am because
Okay, well because I was laying it all out. Yeah thinking that maybe some things would be a better deal at Whole Foods
No, no, no, nothing. Nothing. Whole Foods, dude. Yeah. No, absolutely. Oh, that's so
It's so funny that like you have these like well populated columns like very like like meticulously like Wegmans is a little sparse
Sure, but whatever the point is that you've like gone like really troubled like like perfectly
Calculate all of like these like the best deals at like a variety of stores and there's one column for Whole Foods
Which just is completely empty. You know what the killer though is what the killer is that um
Like a lot of the margin on some of these things
Like on Costco, it's generally worth it. But like on like Aldi and Wegmans
Aldi's looks so good
If I'm like if I'm going there in person like if I'm taking the bus and not just ordering it on instacart
Some of the margins are so small that like literally the bus fare offsets it and doesn't fucking matter
Yeah, but if I'm or but generally these days I order it with instacart
So whatever I'll save like a couple of bucks. I'll save a couple of bucks instacart
I gotta get on that shit instacart is really great. It's it costs like 90 dollars a year
for like free delivery
And like that in terms of like time saved that absolutely pays for itself as far as I wait how much for your 90 dollars
That's nothing bro. Yeah, no just in terms of fucking bus fare on like a year
Yeah, that's crazy for a whole year. I mean
You got to tip the driver. I mean you don't have to tip the driver
But you should probably tip the driver at least a couple bucks. So it's not
Okay, I trip for a while
I wasn't tipping the driver and then I realized that these are fucking poor people in that like this is the
You know, this is just fucking uber for groceries. This is like a fuck these people don't get benefits
They are being this is like exploits. This is absolute. This is the worst kind of exploitation of labor and I was like
If anyone deserves it these people probably fucking deserve a tip
So I fucking so I tip them like they're recommended two dollars or whatever. It's not much. I don't know whatever
so I pay that
and then
You know a fucking but other than that
It's totally worth it. It's totally I mean a company like this
I'm sure it lives and dies on people that like sign up for the service and then forget that they have it
It's like a gym, right? Like gyms don't want you to use their services gyms want you to sign up for a membership and then stop going
Yeah, that's there is actually that's what costco does too
Oh
Maybe the best thing about instacart is that they just have people with costco memberships that will shop at costco for you
You don't have like the thing about costco
You need a bizarre like membership card. They costco makes all its money on memberships
They don't make money selling their products
So now you can just go you can get someone else to go in there and buy your shit for cheap
And you don't have to buy the membership like fuck you
Oh, do you want to talk about this?
Oh, sure. Yeah, dude. Oh my god. Okay. I I I just as I always do when ben's rallying off about god knows what
I did my mind started to wander. Yeah. Yeah, my mind starts to wander. I just started looking around just how I just upgraded milk
Dude, my milk just turned chocolate. Oh my god. Wow, ben. I'm so impressed. Fuck. Yeah. You want me to dunk the cookie?
Dude, hell, yeah, I oh god
Uh, that's fucking ridiculous and stupid. Did you get an achievement for it? Achievement unlocked cookie dunker
That's insane. Yeah, right. I just literally is
I started picking up things on his desk and once we see what a tiny little beautiful pen
Of infinite jest. Yeah, the very one that vincent was holding. That's right. Vapors two. Do you want to tell me what's going on with this
Pen? That's the pen for the Vapors two Kickstarter
What there's going to be a kickstarter for Vapors two. I love that show
I've I've been saying I've been every now and then I'll say like, oh, yeah, it's gonna happen soon
It's gonna happen soon. I'm really trying to actually make it happen. Like actually soon like, um, I wrote
I need the thing that I need to do is I need to write the vaporettes because I I need some fucking guest content
And uh, I was writing I wrote half a script. Uh, yesterday
Yeah, I'm hopefully after this is done. I want to try and finish writing that script before I go to bed
Uh, mm-hmm
Two things. Okay. First of all
Vaporettes, you'll see some more art from me. Yeah, probably less
Long, but if you liked my last one, then you're finally like this one too. And obviously Vapors. I mean
You did go above and beyond and draw a lot of pages
I mean, I would welcome as much as possible because like
The thing about Vapors two is that it's actually quite a bit shorter than than uh
This grandma's name is patreona and she's 101 years old. Well, they all have a they all have names. What the fuck?
Yeah, I did not know that this one's name is dan heinous peanut
Miss mischievous miss mischievous. Yeah. Yeah. Mima ivy. Okay. This is new. I didn't know about this
Looky, looky, looky
Frenzy. Oh my god. I can't talk about my business. I can't talk about the art that I created. Oh guys have to click
I have to make I have to click things too
Oh my fucking god
But yeah, um, you know, all just as you were saying only poor
Exploited, you know uber drivers and instacart workers all those poorer people with foreign accents and
Fuck them hate them. Have got to go the fuck back to wherever it is
They've all come over fresh on the boat from old country and they all start panning your door when the bin sing the vapor
I need bin sing vapor god. I just wish they would go back to old country already
I back in the old country. We do not have bin sing the vapor
We cannot get that when will you release new bin sing vapor? Well, you motherfuckers you fucking foreigners get ready
For this shit. It's gonna be so dude
I I think you posted it in either on twitter or in the pcb chat or somewhere
The the new cover
Yeah, I posted it. I made a tweet where I showed the two books side to side back next week. Do you have the prototype?
Yeah, you want to see it?
This frenzy's almost over. Okay. Oh my god, dude. Hell. Yeah, I want to see that
Yeah, I'm gonna I want to go out and like take some like funny pictures with it or something
Um, it's gonna be pretty good
I was thinking like a picture of it in a trash can the way that infinite jest winds up in a trash can spoilers
Wow
Let's watch this has red bin sing the vapor at least oh my god, it's beautiful. Yeah looks pretty oh my god
Well, actually the language pretty inconsistent actually it's the first one. So yeah, so it's pretty bad
Is it inconsistent? Well, it's just a different widths. Uh, simply well, I guess
Uh, no, frankly, I don't see what you're talking about
You have to but you'll have you'll have to buy the comic books and judge. Yeah judge for yourself
I I thought this was the back cover for there. I'm gonna be really honestly. I should have
It's a for the viewers at home. It's a flyer for the cablam. Which is just the printing service
Um, I probably should have done that because they will like take money off. Okay
Okay, so the thing about there's a lot of like filler pages in there that are just one page repeated over and over again
Just to sort of make it because it's gonna be full of like guest content. Um
Look at that
Yeah, you should definitely go from a thing with like just flipping through these. This is so funny. Who made this?
Uh, the artist's name is fennel ketanurix
That person made a vaporite, which they all are probably aware of. Yeah, it's the one with the sword. Yeah, and um, it's just
Be careful. Be careful. Be very ginger. Be very ginger. It's just that repeat from many a page
It's just like a third of the book is just that page over into that one page vaporite over and over again
Is this the same is this repeat from the this forward? Yeah. Yeah the forward is it's yeah
What's it like trying to print something?
um
Stressful it's stressful. Just like getting everything. Um
Because like to give you templates and it's it's stressful
Just like getting all your pages like sorted and like
Converted to the right file type and at the right resolution and like it's really stressful like before you send it in
It's like, oh, did I did I do it all right? Like did I
Did I have the pages all in order is like did I did I switch anything around to something upside down?
It's actually kind of a nightmare for a pro tub like this. How much is it running out?
Oh, just for the one. Yeah, I think it was like $11. Oh, that's that's not bad. No, no
um
And of course like it's cheaper the more you print. Yeah
specific specifically the kablam
Gives you a price break at like 500 dude. Well right here. It's just one one one. It's $11. Oh my god
I didn't even realize it's $11 and 11 cents. That's crazy. Yeah, does that include shipping? Yeah, cool. Okay
Yeah, well, there's there's the answer to your question. I guess that's insane
Pretty good. I can't do it. Oh my god
You've you've got such a you've got such an empire below your feet
Then you've got such a like a wealth of comics and stuff that you're able to like print out with these cool ass
Fucking four fans for for a hardcore vape heads vape heads to declubber up dude. This is fucking sick
You're gonna sign them again. Yeah
Oh, yeah, sure. I'll offer sign copies again. Uh, definitely probably at the same same. I'm just I'm
I'm gonna just do it like it's gonna be the exact same as the last one
But there's gonna be like additional options for if like you also want to get like the the original and you want to get like
You know the the the book or the pin from the first one like that'll be available
It's like a bundle thing if you want both
If you missed it the first time or whatever and it's actually kind of um
It's just kind of confusing trying to think of like price points and like how much should I
God okay
Picking picking how much deciding how much something should cost is horrible. You ever done it?
No, basically never. It sucks. It's like you there's there's no there's no right answer
You can't like look it up. You can't google like how much should I charge for this?
There's like there's nothing to go on except got feeling
Like you don't want to like overcharge because you don't want to fuck over your people
And also it won't even sell that much
Also, you want to undersell these, you know, it's your work and you don't want to fucking just you know
Yeah
Yeah, I mean the last Kickstarter was pretty successful. So I'm just gonna copy
I'm just gonna copy over the prices from that pretty much. I feel like don't fix what isn't broken sure
Now
If we could talk business for a second here, I'm interested because
I've always thought that the champion
Makes the most sense as like you're sort of like
Main
Thing that you that you say like yes, I've been saying I'm making this web comic called the champion. It's very
Good, but also kind of I don't know. She is
Easily accessible because sort of mainstream in a way very like a lot of why that's sort of why I started doing it because I was like
You know, I should think of a story that maybe has a little more obvious appeal
Where's my fucking jewel dog? What did you do? Did you pocket it?
Uh, I know you've always no, I know you've always coveted my jewel
Wait, hold on. Oh god, what's this fucking fucking cookie? Okay, it's just the lucky. That's fine. Uh, your phone's over there. Uh
You know the cotton the cotton I can't I can't I can't work like this look. I can't work under these jeweless conditions. Okay
I probably just like put it down behind here here sniff this been. Oh sniff a pen. Yeah sniff a pen
That's that'll get me there quick. Look at me there. You know, look at me split
Here here smoke this bro. Just just put this in your room. What happens all the time? I offered him a battery for those
Uh, this happens every fucking day
But I stand up and I look at the ground and I think where's my jewel
I didn't I haven't left the right here right here. Oh, dude. Oh dropped it when I was uh going for the copy
What was I talking about? I bet would you have the champion being more mainstream? Yeah. Yeah. I listen Ben
Yeah, okay. So I just please lay out to me. Yep. What do you do right now?
And this isn't like a oh, why aren't you making comments like like literally like I wanted this
It ties into more things like so you do your comics. You do your streams. What else?
What else would you consider like a thing that you do? Um
Lately I've been I've actually been spending a lot of time like fucking around with um
pins like rfc cape that for the like
I've been I I've
I sort of spent a long time
Kind of fucking around with a slime coin design to make it to try and like get it
You know
Because like you can't fit too many fine details into a pin design
So I've been like reducing the amount of detail to sort of make it more
Ben if there's one thing that you do that is your greatest folly
When you're making merch you get way fucking like
Too into it and like yeah, that's you like
Fucked around with like the shirts a lot with I spent like a week and a half
Yeah, just fucking around with like the shirts in the storefronts. Yeah, I did um
Kind of insane. Yeah, it was stupid. Well what I meant more broadly was just like what could you consider your ongoing products?
They have right now. I don't know would you consider like pin making one of your main projects? I wouldn't think so
Not a main project. That's not a thing that I'm planning to do for a long time. Sure. Well, okay, but your ongoing work
Oh, I'm scattered. I feel it's I'm scattered and this is like my big problem is that I um, I can't I don't focus on one thing and I'm kind of
Oh, okay
Well, well, I was back to doing beast capades for a hot minute there, but then brony con happens
I came back. I had sort of lost focus on it now what I mean
I'm gonna go back to beast capades what I'm
Okay, I'll tell you right at this very moment what I'm trying to focus on is getting the scripts done
For the vapor ads and then starting up the vapors to Kickstarter and then while that's running
I'm going to go back to doing beast capades. You misunderstand what I mean and
Maybe easy to do so
Specifically, like I don't like I don't mean like like like a to-do list of what you're like. Oh, I'm gonna do this
This in this order
I must have checked out this before on like an other rfck or maybe on a pcp or maybe just people in general
But I think what has helped me so much with like work ethic is like
Getting a clear sense of what I want to do like not just like what I'm going to do like oh tomorrow
I work on this tomorrow. I work on this it will be just like like a list of all my
Projects that genuinely care about and all the other bullshit can be just swept to the side because I'm focusing my efforts on like seriously like
two or three
Projects match. I can have like a little bit of like, you know, maybe a little bit extra
You know side projects here and there but like my mind is focused upon a very small set of things
And I want to because it does seem like you're very scattered
You kind of like there's a lot of things that you want to do in various different like way
You know to different levels of interest to you and your audience
But I want to know I don't want to know like what you're going to do tomorrow
I want to know like what do you in your mind? I was like screaming for some reason
What do you in your mind think of as like your projects?
What like to like if someone were to ask you what do you all do Ben? What like what do you do?
It'd be I mean from my feel like you could probably answer this question
I could probably answer this for you, but I think this is that complicated
It's not common, but it's a helpful exercise
I think too like maybe you might want to reduce things in order to become more focused on the stuff
Because it seems like you are indeed scared so from my perspective as someone who doesn't you know
Who follows your patreon?
It was a pretty you know active into it you do your comics in sort of a you know
Whatever suits your fancy at the moment
Bases, you know it kind of bounced back and forth from a lot of things you do your comics you do streams
And then I do do the stream and and then it gets kind of muddy where it's like you kind of make videos
I guess
I haven't thought yeah, I was gonna
Oh, I said I was gonna make another video at some point
I said I was gonna make a video that was gonna own the cuck servatives
and I still
And I would kind of still like to do that, but I sort of lost my nerve halfway through making it
And like wasn't sure what I wanted the tone to be and just put it aside and never picked it back up again
Uh, I don't know. I'm not thinking about videos these days
Okay, so I mean that that's where it sort of gets my words like there's a lot of like things that you could do
And there's a lot of like, you know like things you have done before but like what matters to you right now
You know like what like what are the things that you want to like push as thing you're doing?
Because you know
Is it just streams and comics is that where you want to put all I don't want to push my streams like I that's not a
That's not like that's not like something to like
base my brand on but think about them. They're the most consistent things that you make
And the most frequent
And maybe the thing that people consume the longest
uh
Yeah, and
I mean just because you know, like I'm just saying that they are like a big
Part I mean in a lot of people's minds everything. I mean, there are a lot of my mind when I think about what does Ben do?
Well, I know he streams a lot. I stream like once a week. Well, I mean very consistent. I mean, it's not bad
It's not like oh, it's just streamer like I mean that kind of seems bad
Like that's my goal is not to be a streamer. Well
I mean, I mean part-time occasional like it's
I mean, that's fine and all
No
That twitch is just a thing that I do on the side
It's in no way is it meant to be like my main thing or even a main thing
um
So so there so there
So there you have it. So it's all just you you just want to exclusively do comics
I
Wanted my main. Yeah, I wanted my main thing to be comics. Yeah
um
You say want it. Well, I feel like I haven't followed through on that but you know
That's why like when you ask me like what do I want to do the answer is well one
Vapors to Kickstarter then Biscuits
After that, um
Fuck I gotta buy this temple after that, um probably
Uh
I mean
We'd have to see champion
Yeah, I mean
Biscuits will probably take a little while to finish like a couple months
Um, so like I mean I could change my mind, but yeah, I guess tentatively the plan after finishing Biscuits would be go back to doing champion
Hmm. Okay. Okay. Would there ever be a scenario
under which like
You release champion
And it's not as though it's like
You are switching off between vapors and bcpades and champion
And then you release all all of three of those at like, you know in big chunks aside from basically is obviously which is you know
More flea throwing there would be a scenario where it's like I could like say hey my friend ben
He does the web account called the champion. He releases like every two weeks or something like a new page or something
Every two a page every two weeks
Uh, yes, would would you ever consider that as a thing you do? Yeah, yeah
I kind of want to like finish Biscuits
I don't have any like
I don't have any like, um
I think I've told you this before I don't have like a vapors for in my head. Yes, you have so
Yeah, I guess the idea is like
You know, I'll I'll keep like, you know kick starting like the physical prints of my old stuff
But that's like kind of it's its own thing in terms of like what I'm actively working on
Uh, I would finish Biscuits and then it would just be champion would basically be it unless like
Something were to strike me and I was like, okay
I want to take a break from this and like maybe go back for a minute and do another champion or another vapors thing
but like
Yeah, my my my end goal is
To work on the champion. My end goal is to make the champion the thing that I do. Yeah. Yeah
That's that that's that's good. I'm happy about that
I feel that's I've always wanted maybe maybe the audience wouldn't feel the same way
Where it's just a very clear idea of like what you're trying to push is like the thing that you do
You've been very you're but you've been a very renaissance man. I think that's even really a problem. It's just a very
I mean you were you started like the Winnie the Pooh series and that was like the height of like
Okay, like what is been saying
Like what's going on here? Yeah, um
Not even that they were bad. Like I just I just like I thought it would I thought it would get a big audience and it didn't
um
I don't
I mean I think I mean my goal. I mean I want to grow my audience. That's what I that's what I want
I mean, I think the way you do that in the way that would be best for you is just to yeah
Just have like a main flagship comic series and you probably you know, no, you're probably right. No, no, you're you're right
You're probably right about that. It's hard
Uh, I don't know. I mean I want to you know, you see you got to try new things, right?
Find out what works for you. I don't know
Biscopades was like very different in tone and like
I mean Maryweather tells me that like you gotta
Like people are reading comics online. You got to do them
You got to do comics in like webtoon format and like I think he's not wrong
um
I don't
I sort of feel hopeless when I think about webtoons like when I think about like building an audience on like
To pastic or or well, I mean to I think to pastic's dying but like um
Webtoon or something that's just sort of feels like so Sisyphean and like I'm so behind on it
Like it'll just never happen. I don't know. It's also like very like
New and different from what you're doing, right? So it's very like it's sort of a new paradigm and like you would have to
Maybe like not change like the core of what you're doing at all
But like, you know, there'd be a lot of stuff like structural changes you have to make like it'd be like it's literally like a different format
Literally like the images are displayed in a different way. Yeah
but like
I don't know
I mean
Honestly, it's probably just better in every way
like formatting a page is kind of
a hassle
like fitting panels
like webtoon you just fucking just
Draw it one after another top to bottom like don't even worry about it. And I mean
That's not I mean you can get creative with the layout of a webtoon. You like you absolutely can do that. Um
Uh, you know
It would kind of suck to not be able to make books
People like books
Do they like books so much that it's not that it's worth hamstringing your online audience? I mean
Maybe but probably not. Yeah
I don't know like I'm not I don't I don't I'm not a purist or I'm not a
I'm not married to any particular format. I think I've said this before
I'll fucking I don't know
It's sort of I mean the world
It's sort of weird to think like oh chapter one of the champion would be entirely in like this page form
And then like the rest would be in this like non-page like webtoon form, but like
Who gives a shit? Yeah. Yeah, I don't think that would attract like anyone. I don't think it would fucking be a big deal really
Mm-hmm
People would probably
If if everything worked out
Well, and then like it got really popular or something then like people would just say like oh, yeah
The first chapters in this really shitty format that like is really annoying to read
But then it gets but then he fixes it
Which like, okay, that's fine
I mean at least there would be at that point there would be people who like are into it in that new way
That's that's what matters, you know, yeah
Um, it's it's in such a funny predicament that I'm in because it like on a whole lot of these are
These on all of these rfck's it's always me asking you like what are you doing?
And then the obvious question is like what am I doing? It's funny because it's like
A secret what I'm doing to only the people listening to this way podcast. Is it a secret? Well
No, what I mean by that is like to describe in detail what I'm working on right now
Would be to give away the surprise of what's happening
Like in the game in oh
Oh, I understand. I understand what you're saying. Yeah
So it's like it's it's in a funny like fucked scenario where it's like
Like
All of today I would like really ride very passionately about a thing that will be released and like a new sort of
section of
The slime corp stuff that'll be released soon and like I want to talk about it
But it's also like well like I'm only hurting the people who it's for like on the pcb
It might even be different where it's like I would talk about like more general kind of broad details
But like it would only be like bad for like the people who this
Show is targeted to and like that these are the people that you want it to be a secret from
Exactly. Yeah, sure. And like I'm like
I mean everyone maybe probably scoff because you know, I have been so inactive lately because of the month
I've just had but like I mean you've been you've really had a lot of real life stuff going on
Yeah, like genuinely you've had like you just moved across the country and all that
Oh, well, they don't care about that. All they know is that they aren't getting I care about that. I understand
I understand
But yeah, it's it's just like funny
Because I'm like exclusively working on like in this war as like the thing that I do now
Which is cool and great and like I'm excited about it
But it's also like, you know, I had kind of weird to talk about I had the kind of in like awkward
I hate I hate this. I kind of hate talking about this. I kind of have to stop doing that because it
Wasn't making me money. Yeah, nobody was like and the people that were
The people that were giving me money on patreon like that wasn't what they were doing it for and like
My patreon has dipped a bit and it really
Man, I don't know how to say that I want to sound I want to say this as diplomatically as possible
It really stresses me out
I don't want to say this in a way that's like you you viewer
You person who maybe someone unpatriated me who's listening right now
And I don't want to say like fuck you
What's your problem? It's fine. I'm grateful that you ever supported me at all
But like oh man the fact that it's going down really fucking gives me the fear
Yeah, you know what I mean. Yeah
Yeah, it's
I mean we were talking about this like off air talking about like
Monetizing writer first coplers and we both agree that like it first and foremost is like an art project that we just like I mean
like
I think going back to the start we wouldn't like stop doing our
In this war knowing that it would make money. I mean obviously we would try and make it so that it does but like
We're really happy with the way that it's turned out. We don't want to like gouge out anyone
But also is a consideration that like, you know
With you and with me we're both going to have like me like with school and you just now
Are going to have things that are like far more demand our attention that like have more like
Not just like even the monetary rewards, but just like are maybe even just more fulfilling in a lot of ways
And it's like how can we justify doing endless war in some circumstances?
And I'll always like you can because like it makes so little money and like, you know, it's kind of like slimy
It's a little bit gross a little bit dirty to talk about but like, you know
We do it anyway because we care and we like it a lot. I don't think anyone could like question our like interest in it
I mean in the beginning. I mean you were just going fucking crazy
I mean you would dedicate your entire life to doing this for uh pretty pretty much
Yeah, and me with all the recent story arcs and all the updates and stuff. I mean
It's it's we love endless. All right, but it just is like wrong for us to do so
like
We've got a no sort of pragmatic sense. Yeah, like like we've gotten no benefit from it. I mean
Yeah, I mean a lot of the time people seem to just like hate it like at least I don't know how
Well, okay, I mean
Your your volume like gradually creeps up so occasionally I'm gonna be like hey you crept up creep it down
We gotta wind down by like I have to leave soon
Oh, do you have a time limit? Yeah, I do it feels like we just started it's in two minutes
Really? Yeah
Don't worry guys, this is gonna happen way more often. Let's just like just do this like again
Like why not just like the part this is part one of a thing
Why no part two will come back. Okay. Well next time we'll have the dramatic conclusion. Will
Will I be able to afford a wizard tower?
Find out next time. I just want to say that like
Oh god, what was I fucking talking about? I was thinking about oh
For me like I come in and the game just feels like everyone is like unhappy with like everything that's happened
Oh, I mean, yeah, it was always like yeah, honestly, I feel like it's less like that now
I mean there were there were like crises points were like
I mean you remember you remember the times when the game was just completely broken
And like especially in the in the beginning this this this really weighed on crack. I think like all the like that there was a lot of
Criticism there was a lot of like oh this this part of the game sucks like this part of the game is not good
Uh, and like I mean it was probably mostly true
Uh, I mean, you know, it's it's perpetually a work. I don't think that anyone was like wrong for doing so
You know, I kind of like
That it is sort of a little bit janky
Oh, that's not well. Yes, but that's not what I was gonna say. I really kind of like that it has become
Something that is sort of not like open source, but something that like a lot of people work on
Yeah, that it's like the creation of the game itself has sort of become like a community project in a way. Yeah
Yeah, I
That's just
I think that's great. That's like what
That kind of feels like how it should be
What is that? Oh, it's a cat's millionaire or something. Oh
weird
Yeah, fuck fuck you. I guess uh
What what are you gonna get it's cat's millionaire? Nothing. Okay. I don't care
uh
But yeah, it's it's it's funny because it's like
A
Hot stove top that I really love
Like I love like like I love
Endless war in all ways the setting like the game itself and the community around it
I love it and then like I I wake up in the morning and I go to I check the discord messages
It's all people saying that the game sucks and they hate me personally and I'm like, yeah, I love this
And then she's my big counter and she's plummeting just going just nowhere because I'm spending all my time working on this war
I'm like, yeah, I love this and it's just like it's so funny of a particular event to be in because like I'm not gonna stop
I mean even in college like I think the one thing that it will continue to do is be in endless war because I just love it so much
But it's like so like, you know
It's not like
It's not good for me pragmatically as you said. This is um, this is I've been
Yeah, I mean, um
He's been been stressing lately about
feeling like I'm
Going nowhere in life. Dude. Okay an endless endless as much as I love endless sports
I don't want to say it's going nowhere. It's not going it's going places. But like is it where is it taking me? Yeah
You know, I mean, I mean, that's the whole reason. I mean
been like
Metaphorically and like literally in a long ways can't afford to be the non absentee father he used to be, you know
It's not a matter of like he doesn't care dude. Okay, bin. I'm just gonna fucking suck your dick for a second here
Please
Wait, where's the next one?
Where's
Oh, this whatever keep going cookie chains dog shit. Okay, uh, it
Oh
People will always like fucking like oh ben's never here. Ha ha ha. It's like fucking bad for the game. Whatever. Yeah, okay
Ha ha very easy for you to say this motherfucker
It's not a matter of interest level because he'll spend so much time just fiddly around with the most useless shit
About pens and he like styles his own
Personal stream to be that of endless wars aesthetic. He awfully cares about it
When it's when it's endless war related like when i'm doing when i'm drawing slime wards or or drawing like doing the cop killer
Top killers image. Yeah, I fucking make it and and he gets into it and you obviously fucking care
I spend so long. I spend like
A long time just fucking around with color filters. I don't know. There's something really compelling about it to me
This I should have just been a graphic designer because like fucking around like fucking around with images and like fucking around with color filters and stuff
is like
Really fun and gratifying
It's so like
Obviously the passion is there from both of us
And it's like you specifically like you love endless war so much and I sure do
Have you seen my walls? Yeah. Yeah, dude. Okay, right now. I'm looking at a flag of new los angeles city like the city fight
And I turn around and I see the giant cop killer flag and I look over the side see the
I gave it to you at rfckcon one like this in this war like city image that I made
And it's just like all around here is endless more stuff
It's just a matter of like
It doesn't benefit you in like a living way. You know
Like you need to live you've always been like a person living on like the fucking edge in a way margins of society. Yeah, like it's so like
We love it so much and yet it hurts so so it's it's it's
It's our prodigal son. But anyway, you gotta go. I gotta go. You gotta down the rest of that marshmallow rocks our ex-durance
Oh, you done I
All right, dude, well, I guess I'm gonna end the stream then okay
I'm ending the stream
I'm ending this dude. Look at look how slimy this is this is pretty slimy
This is this will either be like one big video or like several small ones. We'll see whatever see you soon. Fuck off