Good-bye-o-gizai-mas.
Rowdy.
Fucker.
Cot.
Killer.
In. Minecraft.
Minecraft.
You know, I understand that this game is banned in schools across the country because of its seditious remarks against certain ethnicities and its pivotal role in leading to World War II, but I think that Minecraft,
may have some relevance to our current economic and political situation, so we're reviving it for this let's play, if you get what I'm trying to say.
I don't, I don't, oh wait, reviving it.
Oh, right.
What the fuck is happening right now? I've not played Minecraft in like years, so I have no idea what I'm in for. This is a nightmare though.
I was building the world.
I guess so, I guess so.
This should have fucking figured it out. Hey, great. You started the video game.
It's amazing, isn't it?
That's spectacular.
Ben.
Hey, what happened to the fucking, what happened to RFCK Texture Paki, dummy?
We were just talking about it. I don't have it installed.
I want to call attention to the fact that you should have it.
I don't know where it is. I haven't, my long story to history with Minecraft is I played it when I was a kid, and my, eventually they had to update all of their stuff.
They had to update all of their servers, right? So they had to consolidate power because they were about my Microsoft.
So my old, ooh, ravine, my old Minecraft Gmail was unfortunately got corrupted and I was no able to log in.
So just for like a couple years there, I wasn't able to play Minecraft, even though I had rightfully bought it to their acquisition by Minecraft, or by Microsoft and their evil, evil, corrupt policy.
So I'm playing again, or making the Minecraft come back.
Ben.
Naturally.
Yeah.
Two years of Rowdy fuckers cop killers. I guess not. I mean, we've been going for that for like four years or something, I think.
But now, two years of Endless War.
Two years of Endless War.
When was the first, ooh, I wonder when the first Rowdy fucker, not Endless War, but Rowdy fuckers was.
I remember off the top of my head, it was like very, very close to two years before the start of Endless War.
Like within the span of a week, I believe.
Hmm.
Let's find out.
Yeah, let's do it.
Let's uh...
Okay, I see.
Okay, the first one, Nuclear Throne was April 11th, 2016.
So, almost four years ago.
Time flies, doesn't it?
Where does it all go?
At that point, that was like, I'm trying to think about the timeline here, because that was before Radcon 2, right?
That was before I think, I think that was just after Bronycon, right? Because it was definitely, I think it was before the first Radcon, actually.
Was I?
Oh, was that before I moved in with Digi?
I think it might have been, yeah, because the first Radcon's when you moved in with Digi, and I'm pretty sure the first RSC is before the first Radcon.
Yeah, um, I don't remember, like, in my mind, our FCK started, but I don't remember doing it before Radcon 1, but I think, but I guess we did, I don't know, okay.
I mean, it was a very, like, me and you and Davoo all just played Nuclear Throne, and we decided to do a podcast together, because we had all played Nuclear Throne.
Like, no, like, we were not deciding to make a whole new series or a whole new show, it was just like, you want to talk about Nuclear Throne and play it, and it turned into a clusterfuck.
Oh, got it. Dude, look at all these people.
Me and Tom just did something like that today, guess what we fucking recorded today?
The Bustercast, I saw.
The Bustercast.
It's very sad.
It's going up, it's going live in a matter of seconds.
For a while there, I thought that racial tensions were starting to ease and that we were starting to enter into a new realm of, you know, social awareness of the issues facing minorities, but I guess that-
That's because you're stupid is why you thought that.
I guess Ben St. came back and made racism legal again, that's unfortunate.
Hell yeah, dude.
Oh my god, Munn, epic.
Someone just died here, and I have no idea how or why. It's epic.
We just got back from a Radcon.
I think that you guys probably recorded an episode about it, but I was not there.
But I want to talk about Radcon 4, because it felt strange.
It was a very surreal experience doing a Radcon again after not doing it for so long.
And then the weird fact that it just flew by and it felt like it didn't even happen.
It felt so insubstantial.
Yeah, it felt like-
It was like a puff of air.
Even though it was so fucking long.
And it was agonizing. It was like cruel. It was cruel and unusual.
I mean it was fine, it was good, it was fun, but it was over in like a second.
There were a lot of like, you know, big recordings where we had to break out the Victor camera
and we had to, you know, film scenes over and over and over again.
Oh my god, what's happening? Where am I?
Oh, is this poison ivy?
Sweet berries. What the fuck?
I have no idea.
Yeah, it kills me. I don't understand why.
I didn't realize that Tom Oliver's channel is like 128 subscribers.
It's like, he has a personal channel that's like, never uses.
I guess his over on like Rebel, is it Rebel Pixel or Polystation 2?
That would be it, right?
Okay.
Why are you getting the stats?
I just want to fucking put it on the fucking, I just want to get it on the fucking, in the description, in the end card.
There, that's it, that's it, that's it.
Epic.
Yeah, okay.
But yeah, it was weirdly like, it wasn't even really hyped up because I forget what the initial impetus for it was,
but like Radcaud Ford just kind of like, it felt like the planning for it just kind of like happened in one meeting.
I feel like we were talking about the future of the show in one meeting and they were like, well, you know what we got to do is we got to do a Radcon.
And everyone was like, oh yeah, I guess so, huh?
And then we just started looking for houses and then the bull just started rolling like out of the blue really.
And then we planned it for like two months in advance and then it snuck up on us and then I was like, oh shit, I didn't prepare at all.
And so I spent all of Radcon preparing for my lecture.
And then we did those recordings.
It felt like it was just like, oh, a couple days and then it was over.
It felt weird because like a lot of the other Radcons, right?
It felt like they were like super long in a weird way where there was a lot of time just to like hang out and just like talk.
I mean, well, like I think a part of it may be that like a lot of the stuff involved all of us, right?
So there was not a lot of time for like some guys to be recording while other people were doing nothing.
There was a lot of like, we all have to be here or like none of us have to be here because they're saying it for another thing where we all have to be there, right?
I mean, a lot of us, more of us did lectures and the lectures went really long.
Like all, like more than most of the lectures were like four hours long or more.
Is that, is that, it felt like that? I don't know if that's true though, I think.
No, it is true, yours was fucking long, Nate's was fucking long, Tom's was fucking long.
Nate's felt like longer than it was. I was surprised that it was only like four hours.
I mean, I had to go and like lie down. It was too long for me, I couldn't handle it.
Nate's was the longest, but yours was not much, yours and Tom's were not much shorter.
Tom's is epic though, Tom's was so cool.
Tom's was epic, Tom's was too good.
Yeah, it's unfortunate.
I just want everyone, well, I mean, mine's my favorite, but Tom's, Tom's the second, Tom's the second place.
Right.
Okay, you know, I think Radcon 3 was like very unstructured.
We spend a lot of time at Radcon 3 like thinking of like, what should we do now?
Radcon 4, there was like never a moment where we were like, what should we do?
It was always like, here's what we're doing.
It's either here's what we have to do or here's like what we have been like planning to do,
AKA just like the lectures.
Yeah, yeah.
Do you think that that was, I mean, I guess, you know, there's no reason to fret really.
I don't think it's good or bad, but I do think it's why the time flew by so much.
Hmm.
And I had to leave like a day earlier.
Did anything happen on that final day?
Um, I don't, well, I mean, you missed, um, you missed Hippo's lecture, right?
Right, I did.
Other than, I mean, that, yeah, that and probably we did a stream.
So not really.
Okay.
It sucks though, because I didn't actually have to go.
The reason I went back home early is because I was going to go back to school,
but fucking, you know, coronavirus happened and no one was allowed back at school.
So I didn't even have to come back.
Sad, sadly.
Are you getting, um, so you're doing online classes now, right?
Yes, I'm doing online classes.
Please tell me.
Please tell me you don't have to pay full tuition to do online classes.
There is a refund for housing, but the tuition itself is not being refunded.
Well, that's bullshit.
Yeah, it's complete bullshit and like everyone is mad and there's, I mean, it's, I wouldn't say it's up in the air,
but like the pressure from what I can understand is immense to the point where things may change due to the backlash,
but I'm, I'm unsure.
It's almost like college is a big grift.
It is almost like that, isn't it?
You almost suspect.
But yeah, it's a nightmare.
Your life is, is your life changing at all?
No, I mean, functionally, no.
Well, the only thing that's different is that my roommates are around more and I'm playing board games with them sometimes.
That's pretty much it.
That's pretty cool.
That's a pretty positive social change.
I guess it's fine.
You would think so, but actually I feel bad.
I just, I don't know.
Something about, something about the enforced quarantine, even though I didn't leave my house much before,
not being able to like makes me upset.
Oh, totally.
Well, I mean, you know.
I feel mad all the time.
Yeah.
At the government or at the situation before the world.
I just feel, no, it's not, I don't feel mad.
I just feel, I despair.
It's like, I don't know, up until now, I've been like a homebody.
I don't go out very much.
And it's been like, okay, okay, but I could if I ever wanted to.
And now I can't.
And it's like a puncture.
It's like an exclamation point at the end of a sentence.
Or at the beginning of a text to man to be worn out.
It's like, yeah, yeah.
If you get what I'm trying to say, yeah.
And it's like, it's like, well now, you know, hey, you've been doing this anyway, right?
It's like, well here, now you got to do it.
And I'm like, oh, this makes me feel bad.
I would, I get what you're saying.
It's almost.
Now that the privilege has been taken away from me, I suddenly want it back.
It's, it was weirdly, it's, it's strange.
It feels like coronavirus really snuck up on me.
Like with Radcon 4 where it was like, I knew about it, obviously.
Everyone knew about it for a long time.
But then like during Radcon, it went from far away issue to like, you know, oh, now we have to stay inside forever.
Like, you know, we don't get to go outside.
It just is like a new thing.
And it's weird because it's like, I would wager like maybe me the most, maybe not the most.
That's somewhat bold, but like I am one of the more shut in PCP members.
I, I, before college specifically, like I did not leave the house because I was in like a suburb of California,
which is like AKA a prison in all but name.
And there was no way for me to go anywhere.
So I just stayed in the house the entire time, like all of my days.
And so it would, you would think that it was like, I don't know, I'm just going back to the way things were.
I'm just going back to like pre-college munchie.
But now it's like, I've become so accustomed to going outside every single day where it feels like,
I can't believe anyone lives like this.
I can't believe that this is how I used to be.
It's insane.
Yeah.
Um.
Mm.
Yeah.
It makes you like, it's upsetting and it makes me mad.
That's all I have to say.
I feel bad constantly.
That's it.
It's not a good scenario.
No.
It makes you like, for me at least, it makes me cherish all the excuses I can give myself where it's like,
oh, well, I have to go outside because I have to eat food, right?
Like this, you know, that's valid.
But it's like, you know, it's weird that I have to like play this game with myself where it's like,
I cherish all the opportunities where normally they would be chores where it's like,
you know, before going to the grocery store, it's like, oh God, just fucking kill me.
I don't want to leave the house.
But now it's like, I'm leaping at every opportunity.
Oh, we're alone on bananas?
Dude, don't fucking worry.
Dude, I got bananas.
We got bananas at the grocery store.
I'll be right fucking back.
Don't worry, dude.
I got you.
I went to Whole Foods yesterday and I like fucking geared myself up like a wasteland warrior.
Like I was wearing like my mask and my bandana and like, you know, wearing gloves and shit.
I look like I was looking very post-apocalyptic.
I'm looking like an Antifa super soldier.
People are saying like, you know, oh, you live in interesting times like apocalypse.
Oh, well, you know, how, how interesting you should mind this for creative pieces.
But like, it's most boring apocalypse humanly imagined.
It's the most boring interesting times I can easily imagine.
It's not like, you know, people are out there in the streets.
There's like a revolution happening or anything.
It's not like there's anything really happening.
It's the lack of anything.
It's just boring.
It's the most boring interesting times that I can imagine.
This is probably how history feels most of the time.
I guess.
It's like bad.
You know, I guess that's a very privileged thing to say.
You know, nobody likes.
Huh? What?
I was just going to say it's a very privileged thing to say like what I was saying that it's like, you know,
I could be like, oh, it's very boring, but you know, people are fucking dying.
But from my perspective, I assume most of the people watching this show, it's probably going to feel the same.
Um, I think, um, probably like wars probably feel mostly like super boring too.
You know, like it's not like when there's a war on, it's like constant action.
It's like, you know, probably a long time of like nothing happening and you're afraid.
And then maybe if you're unlucky, something happens really fast and then you're dead.
Yeah.
If you're lucky.
I said unlucky.
Okay.
Um.
Hmm.
How long do you think this is going to last?
This podcast?
Oh, I can't be over fast enough.
I know.
The coronavirus.
Um.
Couple months.
Yeah.
I really wanted to do another rfckcon and I was planning to do it like this summer around
like when I got out of school, maybe even around this time because you know, anniversary
and stuff.
But you know, this obviously.
Hmm.
How does it travel?
Ski?
We kawai you to coin an oriental phrase from my long times in the Ottoman Empire.
Um.
Those are like the coolest things about endless war is the meetups.
The Ottoman Empire?
No, not that one.
Are you fucking free?
Yeah, not.
Well, that, you know, that's a big part of it too, honestly.
Um.
The meat.
I mean, the meetups feel very different from like what the game actually is.
You know what I mean?
Well, yeah.
Okay.
Yeah.
We're not shooting each other.
Well, we are.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Whatever.
Maybe this is dumb, but like they feel very, they feel disconnected from the game itself.
They kind of feel just like a separate thing.
I have no idea like what that's supposed to mean.
Like of course they're separate things like.
Yeah, of course they're separate things, but I mean they.
I don't know.
I mean they're.
Yeah.
Shut up.
Epic.
Um.
I'm stupid.
Don't worry about it.
It was really cool.
The last one where we were just inside this old grandma's house and we were able to just
like chip, like, you know, kick back and hang in this weird sort of like goofy, silly old
Boston house and just screaming about slime and rave and do the lecture, which was epic
and has a bunch of new people playing the game again for this game system for the first
time in like a billion years is really breathed some life into the game.
It's pretty epic.
Pretty, pretty down for it.
Pretty into it.
Oh God.
Jesus Christ.
Um.
It's some lava.
Look at this.
How many, how many people like joined?
Diamonds.
Did a lot of people join after like the lecture?
Did that do anything?
A lot of people joined after the lecture.
That's what I was just saying is that there's like a ton of new people, a ton of new faces
and they're all pretty epic.
If you ask me.
Well, you say it.
Well, how many, how many is a lot?
Do we have numbers?
Well, it depends on how like what you want to know by how many people because like technically
I think like now it's keeping track.
I think there was like something like over a hundred new people joined the game.
But as in they entered the server, but there's a decent, I would say, I would say like upwards
of like 40 new like faces who have talked and interacted.
I actually did.
That's a lot.
It is quite a few.
I know.
Exactly.
Um, I hosted a tour of the city.
I went on speed Levich and I did a tour of Lakhakan where I just like add every new guy.
Meet me in downtown.
We're going to go to every district and tell you what happened in each district and what
the deal is with it.
And it was really cool to see so many people like, you know, the game has been up for two
years.
You think this is as big as it's ever going to get.
This is all the people who are ever going to play this game.
This is it.
Uh, and then you have all these people being surprised when I tell them about like how
the food core works.
And dude like, dude, talk about in case you're in this game, like what?
I know.
Yeah.
Okay.
I see.
Maybe there's some life to this thing yet.
Maybe.
Maybe we've did.
Maybe it wasn't all for nothing.
Um, I always think about.
Yeah.
I am at.
Okay.
Sorry.
But as I just released the Buster cast and right now I am trying, I planned it out very
specifically.
I have like two very specific places where I want to put ad breaks.
So I got, I got to scrub through and find like, exactly, exactly the place for perfect
for maximum artistic, artistic merit.
Okay.
Any, what were you saying?
Uh, I was going to say something about RFCK new players.
Oh, oh, I was going to say, I always think about how like I have this sort of weird.
I would say it's probably influenced by the fact that I, you know, we're a part of this
greater sort of analysis film critique YouTuber regurgitation sphere.
But I always think about zooming out and viewing our shows in the context of like, I wonder
what people are going to say when this shit eventually ends because everything has to
end.
And I'm wondering about, I always think about, it's probably not helpful, but I think about
like where we are on the timeline of like, I wonder how long this is going to last.
I wonder how long RFCK is going to be a thing, not just like me and you, but I wonder how
long like the server will exist as like endless war people are playing.
I mean, I guess it's the sort of thing where theoretically could go forever, right?
There's no natural end point.
So, I mean, I imagine it will end when like, Discord is no longer widely used.
I don't see why it would end before that.
Skype 2 comes out and everyone flocks back.
Yeah, basically.
I mean, that or like, like if Discord stops being, and I mean, even then we might, we
might just like port it somehow.
I don't know.
There would probably be like a big initiative.
I mean, unless like interest is completely like fall into zero, we would, I imagine there
would be an effort to, you know, yeah, port it to the new, to a new platform or whatever,
which I'm sure could be done with enough dedication and elbow grease.
I just wonder if it'll, I don't know.
I feel very, I think it's part of the fact that we're inside all the time again.
I feel very reflective nowadays.
I do too.
I feel, I think about death all the time now.
Yeah.
You think it's tied to Rona, Bra?
No.
Okay.
It's not like I'm afraid to die.
I mean, there is that I am afraid to die of the Rona, but it's not like that's what I'm
thinking about.
I just think about death in general.
Recently?
Yeah.
How come?
What do you think?
Well, I mean, it's not like I never did before.
Yeah.
That seemed to be lurking under the surface of a lot of insane discussion.
It's just the sort of like, huh, I'm also scared of dying guys, lol.
You think so?
Yeah.
I feel like I've gotten that vibe from you before.
I'm super scared of dying.
I guess what could be worse?
Yeah.
I mean, true, but everyone is though, right?
It's not like that's unique to me.
It's not, it's not unique to you.
I don't know.
I have no frame of reference for exactly how much you think about it.
A whole bunch.
Yeah?
What do you, Ben, you die right now.
What do people say?
What do they say?
Yeah, what do they say?
Are they happy?
Are they sad?
I mean, I imagine they'd probably be more or less sad.
They would probably say, you know, at least you don't have to hear that guy talking about
communes on the PCP.
America will never be a socialist country.
Fuck that guy.
I don't know, they'll probably say that I was a guy who had, I don't know, I imagine
people would, I imagine people would miss me a little bit.
People would say that I could have realized more potential if I hadn't died early, you
know, normal shit.
So, you know, I guess, I guess that's all fine.
I would hope that like, I would hope that people would say like, boy, I sure was glad,
you know, Ben might be gone, but I sure am glad that he was around.
You know, I made a difference.
I'm better for having him had been here.
That's would be pretty good.
I think it's probably the most you can ask for out of anything.
It's just people being happy that you existed at some point.
Yeah, yeah.
Where's the cave entrance?
Where is it?
Here it is, epic.
I was going to say, oh, okay, this is kind of a left turn, but I was going back to like,
RFCK new people, and this is sort of one of the things I wanted to talk about.
So there's a weird sort of, I'm going to describe it.
I guess culture of, dude, the PCP sucks.
I hate the PCP, not as in like all of us individually, but like the show.
The show.
Yeah, yeah, especially in the RFCK audience.
And I feel like I've sort of like played into it in a way that maybe I shouldn't have.
Oh, definitely we have.
Yeah, we definitely have.
We talk all the times about how much we hate Nate heads and Digi heads.
Well, that's part of it.
I think, I mean, like a lot of people are like, well, no, yeah, that is part of it.
Yes, agree.
Period.
And it made me think about, if you remember, then all those times were recorded like old
RFCKs, like back like Atlanta bin RFCKs way back in the day.
And they would all be like prefaced and then like ended after we stopped recording with
like a big long like time of shit talking.
And in my life, since then, I do remember that I've continually like, you know, grappled
with the fact that I like, I am really unhappy with the fact.
And I find it like a very literally what is happening right now?
How do I get this to stop being what's happening right now?
I don't want this to be on screen right now.
I don't know what you're referring to the side box of all of these things.
Can you not see it?
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
The like recipe.
This is a nightmare.
I hate it.
But I grappled with the fact that I just I like gossip too much and it's a nightmare.
And I was wondering because it feels very like I feel like the PCP something about it as
like an institution attracts shit talking for like no real reason because I know there's
a lot of people who like it's like a joke, you know, it's a big joke in the RFCK community
how the PCP sucks.
But I get the sense from some people in there and in the PCP comments that like there's
something about the PCP that legitimately has attracted a lot of like scorn.
And I would almost say something to the effect of like betrayal in a strange sort of way.
There's a lot of like ire in some people's voices when they talk about something where
I can feel that too where there's sometimes where I feel like fucking PCP.
I feel so fucking betrayed for no reason and there's no real source of like why I should
feel that way.
But there's something about it that makes me feel so angry sometimes.
Do you ever feel that way where it's like there's no real reason to feel that way about
the PCP.
But do you ever feel like it's like do I ever feel scornful?
Yeah.
At like the PCP.
Constantly.
But like there's no reason.
Right.
I mean do you think.
I am.
I am like I'm going to make an embarrassing admission on here.
Right.
That's what RFCK is for.
So don't worry.
Sure.
I mean it's not about the PCP.
I mean about the PCP like I've been I've had reasons to be annoyed at it before but
like these days I'm like I'm like really preoccupied and I think all the time about how mad I am.
That Nate is like a shithead.
Yeah.
Like politically.
Like yes.
It's like it's like very much on my mind and like upsets me.
Like on a regular basis.
Do you ever.
I feel like we might have talked about this before but what like I think like the biggest
flaw of my like character as a human being is in the shower I will fake argue with people
that I know.
I will like I will I will have been thinking about something and then I will thank you.
Do you do like do you do like do you have you have the perfect comeback.
Yeah.
Well I have it's a combination of like oh my like it's either I was talking to someone
and they said something that I fucking thought was so stupid but I didn't have the words
for it at the time or like I'll have been thinking of something else and then I would
think this person would probably have this to say about this and it would be so fucking
stupid for them to think that because that's such a stupid thing to say and it's so
in character for them to say it.
I know.
Yeah.
I did it.
I know what you're talking about.
It's so like it's weird.
Okay.
My like friend circle.
You imagine you imagine like a sort of straw man who is making like this like a very like
obviously like an easily like counterable argue like argument.
Yeah.
Then you imagine like what you would say to that person to destroy to utterly just destroy
their ass with facts and logic.
Yeah.
Exactly.
And there's something about it that feels so like good.
I mean I guess it's obvious you know you feel good for being a smart person and this
is way for you role play being smart without actually having to be smart in the moment.
Hell yeah.
It's pretty epic.
There's something about it where it's like my piece of my like friend group right is the
PCP basically.
It expands a little bit beyond the PCP borders but it's basically the PCP and then fans of
PCP and so it feels like that sort of totem billion in your head of oh I fucking hate
this guy and oh I'm gonna talk about how shit the PCP is.
It feels like weird jockeying for power in like a weird sort of political way where it's
like it's fun to talk about the PCP being shit because in a way it shows that well I'm
the PCP but I'm talking about how shit it is so therefore I'm not the bad ones it's
other people.
Hey listen you should like me still no matter what right?
That's where I think it's probably like coming from the deep recesses of my psyche where it's
like I wanna like shift off blame for something that doesn't really matter like a podcast
going downhill in a nebulous way that doesn't really matter.
I don't really understand the line of thinking that like the podcast has gone downhill.
The podcast is as it ever was.
Yeah.
Some people are weirdly attached to the idea of topics and like I think that's dumb.
This is what every time this comes up this and this comes up like constantly and I constantly
have to repeat myself that the PCP is what it is and it will never be anything more and
like it is not the thing it is not it is for people who already know us and like know our
channel and know who we are and want to hear us talk but like nobody nobody's going to
like find us listen to the PCP and be like oh you know it's not discoverable it's for
people that already know us.
Right.
It's not like the cornerstone.
That like I have to these I don't feel this way about any other thing and maybe just because
I am a part of the PCP maybe it's because I like am you know closer to it than I am
any oh god I thought the problem is what it called me then I am any other like art piece
or like podcast or show anything like that.
There's something about it that it just feels very cathartic to want to try and like distance
myself from any responsibility of its you know quote unquote quality where it's like
you're right the PCP is always been just a thing for us to talk like there's never been
any greater ambition than us just talking.
You know like I think my version of that is like I would I would not like for people
I would not like for people to know me as the guy on the PCP I have like my own stuff that
would rather be known for so it's so it's it's I think that might be one reason why I'm
sometimes inclined to be like oh PCP's PCP sucks PCP's dumb I'm the only good one I'm
I'm different yeah if I were in charge things would be different around here.
Meanwhile it's like a collective collectivized group where any of us have the power to make
the change if we truly are dedicated to it and but like I get that where it's like you
know if I were to care the PCP then yaya yaya but like we're all kind of are the the PCP
if we really want something to happen then it would have happened yeah like I mean at the end
of the day like I probably am like like probably like behind maybe Nate I am probably like one
of the most powerful like driving forces of the of the PCP as an entity I'm like one of
the most involved which is kind of embarrassing yeah why is it embarrassing because like I
said like I mean I don't want to be nobody wants to be just the guy from that podcast you want to
be your own guy with your own identity which I mean I think I am but I'm but like there are
definitely people there are definitely some people I don't think they're a majority or
anything but there must be some people out there who only know me as one of the guys on the PCP
and probably the same with you same with like Tom hippo yeah probably even like Nate probably
probably like most people probably found us through found us through Digi so and then most
some people you know but you know what I mean like if any if there's anyone who doesn't know
your other stuff but does know the PCP to that person you are just some guy on a podcast and
that is the end that is the beginning and end of your existence do you think we take I agree with
the there but do you think that that's partly our fault for not having I mean I think it's
inevitable yeah like inevitably there will be people who are not familiar with Europe with you
outside of the show and it's okay it's not a big deal but you know the less the less it's the
case the better hence me oh fuck the PCP it's dumb yeah that's I that's just the thing I do but
like I actually it sucks you know but actually it's it's not good at all and I don't like at all
yeah that's right I don't know how to prep segue into this but there's something that I think I
appreciate about Digi a lot and it's the sort of thing where like Digi can like enrage me a lot
with the things that he says there's I really do feel like if there is if the chips are ever down
in a certain way then I feel like did you would probably support me do you like I yeah in most
in most cases I think that's probably true it's something I appreciate where it's like again we
were just talking about how like you know it's so easy to like exist in this backbiting sort of
gossipy scenario with the PCP I think because it's so small and there's like so like there's
personality on the line and it feels so pathetic because there's so little to be gained from like
you know shit talking where it's like at most you maneuver politically in such a way where you
have now secured some more fans for you that are more loyal to you than they would have been
otherwise because you have voiced concerns like that doesn't matter fucking at all you know it's
you know yeah like I'll say I'll say some I'll be pretty critical of like Nate or Digi and those
two in particular Lamal but you know it like at the end like I'll still fucking like you know I'm
like I have a pretty limited audience compared to those two so I don't have that much to offer but
at the end of it like I still fucking like retweet them when they like announce projects and stuff
and you know I like I want their endeavors to succeed and all that shit there's something so good
about like I don't know this this is sort of weird and I don't know if they'll agree with this but
there's something I've been really thinking about a lot about like blind loyalty where you will go
down with the ship if you're the captain or I guess if you're one of the crew members in the
scenario where it's like like it's so easy for me to want to like leave in a weird way but I would
never want to do that because like I don't know there's something about it where I want to stick
around even if it's a nightmare or you know as the people may be saying or you know the podcast
going down to Hill or something but like I feel like it's bad for me to always feel them the need
to gossip and be like fuck the PCP is so bad now where it's like there's no reason there's no
reason and I meant I like the guys that was completely incomprehensible point the point is
that I like all of the people and I shouldn't gossip with them so much because I just want to be
their friend and I don't want to do this anymore I don't like being a podcast person where I have
to jog jockey to be a roman senator um I don't you know for a while I think I saw like being on
the PCP as sort of my like venue for like being in the public eye I don't really feel that way
anymore I kind of just show up to the shit I mean you know I kind of just show up to episodes now
just because it's the thing to do and also because there's money but like I like even if there
weren't money I would probably just keep coming just because like I don't know it's tradition it's
just but I don't think I'm I don't I don't really feel like I need the like exposure it offers or
anything I don't I mean there is no exposure ever like everyone already knows you like the PCP is
not growing like you know it's just is like the same audience well I mean it's grown up it's it's
grown a little bit now it's grown more since the like animorphs lecture came out then like it had
in like months before that's cool then yeah pretty pretty good right pretty good right I there's
there's a while I was talking with DeVu for a while at like I don't I don't even remember why but
just like after he left out of the blue I think I just like linked up something and we started
talking and we had a few conversations about like the PCP and about how like shit it was and it was
kind of cool but and you know DeVu is one of the members who decided to leave like publicly and
that's the sort of you know I was thinking maybe maybe I want to do that just because again it's
the sort of thing where it feels like there it maybe I don't know if you feel this way there's
something about it where when the podcast doesn't go exactly your way or when something in the group
or one of the members acts a certain way that you don't condone there's something about that feels
very like oh I guess the only word I can come up with is betrayal like it feels like something has
changed and you don't like it and you feel like oh I was it should have been like this I should have
been the one or you know I should have been the main driver here I should have been able to lead
this I should things were better can you give me an example I'm trying to think I'm trying to think
like I guess it's just hmm okay this is a very small example this isn't really I guess the most
iconic or the best example of it but something about like I know it wasn't on the topics episode
but there is I know there I know I knew it was happening and I knew that I did you listen to it
I did not listen to it okay I talk a bunch of shit about you oh did you oh yeah okay
well I complain about you and I express confusion at you like so like never wanting to be on
episodes anymore um I mean do you want to talk about it you want to I mean we can if you want
but like not to interrupt your point or anything um oh I was like I like I knew Nate wanted well
I knew Nate would say what I think that he'd expressed before where it's like topics bring
you know structure and stuff like that and at rad con he specifically says something in the effect of
like like we were going to do a topic episode I think we were discussing doing the buster cast and
he was like you know we're doing topics episode and it at some point he said it feels like we
can't do those anymore like it feels as though because we haven't done something like that so
long it feels as though that's the sort of thing that we can't do and that's I was gonna come in
and I had notes and stuff and I was gonna be like ah but if you remember I wouldn't when we were
talking about doing topics list I said that we could do those whenever we wanted to and I was
gonna be a big pillar big pillar of it and if only I was here I was I would be able to drive in a
way where it's like yes we would be able to do those very frequently and very suddenly and you
know we would have more buster cast and stuff like that if I were the one leading the helm but I
wasn't and I'm doing it I'm not you know there's no one to blame it blames even the right word
for something like that other than myself that's the sort of thing where it's like I feel as though
it like you know if I were to do things would be different even though the only person stopping
me from doing yaya yada is myself and even if I did there would probably be no real meaningful
difference you want to talk about why I'm not on the show anymore oh if you want everyone said
like you just I think I think Kazi said the other day it's like you just like don't feel like coming
on which like I mean fair enough original like okay there's a few things going on in this in the
thing where this this this may you know given the conversation it may feel more like a like I like
I dislike the PCP than I do and that's sort of why I don't want to ever like leave in the same way
that any of the others in pursuit just because I think there's no point to that at all there's no
point in saying I am leaving the podcast you know hard line this is a capital T thing I'm doing
I'm not going to be on the PCP anymore no I agree yeah I would only consider doing something like
that if there was like a big like problem that it was like a big problem and something that I felt
I needed to make like a serious like statement about yeah and be like it I would only do it in
like protests of something yeah I agree with that but yeah there's just no point I mean you know I
just have not decided to be on episodes for a while and a few things one is I don't really like I
guess I just don't really like it he's the main thing and I and I mean that in both I don't like
being on the show but more so I don't like being a host on the PCP like that being a character
trade of me like you were saying earlier like this is what people think of me as and that sort of ties
in the fact I don't really want to be a YouTube personality and I know I wasn't really trying that
hard to be one you know I was not trying to game the algorithm before but even the limited like
exposure I had to that world of having to always be on and to do that sort of showmanship for like
you know a living really because you know we got money from it and it was a big part of my income
for a while I really didn't like it I really thought it was like a gay and like shit and fake
and so I didn't want to do it because I didn't like the way you have to or why do you have to be fake
um well hmm I don't mean that when I'm on the PCP like I do I do kind of um I do kind of like ramp
up the energy a little bit more than I might in like a casual conversation so I guess in
a way it's like a little fake that way but like I don't know I don't mean I'm my genuine self and I
express my genuine opinions about things the reason I said that is because I said gay before and I
wanted to do the fake and gay YouTube comment joke I don't actually it being fake is not a big
part of stupid stupid okay I I don't like a part okay a part of it is that like the PCP isn't the
sort of show I want to do because I've really gotten into I think through being in college and
just like kind of like I don't know talking to more people outside of the realm like I've really
gotten into my head that I really don't want to have the things that I make solely be like don't
you like munchy munch is cool right dude munchy right come come consume this piece of art which
is simply munchy is here for a little while because I think it's destined to become boring and
stupid after a while and I am I'm so I mean this is gonna sound pretty pretentious I think this whole
podcast probably will and I think that I'm probably becoming more and more pretentious by the day
and it's gay but I feel like I'm really concerned with like quality almost my detriment and sort of
downfall in a way where I get like what's what's the term for when you don't want to go out on
stage at the school talent show stage fright yeah yeah yeah stage fright I get stage fright a lot
now in a weird way that I hadn't before like whenever I like sit down to record something after
like taking a long break from the PCP and after not really doing a whole lot of stuff like this
before and after consuming a lot of like other podcasts and shows and still more things that
like I really enjoy but that like are very very very different from what the PCP is I sort of have
like a weird sort of anxiousness when I record in a weird bizarre sort of twisted way and so
that's part of the reason why I don't like being on I get that I get that with streaming I don't
really get that with the PCP I guess it's because like if I'm on the PCP I can like there's no
there's not that much pressure because like if I wanted to I couldn't just go silent and like
everyone else will just talk when I'm streaming or something especially if I'm by myself it's just
like I have to carry this yeah I have to like and if anyone like finds me annoying or boring like
it's all on me well I think it's precisely because of what we were talking about the shit talking
where it's like when I go on the PCP after having you know talked in the lunch table about how shit
the PCP is in about haha fuck those guys right and then I go on well then I better be a fucking good
edition that show right like I better be the savior at that point otherwise I've just you know I've
revealed myself to only be saying those things so that I can get one up on my opponents which
aren't my opponents they're just my friends but I feel the weird need to distance myself for the
aforementioned pride yeah so it's like it's part of that it's also that like I don't know I've got
I've gotten really autistic that was the scariest moment in my entire fucking life that's that's
what's like recording the PCP is that moment right there oh my god by the way the game's so
choppy by the way I don't know if you can tell how choppy it is it's really funny it feels
kind of recording I assume that was just screen share that was like no no that's the game it's
ever um it's gonna say something oh like I have I have like weird autistic ideas about how I would
like want a show to happen but I know that PCP will never be like that and not like the PCP is
shit and like it's bad it's just one of those things where it's like if I were at the helm yeah
I gotta again I'm I am at the helm indeed and things could be different if I put in the work
but it's like I don't want to because the PCP is not something I even want to do in concept as a
personality driven show which is something I'm not want to move away from so that's why I'm not
on the show anymore is because I don't like doing it because it makes me feel weird recording it and
I think it like sucks and I'm not good on it and I don't want to do shit that's bad yeah I don't
want to do shit it's bad and I am bad is the reasoning so there's no it just I just I don't I
don't really relate I mean yeah and you're on so yeah I mean there's no it'll like I don't think
like it's bad like I think I think I think part of what people may think is that like when you're
on the PCP it feels like you're showing up for like a paycheck which like could be true I mean I
think is true to a certain extent which I don't think there's any problem I mean it is part of my
motivation yeah which I don't think it's like a huge big deal and it's like like I don't blame
anyone for being on the PCP nor I think it's like a problem or like any issue and like again like
there's no like I don't think the show has gone downhill at the point where it's like embarrassing
or anything or even yeah whatever anyone says the show is at the show is at worse as the same as
it's ever been yeah it will I feel the same way so it's like I feel no sense of fuck the PCP I'm
like I'm not protesting by not being on I think it's basically just what I want to do is not the
PCP like I don't want to do it for all the reasons I was just describing but I wish no ill will
towards anyone on it or you specifically or you know is there a reason I have ill will towards you
though yeah now I know specifically specifically I'm typing I'm tweeting I'm tweeting the buster
cast you can't say this is gonna be my big break this is gonna be the my moment it is gonna be
the bus the buster cast is gonna break me into the spotlight it's you're gonna we're gonna get more
views in the in-morphs lecture we're gonna beat away every all the competition can be easy I can't
wait for Canton to take us over how genuine how how much do you think that Nate's actual goal
and maybe the Nate and Digi's actual goal with Canton is to just supplant the PCP but be in charge
now and own it well like again it like the I guess they already own the PCP to an extent
well just well we all own it all yeah we all own it that's what I'm saying is that like you know
them being in charge I don't know if that would make any meaningful difference also Digi was
definitely like like I don't know if he was joking and since he doesn't mean that he wants
Canton to be the new thing that people do but he does like the word takeover was just Digi being
autistic and not being able to communicate clearly ever but that's just part of him like he
definitely meant no malice or like the like the word takeover implies like a hostile like against
people's wills it implies like you know an army marching over a city like he doesn't mean like
that he just means that he hopes that Canton will be the new thing of the PCP is which is to say
shit low-level content that people just do so that they can make money and then make cool
art on the side and they it'll just be like a like an engine for funding their actual art is what
I imagine that he is saying by that um I don't know I don't see the appeal of it I don't really see
I don't really see it succeeding well the appeal of it is just that it is easy content to do and
then people will eat it up and they will give you money and then you can spend more time doing
the vapors because you won't have to do all the other jockeying they have to do it's for political
and social clout like screaming and why would it make more money than the PCP because I guess
they're more dedicated to it I guess they have more of a drive to do it I don't know why I don't
know why they think it would me either maybe well maybe because it's it's um it's art it's content
that is about popular shows whereas the PCP is just about us so it's it's automatically limited to
a slow trickle up burn of new viewers maybe they think that because it's you know more algorithm
me I guess it will have more success maybe that's the idea I guess I guess why do you feel such
an apprehension to the idea of canton being the new thing that is done because because what I would
imagine is that basically nothing would really change I would imagine they would they would like
I mean there's no reason why the PCP as a podcast could still exist but I think I mean I think you
I think you said earlier where it's like the PCP as a podcast doesn't need to exist in the sense
that it's like that's epic like we love recording the PCP podcast specifically it's just like a
means to an end of keeping everyone you know relevant and doing a weekly show and stuff like
that but if something can supplant that like a canton if there's like a weekly canton you know
what's what's the harm like what's the what's the problem well it is just feel weird that like
now digi and Nate are like actually the the head for real this is just feel strange yeah well I
think that's yeah if we can argue about whether it was like a genuine sentiment but like if the
content were to like become like basically the new PCP it would just be the same but Nate and
digi would be in charge of it they would just they would just control it and I don't know that
sucks it's yucky I'm trying to think I guess I do feel like it's it's yucky in the sense that I
would feel like like a coup almost but I definitely I really feel like if did you were here he would
be like arguing against this like I don't know the phrase you know I don't know he is the one
that said take over the PCP but I think I really think that he just can't communicate at all and
that's his problem and that when you get to explain things then it they sound less retired than
they did you might you might be right and did you would backpedal on that yeah I think Nate
genuinely just wants to do that but he over he already has like the admin bonus like he he does
all the real work for the PCP he does all the hard part which is making the show like happen
each week like I like he I'm sure he doesn't even he doesn't own it what would that change like I
guess he gets a bigger cut I guess I mean he would just be in charge of deciding like where the
money goes okay I guess he would just be able to reallocate that in ways he thinks are more
productive to making a business I guess and that may then become the expensive making good
quality podcast in as you this is a zombie I don't know I didn't I didn't think it that far
through I decided that I was mad and then I stopped there I will know I just like why that's I
don't want him to own it I don't want anyone to own it we should I like that we all own it it's all
of our thing I don't know maybe I'm wrong maybe that's not what Canton is supposed to be but they
sure made it seem like that's what it's supposed to be is just like an all a PCP alternative that is
like in somebody other than it like they own instead of now which they don't okay well here I'm
gonna try and phrase it like I how I this is my best okay I'm gonna steel man did you I'm gonna
pretend to be digging steel man is argument I think that in his mind this is what's happening he is
going to make and really push Canton as a new money-making venture and it will get Maddash I
don't know how he's gonna do it but I think that this is his plan to make a maddash doing Canton
and so his idea is okay we will have this more successful I I would say almost more normie show
than the PCP because you know you can link it to anyone you can say hey you like so are online
here's a canton bet sort of online it's opposed to hey do you know like my little pony whether
these guys do the reviews yeah yeah yeah it'll be easier to link people it'll be bigger and more
normie so there'll be this bigger money-making show and then he thinks well why would anyone
want to do the PCP because no one really thinks it's the main thing that they do well they just
come over and do canton because it's way more successful and then everyone will be happy and
everyone will make a lot of money will be epic and it will be straight up so are you so you're
are you saying that the goal of canton is just to make like basically what like buster cast just
like highly specific pieces of like content discussing media well yeah that's what bust that's
what buster that's what I'm what's the name of the fucking show that was just canton that's
what canton already is on the channel I don't you think I fucking watch canton you think I know
what they do over there well if you were so concerned then why didn't you check oh I just know
I don't like it yeah they do like media reviews and stuff like that so so I guess I guess it's
just there it's just the same thing they do on their own channel but now there are two of them
and it's like a lower production so it's easier to create cool canton is it canton is a it's not
a good name it's not a good name for a channel it's not searchable I I don't like it because it
feels okay this is very pretentious again it feels like I don't like the idea of can't content I
don't like it just I wish I wish we all pretended what we did was art still even though we know
it's not I mean I I think that's supposed to be like the joke it's like hey you want like
mindless like you know disposable content here's some is lol but also like it just is yeah is
that yeah it's not like really a joke at all um but it's like self-aware about what it is at
least I guess I think that's the point of it that's fine I don't know if people want to make
people want to make you know that kind of stuff that's fine I mean I don't have anything against it I
just think the name is bad the name is not searchable and it's like an inside joke that like you
wouldn't get if you weren't already familiar with them um that did it I don't even know the
origin of the name did you just come up in some podcast on the side let's I think it's just how
did he says the word when he's being silly um but like you know I don't know it's not searchable
what I imagine is that they have to do how would you hear about canton and be like oh if I heard
that I would go and say oh C A N T E N T no okay give up they're gonna have to put all the variation
of spellings in the um the description and the tags so that no matter what they search they'll
get it now let's have to put in normal content too because some people will just hear the person
will just say that they think that they're saying content weirdly because it's funny which I guess
is the case yeah true um yeah name is not good but I don't know I think I mean as a weirdly sort
of outside perspective like I have no intention to do a canton especially to move to Virginia Beach
to do a canton for like a live-in that's not what I want to do never never never never never
never never never never never never but it seems like it seems like it just is the pcp2 and it
feels like what's the harm I guess other than the did you know what you say it feels like it's the
pcp2 what's the harm I say it's the if it's the pcp2 what's the point okay I'm just a skeleton
man oh I'm gonna die right now cool no dude I don't want to die dude I don't like that yeah I know
right it's real bummer it makes you makes you sad it does make me sad just makes me sad like you
know a hundred a hundred years hence it won't matter what happens it won't matter what I thought
about anything you know but at least I will have been mad at digi bro for a while yeah my standing
monument oh god yeah pretty much epic anyway the pcp2 like sucks dude like they don't even have
they don't even read for Urban Dictionary anymore that's true sad but true you hate to see it happen
you hate to not see Urban Dictionary either oh no I fucked up the tweet I fucked up the tweet how
the fuck could you convince yourself to make the pcb danielson how did that happen literally how
could that have happened I mean it's epic but like why like how could you have maintained sandy
while making it I mean I imagine that probably the guys making it just like like each other and like
had a good time working on it with each other I think that's probably what propelled it to be
finished mm-hmm it had it had to be that shit okay okay I was in production for like a year right
what like a year and a half yeah damn cray I got to go to the nether bra it's gonna be crazy how
are you already nethering because I play the game efficiently like a gamer that's awful
games are meant to be played poorly yeah that's right your speed running I'm a speed
running speed running is antithetical to the true gamer spirit well let's go build a house
been let's go build a nice nice little house I would have to are you in like a server could
I like jump in if I wanted no I I guess I could set one up but that would be a long time and it
would be stupid and take like a year to port forward a survey whatever I don't feel like
fucking playing Minecraft you know they have been playing what animal crossing your roommate
has a switch right yeah Caleb Caleb has a switch I jumped I jumped on his island I'm doing pretty
good I'm almost ready to upgrade my house I played New Leaf for a little while and I liked it so
I might want to get it I do have a switch I like got a switch for a smash played smash for like
two weeks and then like have never played anything else in my switch like since it was
pretty dangerous so I should I should probably get a game to play on my Nintendo switch for once
it's weird I like never played video games it was like a weird thing where as a kid I would game
nonstop and there was a big part of my dinner where it's like I like Nintendo games that's a
personality point put that on my Tinder profile I like Nintendo games and then for a long while
there like I did not interact with an interactive piece of software for like years like it like I
just basically never played I would occasionally boot up civ 5 play like around and then quit
no way through as a kid I wanted to be playing video games like constantly like all the time
and then like now I'm like I don't know all occasionally like distract myself with Pokemon
showdown or something yeah like very rarely do I'm like time for me to play a video game yeah
no I agree but quarantine has made me way like I've been playing video games like constantly
with Kazzie snap here Kazzie snap you want to cameo yeah but yeah what's going on I wasn't
listening we're playing video games yeah yeah I never played Minecraft maybe we should play
yeah okay well we'll play Minecraft after this no I just wanted you to say hi hi we're playing
through the Paper Mario's and it's epic you've played those before right yes well I've I played
didn't she like only play Super Paper Mario yeah that yeah that she only played Super and I had
played Super but only like half of that I did not finish it people hate on Super I think Super
is epic Super is like it's like yeah same like JRPG style that everyone loves about the other
ones no yeah awesome the Mario RPGs are like by far like the best RPGs because action commands are
just like they make the game like playable I mean I mean those are fine that's like a pretty minor
it's like a pretty minor point in the grand scheme of things what no so they're just like charming I
like love the mother games and like Mother 3 has a sort of action command system with music but like
I like cannot stomach play in RPGs where there aren't action commands I like I like hate them
viscerally I cannot play them for any longer than like a minute really yeah like I can't do it I
hate I hate I mean I grew up playing like Final Fantasy 7 and stuff a Final Fantasy 8 did kind of
have action commands a bit seven years awesome that's why Undertale is epic is because they have
like a weird battle system that's awesome no like no one like cares about that part of Undertale
that's like a shoot them up sort of weird dodging system but that's like the coolest part of
Undertale to me I only care about action commands and RPGs I mean you know it didn't invent the
idea well sure I mean obviously but I'm saying like it like if that's cool it's cool I like it cool
it kind of like fades into the background as the game goes on it does it doesn't really get
it's only at like certain like really like it's like boss battles that like you like remember
that it's a thing and are like invested in it you know well I guess that's fine because like it
mostly fades into the background unless it like suddenly becomes important and then it's you
notice it which is I guess is how a mechanic should work lol yeah good game it's a good video game
I thought you hated Toby Fox did I say that yeah I thought you like hated it and you thought that
you didn't deserve it it being anything um no when did I ever say that I'm pretty sure that I mean
I do I do think Undertale is overrated but like that's not to say that it's not good like it's
it would be hard to not be overrated when you're as appreciated as Undertale is right although have
we have we like come around on that has like has culture sort of like swung has the pendulum
swung the other way and like people are kind of like lost enthusiasm for Undertale now I think
it like Undertale has become one of the things where it's like it's so me meified where it's like
people think about like dude Law of Sands more than they think about like the actual game yeah yeah
sure so so in that way they probably don't really like Undertale but do people not but people
not think it's as good as they used to hmm but do they just not care about the actual product
itself I think mine just not actually care about the project itself I think I think people like
don't think about Undertale anymore they think about like Sands are people still um I don't know
is is Delta Room like still relevant they're like people make like Yaoi fan art of Delta Room
but that's basically it like Delta Room was Delta Room was just like like a like a a defibrillator
for the Undertale porn community that's that's all it was a stimulus package yeah hmm oh man I
have been having a lot of fun recently trying to like fill out forms and like obtain facts pertaining
to how I can squeeze as much money out of the government as I possibly can you know what I mean
no I know exactly I mean you and Tom have been going crazy in the PCP chat I mean I've been doing
a lot more of it then like I did talk to him and like explain to him like all the stuff that I had
found and like possible possible venues for that kind of thing but like you know I've been like
checking like websites and stuff like waiting for updates to try and be okay like when do I make my
move it's great it seemed for a while like I might be able to just get ten thousand dollars for
nothing I don't think I don't think that's gonna work out I might get something for being like a
sole proprietor of what might loosely be described as a business I might be able to get
something for that just as like a forward that doesn't need to be paid back which would be so
fucking cool I might be able to get us like a loan that I would not have to pay back provided I
spent it on like it's fun I would have to spend it on like rent mortgage and payroll but like by
payroll I could literally just give myself the money and call that payroll yeah it just be like
yep I paid myself with it it's forgivable now so you know trying trying to maximize all that it's
it's fun it's actually like kind of a an engaging puzzle that is exciting because of like you know
material benefit that I stand to obtain by like doing a good job at it do I love material benefit
I do don't you would you not love material benefit I certainly do I do quite like material
benefit it's good you know all things considered you know one's material circumstances are I would
say fairly relevant well I wouldn't go that far I don't know if you would have thought of this as
a person but I always wondered how like people and like did you who are like way more like you
know I guess big time fuck you small fry do an air net you know stuff like what do you have
planned for like when you're like too old to make poobah videos or not poobah but poobah
videos how what do you plan to do like are you gonna like die like how's retirement gonna look like
gonna like die well I guess I guess the plan is like maybe publish books and like maybe just like
try and live off royalties in the future like I don't have any like I don't have any books in
like stores right now that are so I like I would need to like I think I think like cheese like
memoirs I didn't realize comic books like like oh like my life been the alternative my my
alternative life by been saying shut up no no I mean just like get shit printed and try and live
off royalties from silly you know just get published through a distributor is like I think
that's the long-term goal in terms of like how to actually make money from from like comics I don't
know if I have enough that would be like publishable in that way right now I don't know if it would
make any money but like the hope is that maybe someday it could the I mean I could do other
things like I've talked here and there about how like one thing that I'd be really interested in
getting a like sort of a real job doing is doing like doing like art for like an indie game studio
or something every every now and then I like look on like local Craigslist or something for like
hey anyone like any like fucking dev studios like looking for an artist or anything like how serious
are the looks it's always it's always how serious are the looks would you describe yourself as pounding
the pavement in any way I mean in a purely digital sense perhaps so your dad wouldn't prove no
no you're taking a lot that so I don't know I guess that's the plan that'd be cool been saying
in it like indie game pixel artist I guess it's a great I think I could do it it's a great question
because yeah like I guess I don't know how I plan to like make money when I'm like old or whatever
it's weird since I don't have like since I don't since I don't have like a real job I don't well I
mean I guess I do pay into Social Security like with my like self-employment taxes and I guess that
I yeah so I guess I would be have something like a pension in the future I mean I'm saving up I'm
saving money in like a Fidelity account I have like a fucking I have a I have a small like 401k
or no a Roth IRA I have a small Roth IRA Raphael from the new teenage mutant ninja yeah that's
right he's really small he's not that big and a really big Michael and I don't know but you don't
get like if you don't have a real job you don't get like a pension or anything but like on the other
hand in the these days of the gig economy it's not like there's any guarantee that your employer
won't just like screw you over and fire you for no reason at any given time anyway I don't feel
like that's something that I would necessarily have anyway if I had just like you know gotten a real
job instead of doing internet shit so that that's sort of like it's weird like my I don't know I don't
think a generational thing I don't know if it's like a new phenomenon but like the idea of like job
benefits never really like occurred to me as like a consideration until like a couple years ago
like it was never like you know I want to get a job with good benefits like that was never even like
I don't think I even knew what it was until like I don't like five years ago or something like it was
never I guess was like oh like high salary right like you want a high monthly salary that's what you
wish they aim for right but like I mean you do well sure yeah here in America you also want your
fucking you want to make sure that your boss decides to promise you that you'll have like health
insurance and dental and stuff and then like a like a retirement and then and then they'll probably
take it away later on yeah you know they don't they're not really obligated to do anything that
they said they would do which is good that is that is actually good because that's the free market
and the free market is good yeah what were you talking about how you're gonna not die when you're
old and you're trying to make the vapors but you have the child's sold shaky hand and you can't do
it I'm a downward spiral yeah I know you're gonna be down a little down health trajectory
pair paradoxes 9-11 to your new Charles Schultz to it's gonna be even worse than anyone could have
imagined we only needed one Charles Schultz just has not been up for the two of us I bet Charles
Schultz doesn't have his shit the fucking a millionaire picnic he doesn't know shit he's
no shit about shit no he's fucking dead dude yeah he's fucking he fucking died so that makes
him on his tombstone at least I hate did you bro for a little while I sort of feel like being
cooped up in my in my room here just kind of having to deal with the fact that I look at a
screen all day I think there's something that's been fried in my brain because I just am constantly
like mad or sad always like I'm like that's just the soul like emotion that I feel as a human
being is I'm like yeah no definitely no I definitely agree that's absolutely the case for me I you
know you would think you would think that it would be like I'd have time to like work on stuff but
like I haven't been working on stuff like I have a little bit but like I wouldn't say the quarantine
definitely not made me more productive I find it like really hard to focus nowadays I would say
it's made me more productive I feel like somewhat happy that I'm able to like I don't know it like
it's two sides of the same coin where it's like I really hate the fact I can't go outside and it's
like it really feels like really terrible and like like my mind is melting but also like I'm
forced to feel like it's sort of an excuse yeah there's nothing more magical than that feeling
when you start a new thing or just you know whenever when a fascination fascination just
catches you and you just spend all night working on something because you just want to do it so
fucking badly there's nothing better than that and I've been I've been getting a few of those
lately with them with stuff relating to in those words birthday which is today we said at the
beginning but we didn't really talk about it since this was birthday haha click the link and donate
to our Kickstarter so you can buy pens oh yeah today today's the day today will be the day that the
Kickstarter goes live yeah that's exciting that's very exciting we just kind of like did it it's
kind of just like made it happen I've been thinking about it for a long time I know you know when
you said like oh we're gonna do I don't remember who I don't know it was me I well the thing is
is I just I was like we should do some sort of fundraiser I don't know what it was yeah because
people donated money on the last birthday you're like we should do like a fundraiser yeah it was
like okay but like what would it be the fundraiser for making pins like yeah we could do that but I
think it would be more successful as a Kickstarter yeah so yeah you know you will also be able to
buy more merch which you haven't even seen all the merch I've made you can get a mega slime shirt a
slime skull shirt a slime heart shirt a slime splatter shirt and reduxes of the two gang pride
shirts so go buy those if you don't want to donate to the pins for whatever reason but you really
want to give us money specifically because we aren't making that much profit on the pins it's
epic we gotta like we gotta fix the storefronts oh yeah no they're gonna be consolidated no yeah I
don't know why they were separated into three different things I mean I did it I did it like
that I thought it would be thematic but like actually it's just a night there's too many items
okay there's like I wish I wish you could set it up so you could like go to the storefront and
like just sort by like design like sort by tag or something and maybe you could maybe you could
just like tag like show me all rowdy merch like show me all killer merch show me all slime
court merch you know yeah I don't think you can do that it sucks um it's pretty bad I like hate
teespring I like a hate they're like editor it's like so fucking bad it's not it's not great
especially for the all over print yeah I did make I did make the um the like the neck gator the
face cover that's my like my like slime teeth on it that is epic I think that's pretty epic I
actually really am looking forward to that getting here are you the one purchase that by the way
of course I am yeah okay good yeah I bought it for um yeah I did the thing like it's like
buy a sample and it charges you like the minimum price that doesn't make any profit yeah epic yeah
hell yeah I'm gonna go to the nether guys it's gonna be epic level 17 let's go boys
dude I cannot believe how much money we got for madcon 4 I cannot believe it 34 thousand
dollars yeah it's pretty wild yeah I never would have suspected it I didn't think we'd hit 20k
no not at all I was afraid that we would like I don't know it would be just I guess I feel like
I'm in like a worry-a-worry with these sorts of things I was afraid I think you are you always you
you don't you didn't seem to think that the pins would make a lot of me I think the pins will make
here's my prediction I suspect that the pin I'll be embarrassed if I'm wrong what are you gonna do
my prediction is that the pink starter will make at least three thousand dollars I here's my prediction
I think it will get in the ballpark between 800 and 15 thousand dollars or not 15 thousand 1500
I think there's no way that it does not crack a thousand I think I think you're probably right
I feel extremely confident it'll be it'll break two thousand I know I would say pretty good chance
of 3000 well okay as long as it's not embarrassing then that's fine it's just as long as it's not
like we make two dollars and also we're robbed no there were people in my like birthday stream
yesterday that were like Bevan was like no pins are stupid but everyone else was like no I love
fans pins are like probably one of the coolest things that a person can have I hadn't even
considered making patches but you know thinking about it I would definitely put like patches on
stuff dude on my jacket like a rowdy pin that would be sorry a rowdy patch that would be like
awesome I could be like Scott Pilgrim and you know how he was like the X-men hoodie and it looks
really cool I could be like that but it would be like a rowdy thing yeah yeah uh we should um I
was saying like um when we when we run the polls for like what should we make next I guess I guess
there'd be like here like this pin that pin the other pin this patch that patch the other patch
yeah and they because pins the pins and patches we could make for like basically the same
amount so if they could just like be basically interchangeable with each other right I was oh
do you think okay do you think it's worth like kind of changing the verbiage on the like um
on the um the Kickstarter to be like the reward is not one pin the reward is like one slime credit
and you can like trade in a slime credit for a pin or a patch or like two for a challenge coin
like you get like money I think it's pretty fucking weird to confuse I mean we could easily do the
idea of if you want instead of having one pin you can save this pen design and you can just
with two pen designs saved up with two stretch goals if we do if we do the challenge coin I think
that's how we should do it yeah that's the only thing I think wouldn't just cost one I guess the
only thing is that like um if you want a patch but like the the reward is a pin and it's like okay
we have to say like okay like one patch equals one pin we could call it we could call the reward one
pin slash patch or something or but like what if we don't end up making any patches like what if
they just don't end up being like very widely voted for yeah we might not actually make any yeah um
I mean it doesn't matter I just thought like hey what if it was like a like slime corp like currency
scam I don't know your specialty Ben is coming in with like the absolutely like most autistic
minute changes in graphic design and spending five weeks doing it and it's awesome thank you
yeah pleasure happy to be of service it's awesome I'm glad I offer something
I really really bring a son to the table on that one
man we finally did the buster cast and nobody nobody showed up Nate who was like I can't believe
Nate didn't want to show up it's so strange to me it's me yeah Nate was like uh I don't know if I
could find the time did you was like uh I don't have the time it was like you don't have like
six hours in two days I don't understand this like weak shit of like oh yeah I just didn't have
time you know they've made I know has seen it multiple times he could have probably just shown
up without even watching it ahead of time I have no idea why I almost feel like it was some sort of
weird like making a point kind of thing what like they didn't want to be on it because like he said
we weren't going to do it unless he like uh I don't know I could be totally off base but like
what if Nate didn't want to be on it because he said we weren't going to be able to
organize it without him and then we did I don't know that might be wrong he said that you wouldn't
be able to organize it without him he said on the bonus episode that like guys you know you won't
do it if I don't like set it up what that's yeah okay and I was like no I'll just say when we do it
and then we do it and then I did that and then we did LeMau I don't know but I do not know I do
understand why they thought it would be so difficult to come on considering I know that I know they're
both fans but whatever that's fine just me and Tom just me and Tom just having a little me and Tom
solo double double solo duet cast you know it's new it's a new new character dynamic
chemistry my little pony it's it's like that's that's such a weird dynamic it's like apple jack and
yeah it's like apple jack and twilight like what do they even talk about yeah you're apple jack
could they fuck like I don't know let's find out if the answer yes but you'll have to buy the episode
so you can see all that steamy episode action ah you gotta buy the uncensored version to take the
like light beams oh god like they're like utter they're like down below the legs like utter tits
disgusting yeah I I I can't wait till the OVA comes out it's gonna be awesome
it is gonna be awesome but um we haven't like I feel like we have we haven't really made any
progress on finding an animator uh yes we have I don't know if we want to talk about it but hippo
has made progress he's he's been talking about in chat um I'm shit I haven't I must have missed it
yeah we're getting like yeah yeah I mean do you want to keep a secret or something because uh
well well I'll say in a very vague way that it implies nothing specifically but as everyone in
the audience knows hippo is you know working with like a studio so I don't think that they're gonna
do it but I he knows of people who could ask other people and he and that has been what has happened
as he has asked other people and have they and have they given him leads yes interesting
interesting but who knows if that's what how it will be or not but that's that's where we are
right now there there is there there there are things happening on that front that's good I'm glad
Ben you got so mad I have no fucking clue why I have no idea I don't really know exactly why either
I I think I just could hear I just I could hear in people's voices that they were like prioritizing
something that I thought was like be up beside the point and it really frustrated me and maybe
that's like stupid but that's how I felt you see here's the biggest problem with PCP is that we have
Nate you know uh what's his uh he has like self-defined no low-information voter and it's epic
and funny but max charisma can get anyone to like agree with him because he says things in such a
great way that everyone wants to agree with him because he says it in a great way and then Ben
you try to come on with the with the facts and the logics we have like an anti-charisma that
makes everyone hate you and it's infuriating that you always lose when you shouldn't lose
this thanks no well I didn't mean as in you're retarded I mean that you like you should by all
accounts you've done the reading you've done you know you you're on bread tube like you know
shit but there's just something about like people are just more excited to hear about like
something that sounds right more than something that is right you know do you want me by that
are we still talking about the animator or no no we're not talking about that at all no
no I'm talking about I'm talking about political things on the PCP um see I don't know if I agree
with that uh Nate Nate is not Nate's not convincing like I don't think anyone has been
like convinced of anything by Nate like saying he believes it capitalism just sounds so right though
it's sad it's not it doesn't I think I think a big okay I think a big big draw in the appeal
of capitalism is that it sounds so like something about that feels so like well it's just human
nature it's just human nature to want things and so why wouldn't we allow the obvious scenario to
allow a system where people who want things to remind their own self-interest to acquire them
like that sounds like so like oh of course of course of course I know well I don't know
I don't know if I agree with you that it sounds like obviously true I think the appeal of it
is that if true it require it means that like no action is required and like everything is by
default working as it should and like we definitely don't have to think about it anymore
I think that's the appeal of it
um no I think a lot of like I think oh okay I think this is true of literally everyone like
on on both sides but I think that like everyone wants like everyone like thinks that their side
sounds the most reasonable like and like it's almost obvious in a way which I it thinks makes
sense and I think a big part of what people cherish in these words debates is like when someone is
able to explain something in such a way where I think there's like a socialist term for this but
it's like it makes it seem where it's the only option not so that it's like the best option but
it's like to do something else other than our system that we have currently it would be like
against human nature it would it would be like this is so obviously the case this is so what
has to happen there's nothing else even like possible yeah I think that's a big like a draw
there I don't know draws like that's like the biggest thing I feel like you I feel like you've
missed you've missed the point like you you think that because you've been told it like your whole
life it's same with everyone like everyone's just been told that over and over again and now it just
feels true um because everybody's heard it well maybe that is what I mean that like like I'm saying
that it sounds so correct because we've been told yeah it's not it's yeah it sounds right
because everyone has been told it their whole lives like that's all I'm saying they've learned to
repeat it as a mantra yeah yeah sure yeah I mean that's that's definitely the case yeah and it's a
big problem uh that is uh ruining everything and it makes and it's you know when Nate like
think when Nate thinks he wins an argument because he says the thing that like is like
dogmatically accepted but by everyone by default because it's just that thing you say it's just
that cliche that everyone repeats over and over again it's just like a platitude but everyone
just accepts that it's true so if you you say it usually you automatically win because you said
the thing that everyone know quote unquote knows is true that even you don't even have to think about
it um it's amazing feels great what are we talking about uh I don't know I don't think we're
talking about I think we're talking about that and be stopped because there's nothing else to say
yeah that's all I have to say about that I'm in the nether been it's amazing
is it it's I couldn't have asked for anything better great I think you ever could have dreamed
why why are you in the nether what are you doing here why why are you playing the game stop it
why why why why why no no no man uh I'm going to go get blaze rods so that we can go fight the
nether dragon the nether dragon the dragon man we can go fight strawberry milk I'm not gonna go
fight I'm not gonna fight the nether dragon you're not gonna help me you're not gonna you're on your
own oh sad you stupid idiot well I guess it's just not in your self interest to do such a thing
no definitely not it's the human nature doesn't allow for such a such an action
no we tried the nether dragon before and you know I mean look at china
look at venezuela 100 million dead you criticize capitalism yet yet you exist I love that political
comment I don't know did we just did we just do exactly what we were talking about before did we
just say an unreasonable interpretation of nate's argument we probably did he probably like no
no I I like stopped listening to the podcast a while ago so I don't know how like the things
have changed so I'm like and that was like a while ago I think at this point like like
I think like half a year ago at minimum so I don't know if that's like people have gotten like
uh buff intellectually oh my god what the fuck is this that's terrifying um
you know and people are now have the maximum intellect they've read all the theory in the
entire world and now it's like a battle of undisputed masters of their opinion but last I
checked it was just kind of like you know what we were just describing so I'm going off of that
but maybe maybe things are better now I mean are they maybe now no everyone everyone always
on the last episode everyone was like oh I saw this was just like a ben and nate episode so I clicked
like oh thanks for the comments for letting me know not to watch this one
um everybody hates it everybody hates the punch then why do you do it then why do you
talk about politics because it's mostly you and me um I just have to I just can't I just can't
let people be wrong what like we define have to like who's like I guess it's it's you hate the fact
that this is being spread so you would be it would be immoral of me not to correct wrong things
that's it but if people hate it then then what what if you were to correct
their problem that's their problem isn't it your problem because your entire
line your entire but like you're all the success of this podcast rests upon public opinion
um
I guess well what do you want me to do uh I don't know if I want you to do anything but I'm saying
if if people are like commenting on every episode being like this is gay I hate this die and then
maybe you should be like oh well maybe I shouldn't do that anymore well I mean I'll I'll stop I'll stop
I'll stop bringing it up when other people stop making bad faith arguments against me
done they'll never happen because I know right that's right but that but that's what it's gonna take
and if people want to not hear about it anymore then we should all just agree
that I'm right yeah that I am correct and then and then there will be no more need for debate
epic yeah um we were talking about on the my birthday stream we were talking about
someone was like hey Ben you should debate destiny hey Ben you should debate destiny I was like
I'm not good I'm not actually I don't actually think I'm good at debating yeah like I couldn't
even I couldn't even really like claim like victory in the debate against digi and digi is
definitely not a good debater so like I must not be great either no um I also think I mean I don't
know I mean I I know this isn't what anyone really means but I still am like I have that sort of
repulsion the idea of winning a debate even though I know it's practical I know what everyone
means by it but there's something about it still makes me feel you know yeah I mean it's all very
performative yeah and very like uh you know you just do it for that you do it to win the
cloud or whatever oh you won you you you you you perform strength in front of people they saw
you win and their your reputation points go up or whatever I I feel like like digi like
most the time what he says is not stupid like did you just always needs an extra video to like
respond to comments because I feel like this is the way it always goes with the digi digi says
something which you have to be like a hardcore digi head to like understand what he means and
it will always be misinterpreted and then once everyone is like that's obviously retarded then
digi will say what he actually means because he understands how to respond and like why people
are misunderstanding and in that case it's always just he should just say what he actually
means in the first place then he should but he doesn't know how to he doesn't know he doesn't
get it he doesn't know I mean I think I think he would agree with what I'm saying or I think that
he would agree no I agree that is generally how things go a lot of the time I think digi most
the time says things are very reasonable he just needs an extra well when he yeah yeah most most
of the time upon further explanation you go oh okay oh it's not yeah yeah yeah and that's always
been a thing about him I that this is a bit as a whole entire life quest isn't it that he wants to
be understood yeah he says so and why should we doubt him I don't know maybe we should maybe we
shouldn't maybe it's true who's to say though in this doggy dog world we'll never we'll never know
we have we do we can only speculate this is oh Jesus Christ
oh oh oh oh hey man how's the nettle treating you it's hot a hot are you gonna you're gonna
beat the ender dragon uh yeah I think I can this minecraft's not that long wait really yeah right
if I find some blaze rods and I beat some enderman then yeah why not how how long do you think it'll
take you to beat the ender dragon or the never dragon well we'll see real boss ender ender
well it's hard to say right because it's all random so feel you know I could get a really
lucky spot where the stronghold is really close to me and in which it probably wouldn't take that
much long at all but like you know I could get one where it's very very very far away from me so
it might take a long time all right okay I guess we'll see I guess we will see
um I want to get anything God I yeah so you you asked me if I was gonna have the um
the the the slime and punishment finale done for the birthday yeah I said maybe and the
truth about that is that I definitely could have had it done um but I didn't I just didn't do it and
I mean part of that is because like I have I have basically I just like stopped communicating with
like a couple of people who were going to be like providing stuff for it um like as in their lost
causes oh no they're not lost causes I just like stopped oh it's a new thing it's a okay it's a
it's a new thing it's a new thing I mean well Sixten was gonna make the song but like I didn't
really vibe with the first song he made and he was like okay well if you want me to rewrite it
I'd like to see like a storyboard and I'm like I don't really have a storyboard I kind of just
have to like make the video so I'll just do that because you've made it like a shitty version of
of like just like a quick version so he would have known yeah I guess like I guess I could like
sketch it out yeah that's what that's what a storyboard is Ben I know I know I know well like
I could sketch out what I think it'll look like um I it might not end up looking exactly that way
but I guess that's probably fine yeah yeah I don't know I feel like maybe I didn't like
communicate exactly what I wanted to him and so when he turned to his song and it wasn't exactly
what I had like imagined and so I was like oh what do I do oh god I can't deal with this
I can't deal with my free labor not being completely exact I'm paying him for it oh well
never mind that fuck that guy yeah um I've been um I've been paying everyone it feels good
it is I gave um I gave I paid um a oblivion fall something for like helping me do the audio on the
JDR lecture I paid um shout out some money for like an animation for the something for the
Chris Chan lecture that I'm planning on using um I'm gonna pay six and for making the track
um I offered to pay um to Munich for a thing that she was making for the finale she said like
she didn't want it I don't know uh we'll see we'll see about that just pissed myself um why
just I was hit in the video game
no no that sucks too I was damaged once
bomber um anyway I don't know I made a bunch since I made all this money from the first kick
starter from the very very first two kickstarter I feel like it would I feel like it would be
unacceptable for me to like ask people to make me stuff just as a favor like even if it's not
something I'm selling I don't know yeah I can't just be like hey make me a song for a video you
know for free we're all we're all in this together we're all just pals um but I'm the one who benefits
yeah no no no no um we I kind of like the fact that we're doing like well I mean I really like
the fact that we're doing the kickstart the way that it is I like the fact that R2K is like a
really fucking weird like experimental like community driven consensus nightmare where it's like
everything is only real when the community says it is and we're running the kickstart like that
like this yeah I got I mean I would be a little I would be a little annoyed if like
everyone votes for like some dumb shit you know which I I think there might be like a couple
there might be some like dumb shit that ends up getting made as if it's only a little bit I won't
be too annoyed if it's like a lot of dumb shit I will like grumble about it like this is a waste
well why is it a waste if that's what they want well okay but if there's like okay I like can't do
this imagine we have like a imagine we have a hundred people that are like donating right we
have a hundred people that are buying pins and like we do a vote and like you know a whole bunch
of them vote for like something stupid they might vote for it and it might get passed but like
what what if what if they all like vote for it because it's funny but they don't actually want it
only maybe like five of them actually want like the funny meme design yeah so then we make like
50 or a hundred of these things and remove like five of them and then we're stuck with like 45 pins
that only or 95 pins that only exist for the sake of like a meme like a joke like what do we do with
these right I I um I feel maybe we can um like phrase the vote in a way that's like like if you're
like do you think that we could do it so like a vote is not a vote basically is like a you you want
to buy this right it's like this is something this isn't just something you're voting for on the
for like this like you voting for this basically says like yeah if I have another like like I have
another like credit to spend or whatever on a pin and like this is the design I want yeah um yeah
um we could drive that home yeah I think it's probably implied but it'd be nice to reiterate
yeah yeah I don't know no idea to get home if anyone who anyone who has like multiple like
designs that they wanted probably would be voting that way anyway uh the only like if someone just
bought like one pin maybe they just wanted like the ratty fucker cop kill he didn't care about
anymore and so they just buy two and then they're like well you know I don't actually want anymore
but I'm still voting yeah I guess I'll vote for something fun I don't know I can't you know I
probably am like overthinking it and it won't be a huge deal or anything but you know I can't help
but imagine the worst-case scenario um I give you a bunch of crap uh I I was sort of like I don't
know I mean again like I like that okay this was a thing that the lecture heads the the the the
people are people who want to say the brain deads because it's like born deads but like
they're during the shamblers so it's like zombies right like you get it like brain yeah right I don't
know the jury's still at but anyway they really really liked the like everything is only canon
by consensus they really like latched onto that as like an idea and it was kind of like it's always
been like that no no no I know I'm saying that they like that was like while I was going through
the tour describing the districts they like really like appreciated that as like a core element of
rfck and like a way where it's like I I mean you know it's always been the case but it's like I never
really like thought of it as like yeah I guess that's like a defined characteristic of it and that's
almost like an ideological theme of in this war in a way where it's like everything is up to only
what people like believe is true like you know like there's so little to the actual game like
like the only thing that makes it cool really is what people think about it right um it's it's
like mob rule uh for the greater good um and it's it's epic and I really I I think that's just like
real play yeah it is it's like we're running our own little commune over here hell yeah um
there's a um I've talked I've talked about like the floraverse before you know what I'm you know
what that is it's a comic isn't it it is it is not just a comic it is a um it's it's comics but like
they had like community events where like um the one I remember was there was like there was like an
event in the comic where like the basically like the the the the protagonists were basically
going to be like fighting in a war and there was like a battle plan and like they had a community
event where like people who read the comic got the opportunity to like they could like write stories
or do art or like make videos or whatever that's sort of like it's like depict your character and
like what what is there like you will get assigned to like a commander or something and like like
make art of like your role in the battle right and like I think the creators ended up like featuring
some and be like like these like these the ones that get featured become canon yeah right we don't
even have we don't even have to like feature it yeah it's canon if people want it to be canon
yeah it's like very like it it feels very cool that it's like a big part of this is even though like
you know rck is like very tied into me and you in a way we don't have to be there for it to like
make sense for defunction because it's so like community driven where it's like the appeal is
like what you can do in this setting like we are almost like window dressing for the appeal in a way
yeah yeah for sure it's like your your passion for the show or for us individually like that brings
you here and with that now what are you going to do like what is going to transpire
and I really this is the sort of thing where this is what I'm thinking about uh in the what
kind of stuff do I want to make now that I don't want to do like podcasts and stuff like that uh too
often uh besides this one this one is special to me in rck is special but other than this one I
don't want to do it and I think I really love the like experimental aspect of endless war and I
really want to like do more stuff like it not just like make you know you could say that lonesome
cactus is like endless war but I don't mean like in the I want to make more discord bots but like I
really like I'm getting into like coding in a more like serious not just I can do python because I
have to do it so that I can do endless war stuff like I really like it and I feel like it's the
future in a way and that's the sort of stuff I want to do is I want to do more stuff that engages
people in the weird sort of you know endless war is very democratic sort of it's only the people the
updates do come out only you know are supplemental to the experience of endless war in a way like I
really like that I want to do more stuff like that that's where my head's at um that um I think it's
the most like interesting part about it right that's like the thing that makes it cool everything
else just like you know all right yeah it it does it I remember like reading that stuff about like
this like fan driven portion of like the floor reverse and thinking like that's really weird
like that's really cool like that's interesting I don't know I guess I like that like endless war
has like some elements of that to it um but more yeah um but with less porn unfortunately
unfortunately there's not as much four versus a lot of porn canon porn made by v creators uh I've
seen it it's a cool art style I like it it is a cool art style but so I think it's really good
whoever draws it I forget their name
I I can't I need to get a hose so I can do farming how long have we been going
let's find fucking plum to uh at least two I think maybe like two and a half hours what I don't
we're we're we're doing the edge of two hours right now we're on the edge of two hours okay
um god it really took us till seven to start yeah ball cool um
I don't know what do we what have we not discussed what's been getting mad lately
let's let's just get into the things that make us mad because that's where all my brain powers
going now it is great um do you want to start do you have something um oh god I have to think
about it I asked that question without any indication that would come back around to me uh
hmm I feel like I've been doing nothing but talking about what makes me mad makes me mad
well I hate I going back to what we were talking about the very beginning I hate
I hate school now because it's remote and dumb now and I'm painful that's awful it's really
terrible that's bullshit it's totally bullshit it's like it's unacceptable like they're not
giving you the fucking product you paid for no not at all like no like specifically like if you
want to roll back the clock and go into old pcp episodes like the biggest thing is I wanted to
be around other like new people and I wanted to have teachers one-on-one talk to me and like
that's not that like both of those things are like not happening anymore it's like it's it's
only the boring stupid parts that like I like like it's only the parts where I thought well
it's for the greater good it's but it's now there is no greater good and it's just is only terrible
yeah um I hate I hate how do I make quotes how do I do this guys in chat chat let me know
let me watch do you chat is it this it is that epic um so I'm mad about that I'm mad about like
mad about fucking like everyone you know what okay all right here's the thing I felt like this
way for a long time I think I've said this in a few podcasts before but and I don't know how
legitimate it is I don't know how much it is in my own head but I feel like I don't know anyone I
feel like no one knows me I don't mean that isn't like no one's smart enough to appreciate my
intellect I mean that in the sense that it's like I can talk to no one about anything that I care
about ever like I like I feel like I have been so I guess I guess it's my fault in a way where it's
like I've been like a very like isolated person for a lot of my life and like especially for like a
lot of my life leading up to like going to college and like talking to more people like I feel like
I have developed in ways that other people have not not say that I have done it more but just like
I have different interests than like everyone that I talk to and it feels terrible when I have to
like inner pot like or not inner podcast but in our like discord chats and I have to talk to people
and like remember that like I only am friends with like gamers and shit and it's like oh I have
nothing to say and it is terrible and I want to die I don't know if I don't like when I think about
these it's it flips us between why isn't everyone like me and I'm like why am I not like anyone else
it flips us between itself and then extrinsic man versus world man versus itself that's that's my
hatred that's my main hatred do you ever feel like you like you feel like I don't know no one else
gets it no one else understands no one else likes things that are good everyone else likes things
that are stupid and I can't talk to anyone yeah sure constantly epic I was just thinking that
about you cool hmm um what do you what would um what would you find satisfying what would make
you feel what would make you feel better well here you know what that but before we talk about that
here I'm gonna leave this into saying things that will people will have an emotional grip to this
now because okay here's the thing about the pcp and here's like the unfortunate truth about the
pcp and like here's how to fix it quote-unquote and the most unhelpful way possible is that you
can't quote-unquote fix it because again I guess it's not broken and you know it's not it's not
that bad but what people say like people when people say oh I miss topics they're like they
they miss the sort of cohesion they miss the sort of like you know what this podcast is about a
certain thing this podcast is about and everyone has like stuff contribute here's the thing that
matters most in podcasts is the conversation and people like having interesting things to say about
you know to one another in the conversation that is transpiring and the reason why people
dislike the pcp or at least why I think so is because the conversations usually feel pretty
shallow because most people are doing different things like we aren't usually like okay here's
how the pcp used to happen again when I was on and when I observed it might have changed by now
but it's like you and bin talk about or I'm sorry you and Nate talk about politics for a while and
you guys have something to say about that so it's like you know it is a conversation and it's cool
and then it's Nate and Tom talk about video game news for a little while and then they have something
to say about that but it's kind of like two pairs of people like constantly like reversing and
switching off about like the one thing that they have in common it's never like a big cohesive
like group conversation talking about similar things because not everyone's on the same page
anymore and that's not something to be fixed or like oh you know like fuck the pcp like it sucks
and we have to fix it because there's nothing to be fixed about it it's just that people are
different now and we are no longer all my little pony reviewers who are all in the same cultural
sphere and that just is the way that people grow apart from another but that's that's what I'm feeling
that's the sadness that I get is that I don't know anyone anymore and we all don't be like I don't care
about fucking video game twitter you know I don't care about that so I have nothing to contribute
in those conversations um and I have nothing to contribute in other conversations like that where
it's like well it's just what I was saying yeah that uh I so what would make me feel better
is I guess getting new friends that's that sounds like a rejection of the old friends they don't
mean in a way but like I don't know it's hard it's hard to make friends that you actually want to
because the the entire like what's the words like I don't know it's just hard it's just hard to go
out there and try and meet new people uh when you're so yeah especially considering uh quarantine
yeah exactly so you you can't you have to I I've I've long considered going on like forums and trying
to become like a forum person but like I don't know those days are behind me and my my days role
playing pokemon are behind me um I tried getting to I like really tried really really hard to get
into reddit I just could never get it into my like I don't know I could not get addicted to reddit in
the way that I wanted to where I really wanted to like prowl around subreds and like get involved
with that community but I was always just repulsed by like the UI of reddit and I just hated it but
yeah uh I mean I I tried you know for a while there I was trying to like go out to like a
fucking comics club and stuff trying to like meet people that way didn't work yeah didn't
like with anything I completely agree do I I like try like a big part of like it like
oh I already made it okay never mind um I I tried really hard to go into a lot of clubs and at my
school and you you went to a club um and it was a nightmare and they were all like that it was
pretty funny it was pretty funny though um I guess I guess I guess that I guess that is a
word in the English language hmm um nightmare but yeah it was like
I don't know I feel like I don't click with anyone and it's a nightmare and there's nothing to be
said I guess or done about it uh but that's just that's one of the things that's why I'm angry
that is the thing that I'm angry about always now is that that's relatable I feel that way all
the time even before before quarantine I felt that way and it's become all the more acute now
I feel that hard core but you know hard core okay so there's like degrees of this right where it's
like with like a date like I know nothing in common with Nate like I don't do anime or like
video games or stuff really and that's and say that I don't like it but like you know he's one of
the the ones that I'm most far removed from in in the way that I'm describing right now
for the sake of demonstration but like you and me do talk and stuff like we do hang out in person
so like you know or we did well yeah sure but I'm saying that uh what do you want to talk about Ben
you know we we we are not so far gone that it's not worth it to even try to uh accommodate one
other what do you want to talk about I'll I'll get into some stuff what do you want um we were
doing audible and stuff for a while we were both into books oh you know I I told you that I started
listening to um the bullshit jobs I never finished it I think I like halfway halfway through
yeah that's a thing though right that's pretty cool um um um um um yeah I don't know there's
nothing new there's nothing new to report over here um well I'm saying what what kind of animal
crossing I guess I'm saying what kind of things that you do you wish that people would talk about
or that you wish that you like like what like on what way do you wish that people were more on the
same like cultural level than you and like yeah that um I I guess I I wish that like um
I wish that like when I when I went to like uh the comics round table or something people were
talking about like I wish people were talking about it in a more specific way I wish people were like
there to like first of all I wish people were more like serious about it I wish people were like
better I wish people were there to like collaborate or like work together in some way
to like pool our resources instead of just to kind of like bullshit about like oh yeah here's like
the newest thing I don't know the things that they were there to work on were like
planning on like which like cons to go to and like I don't care about that yeah um
I don't know they just yeah I don't know I would like for I would like to meet people that were like
in your field they were serious about like doing the kind of things that I do and were like interested
in like yeah working together and like doing something so you want to meet more web comics
people is what you're saying well I don't know I mean I guess uh yet well I think a big part of
the comics round table right is that it's like a lot of people who are meeting in person so there's
gonna be a lot of like you know what cons do we go to you know like with our bodies because we're
human beings but yeah that might not like um I say that I say that but like at the same time um
I don't know I don't even know like what I don't really know like what I would like want to work
with people I don't know I guess if they were like well it's not about working way it's just
talking about it's just or like maybe it would be cool if like somebody had like a zine or something
and someone was like looking for like stuff to like put in a zine and I could be like hey I could
make stuff for your zine or some shit like that I don't know you know what the greatest service
we've given to the rfck audiences is that we've created a fandom for them to exist in because
there's nothing nothing better than being a part of a fandom those like that is the ideal state of
a human being you know people in the wild like like a like a Russoian man in the jungle longs be a part
of the homesuck fandom like that's their biggest like what in the world outside of like shelter
to their mazla's hierarchy of needs yeah exactly because it's so home stuck fandom is home stuck
fandom because it's when you're in a fandom right it's just big enough where you get like a big
like display of like a large uh diverse sort of you know there's a lot of different types of artists
who will want to allow different types of things you know it's a very it's big enough where you get
that diversification that goes with civilization then you it's also small enough and you have such
a thing in common with one another where it's easy to make friends and easy to talk to one other
able easy to find people you can google search like carcat anime music video yowie big cock version
two and then you'll get like 15 different results and it'll be epic um right sure but i mean that
that's like the coolest thing and i wish i was a part of a fandom because okay go on go like every
like weekly my little point episodes you tune in every week and then you have like a whole bunch
of new fan stuff to do amazing you know and one of us is a homesuck update there's another whole
round of videos and arts and stuff to do the homesick was crazy about it uh i missed that i want
that how do i get into it without having to deal with new shows which are bad and stupid and i hate it
that's the goal that's the goal for that i think i think that's like the way forward for me is i
need to become a part of a fandom and then just redo that um i um i would be like you know something
like um that like like the dsa or that like like socialist club that you were like that we tried to
go to the meeting of like i feel like if something like that were good it would be really great
but i have the suspicion that it would suck yeah and be boring i mean i don't know but like what like
what do what do you what do they do yeah what do you think they actually just sit around and talk
about shit and like there's i mean i assume there's no real like action probably probably not um
i don't know but like maybe maybe that just means there's nothing there's nothing to do
you just you just gotta like lay just just lay down and die actually like what's the point you know
there's nothing to be done you just give up you have merry weather surely can meet more
webcomics people like that and then merry weather doesn't like no i don't know the i mean yeah i know
merry weather but like he is just kind of he i don't know what does it like what exactly does
that get me access to i'm saying that he's a part of the greater webcomic sphere i mean and he's
particularly well known at that as far i mean i don't know but i i think he's a particularly well
well known as that and you mean i know him and me yeah exactly so you can use that point that
data point in your network to think about cynically and try and reach out to more people try and get
more involved with him and then you'll meet more people merry weather is like a very well connected
guy there you go well no well no don't there you go me because like what what what does it
what does it do for me what what do i take and do with that information what you take and do with
that is become better friends with merry weather and then when you were better friends with merry
weather first of all you may enjoy his company as a friend but if you want to think about extremely
cynically you can become better friends with merry weather to get access to his greater network
through collaborations and stuff like when you were just like you were just saying where
you may be able to meet people through calls and stuff like that and through just me and then while
being his friend you're able to meet more people that you would be able to collaborate with and do
stuff like that zine that hypothetical zine i don't want to like i don't want to come off as like
just poo pooing you out of hand or anything but this is like this this is giving me this is giving
me like pound of pavement vibes like it's network like oh it's just like just network and make
connections and like and and do what you know well like who like like what what what's the play here
like i go hey merry weather hey merry weather uh introduce introduce me to some like well connected
like like artist people and then he's like oh yeah okay okay here here's um here's um the guy who
does like that that one that everyone's heard and i go oh cool cool cool and i say hey uh i'm ben i
drew some comics and they go like oh yeah cool um that's cool i also draw some and i go yeah i know
i've heard about your stuff and they go oh cool nice like okay and like i don't know well well
okay if you have no want to meet other people in the field then yeah okay then there's no point
but i thought you were just saying that you wanted to talk to more people who were taking
webcomic seriously i thought that i thought that was the whole impetus for this conversation um
i i don't maybe maybe i would maybe if i had more like wait dude i'm gonna milk a cow i'm gonna
milk a cow dude shut the fuck up dude shut the fuck maybe if i have i got milk raw got milk dude
yeah more regular contact with people who are doing that kind of thing maybe it would occur to me
like what to do with such in such just scenario oh as it stands i have like no like i have no like
goal or i have no like oh this is what i need to do like here here's how i like take it to the
next level like i have no idea you're you're you're a very even steven sturdy person been your
horizons when i feel like whenever we have a show where like what are we doing guys where
you want to go i feel like you're you're always like i just want to do what i'm doing right now
because i'm having fun and it's cool and i'm i'm perfectly fine where i am i feel like that's
always your responses you don't want to you want like right now you don't want to meet new people
you just want to hang out not to say that's even a bad thing that just seems to be always the case
well maybe it sounds like that but um i don't know i do feel kind of like isolated i guess i do
you know i don't know i i'm like i have two minds about it because like i have like talked to other
like i've talked to other like webcomics people and like they're usually like fine but like i'm not
generally that interested in what they're doing and like they're like only like marginally interested
in what i'm doing and it's like okay well i guess we know each other all right you just keep doing
what you're doing i'll just keep doing what i'm doing you know whatever and um so i don't know
like i i guess like i i would like to know more people like that but like i have when i have done
it in the past it's just been like uh well uh all right see you i think i get what you mean like
it's easy to want that in the abstract but like the steps it would take to require to get to
a point where you have like a good friend that you're able to like confer and like that it seems
like the kind of thing that i ought to want and maybe be like striving for but i do not know what
the end goal of it is we're not the end goal be companionship and and someone's shoulder to cry on
and um fellowship in men i mean sure yes but uh like
i mean that's like um that's like oh but what if you made a new best friend it's like well i don't
know what what if i did yeah you can't like set out to do that i i guess it is sort of like a
almost inherently selfish sort of thing because i'm always like i always am desperate for someone
i can talk about history with not talk to someone about his like you know i did the the lecture and
that was like cool but not at all what is a satiety thing where it's like instead of you know like
describing something to someone i want to like you know discuss it with someone i can't do that to
someone who have just regurgitated information to like i've always wanted that but it's like
you can't just like manufacture someone like like really like the the reason i would want that is so
that i can say things to them and then have them hear my thoughts and be able to understand them
like it like i say that i want someone to discuss it with and have them what the there's a little
cold going on over here uh so that they will be able to understand and like parse what i'm saying
to them but in a way it's also very selfish because it's like well i want them to be able to
parse it so that i can speak to what's in my head like i have things that i want to say to them
right now and i want them to listen to me i get like i guess it's selfish in that way do you want
to be listened to or do you want to be talked to well i i want it it's two things i like i can't
i can't talk to someone in the sense that i can't like you know i meet someone i just want my friends
and they don't know anything about history and i say hey let me relate to you this tale that has
happened once like i don't want to do that because that's bored and there's no reason for me to just
like talk someone's ear off of that something they don't understand but i do want to talk to someone
who does get it like you know someone who knows what i want to discuss about so that we can have
it like a conversation about it because i have a lot of like thoughts about history but i can't
talk to anyone about it because none of them know anything about it so you know there's no
there's no conversation to be had but those conversations would be selfish in the sense
where it's like i want to talk to someone else about history i want them to understand what
i'm talking about so that i can say all these things i've been on my mind but i've not been able to
express anyone else because no one gets their cares you know what i mean do you understand
um kind of maybe a bit well there
but like you can't like it's you can't just like say to someone like hey get into this like genre
of like human experience please so that i can talk to you about it like it's not you know
you can't convince anyone to do something like that no you've got to find someone who's already
into it yeah exactly and and then you have to in order to do that you have to like plot around
r slash history and it's stupid and dumb and i hate that place and i guess i guess i feel like um
you know since i'm like a comics guy i should have like comics friends but i have like i kind of
have like very little to say about my comics like outside of the like the comics themselves
you know it's just like fucking Hideaki ono and even galleon it's like you know he said what he
wanted to say by making the comic he doesn't have like there's not like he doesn't need to like go
and like talk about them or like explain what he means like they just speak for themselves
like all the stuff that i make i feel like it speaks for itself i don't need to like discuss it
you know so um maybe that's like a weakness well i i feel like i feel like ben what's
happening here is that you know that you should want human connection but you don't actually care
and you just have this husk of an idea in your brain that it's good to have those things but you
don't actually care at all is what it seems like like it's like when you say these things like but
like what would be the point of talking to other people well the point to me would be you're talking
to other people and that like that is the point in it of itself but it's not an inherent that's
not an inherent good to me it is but i that's just the difference um it can be good sometimes talking
to other people sucks well okay yeah but that's because those people suck and you shouldn't be
talking to them like if you're talking to someone in the conversation is bad and you don't like that
person then you just don't talk to them well sure easy i mean definitely definitely uh
okay what have you learned i tell you know what good question i i tell you boy i tell you well
i'm waiting for my crops to grow and they will be glorious i'm gonna get pink purple radish
what are you growing you're growing radishes no i'm growing a wheat i only got wheat i only
have seeds with which to grow that sucks dude i have nae but seeds
shit i'm sorry you must be you must be pretty bummed
god this just makes me this makes me want to go and pick apples and animal crossing
i yeah i never got into that game i i played new leap right this makes me this makes me want to go
and harvest bamboo oh god there's even boo in that game it's pretty nice that's somewhat epic
i won't lie that's somewhat epic yeah you think bamboo is epic i kind of do it's an
evasive species you know um the um i've been catching uh i've caught a couple i caught a
couple of new bugs a new fit i caught a cherry salmon no one on my own had ever caught a cherry
salmon before but i got one i put it in the museum did it taste like cherry no
sad no just tasted like fish uh look at these fish right here oh those little fucking guppies
those little fucking those loaches um dude let's dude let's let's fucking talk about animal
crossing no no no this is the animal crossing cast now okay what are you doing in your video game
um i've been um you know you gotta you gotta get nook miles you gotta get miles and you trade
oh well i made um i just unlocked the recipe for like a like stone and wrought iron like a fence
so i'm gonna like i'm gonna build like a fucking sinister looking wall around like a wrought iron
fence around my house uh i'm gonna you know really fuck it up and it'll be really beautiful
and everyone will be really appreciated uh whatever you know i got my own little like
section of the island um no one should fuck with me uh it's my it's my god giving right to do with
it as i please man is the master of his domain um sick hi i'll see hi i'll see a day of small
and um i don't know that i just all what i what i really care about at the end of the day
is like getting like a cool clothes and a cool house um just like in real life just just like in
real life um that that's it that's that anyway in order to do that i just go around like you
know you have your little like in-game smartphone that tells you like what your like next goals are
that you'll win nook miles for and so it's just like oh catch five bugs oh okay uh you know plant
some seeds water some flowers and chop down some trees that's always run around doing that
get the miles traded for recipes craft said recipes repeat step step four question mark
question mark question mark step five profit profit yes yeah oh i've been raking it in i'm
almost i'm almost ready to upgrade my house oh my god i know yeah is it only one island per system
yes it is three which i was i found it annoying at first but then i started playing it's like
i actually got like a big leg up because like my roommate had already he had already found he
already started planting a bunch of like resources that i needed to craft some tools that i needed
like um he already had some stone for me to make an axe out of and he had like wood that i could
make a ladder which is like apparently he had to run around without a ladder for a while which
must have been like so annoying because it means you can't climb cliffs so like half of the island
would have been off limits to him jesus yeah um he built he built like some bridges he built he was
he's in the middle of building a ramp up like the hill that's pretty cool yeah so like i have benefited
i have benefited from his efforts and also like um it's just kind of cool like we're on the same
island like we can like um like leave shit on each other's lawns actually like a bunch of people at
my house started one uh four four different people now or all have like have set up a tent or built a
house on the island uh dwube is like up north in the mountain and he is like turning it into like
trash mountain he has like junk and like boxes and like cardboard boxes and just like life
preservers and just like shit lying out strewn all around that's what he's going for he's doing
on purpose he loves it that sounds like a beautiful place ben hey it's pretty great it's
pretty great there's a beehive right here and i really want i really want to like knock it down
and like see what happens but i'm scared what's the worst what's the worst that can happen but i'm
really fucking scared i mean couldn't you just like slay the bees yeah well sure but like who
knows how powerful those bees may be i have a feeling your diamond sword will have oh god that's a
bee there's a bee right now there's a bee right now where'd he go he was just flying around
he's right there he's right there look he's huge the the malice in his eyes his wrath is palpable
the biggest fucking bee i've ever seen all right you know what let's do this leroy jankins let's do
this you get your sword out bro oh my god this is literally they're coming they're fucking after
your ass you can take them you got this no dude no you don't understand the four you like
do you like pull a winnie the pooh just dive underwater that's how you escape from bees
oh my god the the diamond sword oh come on out of his nothing
unscathed oh my god oh no he did poison you yeah are you gonna die i know i got milk though bro i
got milk though we're good there's milk here poison milk i just like in real life sick
when are we gonna add milk to endless war um is it not already in there when are we going when
are you going to be able to milk your your your friends that gave me nothing why did i do that that
improved my life none just like knocking down a beehive in real life epic you should be able to
like we should make it like a like really robust chat system unless we're gonna add people to your
friends list and stuff you should be able to have a smartphone you gel phone yeah you already have
but you can download discord on your gel phone yeah yeah yeah and like it displays the discord
like menu but it's like in ascii yeah and updates frame by frame uh hey do you still get blaps from
endless war yeah every fucking day well i didn't get any today but um as of like yesterday yeah i was
getting blaps all the time our creations are are rising up against us i'm always getting messages
that i haven't been able to uphold my pledge to people with lots of characters and endless war
is just blapping at you we needed they're rising up in right now they're rising up in our midst
what do we do i can we do there's nothing we're powerless there's there's only absolute is there's
only sweet abyss our creations have outgrown us who would win a fight probably endless war i i don't
think there's anything that wants me to just kind of like do he's just like a cactus yeah he just
dances yeah that's that's cool that's cool though he doesn't have a single beam
or does he well make a madden we'll find out only
oh did i just he's what did he just oh he dropped beef amazing i've never imagined such a thing would
happen if i slayed a cow anything anything else happening ben anything going on do you think
do you think we're gonna survive to see another radcon do you think we're gonna see another radcon
before uh we're we're running out of dodge and the pcp crumbles like the usyrian empire and we are
all scattered across the air we always think the pcp is gonna crumble it probably never will
no i mean there have been times in the past when we like it it actually seemed like the pcp might
just like be over soon or we're everyone's gonna get sick of it i actually don't win like when when
would it hasn't happened yet um i don't think i've ever actually seriously there's ever actually
been like seriously on the table at least i've never thought so uh because there's been no reason
like like it's like it there's no reason to leave the pcp there's no reason for the pcp to end there's
no reason to not be on the pcp like there's no reason well that's how i feel that's how i feel now
yeah how i feel now i don't know um shit when was i feel like there were like not that recently
i don't know maybe it was back in like the monkey era it seemed like it seemed like man this
shit is getting like this shit is getting heated she's getting toxic maybe she like shouldn't be
here anymore really damn there were there were times but like you know i was never like on the
verge of like handing in my tenuring my resignation letter or anything um i guess it's not it's i guess
there were times i had the sense that like this this shit is not going to go on for like another
year like what are we even going to do for another year uh same thing that's oh yeah i mean the
question the answer to that is just like what we've done every year well we do every night pinky
mm-hmm um what do you think okay radcon five do you think we should do anything different
like having done radcon four and that we all agree like it went by really fast i there are two things
felt insubstantial i i think there's anything yes yes 100 i've been thinking about this i think
there are two things number one we have to force everyone they have to have like a gentleman's agreement
where your your lecture has to be like 99 done when you come or like very like you have to
like your lecture like you know that's fair i i really wish i had like i i meant to prepare mine
ahead of time but then i forgot that i had yet i had to do like the group shot art and so i spent
like the last couple days before radcon doing that otherwise i would have been like doing all the
notes and stuff for the year and i would have had it done um not yet like me and you specifically
just because we i don't know just do whatever same chances we took a long time to do like to
make the notes and do the stuff for our lectures and uh it was a lot of time wasted and it sucked
and i feel ashamed and it won't happen again uh and i i was i was doing the research for my
lecture but like i don't even know what it was it just felt like like i was i think it's because
like history it's like that's a big area where like a big thing is you don't want to be inaccurate
when you say something like you don't want to fuck up when you're saying something about a history
or else you know your ball is going to be ripped off uh so like there's a lot of like moments where
it's like i i think i can just talk off the cup about this because i think i remember it pretty
well and then like you know i i would be like well let's make sure uh and so i would spend like a
fucking hour researching just make sure i did everything correctly um uh i'm scared i'm scared
of my lecture i'm oh well actually before we get into that so number one we make sure that all of
our ideas you know our lectures and notes are taken and we're ready to like go um but also
we i want to do like a really fucking long i just want i just want to be as long as fucking i want
to be like like a month like two three weeks i want like a long rad con
um you you see want to be longer yeah i want to be longer and for us to come into it with all of
our stuff so we can just have like like days upon days to work and just to do like record stuff i
yeah longer i mean it would it makes it cost more to like stay longer but yeah i do in hindsight
i do wish it had been longer ten ten days didn't feel like enough no not at all
so do it i do so i would i would like i think that we should do it we we kind i mean we kind of
did it at the time that we did and for the length that we did because it was around when i would be
able to for school um and so i think that next time i think we should just do it next summer
and like so i'm able to come you know selfish so i can come for as long as possible i think we
should do it for like seriously like two to three weeks like i think we should do like a long like
a fucking like radcon five like sabbatical it should be like a big deal like we were at there for
like a while um at radcon five yeah yeah like how long two to three weeks man three weeks god damn
two two two three you know around around that but yeah oh a lot two weeks is a lot i mean i
guess ten days is a pretty long time two weeks is a long time well i mean it's four more days
than we were there which yeah you're right you're right just that's like that's half of a month uh
yeah but but but think about how like if we like okay next radcon we will probably have more things
like the ova like we know we'll probably have a thing like that for next radcon so if we just like
and theoretically given the more time we could get more ambitious just keep it the thing as it is but
like we could directly like have like i don't know again more stuff more obligations and stuff we
have to do so having us be there for much longer just allow for more things to promise the kick
start and more like opportunities for us to record things other than you know the two big things
we're able to do now than just like a fuck ton of lectures and streams i'm i don't know i'm
undecided on how i think about this how do you think radcon went i think i'm second guess
in myself by what by what metric by like house like i guess like i guess this could mean anything
but like how successful like do you think that we yeah that could mean well i think in terms of
like the stuff that we made it was a big success like that we made good stuff yeah do you think we
made enough you know it does like because it feels like it was over too soon i feel like
there was more we could have made but when i think back on it like it's not like we wasted a whole
lot of the time like people were working on their stuff or like doing their stuff like most of the
time so like i can't really feel like oh we could have we could have done more i do i do feel like
we made good use of the time um yeah i think the only i think the only thing was there wasn't
there wasn't enough like unstructured like downtime i mean there were streams there were casual streams
but those were like those are not the same as just like hanging out and you're kind of on during
them a little bit even the sleepy ones it's it's interesting that you say that i i feel like that's
a very unbeen same thing to say why because i feel like we've had conversations like this before
where it's like i feel like you i mean we were just saying earlier about how uh you don't have to
fake it to be on a show like i would i would imagine that you would feel like being on a stream
would be the same thing as talking to us normally no that's not what i said what i said was that
like i'm my genuine self but i do like bring extra energy to it i do kind of like you know
i do like um try and like present like a higher like energy like the most engaging version
of myself which does require some some amount of like effort this does require some mental
energy not like a lot but like it's just being on a stream is not like just hanging out in private
yeah well i definitely agree yeah oh i felt that if i'm stupid and we didn't we didn't really do a
lot of just hanging out in any like context that wasn't like on a stream we were always either
like working on getting something ready that we were planning on doing or we were or we were on
stream meaning you hung out my bedroom a lot weirdly led red con um three we just hung out yeah yeah
i feel like that's like what red con four was missing yeah well that and like coming up with
like shit that like no one had thought like like 10 paces in draw like we just came up with that
like while we were there yeah and then we just did it and i feel like that fact that it was like a
new thing that we were sort of like envisioning and then executing made it feel new and like made
the process feel like more memorable and therefore it like seems longer in memory maybe um i imagine
it's a lot of like warped like what we perceive to have been longer like you are only at red
con three for like nothing like you were there for like half of it so like it was definitely
longer like right on four was definitely like objectively longer especially for you but like
it didn't feel it didn't feel longer yeah even for me and i've said that over and over again
but it's true it's weird but it's true and it's very i i really just think it comes down to the
fact that like more of the time at red con four was like structured and being used deliberately
yeah and made it go made it makes it not really like sticking my memory very much because like i
was focused on accomplishing a specific task i don't know if this is a good dichotomy to do you
to work in but like red con three had a lot of like mid level content where there's a lot of
like sequels to shows that we were doing already um so there's like the the hippos jrpg series and
then um like you know potty cast and stuff like that at red con three there's a lot of like medium
level stuff like that where people were constantly recording like kind of just like new installments
of series but here it was like non-stop just like the highest level like lectures um kicks
our obligations like the big shit like it was not well well i mean there were um there was
mid-level stuff like there was um the digi like interviews those are cool i wish you had gotten
one i wish yeah i wish i had gotten to do one too i he had meant to do it with everyone but we
just ran out of time i mean i guess i could do one anytime if you wanted to reach out we wouldn't
have to be in person and there was like the um the weed or the two two toks in a bloke uh was a thing
i guess i would call that mid-level content what it was like low level content is like pooping on
yeah yeah yeah yeah exactly yes yeah exactly that yeah um yeah there was there was a decent
them there was i think there was a decent amount of that of the low level stuff it's it's funny that
we like have just just now like sort of invented this like category this level categorizing system
but like we know what it means yeah um do you think there was more or less of that at four than
i think i think that it was highly stratified i don't think that's right it was like very like
up to contrast redcon four where it's like a lot of low level and a lot of high level but not that
much mid-level and then redcon three was more like it like an even sort of blend yeah no you're
probably right there because like yeah maybe this is something that didn't happen as much at redcon
four was like one person would be doing one thing in one room and some other people would be doing
something else in some other room yeah like i was saying earlier yeah we kind of expected that
because like looking at the house we all we all kind of agreed that like all right so basically
there's going to be like one central main room yeah we're mostly all going to be occupying yeah
and like there's going to be less of an opportunity for like people to split up and go to like a
separate part of the house and do a separate thing because like the redcon three house was massive
it was insane do you think we used the beach enough um i think we should have done more just like
on it like you know not having it be like a big you know like i think we're fine on like beach
themed things right but i feel like we have just like been on it more maybe i mean i didn't really
i didn't really want to like just hang out on the beach for the sake of being there
mm-hmm so like i don't feel like i like missed out on the beach at all um i feel like we did
enough with it in terms of like videos that it was justified i don't know i don't know what
else we would have done i want rckcon again so badly i love that shit i love it what is this
i feel like we just did one we did one in february uh january right was it january i think it was
january mm okay you're probably right um yeah still it feels like it just happens no dude i i'm
i'm hunkering for it i'm hankering i want that i want it real bad because that's like the cool
that's like the people who show up to that are like so like such like old rck people it really
feels like i've known them for a long time so it's cool it's cool just to talk to them it is it's
really is really great like um i'm sure we've talked about this before but like after after the
lecture we all just like talked about like funny rfck stuff that happened and we were like oh we
should have talked about that in the lecture like yeah we could have talked about that in the lecture
really oh that's a great story um i'm stupid we all said in unison are we are we judging are we
judging moments oh god yeah oh no no what i don't want it do you want to do you want to push that
back uh well we'll see we'll see how tomorrow goes we have a pretty pat i'm we're doing oh i don't
know like that we're doing a muck tournament there's a muck tournament happening tomorrow
wait really yeah the muck cup is back yeah oh my god yeah uh no i had not even heard about that
and it'll be happening currently when you watch this have you watched this as it comes out and
viewer it'll be happening right now so if you're listening to this have you already missed it um
no it will be ongoing currently if you if you click on it as soon as it comes out on this episode
i mean um it'll still be ongoing uh you know one of the one of the pins i did design a pin that
was supposed to be like a muck cup batch and that's one of the pins that we could end up making if
like enough people wanted i think it would be cool but like like with everything i'm worried
about like okay but it would be cool but how many people actually want one right how is would the
cost of making it actually be justified well i mean yeah it's cool though do you know you know
the one it's like it's like a little glob of goo and it looks like the muck colors
it's a weird little bug it just like hops on my hand i have to pee real quick if you
no i have no i have to pee real quick fuck a weird little bug just hopped on my hand
it's it's like a tiny little like i guess it was like a beetle it was very small
i don't see bugs like this very often hey guys munchie here oh god hey can you hear me
yeah hey munchie how did you feel about radcon for i loved it it was great the best part was
when we did the group come that kazi requested we we listened to her and we did it yeah that was
pretty good she was real happy about it but it was mostly i was happy about it it was so messy it
was so goopy and drippy yeah i'm gonna get yelled at very unhygienic i'm gonna get yelled at
soon in about in about 10 seconds you're gonna get yelled at by me um i'm about to fly off the
handle that you would step out of your place you can't you can't let munchie know about this
you can't please i'm begging you you don't you don't know what he's capable of you don't know what he's
like oh god the tension
hi uh hey everything okay over there no uh no uh problems
well my pee is a dark crimson i think that's okay that's no that's not what i'm talking about no no
okay few what a relief yeah good another day another day another dollar ben what do you want
why are you alive right now i i want to go i want to go back what do you like what do you want
like you want you want to talk to people about socialism is that what you want you want to talk
to people about comics do you want to talk to anyone what do you want you want the world to end
or you want to want to kill everyone you want to go on a killing spree what's going on what has
been saying well um um i just want to have fun you're you're like the tender by people are like
hi i i like music i like hanging out with my friends i like to have a good time
like that's your personality no but i like having a good time i do like to have a good time
when i say it i mean it um i want to um have um fun i don't know what to tell you
you're the highest aspirations a man can hope to achieve i don't know what to tell you i want to
look at this bell huh look at this bell the only bells i'm interested are the ones from beauty
and the beast are the ones in my pocketbook and animal crossing oh my god um i want to have
a beautiful wife and children and lead accessible trad lifestyle i want to um have a um i want to
have all my material needs met you know there's that and then on top of that i just want to have
i want to be i want to be known and respected for my craft right i want to be admired for my for
my skill and for my craftsmanship and for my artistry and i want to be you know known for that
and and stuff and i want um to have um uh you know like a a life outside the house where i go out
and i meet people and i have uh interactions that are varied and uh engaging and uh not boring
you and like i don't know that's it hmm a tough equation to crack a very tough thing to acquire
a life very sad very strange it's pretty wacky huh pretty wacky i guess that you know i i guess
there's no need for like a like a greater thing than that i guess that is what everyone wants
at the end of the day just to have to talk to i feel like that's all pretty normal it's all
pretty normal hashtag relatable shit it's just it's relatable in the same way that like i love
drinking water is like a very normal like relatable thing to say that's right you know i am like i
feel like i should you know like you said before like i guess i have the sense that i should be
like socializing with people like being friends with people who like make
comics or something because like that's what i do but like i don't need to like i don't really at the
end of the day if i'm not like doing it if i'm not doing anything that's like advancing my career
with that or whatever i don't actually care if like my friends make comics or anything you're such
an enigma bin you like two sentences ago you're like i want to have like a diverse interactions
with human beings i want to go outside i want to have fun but like that's how is that not how is
that in any way in conflict with what i just said i like you want like do you okay what is what do
you want okay why do you want to have to go outside and have complex interactions with people
other than to talk with people like what in what way other is because it's what no like
i feel like i feel like we've got our wires crossed here like i definitely i yeah i do like like
meeting people and interacting with you i was just saying that it doesn't have to be i don't
care if it's like about comics oh well okay um and so like if we're talking if we're talking about
like oh you know have like friends who do comic stuff like had like be part of like a web comic
circle or whatever it's like well do i actually get anything out of it like does that actually
does does that benefit me in any way if not then like what's the point like why even focus on like
having that particular kind of like a circle you know what i mean okay i get what you mean now
but i think the the obvious answer is that is that like is that not the easiest way to acquire new
people like it maybe it's not well that's what i thought that's what i thought but it never worked
it never like got it never made any headway how hard have you tried though i don't know
how hard am i supposed to try with all your might it will make you turn red with the force of blood
you say you say that you say that like oh well how hard have you tried it's like okay well how
well how should i be trying what what what are the steps i should be following that i'm not doing
the ones we're talking about i mean okay i mean it's it's easier said than done like and you know
it may not be the best way but like you know talking to maryweather is a way to accomplish
meeting new people maybe it's not the best but that is a way you're you're gonna sit there and
you're gonna tell me that if you were in my position you would like shoot maryweather a
discord message that's like hey maryweather introduce me to some no no no no because i'm not
because i'm not insane because i'm not insane i wouldn't do that yeah that's right that's right
okay that's not like okay okay okay okay i'm using the language i'm using because it's
easiest to communicate but i'm like none of this is like you have to use maryweather to
and ends like you use a tool like i that's what you just said that's not no i did not say that you
have to use him like a tool i know that's what it may sound like but that's not what i mean like you
don't have to just use him i'm saying that if you want to make friends then maryweather has friends
maybe you want to hang out with maryweather so that you can meet new people but you don't have to
treat so cynically a part of that could just be you want to hang out with the maryweather or you
know what am i gonna what am i gonna do with maryweather well if you have nothing in common
my interactions with maryweather are just like he'll occasionally like send me a funny
hello message on twitter dm's and i'll like respond with like i'll say something to him
well i mean there there there are ways to talk to people other than waiting for them to contact
you i mean you this is what i'm saying so so you're saying that i should just like be like dm and
say hey do hey what's going on i saw that post they made their day or i follow your comic i'm
interested in you or anything like hey maryweather what's up do you want to do something maybe not
even related to what what like what do you have interest like animal like animal crossing animal
crossing how about that how about that you're literally telling me to pound the pavement
and network right now i i'm i'm telling you that you can make friends if you want to that's what
i'm saying to you right now is that you have the power to do so and i don't understand why you don't
is right i'm telling me pound the pavement okay what what what it what it okay what does that
mean exactly and just try harder you're not trying hard enough you're not working hard enough
it's not like a like a Protestant work ethic thing it's not that you aren't like
it's not i okay okay here's what i say here's here's what i am seeing right now i you say that you
want do you want you're kidding no no no hold on hold on hold on i feel like you've got the wrong
idea i feel like you are advising me as though i'm sitting here like i'm so lonely like i don't
know anyone like oh i can't i just can't i would i would i would love i would love to just have like
anyone that i could just talk to like oh if only if only i could talk to somebody
and about anything and you're like hmm well let me just pick a person that you know like why
don't you talk to this person like yeah like obviate if i wanted to do that i would just do it
but like i talk to mary whether occasionally there's nothing like there's nothing like
like there's nothing like wanting there there's like i don't need to like push that there's no
where to push that that just is what it is i don't know if i'm just being misunderstood i don't
have your misunderstanding no i i i guess i guess i'm misunderstanding you because i definitely like
okay i know that you said you don't want to meet comics people the reason why we got back on to
mary with like i don't think that he's your like way too like okay okay well okay let me repeat back
to you what i think that you want you just want to have cool people to talk to not you that you
need to talk to anyone for any amount of human substance like you need to talk to someone like
you want to have a good repertoire of friends that are nice whether or not they are comics people
is relevant is that the correct is that the situation here yeah sure sure isn't okay sounds
pretty good okay okay okay so the only reason who wouldn't want that agreed the only reason we got
back on the matter with mary whether is because uh we the idea of it would be the easiest like group
of people to communicate with because you share a thing in common but i do not think that's the only
way or like like i i didn't mean to like focus on like the mary weather angle as your like only
thing it just was one that asked you know i just i don't know i've never i've never like clicked
with another like web comics person in a way that's like oh let's like bond over the fact
that we both make a web comic or anything like that like that's just that's just never happens
and i i don't know i maybe that just says something about me uh no i mean there's nothing
like inherent about like liking the same thing as someone else that will make you like them i mean
like i was saying before that like you know i want to meet people who have the same interests
maybe that doesn't end like fadden stuff and that while it does like help like it doesn't go all the
way i don't know like okay i don't i don't think that you're doing anything wrong i don't think
that there's anything wrong happening here i don't know i guess you're right i guess you're
right that there's no like easy way to meet people and if you don't i mean that like there's not
i'm i'm i'm just like okay like like what is what is what is my ideal my ideal life my best life
i would say it differs from my current life and then i have like more and then i have like
more interactions with more people i have like a broader circle right it's not that i'm like
completely starved for like interactions entirely but like i don't know i i would want i would want
to like i would want to widen my circle but like in a in a in a natural way not in like a you're
searching for people way yeah i don't know well i mean i i don't think i don't know if anyone is
like i like searching i really hope i really god i'll be so fucking mad if this comes out and like
people listen to it and the takeaway is like oh ben's lonely oh we need to make we need to be his
friend oh guys let's let's like reach out to helping him let's go oh ben's up on his hill
he's up on his e or hill like looking up at like the sad clouds we gotta go we gotta go cheer him up
or something you know that's not i please please don't get that impression
i feel like this the way we the way we are talking about this just kind of naturally
frames me in like a in like a position of like lack and i don't even though i have like i have
like things that i feel like i could improve it's not that i'm like
totally bereft right i don't know you know you know what ben i i was misunderstanding you know i
i was bringing a lot of like my own like like what i was like i what i'm thinking about right
where like okay like i i saw that you like had a connection in like with a similar interest
and i latched on that because that's the sort of thing that i want but just because i
like him like like to me that would matter but i guess it wouldn't necessarily matter to anyone
else and so it seemed like the obvious solution of like well ben has this thing that i wish i had
so why doesn't he just do that because that's what i would do if i was in a scenario but like that
doesn't you know that doesn't mean anything that was just me that was just me coming in here but
do you want me to introduce you to mary weller no well not that specifically that idea i don't
want to i don't have any i have no beans there i don't even i've like never like heard mary
weller speak by the way i only know him as a name that you know i do not even know anything about him
there's a fire over there do you see that really do you fire up you see that yeah i see fire mountain
oh my god let's go find out what's happening over here i don't know where my home is by the way i got
lost i'm just been like traversing the minecraft world i mean whatever you don't have to go home
you just have to kill the the ender dragon yeah but i can't find where he is oh so the kkk's been
here they've been burning crosses oh must have been a lightning oh no the lava just like set trees
on fire why is there lava here that's just sometimes happens in the overworld we don't know why
um
all right what do you want munchie what's your what's your kokoro wish my kokoro wish
is i want to like i don't know i i'm of sort of two minds about it i sort of like want to like
kill myself and restart like not as like i kind of just want to like video game respond
i kind of just want to like have everything i want to like ghost like the world and like
disappear and then become like a like just like restart in a new like i want to pick up new language
and go to mexico and start up a new life um and what i and what i mean by that is as like
everything i'm doing right now just makes me sad and mad and i feel like i'm not in a good
headspace to engage with the things that i'm doing right now like being a personality and so i
want to i want to take a break from doing all of it uh like hardcore and just like stop and
not become an online man for a while and hone myself as like a human being to go train underneath the
waterfall um that's um that's not exactly what i was expecting but okay i mean i understand the whole
like not wanting to be a personality thing i get that what do you mean when you say that everything
you're doing now is making you mad what i mean what do you mean by everything what what i mean by
that is okay well you gotta understand that i have like very little of like a life especially like
i used to i was as growing one out but then quarantine happened so like right now my life
is simply that i am making things online and that i mean i sometimes play video games and yeah i am
waiting to create things and i have not stopped doing that but like all the things that i create
just kind of like bring me like sorrow like they just make things my life like i don't like it i
don't even think that's because like part of it is like the the like the inherent interactions
and like dynamic inherent with like having like a fan base and things like that which i i don't
want to seem ungrateful for but just like i don't know i've become i don't want to do that anymore
uh but like so so stuff like endless war right like i like making endless war a lot and i have a
lot of like plans and i want to do stuff with it but in certain ways like sometimes i'll come on to
endless war and i'll just be like man i want to kill myself reading reading the chat i want to kill
myself i hate what i hate living because i've read this comment in a like nurse's office or something
and i want to die now i don't want to be alive i don't know if you've noticed like i don't really
do a whole lot of that no i know and you're right and you're correct but i like i can't but i mean
that's sort of like i mean you appear as though you are farther away from this war as you do to
like the average player like people are like oh where's ben but like to me to anyone who knows you
it's obvious that you are like an endless warhead like greater than anyone you just will not stop
talking about it no matter what and you have like like this whole comic is like a huge part of your
like your personality as a human being alive on earth so it's like it's not like you left it i don't
um i just don't like i just don't okay like making endless war was cool and like i'm glad it exists
but i don't like i don't think i like engage with media in like a like an active way like i don't
know like when you talk about like being in a fandom the way you describe it is like maybe a little
different from how i would do it um like how would you describe that i was never really like when i
was in like the homestuck fandom i was never like i was never like out there like engaging and like
i wasn't like meeting people through it i wasn't like forming like connections with people i was
just like soaking up like fan creations and like reading like reddit posts and like just like reading
about it and like thinking about it all the time and maybe like drawing a thing related to it if i was
feeling really saucy that day so like endless war it's like um like i don't what i'm saying is i would
definitely be if i was like just a normal rfck head i would be i would be i would not be a gameplay
guy i'd get all i would be like all i would just only be an art guy i would only be like i wouldn't
even be like an active poster or anything i would probably just like show up having made a thing
like drop it in the chat and then like leave right um yeah that's and like that's kind of what i
i can i kind of continue that proud tradition in the way that i interact with endless war
to this day i mean i don't want to feel say like make it seem like i'm like a social butterfly
and fandom since like if like if i'm in the same like community as someone else like i know everyone
i talk to everyone or anything most of it is like lurking but like with brony stuff like
i would like be in the community i would read those reddit posts and i would know what's
happening in the show and then i'd be like okay i'm gonna draw some fan art and then i draw some
fan art people would comment like hey i like your art too you want to be friends and they would
say yes i'm also 12 and i'd be like cool let's hang out and then they would say okay and then
that's how like i i i really do see like fandom as like like an excuse to meet people which i guess
is not the the case for you i had i had i had like zero interaction with like any other bronies
before i started before tbap well i mean yeah i mean i think creation is like a central part of
this equation where it's like you are inspired to create via the fandom and that's how you meet
people is through each other's art of said thing it just it like it like it gives you a tag to
search on twitter like that's the appeal yeah um you know i think maybe for a while i thought i would
like i would i would like search like um bernie tags and stuff on twitter i would like search
like i would like follow like other accounts that have like roses in their name and stuff yeah
i was like here like um why don't i fucking make like why don't i build like a fucking good like
socialist circle of like friends or whatever but like i don't know it again like i wasn't like
i mean i would occasionally reply to people's posts but it all just it all felt very it all
felt very superficial it all felt like it wasn't really building anything um it was just like kind
of just a way to like i would just end up getting frustrated like i would just just read lots of
posts that but that may be mad like followed a bunch of people i would read their posts they
would make me mad or i would just not care and scroll by them a while back like last week i
like unfollowed a bunch of people that i had followed who were like that because like i don't
i don't need to be following this person yeah there's no actual yeah i'm not learning anything
um i'm not accomplishing anything uh so i don't know that was like another another another failure
i guess i i mean i don't want to make it seem like i it's easier like i like i tried like i
was saying before like i tried to do a sort of thing with history but like it didn't work out
i i think i i think when it's not well okay there's a thousand factors in it but like when it's
not like a show right when it's like a historical or like it's a political thing like i think that
i think that's like the cutoff point where it's like okay this is officially too big of a fandom
if you can even be called that to the point where it loses it's like luster of like diverse enough
but also like small enough where it's it's close knit enough where you can meet people and it's easy
i feel like it loses it's like cohesion as like a group like i feel like
i feel like bernie twitter is like too unwieldy of like an entity where it's like yeah i don't
think you could just like search bernie and get like people who you would be able to vibe with
i see like i see like people that i subscribe to on youtube like replying to each other's tweets
and stuff and i'm thinking like man i kind of wish i had something like that but like but why
i don't really i don't know it just seems like it seems like they're they're bonding over like
their shared beliefs which seems like as good a thing to bond over as any yeah and like but i don't
like i don't know i don't make like quippy like observational posts i just make like angry
screams when i when i like state my opinions and it's not i don't think i do it in the right way
to like get that kind of a thing of like a rapport going with people
so i don't know here's i guess that's something i'm jealous of here's like i guess like the point
of friendship for me if i wanted to like analyze it like my purely in my in my right brain lumarian
point of view is like the point is that i can have someone that we can like hang out and have fun
and number one first of all we can like you know enjoy each other but also that we're able to like
communicate and like advance each other in in well whatever way that could mean at the time
whether it be like you know we just advance an idea where it's like hey did you hear about this
yeah i heard about that here's what i think here's what i think about that i'm glad that i heard your
opinion because that's very interesting to me or it's like you know we we fucking we're gonna
draw every day and if you don't post in this discord server that i made then i'll kill you like
you know in a more like literal sort of advancement but like in some way i want to like have people
that like get it in whatever way that means and then i can talk to you about it and then continue
my further my further thought on it if you know what i mean okay i see makes makes sense i'm gonna
get a wolf please be my friend wolf you know he's my friend he's my friend oh you gave it a bone
yes oh very nice how epic is that i didn't know there were wolves in minecraft that's a that's
yeah you can make them be your dog dude are they new there no they've been around for like several
years like before it was officially released like when not like notch added dogs oh weird okay
they came around with cookies they were adding the same update that cookies were updated cool okay
um i feel like what were we saying that got us on this we were saying something about want
um what did we're talking about what we wanted to talk like
oh i mean i mean how far back are we how far back are we going i don't know i don't the whole thing
has just been a stream of consciousness it has i love the stream my consciousness is my favorite
streamer hey here's the best you you got to go pee i need to pee too i'll be back that's fine
what's up guys what do you what do you think about oh god why am i asking you what you think
about you see this is the sort of thing god okay i i come across as so fucking bad when i talk about
things like this one it's like oh i don't want to be personality haha oh having a fan base is so
bad but like i've never i should like have a podcast where i explain what i mean by that
because i don't mean like i'm like oh the though the the fucking hardships of fame is so fucking
hard you know like i don't mean like that or like i you know taking the heat is like so difficult
when you're at the level that i'm at which is to say nothing and i have like 20 fans like i don't
simply what i mean okay okay i'm gonna say it really simply i think that personality driven
shows are boring and i think that they're stuck like dumb and i think that they suck and i don't
like making them because i think that they're bad and so oh god skeleton and so what i mean when i
don't want to become like a personality is i don't want to be like a youtuber i i seem like
really hoi-du-toi-di and like oh god like you know you fucking you're selling out you're making
canton law epic simply what i mean by that is that i wish that i was making more like
stuff that i perceived to be good like you know like like a like a i just want to throw out there
like a like a comic or just like an animation or something something that felt like it wasn't the
sole appeal of it wasn't that it was just me and i want to make a thing that can stand on its own
and i because i think that that's better and that's what i mean by that audience i hope you
enjoy this intermission okay i'm back i i talk such mad shit about you been here i'm gonna
believe the audience will know about how i told them about your onion breath and your toes and
your feet yeah oh no your bunions your bunions oh my god you'll they'll know all about your mad
bunions i don't know what those are i know there's something you get on your foot they're like i think
they're like a callous sort of semi-ward i believe like a ward out of callous feet fibers
oh no it's like in your bone oh pain and stiffness in the big toe a bony bump that forms on the
joint i've got a bony bump for you of the big toe oh jeez yeah i thought it was like a ward yeah
oh god oh no the picture is like it's like a big like gray like lump in between like the your
toe bones oh god why why well okay now i know watch out for those i will i will get them as soon
as possible sir what where do you where do you want to discuss i don't know i think i think
we're winding down we've been going on for like a few hours i feel like i feel like we're winding
down i don't feel like we solved anything or arrived at any like new truths well what's there
to discover i guess i mean we're just talking about things and trying to come to a greater i mean
i i guess in a way this is sort of the ideal in my circumstance where it's just like i just want to
know what other people are thinking god the king keeps freezing i don't know why my craft is chugging
so hard on my it's like it's like i it's like i said like what's even the point like what's even
the point of having a conversation if you don't get anything out of it here's my point is i know
i'm dumping you i'm breaking up with you you're not you're not serving you're not delivering on
utility my my you're not pulling your way my end game is that i think ooh now i know ben
saint thinks about this maybe i'll be able to better accommodate him in the future now that i know this
why would you want to accommodate me because i i because you bring joy to my life and the way
to show that i appreciate that is to uh do things for you and so i say ben i'm happy we're friends
here i got you this monster like i did like 15 times at radcon four weird you did get me a bunch
weird you say reaching for the monster
i think i found home again i think i don't know this game has no volumes anymore remember when
they were like deserts in this game what are they're not deserts i mean there are but like i've
just been going through mountains and plains like over and over and over again dude where's the ender
i'm trying to find him bro it's hard it's hard okay you gotta pound the pavement i know i well
here get married weather online maybe i'll know where the other dragon you know hey maybe you
get married weather like you're welcome i can't come in contact with the nether dragon real quick
please do you hey i actually was wondering if like the nether dragon would want to be on like a podcast
i'm starting two best brothers bitch about politics actually i hear some really black
pill that takes because he's black because he's a dragon get it
can we agree on something dragons don't have fur they have scales can we agree on this
well i mean is that like is that in contention yeah mammalian dragons big contention i mean
i mean yeah i mean it wouldn't i don't i mean if i mean whatever it's a fantasy creature who
knows maybe there are like mutants that have fur i don't know i do i do feel like if it's got fur
then it's a mammal and like dragons are a reptilian it would just be like a mammal that
happens to resemble a dragon in shape yeah so yeah i guess i'm with you i guess i'm with you on that
god god no this is so terrible my dog can get hit by my own screechy scratches this is terrible
oh not the screechy scratches i know with the diamond sword but how does he feel about your
crisscrosses even worse he bowed out painfully at that oh sad we have arrived no more truths
no i didn't we haven't learned anything i didn't learn anything oh zombie well i learned that
dogs are double edged sword in Minecraft because they'll help you kill people but maybe they'll
die one day too that's what we learned today everyone that's i hope you're glad you enjoyed
though the the lesson is don't get a dog in Minecraft it'll just die and leave you bereft
it'll just suck up all your it'll just absorb all the arrows that you're shooting
sad and riddled with guilt what's his name um
didorian epic his name is dory like my favorite Nemo character
uh oh dude i caught a um i caught a dory in uh yeah in animal crossing yeah i did
it was based i got like 3000 bells for it uh i'm gonna check my oh hey wait wait no no no no no
storm before the storm we have to we are obligated by the company to mention it oh yeah that's right
um we we read it at some point um and yeah okay correct me if i'm wrong haven't i read it
before the last one yes okay and i don't think did you reread it again no okay
okay okay well there is nothing there's nothing to like talk about because you i mean there's nothing
that you found like found that interesting correct or that you really cared about that much i i thought
that what was interesting was just all the times in history where like basically just an angry mob
decided what the rules were oh yeah that's like every revolution ever that's that's the coolest
part of every revolution yeah it's just like if if like the government or like some politician like
fucked around and and found that they would find out because like either some other like
a powerful person would lead like his like clan out into the streets or just like the general
population would like fucking revolt and just like threaten murder and like to destroy to
like tear the whole fucking thing down and the government would be like uh uh uh okay uh no
actually no we were wrong uh the rules say we do this other thing so yep sorry everyone don't worry
about it and it was that's that's the biggest takeaway from it there was a top so Mike Duncan the
creator of uh that book as well as my favorite podcast series revolutions and the history of
Rome uh is is a historic or a gruffer man and he was at a top did i i want to mention that i just
happened to see someone retweet him like um i think i think just like saying lol or like laughing at
someone else's tweet saying that like um the grain doll uh was like what ended Rome or something
yeah well uh when he like extensively lines out about how that's not the case um um and it's epic
but uh so i really like his stuff and so he has a talk where he talks about this book and about
like why he made it and he made it because he like like you know he uh felt that it was analogous
in a way to like what current like political climate was and i thought it was interesting
and he sort of touches that and then on like the like the beginning of the book where he talks about
like i remember him saying that like we're not living in like the end times but like we might
be living in like the lead up to the end times yeah uh and i thought yeah i thought that was
interesting and that's that's the sort of like that's the sort of reason why i wanted i thought
it'd be a cool introductory so this was all part of my long game like we were talking about earlier
where it's like dude what have been really like storm before the storm and then he's like hey
munchie what other sort of things kind of listen to him like haha well been you see and then i would
pull out my big long list of things uh that you can watch and then we would be friends and it'd be great
but that didn't happen now that was a pipe dream yeah unfortunately but but i also thought that you
would like it because it was about you know current political stuff and and what uh societal unrest
would lead to something i did like a lot of it i just had a hard time like remembering which
person had which name yeah i mean roman names are very like everyone has like the same first name
yeah yeah it was a little bit of a challenge pumpkin this is so weird i don't this is like
a mod that used to be in the game where it's like you can see recipes now it's like a real thing
that just everyone can do i don't know if i like it um but we don't have to like my special anymore
no we don't have to talk about it for too long because i you know there's no reason to talk about
but i just want to mention it because we said the bigger need to talk about it on the podcast
last time we said like book club yeah but i just i didn't want to reuse again i read a bunch of other
books instead i read a bunch of david graver you want to talk about graver then you can talk about
graver well what which ones have you read so far i read um uh debts i read um the one that's got
like democracy in the title of the democracy movement or the democracy project or something
something like it's something like i know it's about him and the one in the wall street i know
you're talking about yeah dude i love that one was sick i don't know what you think about that one
okay that one was um it wasn't as interesting as debt no sure but it was like it was very different
it was like i felt like guilty reading it because like occupy wall street was not that long ago
but like i already had like forgotten like about it yeah it feels like ancient history
but like it like just happened and it's like feels like something that could like very easily
happen again and i kind of feel like i should have like supported it back when it was happening
yeah well so it was very like weird because okay my experience with david graver was not like like
i like i found out after like i google searched more about him that he was like apparently like
this like anarchist anthropologist i had no idea i just got him debt because i heard it was a good
book and i read it and i was like oh cool book epic um oh he's another book on honorable i'll check
it out democracy whatever okay i'll put on this apparently he's like you know like he was one of
the like the creators of occupy wall street and i was like whoa what i had no idea i had no idea
this was a thing and all like the coolest thing about this was like that shock of like dude this guy
who's smart is also like a weird like political activist that's like epic and awesome um but the
coolest part about it for me was like hearing all like the weird like practical advice and like the
blow by blows like what it's like being in one of those like occupy wall street like tent city
sort of things and like hearing about like the general assemblies about how like how do you like
run a group with like anarchist ideals that also has to have like structure in it so that it can
produce anything of merit um and it was really cool about like the structures in place for like
voting about the general assembly like there was this long die tribe like chapters long discussion
about like how do you vote do you vote by like majority or do you vote by consistency like how
do you like which do you do when do you do it and stuff like that it's like interesting cool um so
like hearing like the practical advice of like someone who i respect who's also part of this
like you know occupy wall street which like i basically didn't even like i had the vaguest
conceptions of it i knew like we are the 99 percent that's all i knew and it's like it's cool
hearing about it um because like i totally passed by totally completely yeah whoa whoa what the
fuck is that shit oh my god oh my god there's fucking scary people i don't what do you wear
over there over there's a banner you can see their banner what are they like bandits yeah they're
yes exactly oh shit you know my wolf they killed my wolf they killed my wolf that freak
you have to end you have to end him oh my god these guys are fucking terrifying i know they're
so fucking scary i hate them i can't believe you killed your dog this is this is a nightmare
you have to john wick them my god john wick no i haven't i'm too fucking scared to have
media in my brain right now um john wick is about a man getting revenge on like a gangster
organization or whatever because like they killed his dog that's awesome it is awesome it's really
good i haven't seen two or three but i hear they're good too um oh god my my wolf all i have to show
for is this ominous banner what the fuck is this cozy logic i was like it's ingredients i don't know
can i place yeah i can place it i don't know what this i don't i don't i'm i'm i'm in the
fuck out of here i don't like anything about what's going on right now you gotta bury your dog
it there's no remains he has no remains you gotta pick up his meat he didn't drop any damn it what
good is he then dude imagine if you eat your dog after he's killed he's so sick every fucking base
dude it's like a boy uh fucking dorian you know he was a good boy but like all that's left now
are these like fucking mutton mutton that he left hold on here here we're gonna we're gonna
we're gonna bury the banner so that no one may ever know what has happened here
mm goodbye cruel world i hardly knew you good job history history will must forget them
what this ever happens um it's gonna it's gonna be written down forever okay all right you all right
are we are we done here we talk about short I think we've i think we've said all we had to
say about nothing in particular cool I hope people enjoyed this for whatever reasons someone may
like something hey let's fucking amp let's bring the energy back at the end to plug the kick starter
yeah let's do we should run at the beginning maybe we should we should have done it at the
beginning maybe we should like say something to record a thing that we put at the beginning
that just is audio where we say go to the kickstarter but hey well there's a lot of things
viewers that you can do right now after this video ends you can go to right of frickers
to cop killers at twitch and we will be streaming a tournament pokemon tournament and after that
we'll be playing the endless war root of the pcb dating sim and then we'll be doing a fight between
me and ben where we wager our slime over a battle of slime tassan which will be cool and we're gonna
do it in um that one game that we're able to do it and get some logic jelly um and the entire time
well that's going on you're going to be able to donate to the kickstarter and you'll be able to
get pins you'll be able to go on launching the kickstarter today it is going to run for a month
give or take um it's going to be pretty fucking epic what do you want to do you want to end on
friday or do you want to end on the sunday i don't think it really matters that much we
we can end on sunday if you think that that will bring the most amount of people in at the end
i mean whatever i have no strong opinion about it one way or the other um what's that you want
to end like friday night yeah sure hey okay wait what is what is this thing i have on was this
always there what is this thing on the side of my why do i have that what there's an icon on the
top right of my screen do you see it on the minecraft oh what is it it's it's like the it's a
face of the guy is it because you held the banner maybe i don't know i don't know what it means and
i don't want to find out i think the banner gives you buffs but it seems like a debuff because i
read eyes bro um maybe it was too scary and it spooked you i think that was the case yes
yes so many bees out now it is fucking bees minecraft oh anyway you go to the uh i don't
know if we explain it properly like the do we not explain it properly i'm at we should
say something at the beginning yeah okay we'll explain at the beat so you'll know but just
vote you know pledge you know get a pin so that you can have a vote so that you can pledge to get
pins if you have pins and your name on the Kickstarter is not your endless war name
message us to be like oh i'm this guy we will give you a role in endless war that will let you
have access to a room where you can vote on which additional pins because like we set the goal really
low because we want to have like we're gonna have stretch goals they're like we're gonna make more
designs but we're gonna let people we're gonna let you the donors vote on like which designs we're
making that's that's the idea and so if you want to actually want to have yes and it'll be cool
and again it'll be designed by consensus and it will be epic yes so do that uh and come by
hang out on the stream and click the link and play a free text based mmorpg playable
entirely within a just for a server if you have not already done so um i hope you still like us
goodbye yeah later nerds epic i'm indian my life