Hey, welcome back to the Rowdyfuckers. It's been a while, but we're back and we're playing...
Rowdyfuckers Cop Killers!
Hey, last time we played Frog Fractions and Tadpo, a commenter. I asked if anyone would buy me Frog Fractions 2, and they did.
So, thank you, my friend. Thank you very much. And now we've got a goddamn... Wait, was it Tadpo? Oh my god.
I might look it up later and confirm that I have that name right. Anyway, this is Frog Fractions 2, but not really,
because Frog Fractions 2 is actually hidden somewhere in Glittermint and Grove.
So, this video, we're going to be Rowdyfucking... Rowdykilling some copfuckers.
Wow, I'm trying to search for the answer to the rawt of VK and Frog Fractions 2.
If we find Frog Fractions 2, then so be it.
But we can't have been oh well.
Yeah, it's really not.
We're going to call this a Frog Fractions 2, regardless if we find it or not.
Yeah, I mean, guaranteed. That's a guarantee. I knew that going into this.
Alright, I'm just going to start a new village.
What is Grythermint and Grove? What is this game?
It's a game where... Oh, Cosmic Field sounds good.
You play as a bunch of fairies. You're a bunch of fairies in a land.
And you have to build a fairy land.
And I think some trees are growing.
I actually have no idea. I tried playing this before.
I tried playing this before and I couldn't really figure it out.
I know that I need sparkles. I need to collect more sparkles.
I'm going to build a house. I'm going to build a house in this little flowery tree right there.
Is this game an epic, funny joke like Frog Fractions or is it an actual video game that just happens to have Frog Fractions 2 in it?
I think this Grythermint and Grove is an actual game that you can just play if you want to.
Oh, that's horrible.
No, no, no! My house fell out of the tree.
Here. That looks solid.
I wonder if maybe there were people out there that bought Grythermint and Grove just because it looked good
and never realized that Frog Fractions 2 lived inside of it.
If you bought Grythermint and Grove because you thought it looked good, get your fucking eyes checked and also get a lobotomy while you're at the doctor's office.
If you haven't gotten one already.
Get your shit together.
Oh, welcome to Cosmic Field. The fairies need houses to sleep and you can build them in the tree tops. Okay, done.
Maybe I'll build one more?
Sure.
Try building a sight orb so you can see farther from the wagon.
Oh my god.
I'll put it over here. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll build two. I'll put two sight orbs.
You know what? This actually looks kind of cool and I like it.
Yeah, same.
I was too hard shot at it the first day. I'm actually down.
Yeah, don't judge a book by its cover and don't judge a game by the way it looks and plays and feels.
Yeah.
I'm going to turn this...
It matters if you decide you like it or not arbitrarily based on nothing.
Yeah, it's just what you feel in your heart and your heart is a fickle mistress, as they say.
I'm going to turn you up and I'm going to turn the game volume down because it's drowning me out.
It's probably a good idea.
All this atmospheric harp music is just really cramping my style.
Hey, is it okay if Popeye's chicken sponsors, right?
Are you down with that?
Oh my god.
You're down, bro.
I'm so fucking down with that.
When I was a little kid, I always liked to have Kentucky Fried Chicken because I thought it was good.
I just like Fried Chicken but then I realized Kentucky Fried Chicken was horrible.
I've been itching for another fast food chicken place and I just didn't know that any others even fucking existed.
You know, Popeye's Chicken opened and it was a revolution.
You know, I've eaten nothing but KFC in terms of Fried Chicken.
I only ever had KFC until very recently.
One time I had Popeye's.
One time I was traveling and there just happened to be a Popeye's so I got to experience it.
I was like, oh shit, this is really good.
But then never again until both Digi and Jackie both swear by...
What's the racist one?
What's the one that hates the game?
Both Jengles?
No, no, no. The one that's Chick-fil-A.
Chick-fil-A.
I hate Chick-fil-A too, so I'm down with that part.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's why I went.
All right, so it looks like my little fairy town is growing nicely.
Now I think to find frog fractions too, I either have to go up into the sky and like grow my trees,
or I have to go down and like...
I think I have to use fireworks to explode the ground and like mine down into the earth to find frog fractions too.
I don't think that's what fireworks are used for, normally.
No, but well, who the fuck asked you?
What did you do for 4th of July speaking of fireworks?
Well, I went out and saw some fireworks.
Actually, actually, here in, well not in my town of Ackworth, but in Kennesaw,
Kennesaw, Georgia, there was like...
I heard there was going to be like a fireworks show and I heard there's going to be like some shit,
there's going to be like a party or whatever, like a block party, and we went.
Me and Jackie went and there was a big, there was like a huge fucking street festival with like a big stage show.
There was like a big old stage show and it was fucking impressive.
Did a powerful wizard come out onto the stage and show you his tricks?
Tricks with an X instead of a K and a C?
I mean, I couldn't really see the stage, I couldn't see the stage because it was just a C, it was just a C of humanity.
Yeah, same, same, it's pretty good, it's pretty good when the getting's good.
Humanity, Dark Souls, this game is the, this game really is the Dark Souls of video games.
Trying to find frog factions too, and this...
Oh wow, it's Dark Souls!
It's Dark Souls of fairies, it's the fairy of Dark Souls and you know,
I really wish that another fucking note...
Oh, I was just wishing, I was just wishing for a little speech bubble to come and tell me what to do and now here one is.
Try planting a thimbleberry bush to grow more food for winter, the more sunlight it gets, the more fruit it'll grow.
This game knows its target demographic too well, to the point it's disgusting.
Thimbleberry bush, here we go, I'll plant it right here in this nice little sunny, grassy knoll.
I actually stepped foot here and corrupted it with my seed.
Spread your seed, spreading your seed across this fairy land.
You're building too much to left, go to the right, you're gonna hit corruption that way.
I mean my goal is to go up, but yeah...
Why did I build this thimbleberry, I've already got thimbleberries, I've got so many thimbleberries,
it's just outlandish, how many thimbleberries I have.
Plant a hairy potter bush.
I only have thimbleberries, it's thimbleberry or nothing.
Go to the store and buy a hairy potter.
I have to build a store, I have to build a store before I can...
Oh, a pantry, a woodshed.
Alright, well I've got wood, I've got a bunch of wood, so I'm just gonna put a woodshed right there.
Alright, we're on track, we're on track to find frog fractions too, and we can finally get this sequel to the last rowdy fuckers cop killers gone.
We can unlock this special DLC content that we want to talk about, but we just can't because we're not on frog fractions too yet.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we're saving the good stuff, we're saving the good stuff for frog fractions too.
If we ever find it, which we might just not, so we might just not be able to get to talk about that stuff, which would be really funny, very funny.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, our content will die with us, all that potential entertainment will just go right down the drain, right down the drain of eternity.
And you know what, that's how I want it, that's what I like.
The right of fuckers cop killers is the cutting edge of petrol-
Petrol-based military accoutrements.
I do not know this guys, but the right of fuckers cop killers are people who made the petrodollar, we created it.
No, I don't have enough sparkles to build another site orb.
How do you get sparkles?
I have no idea, I have no idea how to get sparkles.
I built a woodshed, I'll build a pantry I guess, not enough wood, okay I gotta chop down, I'm gonna chop down, oh what the fuck is this?
Three extra fairies have arrived, alright sounds cool.
I'm gonna cut this tree down, there we go.
It might be like resource management, you might be building too many buildings for your current population of fairies.
It's like a Civ 5 city where you want to get all the luxury resources, but you don't have enough population to sustain those good tiles.
I don't know, I just don't know, what do fairies need, what is required for a fairies life cycle to continue?
I just don't know.
How can they suck dude, just build stuff that sucks and fucks?
How do we get, like I think they want sparkles, I think they want sparkles, but like, whence, whence cometh of the sparkles?
Not, I don't see any, I don't see any forthcoming.
Maybe if I built some fireworks and like exploded this treasure chest down here, maybe some sparkles would come out.
Wait what, crystals, okay I can get crystals, I can get food, why am I short on food, look at all the fucking berries on those trees.
I planted these thimbleberry bushes and like, they're just not taking advantage, so I'm just real disappointed.
Maybe you should click on them to harvest them yourself, or is...
Oh no, oh no I don't want to do that.
Okay, cancel, cancel.
A thimbleberry bush would like fertilizer, do I have fertilizer?
Not enough sparkles, okay, fertilizer takes...
Cast light, cast light costs food.
Reveals a fogged area like a sight ore, but only for a little...
Fireworks take sparkles, torches, torches reveal darkened areas underground, sparkle hut,
it's giving you more space to store sparkles, oh yes, oh yes that's what I want, that's what I fucking want.
Do it bro, smash that shit, smash that fucking tree.
That's gonna take all my crystal, and I might need to mine more crystal so I can build more sparkle huts.
Build crystal vault, vault gives you more...
Oh no, I should have just built a goddamn vault, should have just built a goddamn vault.
It's too late now.
Okay, that's fine, it's fine, it's all good, I don't need wood for anything else, I think I've got all the houses I need.
God, the strategy, this is the deep and involving strategy that is glittermint and grove, it's just engrossing.
Why doesn't the president of every single country just play this game to understand how government works?
It's new, it's new, and new ideas take time, new ideas take time to percolate and spread throughout the population and reach the top.
Change doesn't come from the top down, change comes from the bottom up, change comes from the bottom changing the top so that things can change from the top down.
This is the definition of a libertarian government, this game right here.
Oh, I've got so much room for sparkles now, I've got so much room for sparkles, but how do I get the sparkles?
Rules, uh, gathering, oh gatherings, what?
Okay, it won't tell me how to gather sparkles, but I can gather sparkles.
Just try everything.
Remember when, remember when all those pony guys got really mad at us last time?
We can't talk about that yet, Ben, we haven't reached frog fractions too!
Oh god, but I'm just itching, but I'm just itching, it's the most interesting thing that ever happens.
No, we'll ward off that interesting topic for when we reach frog fractions too, with how much anime I saw.
Oh, that's right, you've been at Anthrocon.
Yeah, I've been at AnthroExpo.
I've been at Bronycon, I've been all around at Bronycon.
Yeah, man.
Yeah, I bet lots of people were really mad at you about Rowdyfuckers Episode 4.
Oh my god!
I bet you were just getting lambasted left and right.
Yeah, dude, I met the president of the Brony's FNGR, he was a populist, and he split the vote, so he got the populist win landslide victory.
Yeah, naturally.
And he was like, fucking, I'm gonna play you in basketball, and he killed me in basketball.
Oh no, how embarrassing.
If you die in basketball, you have to leave Bronycon.
If you die in basketball, you die in real life.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, it did.
Why are you at Davoo's channel?
Wait, what?
Oh, I don't know, I just had Davoo's channel open.
Type in how to get to Frog Fractions 2.
I know how to get it, like, in general.
In general, it's not good enough, also, I can't see what you're typing.
Uh, no, no, see, like, I know how to reach Glitterm, or how to get to Frog Fractions 2, but I know that to do it, I need to get sparkles, and I just...
Oh, okay, here we go, here we go.
Uh, Grow High.
Oh wait, there's, oh, I didn't see that, there actually is a secret way to get to Frog Fractions 2 immediately.
Oh yeah?
Yeah, yeah, it's like, we can cheat our way there if we want.
Um, no, Grow High's calculation is not about cheating, that's what the PCP race is for.
Yeah, okay, I'm just gonna, viewers, pretend you didn't see that.
Um, okay.
Uh, invest in things that get you more sparkles, like prisms and sparkle huts.
Um, you need to be gathering other resources, wood and crystal to do this, so chop down some trees in mine for the required goods.
I got some wood for you.
Where?
I could really use it to, like, build a house out of.
It's my wood, I'm selling wood, here you go.
Yeah, you chop that yourself, you chop that yourself.
Oh my god, I can't flare it through the computer's screen, it's too tiny.
Other than, it would have worked if it was just big enough, but it's just not.
Oh noooo.
Wait, hang on, hang on, prism, oh, build a sparkly prism and a beam of light and it will turn the light into sparkles, oh okay.
Incredible.
This game is about the American economy, it's like, you know, it's, it's like, what would you call it?
It's like a movie, but, like a real movie with facts.
Yeah, like a film.
Yeah, it's like a, it's like a, it's like a, it's like a keynote, basically.
Yeah, yeah, it's a keynote, I was just gonna say.
It's real Kino. It's real. This game is a tone piece, as it is.
Yeah. Period piece.
It's a tone period piece. Wait.
Daisy Charmedew, cheerful. Yeah, that's my favorite.
Twilight Sparkle.
Utopia Petal Glow, also a good fairy.
There's Daisy again.
Blossom Gentlemeadow is my friend, personally.
Oh shit. Oh dude, I'm getting...
Okay. Yeah, I'm generating an outrageous amount of sparkles right now.
Oh shit. You're rigging the system, dude.
Oh wait, wait, wait. I need 20 sparkles? Are you fucking kidding me? Are you fucking kidding me?
Yeah, I managed to build Christ of Yours, dude.
I need... Okay, I need to get a crystal. I need to get crystal.
I think I need to mine for it.
Okay, here's what I'm gonna do.
Uh...
Okay, here's what you do.
I gotta blast it with fireworks.
Oh shit. Oh my fucking god.
Okay, I got some crystal, but not that much.
I just need more crystal so I can make more prisms so I can generate more fucking sparkles.
It's all about the sparkles, really.
Yeah.
Oh man, I'm actually really...
It's gonna be a well-oiled machine.
I'm actually really digging, glittering it and grove.
Yeah, it's actually pretty fucking sick.
I'm actually really enjoying my time with these fairies.
Oh, I kind of blew the roots off of these fucking thimbleberry bush, but it looks like it's managing just fine.
Excellent.
By the way, I do not know how long this is going to take.
It could be like a really involved process.
Oh, what's this? Oh, three extra fairies have arrived. That's fine.
Oh my god. Here, here. I'm gonna give my anime expo rant.
Yeah, yeah, please.
Like it's 3,000 views on YouTube and then it starts like a controversy.
I don't know. I don't know what's that. That's what that's like, by the way.
I don't know what it's like to start a YouTube with controversy.
No.
It would probably be insanity.
It's probably just terrible and not something that we here at the Rowdy fuckers cockpills would ever want to fuck around with.
That's just my personal assessment.
Yeah, you know. You never know.
No.
So I went to an expo with Nate and Digi.
Yeah.
And I was real jealous, by the way. I was seeing you guys' tweets.
And I was like, you know what? Like when you guys asked me if I wanted to go,
I remembered that like BronyCon was never really that good.
It was only good because we were hanging out with each other.
And then I saw, I was like, oh, no, this is dumb.
But then I saw you guys hanging out with each other and I was like, oh yeah,
BronyCon was bad except it was really good that we were hanging out with each other.
Yeah.
It all came, it all came together for me.
I put the pieces together.
Yeah.
I campaigned hard, at least hard in the sense that I sent you like two messages confirming that you didn't want to go,
which is my definition of hard.
Well, you know, I was, I mean, I still am hard up for cash,
but I was like much more hard up for cash around that time.
So like at that point it was like not even a quit.
Like even now I would be, I still don't know if I could justify an expense like that.
But like at the time it was like definitely out of the question.
Oh no, my thimbleberry bush is dying from a lack of light.
Oh my God.
What a goddamn shame.
I need more, I need more houses.
Oh fuck.
God, it's so fucking hard.
This game is just too fucking hard.
It's, it really is the dark souls of video games.
I know, no kidding, no kidding, bro.
Dude, did Tim Buckley make this because it reminds me of a video game for one reason or another?
Like a big fucking branch just fell.
A big fucking branch just fell out of those um,
just fell out of those trees and like,
can we get some of that wood please?
Can we get some of that wood please?
Actually, I'm gonna cut off this branch.
Ooh, that's a...
It behooves you to know that for literally every single day of the con,
at least once I said I wish Ben was here.
Oh, munchie.
Oh man, yeah, it makes me wish I'd gone.
Makes me wish I'd gone.
Oh man.
But you know, but you know, I'm hoping,
I'm really hoping that like, oh, look at all that wood.
I'm really hoping that we can get Radcon 3 to happen before too long.
We can talk about that in private later,
because there's like, you know, there's things going around.
I think, I think it might be sooner or later than later.
It like, it should be.
At least in great sense.
The last one was like six months ago.
Yeah.
What was there like six months between the first one and the second one?
I think so.
So like, I think it's, I mean, it was, that sounds right.
I don't know.
I think it's time.
Like, it's fucking, it's time.
It's time for, it's time for a woman, is what I'm saying.
I could talk about that on the show.
I don't know.
Do you think the other guys will mind?
If we just go like, like hard into the fucking like,
financial like, logistical like, problems of Radcon?
Um, no, I don't think so.
I mean, we want, I was just watching Davoo.
As you saw, I was watching Davoo's latest video and he was talking about how like,
just how important like full disclosure is and like, he's right.
So yeah, let's, I mean, I guess let's just fucking go into it because I'm interested
because like, you've been saying, it sounds like it was a topic of discussion at,
at, at, um, Anthro Expo and I'm, and I'm curious about it.
Uh, yeah.
So, uh, if, if, if, if you're in Nate and you're watching this and you're shaking
your head like, oh, like those fuck, those motherfuckers,
then please take us out of the PCP, please.
Yeah.
Anyway, so yeah, uh, uh, it was only day three where I brought it up to Nate or maybe
it was two, whatever.
Anyway, uh, we were talking about it and we basically just talked about how, uh, like,
the PCP headquarters is basically like, at least from the way we were talking about,
it's like almost guaranteed to be Atlanta.
That's where we all think it's going to be.
I mean, I would really like, oh, everything, shit, everything's fucking falling.
Oh, no, oh, cause it's fall.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
It just became fall.
Um, all right.
I mean, that's, that's great for me cause that's where I am.
And like, I've wanted that.
Like, I hoped that that would be the case.
Like back in the day when I was considering whether I was going to move here or not.
Like I hoped that everyone would come with me and like we would have fucking PCP headquarters
here, but it didn't seem like it was going to happen.
Uh, so like what's, what's going on with that?
What are people saying?
Uh, well, Nate's reasoning is literally just that you are lazy and probably won't want to
move.
Um, well, I mean, there's reasons not to move besides being lazy.
Sure.
Oh no, a ferry left cause there was nowhere to sleep.
I need, I need another house.
I need another house.
Prano.
Uh, but yeah.
Uh, and just like, like this wasn't like a part of the discussion, but I later found
out that like there's like a ton of fucking anime people based in Atlanta.
And I'm assuming that's going to be at least a little bit.
Uh, and I mean, I, I mean, I know there's nine own econ.
There's a ton.
There's, uh, I don't know any of their names.
There's like the wave motion camera.
Wave motion cannon.
Yeah.
And I don't know anything about him, but I've heard the name.
I, I don't know anything about them.
And I don't think I've heard the name ever, even besides the ones I just said.
There's, there's a ton of people.
A ton of people came up to us and said they're based in Atlanta.
Uh, econ's there.
Do you know who econ is?
Were you there?
Yeah.
I hung out with you.
We're like friends now, I think he's like a friend.
You and him?
Well, I think all of us were like, he's like a friend of the show now.
I mean, I saw that he, I saw that he put a video out on Nino's channel.
I know, which is, I know what did you, what did you wanted him to do?
Um, and I thought, I watched it and I thought it was fine.
We thought it was fine.
All he did is just like, we hung out a lot.
He kind of warmed his way into the, uh, hang out with us a lot, which is fine.
Yeah.
Uh, but yeah, but yeah, the point is there's a ton of people down there.
Did you say it was the best place he saw on the trip?
Did he?
Uh, well, good.
Yeah.
I mean, it is a pretty fucking cool zone.
I mean, in my humble opinion, uh, in my humble, I haven't seen it, but it's like, I don't know.
It just feels like that's where the gravitational pull is.
I just, it just feels, I'm really, I'm super, I'm super excited to hear that.
I'm super excited to hear that.
And fuck, fuck Nate.
I don't want to move because I'm lazy.
Oh yeah.
Like, like it's just a question of like, oh yeah, I would move, but I'm just, I just
don't feel like it right now.
Well, he did, he didn't mention your laziness.
I don't know if he thinks it's just because of the laziness.
Well, I mean, I am lazy.
I mean, I am lazy, but like, that's not, that's not the deciding factor here.
All right.
Sorry, Nate, if I missed this up to your point, though, I don't think I did.
Though, I'm fairly certain I didn't.
Yeah.
Me too.
Uh, yeah.
And, uh, I haven't been there, uh, I kind of, I like my home city a lot, though, like,
I'm not married to it.
It's more just like, oh man, I'm not going to be here for the first time.
That's going to be fucking crazy.
Um, I don't know.
I mean, I haven't lived, I haven't lived in my hometown for a long time and I don't
miss it, but, uh, you know, I mean, I guess everyone's deciding factor on me not
wanting to move to Atlanta.
I'm just saying that's going to be like, oh, crazy.
It's just a note.
Yeah.
Yeah, fair enough.
Come on.
Get these crystals.
Okay.
I got a few.
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
Uh, I remember Nate, like, like the last day before Nate left, we were discussing, uh,
that like the deciding, like, like the two things that we need to do in order for
ACON 3 to happen is get hippo over through any means necessary and find a good place.
Well, I think, I think we need, well, we need to find a good place.
I mean, I think ideally we would like go fund, do like some kind of fundraiser, like just
to pay for tickets, like plane tickets for everyone.
Cause like, I mean, I guess we wouldn't need to do that.
But like, I mean, I mean, monkey was saying like, who's going to pay for transport.
And like, like if it's in Atlanta, I don't need transport, but like I understand that
like for other people, it would, it would help.
So.
I think the only person that we need to fund is hippo.
Oh, yeah.
Which also is funny because I realized I'm fairly certain that this is not completely accurate,
but it was funny just to hear, uh, did you explain the car ride that like the plane ride
for hippo is around like a thousand dollars?
And that's the same amount of both ways for me to go to Radcon.
Oh, so, so you, so like you paid that much last time.
Oh God.
Well, I hope it was worth it.
It was.
Okay.
Good view.
Yeah.
Uh, I, I need to start, I need to start growing these trees vertically.
How do you do that?
Like this one is looking re, I think fertilizer.
I think fertilizer is, is how you do that.
That's not realistic.
At least I don't think.
Here we go.
Oh, there it goes.
It's getting real erect.
Oh man.
Yes.
Did you say that your house is not good for Radcon three?
My house is not big.
Like it's.
That's, that's not the problem you said.
He said it was just too open that way.
Like there was no like.
It is.
It is extremely open.
There's like, there's like one main, there's like, like there's, it's two stories, but
like both stories are like basically the same room.
And then there's like one side room.
And then there's a bedroom.
Like that's awful.
It's not, it would not be a great place for like.
Did he also said that he, we could theoretically use his house.
Or I guess his parents house now.
Um, I mean, maybe so.
But he said his parents would like still be there.
What does it mean?
There's not enough sparkles.
Oh, so I don't know what he's thinking.
But anyway, that's, I guess that's on the table.
Really?
Uh, we see you get hippo and we need to get a place.
Those are the only two things.
And, and, and Nate, you know, he has to take what is like Nate, uh, like four C's that
Radcom three will happen at least next year, like January next year, at least.
Well, that's, that's like a million years from now.
Next year is like a million years away, dude.
That's true.
That's not, that's not acceptable.
Uh, I mean, sure, but I don't know if any of us can afford it.
I mean, I, I might be able to question Mark.
Hmm.
I've just been, I've just been, I mean, I've got, I mean, I've got somewhat selfish reasons
because my greatest regret in life is that at Radcom two, I did not record another lecture.
Yes.
Did you mention this?
And like, yeah.
And like my sonnachu lecture is like so fucking big.
I mean, you know, by my standards, uh, um, my sonnachu lecture got so big relative to
everything else I've done that like I wish I, I, if I'd had two, I feel like if people
had seen that I had two videos all the time to be like, Oh, this is a thing this guy does.
But like now it's like with only one, it's like an isolated incident.
The point being is that I just, I just want to do another one.
Like I just really want to do another one.
I think it'd be good.
I think it'd be big.
I really like the first one.
And I let that opportunity slip away at Radcom two and I don't want, and I want to rectify
that.
Yeah.
I probably, I probably do one on tails gets trolled.
Funny you mentioned that.
So like, yeah.
Uh, because like at the, at the breakfast table where we were discussing how we need
hippo in the house.
Uh, I, I mentioned that you were thirsty for Radcom three and did you was like, yeah,
he just wants to get another lecture for money.
I was like, nah, dude, he just wants to see us, dude.
He was like, no, he told me that's what he wants.
Well, it's both.
I mean, I do.
I mean, I would want Radcom three regardless, but yeah, that is, that is the thing that
I was like, God damn it.
I'm, I, I fucked up Radcom two never again.
Um, yeah, it was cool.
It was real cool.
It was my fucking, it's a, like it's, it makes me mad because like, I'm in like one
or two fucking shitty discord groups for like comic people.
Yes.
I've been recognized in there.
Yeah.
I've been recognized in there not for my comics, but for my fucking son of two lecture.
Like, like, oh, you're, you're the son of two guy.
I'm like, yeah, sure.
Have it your way, buckaroo.
Damn.
But whatever.
Still.
It's, I mean, it's good.
It's good.
No, I'm not mad.
I'm not mad, bro.
Not even mad.
Not even slightly mad, bro.
That is your real name, bro.
So other than Radcom three, like immediately, just like the HQ.
Yeah.
The plan for me is the following.
The only two, like much like the Radcom three, the only two prerequisites for me, uh, moving
to Atlanta is finishing both high school and investigator.
Those are the only two things I need.
And then I will become a literal God who can do anything.
I, you know, I was just thinking about investigator the other day.
As was I.
And I thought, like, okay, you know what, I'm not going to ask about investigator because
I feel like if there's going to, if there's details forthcoming about investigator, Munchy
will share them.
And I don't want to, like, prod about it or anything.
Uh, I mean, what details do you mean?
What, what, what details did you?
Well, like, like, like how, like how, like how it's going or like, whether it's, whether
it's getting done or anything like that.
It's getting done.
Just.
Okay.
Here.
I'll go like, I haven't been trying to be like close about it.
Like, like close chest about it.
Yeah.
I just, I just haven't thought to talk about it.
The reason investigators taking so long is because I don't like writing things.
I just like to draw things.
I understand.
I agree.
I, I have so much.
I mean, it's not like, it's not that I never have a hard time drawing, but like, I always
have a hard time writing, writing, writing, like, I mean, I don't write like a script
out, but like when I go to write the dialogue into a page, like I struggle with it a lot.
And it's hard, man.
It's hard.
It's hard work.
It's hard shit.
Yeah, man.
I.
Making decisions is difficult.
Like.
I feel it.
Because the idea of investigator, the entire comic is based off of a character design.
That is what it was originally like.
I made, I made the main character one day.
Just doodling.
I was like, I should make a comic out of this.
Yeah.
Whereas in there are ideas in my head for like stories instead of like a design where
I think like if I wanted to, I could, I could make another comic if I wanted to.
And it would probably be easier because I have like a story in my head.
But I don't want to.
I want to make investigator.
But it's hard for me to like make a plot to like stick to.
So that's really all.
Because if you've ever convention, convention me, at least on a good day, then you know that
I can, I can draw very fast.
It's one of my strong suits.
Uh, so.
True.
I think drawing of investigator will take, will like be a month.
Like on ironically, it will be a month.
I, I got you.
I got you.
Uh, the only problem is figuring out, because I have, I have ideas.
I have a ton of ideas.
But how am I going to turn those ideas into words on a page?
And it's not just like the, how do I write it?
But like what plot points do I keep in?
How do I make this coherent and, you know, good?
Instead of just a loose collection of like, like, I have a ton of like, oh man, this
shot's going to be so cool.
It's going to convey this, this and this.
But like, how will I fit that scene into a comic story wise?
Um, it's hard.
Oh God.
Can I, can I cut there?
I'm scared.
I'm scared to cut in the wrong spot.
Okay.
Right there.
Cut that.
Um, yeah, dude.
Well, I mean how much, like how much of the plot do you have like hammered out?
Uh, like, I'm going to go low.
I'm going to estimate low and say like 33%.
But that doesn't account for all the like, just scenes.
Like I, I can't overestimate.
I can't underestimate, rather.
How, I will, like how many, like how much of it is inside of my brain?
Like in a sort of like goop that like is just a ton of like DNA codes of like different
scenes, all completely randomized.
And so it's like, I know more about, but what I actually have like hammered out like into
words, describe what is less.
So you've got like, so you've got like, so you've got like plot ideas, but I'm saying,
I'm like, like, is the, so like what you don't have is like the connecting tissue that like
gets you from one to the other.
Yeah, basically.
Yeah.
I understand.
Oh, I mean, fuck.
Fuck.
You could always just like go the like, go the route of like, it doesn't even have like
an overarching plot.
Like it's just like a bunch of like short, real short comics about the character.
I thought about that, but I don't want that.
I don't want to do that.
Yeah.
You want, you want it to be like a real story.
I want it to be a real boy.
Yeah.
And it's like, I, I, I don't like investigator is coming.
There's not ever a moment where I just like, I'm always thinking about investigator always.
I'm never like forgetting about it.
So I don't know if that's an issue for anyone, but yeah, don't think that I'm ever like forgetting
that an investigator exists because I'm always trying to do it.
Like, like at an expo, I was surrounded by people in a Japanese restaurant and I was
just staring off into space and I was like, hmm, this would be a pretty cool location
investigator.
Do you?
Ah, I got to get those, getting those creative juices flowing.
Yeah.
Getting that goo.
Just getting all that goo.
Getting that important slime going.
It's a, I love it.
I don't want to say any plot points because then it will be awful.
That would be the worst possible thing.
Just know I'm working on it.
It will, it will be here by 2018.
That is a deadline for myself.
And if I don't, then kick me out of the PCP.
This isn't a fucking joke.
Kick me out of the PCP.
It's not here by 2018.
I want to kill myself every day because I thought champion would be done before the
end of 2016.
And yeah, yeah, it's funny.
It's funny how much I hate myself.
Oh God.
No.
At least you don't have nose locks, dude.
I don't have nose locks weighing you down anymore.
Oh yeah.
I have, I have been, I have been drawing more the last little while and it's, it's good.
It's good.
It's good, but like, man, I got into, I got into a groove of not drawing it that much.
And now it's like, I keep like wanting to draw that same amount.
And I'm like, no, no, I can be drawing more because I've got time now.
You know what I mean?
Oh shit.
Oh no, there's nothing to eat.
Oh no.
My fairies are going to starve.
They're going to starve.
It's a fucking famine.
Uh, uh, okay.
I got to plant, I got to plant a seed.
I got to plant a seed, grow a little seed, grow a little princess, 12 new pennies.
Can't plant seeds during winter.
Oh my God.
Oh God.
No.
I've, I fucked up, Munchie.
Holy shit, dude.
I fucked up.
I can't.
I should have built a pantry.
I should have built a fucking pantry.
If I, God, God, if you can hear me, Gaia, God of fairies.
I'm not a praying man, but please convince me you're real.
If you can hear me, like if you, if you just let my fairy tribe last through the winter,
just let them, just let them.
Oh wait, wait, wait.
I know what I can do.
Maybe there might be food in these treasure chests.
I mean, it's worth a shot.
If you can let my fairy colony last through the winter, I will give myself over to the
police.
If you help our fairies through the winter, I will draw like the first like letter of
Christ in the Roman alphabet and lead my men into battle.
And if we win that battle, then I will convert to Christianity and like do all the shit that
I did.
I forgot who I'm referencing, but I, someone did that.
It's a, Munchie, it's a miracle.
That chest had food in it.
Oh my God.
Gaia fucking answered my prayer, my ardent prayer.
I'm going to convert to Christianity.
Yeah, bro.
What's in this one?
Sparkles.
All right.
That's fine.
I'll take those two.
Oh man.
Okay.
Cool.
It's a good thing I had those extra sparkles lying around to power those fireworks.
This guy is actually really fucking cool.
Yeah.
It, it actually looks like I'm going to eat those words.
I'm going to eat those negative words I had to say.
It looks like shit, but it looks cool.
Yeah.
Truly.
What do you mean not on a fucking sparkles?
You dumb ass.
You fucking dumb ass.
You damn ass.
Like how many do I goddamn need?
Oh, we need 60 now?
Oh, each shit.
Oh, each shit you fuck.
That's going to, that's not acceptable.
Whatever.
We're talking about investigator.
Oh yeah.
It's coming.
I don't think I actually need this crystal vault.
Do I?
No, I'll leave it.
Why not?
It's not, it's not hurting anybody.
Oh, I can demolish this.
I can demolish this site orb.
Did I ever, did I ever talk about anime expo or did I just talk about radcon?
You only talked about anime expo in the context of the discussion about radcon and PCP headquarters.
Yeah, I'm just going to, I'm just going to fucking like, like vent about anime expo.
Like the entire trip.
Please.
Because I really want, oh god, it fucking costs food.
Jesus.
Why the fuck would it cost food?
Yeah.
Please.
Okay.
Tell me all about anime.
The only thing I know about anime expo is that you taunted hippo with pictures of risque cosplayers and it was really great.
I called him a drool master.
It was really fun.
You called him a drool master, which is true, which is an accurate assessment.
And yeah, it just seemed like a real good time.
Yeah, here, I'll just, here, I'm just going to say all of what happened during anime expo.
I'm just going to give you the story so you can live vicariously through past me.
Yes.
Please.
So I got there.
I got there and I meet Digi.
And I have this whole speech recorded.
Here, here, hold on.
Let me read the speech that I wanted to tell Digi.
Okay.
Again on my phone.
Real quick.
Fill the radio, fill the radio with fucking shit.
All right.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
You are entering an alien world consisting only of pain.
Welcome to the new extreme.
I want you to know that it was your own doing that led you to this fate.
All the hatred and misfortune you have cast upon this realm has manifested itself into
a strange and disturbing cosmic being of dark powers.
It has come time for you to learn the true nature of those formidable demons you have unwittingly unleashed.
By the time we're done with you, you're not going to need antidepressants.
But I only got like half of it and then he just hugged me.
Well, I mean, pretty good.
Yeah.
I think the point probably got across.
Yeah, probably got across.
Message received.
Excellent.
Oh, look at all this crystal.
Look at all that crystal.
Dude, just fucking slam that shit with your fireworks, bro.
Fireworks and quotes double entendre, bro.
Here we go.
I'm going to blast it this way.
Yeah.
Damn, nigga.
It needs.
Fuck it needs.
Okay, I'm going to plant.
I'm going to plant a thimbleberry bush.
I'm going to plant a thimbleberry right there.
And then I'll put a site orb in said bush.
You know what?
I have made very little progress.
It feels good.
Like I need, it does feel good.
Like I need to be going up.
Like I know that frog, I know that frog fractions is somewhere up there in the sky, somewhere
up there among among the firmament.
The ozone.
But yeah, but like, you know, it's hard.
It's hard and it's alluding me.
It's hard growing up and nobody understands.
I know.
Fucking hell.
Whoa.
Look at, look at this twisty tree on the left there.
Look at that like pattern.
You have to get that shit, bro.
You have to get that shit.
Yeah.
I want that tree.
I want, I want it.
Okay.
I want it more than I want it life itself.
Anyway, did you take me up to his room?
And it's a great room.
Yes.
Great room.
And he just plays me gay and dead because it's didgy.
Yeah.
Because that's what he does.
And I put on my, I put on my, uh, pizza jumpsuit and he puts on his hamburger sweater.
Uh, that, that, you know, my, my old one has now been passed on to him.
By the way, did you, if you're listening, I want that swear to be like a, like an item
in home stock, like, like, like, like little cow where it just like transfers like hands,
like every so often.
And it has its like own history.
And if you do like, like, like hamburger sweater, fast forward to now, they like switches
hands a ton and it has its own adventure.
So please accidentally forget it somewhere.
Uh, you talking about your, you talking about your, you talking about your, you talking
about your burger, your burger jumper?
Yeah.
Shit.
God, what I wouldn't give.
What I wouldn't give for one night with that burger jumper.
Just one night's all I need.
Fuck yeah.
So we go out of the town, we go to a pizza place and immediately like the first place
we go, hey, can I get a picture with you didgy?
Like the first like the day before the con.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Uh, anyway, so that's great.
We meet up with Nate.
I don't think we do anything.
Oh no.
Here's what we do.
It's fucking great.
Uh, we meet up with Cider as well.
Do you know who Cider is?
Uh, Cider.
Oh, wait.
Oh yeah.
The Australian guy.
Um, I'm, oh, I see what the problem is.
I only have, dude, all my fairies left.
I only have two fucking fairies left.
Oh, that fucking famine ruined me, dude.
Great famine of 2016.
I mean, that's famine wrecked me.
Oh God.
Damn.
Got in, got in the himmel.
Got in the himmel.
Uh, yeah.
So we meet up with them and, uh, I go off to Cider to get my normal person badge.
Well, Nate and didgy try and get their super person badge.
Their uber minch badge.
Yeah.
Uh, but they can't get it for some reason.
So we go all around, walk around for a bit.
Rick are fucking the, trying to walk places because the anime place is huge and also we
had to walk to different hotels.
It was awful.
By the time, it's like two hours after we go to like this hotel, uh, the western bone
adventure and we, and we get their super person badges and due to taking so long and we being
pissed off, uh, we were allowed onto this like fucking insane, swanky, like rooftop soiree
like with like industry people and like, okay, okay, okay.
So wait, wait, wait, how did you, how did you get into this?
It was like compensation for us, like being like for them fucking up and knocking us our
badges correctly.
Oh, neat.
Yeah.
So I want, I can't paint the picture well enough.
I have a video of it on my YouTube, on my channel called a free mason eye hop party.
It gives you want a better picture.
But anyway, we walk up to the roof of this fucking beautiful hotel and there's, there's
like a cool ass fucking like, like jazz band playing Sonic, Sonic 2 music.
Uh, it is super fucking like, like high class and fancy with a ton of people like business
suits.
And like Japanese people and there's free food and beer.
And there's like these fucking like made cafe fucking like necko sugar girls have fun
neckoos just walking around being themselves.
Have fun neckoos.
Yeah.
I feel you.
And it's fucking insanity.
The food is great.
It's super high class.
I, and the view is beautiful.
We just see, we're surrounded by cool skyscrapers with a ton of like cool like vivid lights everywhere.
Hello.
Copper's going around.
Probably is Baron Trump in them.
It's fucking great.
And we got a picture with a ton of maids.
It was fantastic.
Econ just messaged me.
I think I might have seen that.
Hey, Munchy, what are you up to?
How do you feel?
What?
You know, you know, Econ doesn't strike me as the what's up, how do you feel kind of guy?
But I mean, I guess what do I know?
Sad the con is over question.
Okay.
This text, it's personal text.
Weird.
Anyway, so yeah, six more fairies have arrived.
Oh, that's just what I needed.
So that's literally incredible.
That is like the best experience the entire con.
It's fucking great.
And that was like the first day.
First day.
Yeah.
Okay.
I wish pin was there.
I wish it was great.
It was insane.
Oh, no, me too, man.
Damn it.
It would have been great.
Oh, shit.
And keep in mind, I was sneaked in because I didn't have the right badge for it.
It was supposed to be like an interesting thing.
Only Nate and DJ were supposed to be allowed in.
But I just got in.
I just, I just was allowed in because I was with them.
It was great.
It was incredible.
The best night of the entire con by far.
Besides the Gimp is better than Photoshop night, which happens later.
Gimp is not better than Photoshop.
Gimp is the worst thing that ever happened.
Dude.
I hate Gimp.
It's awful.
Ben.
Gimp can do everything Photoshop can do, but better and for free.
No.
Dude.
No, dude.
Yeah, bro.
It just, it just ain't so, dude.
It just ain't so.
Are you going to use Photoshop?
No, I don't use.
I can't use.
Actually, I hate Photoshop.
I can't use it.
I use Manga Studio.
Manga Studio can do everything Photoshop can do, but better and free if you steal it like I did.
Well, here, I'll get to that later.
Okay.
That's the first night.
And then we wake up and we go to the con.
Or also on top of the fucking swanky, like soiree.
We also got free vouchers for that hotel for free breakfast every night of the, or every
day of the fucking con.
Free breakfast.
Hot dog.
Hot fucking dog.
It was fucking insane.
Me and Nate's easily best part of the con besides the rooftop swaree and Gimp is better
than Photoshop.
So that was great.
So we go there, we get some nice grub.
It's great.
Literally every single day of the con, I got way too much on my plate and I couldn't eat
it all.
It doesn't matter because it was free and it was great.
So we go there and almost instantly re-realize this is pain.
This is a hellscape.
This is the world-
What the con itself is.
Yeah.
It's just so fucking huge dude.
It is so huge.
It's Xbox huge.
The con is Xbox huge.
Oh no.
It's not that.
In every conceivable way a person could possibly mean Xbox huge.
There's so many guests and then the con itself, like the convention center itself is huge to
support that many people.
It is a behemoth.
It is too large, it's too big to fail.
It's like a big bang.
It's like the Titanic.
Fucking hell.
Imagine you're in like a huge room and literally like you are constantly bumping shoulders with
sweaty, like either a horribly obese fat guy, a horribly anorexic skinny guy, a sexy
cosplayer or a horribly fat woman.
That's those are the four kinds.
The four kinds that are around.
Sick.
Oh I got a cosmic field has grown into a neighborhood.
Look at all these new friends.
See if you can get 20 fairies.
I need to start cutting down trees because I need to build a palace.
I need to build a fucking palace is what I need.
That's really going to bring all the fairies.
That's really going to get me some traction here in the fairy something.
I'm going to cut down this whole tree except for, oh God, there it goes.
It's fucking crazy.
Oh yeah.
Die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die.
Oh look at them.
Look at this.
I'm playing at four times speed right now.
Fuck really?
Yeah.
It was going too slow.
Because when I was waiting for fairies to get here, because they all left in the winter,
I was like, it's time to accelerate.
There we go.
Go faster.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
S bit accelerate.
My strategy now is I'm just going to grow this one tree really tall and hope that it reaches
frog fractions.
That's a good idea.
That's like, I think it's the best idea.
So yeah, that's horrible.
And we also quickly realized that all the panels are awful.
Oh, sure.
The only two that are good are both of the trigger panels because trigger is a cool anime
studio.
Yeah.
I forget if it's this day or the next day.
It's probably the next day.
I actually know it's that day.
Yeah, it's that day.
I'm pretty sure.
Maybe.
I don't know.
Fuck it.
We just hang out basically.
I don't think there's anything cool that happens on the first day, like at all.
Oh.
Okay, yeah.
We fuck around for a little bit together and then we branch off.
I see in the place how to draw manga, study with industry people.
Oh, I would have fucking gone to that.
I would have gone to that in a goddamn second.
Yeah, I think that sounds cool.
It does.
Yeah.
So I go to where it is, like 30 minutes before, no one.
Oh, cool.
So I walk up and say, hey, this is for the manga, right?
And he was like, yeah, but you have to go wait outside for it.
I am like, what?
Yeah.
I like the convention.
Okay.
Ooh.
Yeah.
Sounds good.
Promising.
Yeah.
So I go like, it's like, like outside, but like still in the convention center, technically,
it's like, not like, not like on the street, but like there's like, it lays like an, an
above ground, like bridge sort of concrete outside area, just hang out and there's, and
there's like a couple of food trucks and like the crowd.
Yeah.
That's like where all the cosplay stuff is.
Sure.
So I, I'm built, I'm building this palace.
I'm building this palace.
Not enough wood.
How much do we need?
Oh, we need 36 wood.
Okay.
I'm pretty close.
So I stand in line and I realized that this line is pretty long and I start having a glimpse
of fear in my heart that I might not be able to get in, but it doesn't matter.
And yeah, there's a little backstory here.
I brought my homesick book because I thought it would be funny if I saw Andrew Hussie at
an expo because I thought that was just like an out of like an out, like there was no way
that was going to happen.
But I left it in the hotel room.
I just like brought as a joke to say to Digi, though I don't think I, I even remembered
that was the original, the original purpose of that homesick book that I brought because
I have a book one of cause it's sick was just, yeah, I have, I wait, no, I don't have, I
have all of problems, Luth, but I don't have any of the homesick.
They're sick.
I have a commentary by Hussie on them for great.
I recommend them how many are, how many are out now three and I don't think there's gonna
be anymore.
Oh, what?
No.
Oh, I want the whole fucking thing.
Yeah, it would be great if they're, I mean, I don't, it just seems like why would he?
Yeah.
I mean, I would buy them, but I don't think anyone else.
I would.
Yeah.
But like, we're not normal.
I bought that like as like a joke, funny, huh?
So I leave it at, I leave it at the hotel.
Yeah.
So I'm sitting in line, just, you know, hanging out.
I keep in mind, he's hippo said like, go to MS, when we see a risk a cosplayer, get
a picture because I want to see Riska because I'm a fucking bitch.
I am president.
Yeah.
A degenerate.
I'm president of the Tavros fan club.
So I see like out of the corner of my eye, I see two Riska cosplayers.
I think, oh man, well, I don't really want to get out of this line, but I'll have to
make sure to flag those guys down later because I want to get for hippo and I'm really, really
debating if I should get out of line because I feel like, you know, this line isn't going
anywhere.
I'm not going to be able to get in, but I still have that sliver of a, well, I might
be able to get in.
You know, you never know.
So I wait, wait, wait, wait, is this still for the manga panel?
So for the manga panel.
Okay.
So I brush it off and say, you know, I'll try and get them later.
Then I see with them a man with big lips in a yellow shirt.
No fucking way.
Oh, I only see the side of his face and he has a fidget spinner.
Dude.
Are you kidding me?
And I say to myself, that guy looks a lot like Hussey from this angle, but I mean, there's
no way.
Just like, that's pretty funny that that guy, there's, there's, I mean, it would be ridiculous
if it were him.
So clearly it can't be.
It can't be.
Yeah.
There's no way.
Then, uh, you know, they, they, they leave.
I only see this guy from the side of his face and they don't, they walk away the risk
and all.
And okay.
Sure.
So then the line gets in.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
So, sorry.
This mystery person was hanging out with brisket cosplayers.
Lol.
Okay.
Cool.
Yeah.
Uh, it was great.
Uh, so, so yeah.
So they walk off and, uh, so I'm like, okay.
And then I stay in line and then we get like, it, it takes a long, like the panel is late.
This will become a writing theme at literally every single panel.
So I attended an expo was late by at least 15 minutes, right?
At least if not like 30.
Yeah.
Uh, so I, we, we get in the lines marching and then, uh, the line just stops, but the
staff doesn't say like it's full.
It just stops.
So we wait there again.
It's late.
It's, it's late against, it's still late by like 15 minutes.
And then I wait, uh, an additional 17 minutes.
And then the staff says, Oh, Hey, by the way, we just got word.
The, uh, the room is full.
You can't get in.
It's a, yeah.
They're closing the doors.
Yeah.
Bastards.
So we walk out, uh, keep in mind, I'm sweating as is everyone because it's fucking blistering
and we're outside and no one has any water.
So we're just sitting there fucking sweating our asses off.
So I walk away.
Yeah.
And then I see a risk of cause player, not the same one, just a one.
So I walk up to where I get a picture for, for hippo.
And then I see, I turn my, I turn my head and I see a like a confederation, a league
of Homestuck cause players, like at least 30.
Now if you're a homestuck fan, 30 homes and call players probably seems like nothing because
at cons, you know, in the hay day, there were fucking in the hay day, it was like, there
were like more homestuck than anime is exactly.
It was insanity.
But you know, I, there were a lot and they were doing a shoot.
So I got all the, I got all the risks there and it was pretty cool.
I got to see everyone.
I basically didn't like any of their cause plays, you know, really, I'm pretty, I'm
pretty picky.
That's unfortunate.
Yeah.
I would be too.
Like why fucking Homestuck Cosplay if you're not gonna, if you're not gonna fucking do
it right.
Yeah.
Bitch.
Anyway, anyway.
So, so yeah.
I began to walk away and, and I think back to that guy in the yell and I think, huh,
well, if that was Andrew Hussie, first of all, that's crazy, but I wondered if he was
here.
That would be, that would have been funny.
So I started walking away and then I see another risk of cosplay with a Tresi.
Just there, there were a couple of risk is there.
So I walk up to her and say, Hey, I can't get a picture.
And she's like, yeah, sure.
And then after I take it, she says, Hey, did you see Hussie here earlier, by the way?
And I was like, uh-huh.
Yeah.
And she's like, yeah, we got a picture.
It was hanging out here earlier, like a couple of minutes before that one, uh, manga panel.
And I was like, Oh, no, no, tragedy.
I got my Homestuck book signed.
Wait, wait, you found him?
No, no, no, no.
That's what she's saying to me.
Oh.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Fuck you, buddy.
God damn it, Munchie.
I am just, I'm just triggered as hell by this, by this tragic tale.
What a bunch of bullshit.
Fucking Hussie.
Thanks Hussie.
Thanks for everything.
First, you fucking give us this anti-climactic bullshit ending and then you don't even sign
Munchie's fucking book that he, that he brought to the anime expo to Anthro Expo for you to
sign.
It just makes me mad, man.
It just makes me feel, just makes me, just makes me wonder what it was all for.
It was, it was all for nothing.
So I miss meeting, and I later confirmed on Twitter that someone took a picture with
them and posted he was indeed having a fidget spinner and he was wearing a Minion shirt.
He would.
Anyway, so I don't meet Andrew Hussie.
And to those of you who don't know the Munchie lore, you think, okay, you didn't see one,
you know, like author, a con.
Yeah, yeah, no.
Big deal.
Yeah, that's, that's not, it's not like that.
What is my favorite piece of media ever created?
Not Kuiper Bowl.
It is my favorite piece of media ever.
And not only Homestuck.
The problem with Sooth is up in my favorites as well.
I love, I see, I'm not a fucking JoJo Brony.
I've seen all of Andrew's stuff.
I read all of his stuff.
I went through all of the Teen Special Olympics.
I've seen Wisdom of the Crown, Anna Don't Stop, all that shit.
I've seen all, inappropriate time for him.
Everything.
Ryan Quest, oh, I guess that's not that weird, but you know what I mean.
I'm a big, very big fan of Hussie.
I love him.
I model my entire life after him.
I, his work has touched me in ways that no other work has ever done before.
And I missed him because I didn't want to get out of line of the How To Draw Manga
panel.
I'm so fucking sorry, dude.
That's like the saddest thing.
That is like the saddest fucking thing.
I don't even want to draw a manga.
I want to draw Homestuck.
Yup.
That's the dream.
That's the beautiful dream.
It's not fucking fair.
My heart, my heart goes out to you, munchman.
The tragedy, the tragedy, oh, what is it?
The tragedy is indescribable.
What is it saying?
What's the Homestuck line?
The tragedy is, you know what I'm talking about?
Like the tragedy is palpable or like the tragedy is indescribable?
I think the tragedy is palpable.
I think that's it.
Yeah.
Something like that.
Some Homestuck bullshit.
By the way, I've completely lost, I've completely lost what small handle I once had on this
fucking fairy game.
No, it's just, I mean, I grew this tree as big as
it'll go, as it'll go, and I didn't find frog fractions.
I almost said Homestuck.
It's basically Homestuck.
Where is it?
Where?
I mean, you just need to go higher, I guess.
I guess I just need to go, oh, you know what, I'm going to fucking, I'm going to fertilize
this tree.
Can't fertilize dead plant, eat my fucking ass.
So that's in the first date.
Well, not at the end of the night, but we do some other stuff, doesn't matter.
So we, Donald the Second, oh, I think we meet up with Econ that day, and we just hang
out.
Donald the Second Day, we immediately go to the Yuri on Ice panel, because that panel
is, you know, Digi likes that show, and I've seen a little bit of it, seems fine.
So we go there.
And I'm just going to copy what he said, because he's the anime guy, and he explained
what was wrong with it good.
At Otacon, quote, from Digi, quote, okay, this is me, this is Digi talking, at Otacon,
there would have been a Sato Yanamoto panel, I think that's her name, the person who made
Yuri on Ice.
But basically, it was just full of fangirls, is the point, it was full of awful Fujioshis,
they were fucking weird, there was like a slideshow before the panel, and it just was
showing.
I mean, that's who I, that's the kind of person I would have, I would have naively
imagined would go to a Yuri on Ice panel.
So basically, they just scream, and the person, you know, the creator, they're like, their
mic is too far away from them, so we can't hear them.
And all of the questions are just super fucking like, what inspires you?
And then she was like, by skating.
Cool.
Good answer.
And everything she said was just like wave of fangirl screens, so it was awful.
So we leave that.
Yeah.
Actually, I think that was day one, that might have been day one, oh yeah, okay, that was
day one.
On day two, we go there, and there's like a shitty like voice actor panel, we see the,
we sit in line for the, like we sit in the room for the trigger thing, because they don't
clear rooms, so our strat was just to go to the earliest panel and then just stay in the
front row.
And it worked, worked flawlessly.
Econ stage was some C2, shot to Econ.
So we get there, we see the Fooly Cooly 2 and 3 panel.
Oh yeah, I heard that the trailers, that the Fooly Cooly 2 and 3 trailers are out, haven't
seen them, don't want, I don't want to think about them, makes me mad.
I don't know anything about anime, is my response to those panels, I don't know what
Fooly Cooly is.
Yeah.
Well, it used to be good.
Okay.
That's all you need to know, it's a thing that I used to, I would have wanted it, maybe
one time in my life I would have wanted this, but not anymore.
Yeah.
So we see that, and then we see the trigger panel, and trigger, here are the anime that
I've seen, Gurren Lagann, Kill a Kill, Panty and Stocking, The Jojo Animes But Those Don't
Count, Avan Galeon.
Noticing a trend.
Yeah.
And Popey the Reformer, that's kind of an outliner, but I just like ones.
Of course.
We all, we're all with the other ones.
I'm deep in the Juggler culture.
Anyway, so trigger is the only studio that I actually know.
I only know about Gainex and Trigger, I mean, obviously I know the names of the ones, I
know Kyoto Animation, you know, Shaft, I know the names of shit, just because I've been
around Digilaw, I know a little bit about anime, but you know, I don't give a shit about
any that's not trigger.
Yeah, of course.
I mean, who would?
I agree.
So we go to that.
It's pretty good.
Yeah.
They didn't ask three new shows.
The only, even though it was late, as, you know, the fully coolie one, and every other,
even though it was late, it was fun.
We were first, we were like, like, the trigger like posted a tweet of the crowd, and I was
literally like front and center in the photo.
Like, oh, on the official trigger Twitter, trigger Twitter.
Yeah, good.
Um, fucking cool.
Yeah, I would have gone to that.
I would have been excited for that.
Yeah, it was cool.
Although, you know what, you know what I'll say about trigger, um, uh, fuck trigger,
um, I've given up on them, they suck now because I watched Luluko and everyone told me Luluko
was really great and I watched it and I hated it.
Really?
Yeah, it was dumb.
It was boring.
The purpose was to be like a fucking mishmash of other trigger shows, but it was just a
fucking mishmash of other trigger shows.
Why did I need to watch it?
I don't know.
I just thought it was terrible.
I mean, not terrible.
Oh, well, I got through the whole thing and I was like, well, that was a waste of my
time.
Did that just say autism on your screen right now?
No, it said autism.
Okay.
It came autumn.
I thought it knew what I'm talking about.
No, no, no.
Soon.
They'll all know soon.
My plan is I want to get into anime somewhat.
Why?
Just a little bit.
So my plan is to one day just watch all Gainex and trigger shows and then only watch like
normally shit.
So I can have a cursory understanding of what's happening.
I mean, anime must be good for something, right?
Like anime must have some appeal.
Maybe.
I don't know, man.
I don't know about all that.
Yeah, I want to do that.
But anyway, we saw that.
That was pretty good.
Then we, after that, it was basically just nothing.
Like, we don't, like, here's the thing.
The con is awful.
We don't want to ever be at the con, ever.
Yeah.
Like, I had a great, years ago, I had a great time in Baltimore, the weekend of Otacon.
And I didn't go to Otacon.
And like, I was just there.
Like I was just there at the time and like saw people who were there for Otacon.
And that was like 75% of the appeal anyway.
Yeah.
Exactly.
I hate, I hate these, where, I'm just, okay, like I want to fucking, I want to fuck, I
chopped all the branches off of this fucking tree and now I can't like, I can't like ascend.
I have to fucking WV ascend this tree.
And uh, what is this, pantry?
Maybe we should just restart.
I mean,
Maybe you fucked too much about the early game.
I don't think so.
I think it's just like, it's just slow going.
Uh, I just, I just, hang on, maybe if I, maybe if I fertilize this tree a little bit, oh
it's dead.
Oh my god.
Oh no, that one's not, I mean, it says it's not dead, but it's not growing.
All right, whatever, this one, this one will grow.
This one will fucking do me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, bigger, bigger, higher, more, big tree, big tree, big tree, uh, building's
side orb.
No, I'm all out of sparkles.
I should build more prisons.
Do it Iceman.
What?
Uh.
Do it Iceman.
Do it.
I just, I know it's up there.
You know what?
Maybe I should, maybe I should be refocusing my efforts and trying to dig down to it.
But like, it's just, there's like so much shit down there, like, I don't feel safe.
Are there like enemies in this game?
No, I don't think so.
All right, you know what?
Forget the trees.
They're hard and they're finicky and they're needy and they don't like them.
They're bitches.
Um, I'm just gonna, I'm just gonna, there we go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, good.
Okay, we're going, we're going underground.
We're going down.
It's winter time.
Oh, I have no food.
Um, shit.
Fucked.
What happened to my fucking thimbleberries?
No, no, but like, why am I, why are my stores so low already?
I, I, like, I built so many pantries.
Like, I built two extra pantries.
No clue.
Okay.
We're going down.
This is gonna be tough.
This is gonna be tough and I don't think we're gonna survive.
Great.
I don't think, I don't, I don't think most of my fairies are gonna stick around through
the winter.
But that's all right.
You know what?
Only the, only the true believers.
Oh, sweet food.
Um, that'll help, like, two guys for a minute.
Yeah.
Uh, shit.
All right.
So, so most of the time we just spend, like, time in the hotel room just fucking around.
Yeah.
Oh, except we couldn't for a little while because Nate was, was, was talking, was talking
to his girlfriend.
Does he have a girlfriend?
Oh, he doesn't want to call her a girlfriend.
It's based, like, like for all intents and purposes.
Just, it's his girlfriend.
Is it someone I know?
Uh, I don't know.
I mean, it's public.
He talks about it.
So I guess I don't feel too bad.
Michelle Tobis.
Oh.
Does, do I know that person?
I don't know.
Do you?
No?
Okay.
I mean, I wondered, okay, cool.
That's news to me.
Does he, does he talk about this on his Twitter or something?
Yeah.
Well, I mean.
So I haven't been paying attention.
I mean, I'm sure he's intrigued stuff and I think he said it on a podcast or something.
I don't know.
Maybe he hasn't said it publicly.
Maybe.
I don't know.
I mean, I wouldn't, I wouldn't be surprised if this is true and I just don't know about
it, you know.
I feel like, I feel like he hasn't said it publicly.
That's believable.
But yeah, but just to clarify, he does not call her his girlfriend.
And so it's not like a first story thing.
But you know.
All right.
Like.
But it's functionally, that's what it is.
Yeah.
Functionally, that's what it is.
Okay.
Fair enough.
Yeah.
Gotcha.
Come on.
Times four.
I'm times four.
I'm times four fast forward playing.
I just, I just need, I just need to dig.
I just have to dig and just wait for winter to be over.
Oh, the fairies are leaving.
Oh, shit.
Get fucked, dude.
Like how they don't leave or die.
Or, I mean, they don't die.
They leave.
I actually might like lose this game.
You might.
Everyone might, everyone might leave because I'm out of food.
You might have to restart.
I might have to restart.
Fuck.
Oh.
I've got like shit tons of sparkles though.
Like I've got my, my sparkle game is on point.
Hmm.
Oh, wait, some more.
Oh, twinkle fancy heart came back and she brought food.
Oh my God.
What are you saying?
Well, she brought like, she brought like four food, but I mean, I'll take it.
Yeah.
It's pretty good of her.
Pretty good of her.
Twinkle, twinkle fancy bum.
Twinkle fuck.
Twinkle, twinkle fuck.
Okay.
Now we got food.
It's only a matter of time before everyone comes back.
So don't wait.
And look at these, and look at these berries.
We got these sweet berries over here on this, on this.
It's spring.
Yeah.
I uncovered this tree.
It's spring now.
Yep.
We're good.
We made it.
Hey.
Oh.
Nate, hanging out with a girlfriend was the worst part of the con, except it wasn't.
Why?
It was fine.
There was no actual problem.
Oh, damn.
Fuck.
That's not what I wanted to hear.
And it was good for him.
All right.
I don't care.
Cool.
Cool, bro.
There was that shit.
Are you on, what day are we on now?
Well, like on day three.
He met up with her.
How many days was it?
Four.
Okay.
But day four was negligible.
Negicable.
Hello.
This is Christian Weston Chandler, creator of Sonichu, the electric hedgehog poker.
Here to tell you.
Here to tell you that I am feeling good and my stress due to the trolls and internet bullies
is currently negligible.
I'm going to kill you.
Fuck.
Yeah, yeah.
That's fine.
That's good.
Actually.
So yeah, just a ton of shit happens.
We go to a Japanese restaurant.
I think about investigator and how cool it is.
Oh, you met up with Sai.
No.
Cider.
You know I hate Sai, right?
I don't know how anyone feels about Sai anymore.
I mean, I hear people saying they love Sai.
I hear people saying they hate Sai.
I don't know how much of this is real.
How much of this is just some kind of Truman show Eskipa Sai.
I fucking hate Sai so much.
I see.
So much.
What did he do?
He's literally the worst PCP fan.
He's so fucking bad, dude.
I mean, he's a good boy.
He's so fucking bad.
He does his best.
Oh, a hexacomb seed.
I don't know what that is, but it's exciting.
Frog fractions, where you'll be, I'll go.
Where you'll be, I'll find you.
Yeah.
We met up with Cider.
I would never talk to Sai ever.
Earlier today, Jesse and Digi and Nate and Monkey all recorded a thing about Monkey's
book, and Monkey wanted to bring Sai on, but me and Jesse just would not allow it.
We just wouldn't let that happen.
Monkey is a big Sai supporter for whatever reason.
Yeah, it's awful.
There's something going on there, if you know what I mean.
You know what I'm saying.
It seems a little...
Sai?
More like, oral cum shot on my right, bros.
Yeah, bro.
Sai fucked.
That's the opposite.
He's a sexy man with a girlfriend.
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
I want to meet Sai's girlfriend so I can ask why.
What's wrong with Sai?
Observe his actions.
Observe him.
Observe his habitat the way he is, the way he acts, the things that he say.
Observe him do.
I won't, but I'll take your word for it, I guess.
Everything about him is a perfect storm of horrible things.
He is the alpha and the omega of horrible actions.
He is awful.
Observe.
He has no redeeming qualities.
I mean, he is what he is, you know?
He is what he is, and no more and no less.
He's less than the sum of his parts.
Jesus Christ.
He doesn't deserve to exist.
I mean, I see it.
I see it.
He's the light on reality.
He's the lord agents of our session.
Terrible.
Terrible at Pokemon.
Just an embarrassment.
So bad.
Please let him in.
And him now.
Before.
Before the charade can go on any longer.
Listen, Maiden, listen to this.
I'm sorry, dude.
I don't, I mean, I would say I don't have anything against you, personally, but I do.
I really don't ever want to see you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sure, I'm sure you're you're like nice to hang out with in-person, but please never
talk to me or any one that I know I never wanted to see you or your name ever
mentioned ever again please monkey monkey is like pushing the side he's like
pushing the side agenda hard I know he's been he's been consistent about it for
like god it's got to be months now sorry I'm sorry sigh I I'm just I just I can't
I can't I don't have any sympathy it just can't do this anymore I just can't do it
anymore I just can't sit by and watch you exist I can't let you do this to the
planet we've got it we've got to take a hard line stance we've got to take a
hard line God I'm so fucking frustrated with this goddamn game frog fractions to
it's the worst game in the world because you can't even fucking play the
site okay the second method for finding frog fractions to is to do okay
everyone ignore that that bottom part is to dig down as low as you can go with
fireworks fireworks are a magic spell yeah yeah you prioritize gathering
sparkles you need a lot more wood resist the temptation to chop down all
your excess trees immediately just keep digging down deeper and deeper until
you when I've the door okay that's that's the plan oh ho hoochie mama hi hi
chihuahua anyway I just want to play I just want to play this game that someone
else paid their money for you know what I'm saying yeah I'm trying to think is
there anything cool ever ever happened in an expo oh I sincerely doubted the
breakfast place we would do that we got free breakfast every single day we got
this like like little humble like Italian guy he was like he was like going
on he's used late in his years but not like like old-old he was just you know
an experienced older short Italian man who was really humbles like please sir
let me get you your orange juice please I love to serve it I am a follower and I
am not a leader I will do whatever you're bidding desires I will bring you exotic
gyms and fruits please sir let's let me let me wipe the shit from your eyebrow
please was it what kind of restaurant was this at it was like an in-hotel like
constantly like buffet restaurant oh he was a hotel waiter those are those are
a special breed no no oh my god I found it oh shit oh my god is that it I
think that's it dude anyway that looks like it was cool the last day we look
with econ and I know we live a bunch of fireworks in a place in a cop saw so we
almost went to jail why because of fireworks um oh yeah that's right oh
that's right it was fireworks day yeah it was national fireworks day I forgot
yeah oh the last day we just hung out with anime youtubers and I said nothing yeah
that's what I mean that's what I you know when me and when me and digi and
divu were hanging out with like econ and nino and Jackie was there and like you
know they were fine guys but like they just talked about anime the whole yeah
yeah and I was just like okay have have fun have fun bye yeah like I think I
like I think I ended up leaving early cuz like you know you guys are cool and
all digi you're in divu you're my you're my bro but I don't want to fucking
talk about your anime YouTube channel anymore I'm going home I like you know
if there's like econ is cool because he knows about history and we talked about
history for a while that was pretty cool I didn't get to talk to econ like at all
because again he was just fucking talking to digi about fucking anime
YouTube being and like so whatever he seemed like a pretty decent guy yeah I
don't know how come you see he seems alright yeah you're talking about history
that was great I'm on a history guide so was he what kind of history world
history civil war history no history of racism in America oh that's the only
one that I just like racism history yeah yeah I majored in racism please let it
be true I can't think is there anything we've already seen your dad live in an
outburger oh hey what happened to um what happened to the Arby's stealing your
dad oh did you not watch the Carl's Jr. one I did not watch it all the way
through the beginning part it told what happened about Arby's oh okay maybe I
didn't watch it at all okay anyway do you should I should I just go watch it or
do you want to give me the yeah no yeah I'll tell you basically just just digi
either like he just did not send me the audio for Arby's and by the time I got
around to it he deleted off his computer so there was just no way oh what a
fucking asshole god damn it that was good that was good shit no did you know
asked for it earlier because it was like two weeks afterwards so I don't blame
him I would have been sent oh fair enough I guess bummer yeah bummer oh well
okay okay Carl's Jr. was good yeah it was a good time yeah you want you want to
do another one soon yeah let's do another one cool we'll have to find ones like we
both have Burger King I know fan that wants to do that with me who fan oh okay
so well there's a burger there's Burger Kings around here yeah all right yeah
yeah yeah I guess I could organize that yeah oh oh you know would actually be
really great I don't know if you have them around there but waffle house no I
don't okay well I don't even think I do I don't even I don't even know if you can
like get takeout from waffle house but like surely they're not gonna say no if
you want to be like I'll just get my food and leave yeah yeah yeah I would I would
do I would do waffle house um um sweet yeah sick brown things are any oh yeah
there's one other story I want to tell yeah I might think about okay you love
ones at the trigger panel I'm sitting there and I you know I've watched a
couple trigger shows but the main thing is that you know there was that one
super humorous episode that was edited or not edited like animated by a guy from
trigger so I looked up I was I was wait wait which which which episode mindful
education is that the one with the they fight they fight in a lot of ones no the
one where Steven and and amethyst no that's called and that's called see when
you use animus and with this oh yeah it's fair enough that's the one where they
sing that like Connie like fucking almost killed a guy for no reason oh is
that the one with the song that's like yeah yeah yeah okay I remember yeah
anyway that you tell me that was the only episode there's even worse that looks
good right yeah guys it really looks like shit it's so bad sometimes it's real
bad and that's just a damn shame yeah so I was talking about that and that's
that's I just want to see that guy just like look at him and gaze upon his his
his visage yeah something I want to do so I look I look up his name you know I
confirm that he's gonna be here and I all I want to do is see you turn into a
giant woman hey Steven anyway and I have my hamburger backpack with me I'm
pretty sure I'm in the senior Union University cosplay fairly certain and you
know I'm just thinking like yeah I can't wait to see like I basically just
started thinking about Steven Universe and how I like Steven Universe more than
I like anime and I don't know why yeah yeah yeah that was basically what I was
thinking about and I like I was just I was just waiting for the panel to go on
and then I'm just I'm just sitting there I'm just sitting there in my in my
chair unaware of the current event that the events in the near future that
will leave me wanting to kill myself so I'm just sitting there I'm looking up
the panel and then I see a guy like a guy just like come up to a guy that's
kind of like in front of me a little bit and just start talking he's like so
they're gonna be on soon right and he was like yeah yeah they're gonna be on
soon all right yeah I'm gonna go back I'm gonna go talk to Rebecca and then I
look up I look up and I fucking see Ian Jones QWERTY just there who's that
guy co-creator Steven Universe oh yeah okay I just see him I have seen him
before okay he's just there alright in front directly like less than a foot in
front of me huh just standing there just talking to a guy need turning around to
go back and and since I'm so like discombobulated I I like actually like
ask are are you and then like like by the time he's walking away and then like
like I like do the angle he like he turned back his head just a little bit
he smiles slyly look like doesn't turn he doesn't turn back just answer anything
he just looks at me slyly and like we make eye contact so he knows that I saw
him he just smiles and then like jets the fuck out of there what is what was his
purpose just just like no if fucking trigger was there I guess I saw Ian Jones
QWERTY and I didn't get a picture with him along with answer Hussey oh god what
a fucking what a fucking shit show man fuck fuck cons fuck all cons except rad
con yeah so he goes back and I don't see him and I'm just fucking in awe I'm an
ecstasy wait so he was just there for the trigger panel
sweet they're like good friends wait wait oh I was gonna ask like was he there
for like a reason or was he just there for the con no okay there was another
trigger panel that was like watch the guys draw which was not as informational as I
would have liked like like yeah because like they just drew but the thing is is
that they are they like they're too good at drawing for me to get any
information like they're just so high level that I like I can't implement
anything it's just like like been they they only do line art they just start
with the line art they don't do rough sketches they don't do rough sketches
yeah yeah jealous yeah so there's something I could get some people but
but the guy who did Steven Universe episode really just drew Steven Universe
fan art at the end of panel is like hey yeah Rebecca if you're watching please
let me on your show again please I really I really want to be in Steven
Universe again please wait who said that I did mindful education oh oh oh oh in
the thing nice man it's so nice it's so nice when the Japanese appreciate
Western culture makes me feel makes me feel warm and fuzzy and proud to be an
American or a Canadian or whatever Steven Universe is from I don't say
squares and I don't brag and I don't I don't cuss and my pants don't sag proud
to be in America be an American Jesus Christ is my nigga let his light shine
through you he's the sun let his love pop a cap in your butt and say hallelujah
video oh oh oh that video oh that video oh my god better than anime oh my oh my
word oh by my by a mile oh oh oh and and and so okay separate I'm gonna catch
you up to the memes of an expo okay yeah yeah I'm sure I will appreciate that
and I'm sure that our listeners will yeah yeah so so here are the new memes
guys we're not like these will probably be I mean I'm always Jones and for some
hot new exactly some fresh new memes this will probably be introduced more
more like you know naturally into other you know PCP podcast but just just ahead
of time here are the new memes whenever you see something funny or you want to
something just say say something really fucking funny really fucking funny
that's that's that's a new meme all right all right noted noting it down in my
little meme book here's the second one when you wouldn't when you hate someone
you say you must kill that judge your brother me I will get my spanky'll that
judge your brother he said if that's right if you hate Jojo Bronies okay what's
a Jojo Bronie Jojo Bronie is a fan of Jojo who's only seen the anime oh that's
me that's me yeah although I don't even care that much about it so I don't know
if I like I don't know if I like Jojo enough to be considered a Jojo Bronie
yeah yeah you might not I'm just I'm just I'm just kind of casually like yeah
it's good oh oh dropping some shit I'm gonna chop this fucking tree right the
fuck down it's gonna be dramatic holy shit dude lifts huge branches gonna come
down look at him go look at him go look at him go fucking come on dude oh god
oh I'm Jones and for it I'm Jones and also it might send those houses like
fucking flying cuz this tree is under a lot of strain oh well that was a bit a
bit anticlimactic yeah yeah but hey oh you did it I did it whatever it is
here's hi and here's the final meme the best name of the entire convention so
they're take at the trigger like live drawing panel they're taking questions
and they're going around I'm like what like like hey so what program do you
because I because I think that the program's actually matter and I don't
want to actually get any skills I just want to like get the the program that
the people are using wait was this that was this at the trigger panel asking what
like what program do you draw in pitiful pitiful awful I say that even though I
literally I draw in Photoshop mostly because Andrew Hussie drives in
Photoshop but don't worry about that yeah yeah but like but like you go to a
fucking panel and you think that like the best information you can get out of
these people is what program do you draw in like just go home just like just go
go fucking yeah leave and so and so they go around and then there's you know like
I use I use Photoshop I use I use you know whatever and then yeah and this this
is not going to be funny for you this this will not have a community good
timing or like any sort of relevance whatsoever but nice but I lean over to
Nate and I say in a Japanese accent oh I use I use a gimp because it's free and
we can do anything foreshad can do but is better and for free okay that that's
it that that is the that that's the meme and okay that that like we we literally
cannot stop laughing for like 20 minutes afterwards loudly in the middle of
like a mostly quiet panel and like there's like a guy that like in front of
us just says hey I know you're not enjoying this penalty please be quite
for people who are enjoying it and like we try and supple we just can't we can't
stop laughing about I know you're not enjoying this panel how did he know it
seemed like you guys were having a great time yeah they get another question so
you guys work for Pixar what was that like and then I lean over and say they
made the fun of us for using gimp even though they are just Photoshop loyalists
they're wasting their money for gimp can do anything for sure can do but the
better and for free oh man I wish I'd been there it would have been great so
yeah we go home her to the hotel and literally from like 11 no let me from
like 12 to 2 in the morning we stay in bed with the lights out trying to go to
sleep but we can't stop making gimp jokes but how great gimp is about how
like like immaculate of a program it is and how we're gonna install Linux and
like get gimp to get the most like pure open software experience of all time and
how photoshop is a piece of shit it's only for industry loyalists and then how
gimp is like like like the populist vote and it's gonna like like change the it's
like it's like the Bernie Sanders of drawing programs yeah free open source
knew everything I'm gonna do but better and for free there's no point in not
ever and for yeah well sure I mean even even if it can't send our text if you
learn how to center it yourself that's better because you get the experience you
get the industry knowledge yeah yeah it's it's like I mean I mean using gimp
is like it's like wearing the master Roshi turtle shell when you train like
you just become a better warrior yeah yeah and it's for free it's for free so
yeah there's no so so what's your excuse what's your what's your excuse you
in you photoshop industry loyalists cut you fucking globalists that's what the
only people who like photoshop are globalists fact yeah it sounds it sounds
right that sounds true to my it must be I mean you know there's no there's no
news like all news is biased so you just have to you just have to believe what
sounds true yeah exactly so that's great oh I got a dripple tree yeah I'll do
that I'll play this dream tree I'm trying to think there's anything else it's even
like worth mentioning all right now I'll be caught up now I'll be caught up and
when Nate tries to trip me up with a meme that I'm not familiar with on the
next PCP I'll counter I'll counter with a devastating counter attack I'll
parry it and just send him flying just send him flying right over the edge and
into the pool of lava under perfect beautiful incredible I think that's
the only thing of like it like like we'd be hanging around LA we kind of just
walk around we just fuck around a little bit it's cool I don't know it was
just fun it was a lot of fun it was it was a great time I should I explore a
lot but I it was a great experience I'm glad we did it and I made me feel
something didgy you know he hates an expo a lot but you know it was great it
was great experience I'm glad I got it hanging with my handboys it was
fantastic oh my handboys oh man you know sometimes sometimes I miss my handboys
yeah can't wait for Redcon 3 hashtag fund it guys or just or maybe just
fucking maybe someone god I mean if anyone if anyone wanted to if any PCP
members wanted to come out to Atlanta and be put up and be put up for like a
while and just like fucking stay in my guest bedroom that would be great too
and oh man I would honestly be fine with like not like recording anything at a
Redcon I mean I know that's like the point of it I guess yeah like I agree
it's not the it's not the point for me neither like the point for me is not
that like oh a shit time I mean yeah I'll make let's play like that's like
that's fun well you don't need to plead with a weeb or anything no god
heaven forbid yeah heaven so yeah I'd be fine just going and I see in text you
should just like come down here to hang out with me that'd be cool I I would I
would if I I mean if I could do it like for no money I would love I would
fucking like if someone were like if someone were like hey Ben I'm just like
flying in my private jet over to Munchies place you want to pop down with me
for a bit I'd be like hell hell yeah hell yeah dude yeah guys press one in
chat if you would find Radcon 3 press one in chat yeah and if you don't press
one get the fuck out of here what the fuck do we need you for yeah not much not
much honestly yeah so that was great it was a lot of fun pretty good wait we
had a hard everyone's talking about their girlfriend situation was pretty
funny oh man I miss I miss standing out on Digi's back porch and just fucking
talking about girlfriends yeah or the lack there or the lack there oh good
times good time do do do do do do do pretty good yeah yeah like like the
best part of radicons in well you know a great part of it that I sorely miss
that I guess yeah replicated in over the internet but it wouldn't feel the same
it's just talking about like real shit like real shit bro you know yeah I mean
that's what that's what friends do right you sit around and talk about real
shit yeah and yeah you know like being in the PCP being in the PCP like all the
PCP guys are like my good friends and compatriots and stuff but you know it's
outside of Radcon we don't get to like hang out and and and just fucking be like
IRL friends very much which is a little sad and getting sad thinking yeah I mean
and even like it's just not in our nature I don't think to like just call
each other no it's really not like like I really am like sometimes I feel bad
like sometimes I feel guilty sometimes I feel bad like I never just like I never
just like I don't know like Skype munchy or hippo right it would be like how are
things going but then like I mean none of us do it like none of us do that I we
just kind of we just kind of like passively like no that one another are
like allies yeah and can be called upon in times apparel it were a league I mean
yeah I mean my friend Ethan do you know who that is he's like even cartoons
Ethan cartoons no that's a good guy anyway it doesn't matter like like he is the
only guy who I still like play video games with yeah like a relica like an
like an ancient relic like yeah I like it's not even that much anymore which is
a shame I really enjoy it like sometimes if the mood is just right I will like
play a video game with someone and I can imagine that's not what any of you do
and it's not like I even do it a lot I do like maybe once a week at the very
most I mean I pop into Pokemon showdown every once in a while but I don't that
doesn't feel like playing video games that's just like a thing other than that
like yeah I never like I almost never play video games like once in a blue
moon I'll like try out some new game that I saw on state on sale on steam or
something well I meant that I will like we'll get into like a Skype call and
like like talk to each other and play a game you know you know what used to be
like that is me every now and then mage used to like message me on Skype and
ask me if I wanted to watch anime with her and every now and then I would do
yeah yeah that used to happen like god I want that that used to happen like a
bunch but I don't know me and mage haven't I mean it's not even not just mage
but like ever like everyone but yeah we haven't we haven't done that in a while
should we I mean that's something we should do I mean it was it was fun
once in a while like pretty often I'd be like cuz like you know I don't actually
really yeah we're busy guys and like frankly you know we don't really care
that much about anime so it was just so so I wasn't doing it like for the
anime I was just I was just doing it I would just do it for like you know
friends actually you know what back in the day me and mage had a couple of like
real heart-to-hearts and God man it's been forever yeah that was like that was
like two or three years ago that seems like I barely sometimes I forget that
even happened but it totally did yeah I think last time I did that over the
internet was like four frog fractions one like yeah me too like after our
fractions over we continue to talk shit but about different people yeah we talked
a lot of shit that day it was great I had a lot of fun doing that that was
fantastic yeah me too and I've kind of I've been I've been missing it actually
like that's I mean one I just I just love the ratty fuckers cop killers brand
and want to contribute to it in any way that I can but also it was yeah yeah it
was magical and here we are and here we are finally back how many it's been like
two months or more something like that yeah that's yeah we yeah I want to get
we want to make more make more ratty fuckers hang out with my my boy Munchie
it didn't get didn't get to hang out with you at anime expo and that's real
sad but whatever we can we can make up for it would it be on the internet like
cost-effective at all to like not just me you like in general for like for any of
us to meet halfway would that be worth it like at all like like in Texas
somewhere or something I think that probably it's cheaper like for no I
think probably it's cheaper like I mean but for two people it's probably cheaper
for like one person to travel and the two of them to split the ticket costs
meeting in the middle is it's a nice idea I don't think I don't know how much
it would actually say yeah I don't think it would but I figured you know I might
as well ask yeah I just I do I want it I want so bad I just want to do me too
yeah I mean I think I think we could I mean you're talking about are you talking
about Radcon 3 or are you talking about anything Radcon anything you know one
one whatever anything you know monkey was monkey was bummed when it was
discussed that like we were all gonna move out of Digi house because well at
the time it seemed like we were gonna move to Austin Texas and he was like
well don't do that because right now you're only like a couple hours away
for me and if you move to Austin you'll be like six hours away from me because
at the because at Digi's house it was like a long but not an unreasonably
long drive like for him to just come visit but now it's like even worse now
it's now it's we're all just like scattered to the winds and there is no
fucking PCPHQ there is none anymore yeah like I guess Digi is is Digi just
going back to his parents no where is he moving to Rochester with his girlfriend
oh I didn't fucking know that yeah maybe if maybe if I fucking maybe if I talk
to my friends a couple times in a once in a while I didn't know Nate had a
girlfriend didn't know fucking Digi's moving to Rochester I'm so fucking out
of the loop yeah we I like on one hand we all are busy we all don't have time to
just fuck around and play video games the same yeah we all aren't that big we
do like I'm sure we have the time to just talk it every once in a while like
not every day I mean like we've got the PCP but the PCP isn't really hanging out
it's not the PCP is it's great I love it as a vehicle to podcast and to hang out
like it is nice to talk to people that way but yeah like we can't we can't do
the real shit there because it's very first couple is the only place where we
get real real shit yeah yeah we don't we can't we can't you know cuz we're
all on we're all on on the PCP we're all like being as as we're all going at it
real hard we're all jousting it's all jousts of words yeah and a clash of
ideologies your weird utilitarianism versus being good yeah yeah yeah being a
real person being being a human
hang on I gotta take a I gotta take a long slow sip of my mio energy nice by
the way shout out to Nate yeah when I was a when I was a wee boy like just
watching the PCP or yeah like wait you knew us before the PCP yes okay okay
we'll go on sorry yeah yeah all right like I always like kind of knew at least
I thought I knew who I would have like chemistry with and who I wouldn't like I
knew from the first burning con that me and you were good and I knew me and did
you were good and I thought you know I can get along with hippo and a few
people but I me and Nate are like great together we we are we have great
chemistry together and I knew before in an expo and like I knew that at radcon
and ever and ever since then everything we've been in has been really great I
really really enjoy Nate so shout out to Nate I love him a lot me and Nate you
know like ever we still we still have like no plans to fucking hashtag max
revive tbap and do a ben and Nate thing because like tbap was founded on the
ben and Nate chemistry and it has like it has never never again has it been
capitalized upon or used for fucking anything and it's fucking sad yeah maybe
if maybe if fucking wee PCP years like fucking took the time out of our days to
talk to each other maybe we could maybe we maybe things could happen you know
maybe this you know this isn't even like a group-wide PCP thing this is like
this this is like maybe and bitter but like I'm I'm I don't know man like hit
like hippo like hippo and Jesse have the have the have their podcast their
their pony cast like hippo and Nate have the have the po-d cast and like
monkey and Digi have the whatever and I'm like man and I'm like man you know
like it's not really like this but it feels sometimes like everyone else is
doing all this is doing all this interesting stuff on the side and I'm
just stuck on the sidelines but then I remember that like no not really everyone
else is pretty much only has like one or maybe two things going on and like I've
got the I've got ready fuckers cop killers I've got I've got ready fuckers
cop killers I've just let it lie fallow for like two months because I don't know
why so let's not do that yeah yeah ever since I was crowned chancellor of the
PCB draw cast I've I've been coming with plans for like a schedule for the
draw cast oh god yes more draw cast I would do a draw cast like at least once
a month that's my plan once a month yeah a draw cast once a month and rowdy
fuckers cop killers like twice a month you want twice a month I'm down twice a
month are you down I thought we talked yeah I thought like once a month would
be like the bare minimum yeah okay yeah I'm down with that okay cool I mean I I
do love right fuckers cop killers we do need because I hate the green PCP one
not that I was aesthetically bad but just that it is the PCP I mean we're
like I mean different guys completely different yeah no really there's no
relation to the to the Ben St. and Munchie of PCP fame
different universes this is us this is us unfiltered unfiltered I just I mean raw
I just use the I just use the green was was rowdy fuckers cop killers the first
show to use like a palette swap yes okay well it seemed like a good idea at the
time it was but then but then it became never but then the convention became
adopted that like other shows got their own color palettes and yeah this is this
is not this is not like a draw cast which is just the PCP but withdrawing
this is this is the real shit this is the raw shit you know and I don't think
any of us thought that it would like I had no idea in my mind that I would ever
even be on the PCP channel again after the recording the reference cop killers
oh that's right that was before you were on the PCP I forgot about that okay yeah
me after that recording what he'd never that was like the first time you guys
talked right yeah I think I think he was just kind of baffled I think he was
just kind of like what do I even say to all this it was good um yeah a rowdy
fuckers cop killers deserves its own channel branding branding oh shit it's
own shit I don't think so just yet not just not yeah yeah I like it would be
pretty cool but like not yet soon soon that's that's a straight that's a stretch
goal dude Ben can you fucking imagine PCPHQ every like other week week like I
come over you have to come over to mine and like we record reference cop killers
in person and like chill out can you imagine that sounds that sounds like
pretty much the most fun I can imagine in this lifetime I would like that a
whole bunch yeah I would I would be way into that and I think man oh man it sure
is exciting it sure is exciting for me to hear that like Atlanta seems like the
spot cuz that's just like like I moved down here to Atlanta kind like kind of
hoping that like other people would following but with like the full
knowledge that it was not necessarily gonna happen that I might just end up
coming on my own and that would be what it would be what do you think about like
like I am not sold on Atlanta merely because I have not been there what do I
think about Atlanta I mean like like what would you like could you even
possibly consider like moving to a different part for the HQ I could like
a different city or are you like nailed down to Atlanta I'm I'm I would say I'm
I would say I'm pretty nailed down it would have to like I would I mean I'm
gonna say I'm fairly nailed down yeah yeah yeah yeah I mean and for me I can go
anywhere at least yeah do time I can go anywhere yeah I mean if fucking people
came and lived around Atlanta I mean I would be really excited and not like not
just for my own sake like I think Atlanta is a pretty good choice like you
know I mean there's there's people there's good people there's anime people
and like it's just a pretty cool city it's got I mean I really like I haven't
spent like a ton of time in the city proper but the time I have spent there
like you know there's a good fucking there's good public transit which is
like a big deal for me like that's what like that's pretty much what makes a
good city for me is like good public transit and like there's a subway and
there's just like some cool fucking downtown zones and like there's you know
cool bars and whatever and it's just I mean like I really liked Boston and I
think Atlanta pretty much has all the attractions that Boston had so you know
thumbs up for me I'm like I'm sure when I if I ever go there if when I ever go
there I will be pretty down but I I know it's pretty like like well duh but I
kind of like my home city I'm kind of like yeah I'm pretty yeah I'm pretty in
favor of it I mean I would be I wouldn't I could had a complete sway I would like
to live I would like to live in San Diego all my life I would really like to
visit San Diego I'm gonna shill San Diego real quick just shill it real quick
first sure dude go for it it's a coastal city which is a big thing for me I
don't know how much it is for anyone else but I really like the ocean okay I
don't really care about the ocean but whatever whatever there's a lot of other
like podcasts were based here there's there's a sleepy cast and it's like close
to LA which is where you know everyone is but it's not in LA so it's not super
expensive or anything or hard to get around in it's like it's close enough to
LA to where like okay if I ever need to meet someone LA I can do it I can I can
do it but it's not like to the point of where it's gonna be always crowded and
so in LA people like meme a lot about it it is a meme city it is expensive and
you know congested but that's only because there's so much shit to do there
that like there it is warranted to want to be there a lot there's a ton of
talent there and it's for the pcp like as a business I know I don't mean any of
the only people who give a single shit about like growing the pcp at all but
if we ever wanted to be issues about that that would be a great location do it or
or you know anywhere like like population center would be great and uh yeah so it's
close to that and plus there's just a ton of like places to hang out there and I
know there's like a ton of places that there's oh in a city there's gonna be
tons of places to hang out but uh there's like a lot of like varied locations
there's a lot of rich there's a lot of poor places there's a lot of rich places
very very it's it's a very varied city so if you ever want to like hang out with
homeless people you can go out to the yeah go to the homeless people place if you
want to hang out with rich people you can go to the rich people place it's very
diverse in a lot of ways and it's pretty cheap if you know where to go uh there's
some like you know free food play like it there's just a lot of varied places you
can go so you can uh fucking hang out a lot and I know like the back of my hand
there's a lot there's a lot of interesting unique places that I guess like I'm sure
there are places like that it landed but I just don't know about them so I don't
know mm-hmm and uh yeah I'd love I'd love to visit I'd love to come visit uh
fuck it man yeah it'd be really great if I could
fucking uh get out there at some point oh and we could chill in your home city
and also there is I don't like there is from my perspective good public transport
like like there are a lot of but stops is there bus stops around but but stops
is that the is that the city with all the trolleys uh no i'm thinking of san francisco
but there are okay fuck me it's like it's for the same thing about is san francisco
but like there are trolleys here and it's kind of like like trolleys are kind of like a meme
and in coastal cities like they all have them yeah I mean I I think I think living in in like a
big city is is pretty neat although like I think digi is more of the mindset of like
not in not living in a city but like you know close enough to one yeah that that's another thing
I kind of live on like the outskirts of the city so I live near like where houses are that are
very similar to digis in the so far that they are kind of isolated but so like there's like a ton
bus stops near there so you can get to the city very easily there's there's a lot of like
not like rural or like not even suburban by any means but there's like there are there's
like a heart that there's a core of the city that's very easily accessible like via bus stops and
stuff uh or like uber or whatever from like outer sort of uh outer layered houses that are pretty big
from what I can tell yeah like I think I think that's the kind of vibe uh that like digi for
instance is going for like I'm just bringing him up because like I know we talked about like what
kind of place um he wanted to move to and uh like when we walked around in Atlanta like we went to
Atlanta and hung out with econ and I know and that was and that was all good but like digi seemed to
more enjoy the like like like we hung out in like a little town center in marietta and like got
some bubble tea and that was cool and uh like we went out like we went out oh we went out on a
fucking jackie showed us all this like hiking trail that like led up through this like hilly grassy
field and like we stumbled upon like a junkyard and like yeah we played with all this secret
junk um it was cool as hell um yeah and that was like not like a city experience per se
but it was like uh you know like a suburban like a suburban georgia kind of kind of feel there and
that was good everyone everyone had a real good fucking time real good real good goddamn time
real good time talking real good time that sounds cool I I do want to see it I do really want to
like see Atlanta uh I don't have the privilege of being digi just like drive across the United States
but one day I know I know right yeah same uh because I don't feel comfortable super like hard
selling in San Diego because I just don't like I I have lived and like seen a lot of cities
but not living I've seen a lot of cities and I've lived in a couple but it like I still don't I don't
this is the problem with me for like politics or like anything just animate anything even if I
have seen a lot of something I will never ever feel like I am capable of talking about it ever
unless I know god because like because like you know you're not an expert so like surely
someone else knows better you know but like but not really yeah and like like the thing is like
like to some extent like every city is pretty much the same yeah like any like any city would do
yeah I feel similarly yeah um but if if if if everyone moved to Atlanta it would work out
it would work out for me it would work out for me personally pretty well yeah so so that's so
that's my that's my vote oh there's also a ton of like like it's gonna sound really fucking like
not a selling point but there's a lot of like hipster nerd shit here but not no that's a that's a
huge selling point for me actually oh okay good it is for me to that's all but I didn't want to sound
like I'm a hipster nerd even though I am I am a big fucking hipster nerd dude yeah I'm the biggest
and the most shameful there's a I'm just I'm embarrassing there's a ton of like indie comic
book places and like and like like used game stores and like a ton of that kind of culture
especially in uh like more outer parts of San Diego there's a ton of that even the city though
ton of it good that's what I want well that's all pretty sweet uh yeah but we just need to like
trade places for little us we can live in each city because really like like even like I don't
even know like like I know I like it here but I have no idea if anyone else would like it here
so um we just need like we should just have a rad con here or in Atlanta just we need to have
before like before we move everyone like a place we should move like we do a rad con someplace and
then like just and see the like fucking around indoors we should do that for like a couple days
but then just also just like look around the city any any excuse any excuse for a rad con
three is um is good with me I just wanted I would have wanted to host it if I just had the house
yeah same I am I've been thinking of looking into like like venues or like some kind of like space
like like a like a studio space that could be rented for like a couple days or something
because yeah like my house is not my house is not like people could stay here to a certain
extent but like it's not it's just not gonna do it like for actually like hosting the the event uh
yeah unfortunately but there I mean but now like well unless unless digi's house ends up being
available and we do it there uh then like that's true no matter where like no matter where we do it
there's gonna be the question of like what what fucking locale is it held in uh yeah when we do
do the pcp headquarters which I view that as an inevitability I don't know if anyone else does but
I feel like it's just so genius I hope it I hope it's an inevitability like I want I want that to be
true for a while there I'd kind of given up on it yeah like when did like when digi said
because because because when I moved here like I said I hoped everyone would follow
but then like when it was when digi was like no I'm going somewhere else and I'm moving somewhere
else and I was like well I didn't think that it was well first I was like oh no shit it's gonna be
somewhere else and then it was like nobody knew where it was gonna be so I was like oh it looks
like it's it's just it's just not happening after all and like did or divus moved back to Missouri
and he's just there and he doesn't seem like he wants to go anywhere anytime soon and like Jesse's
in michigan and he doesn't seem like he's going anywhere but um but lately it's been seeming
like lately I've been getting my hopes up again uh it did feel a super dark there for a little bit
but it's like like the like the worst thing about that is that people would just we would all think
that it wasn't gonna happen so we would lose hope but I know the Nate desperately wants it I desperately
want it and I'm pretty sure I desperately wanted to and yeah yeah yeah uh I'm very very pro I want
to go gung-ho patreon I want to start from a young age and I want to do patreon I want that that is my
goal yeah uh I mean I want to be a guy it's good fucking it's it's cool it's cool and it works
somehow somehow out of doing of like moving to like the pcphq you know like dude just just go to
college bro just go to college go to art I mean I go to whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa go to art
go to art college uh I mean I mean if he was I thought he was gonna give you like I mean I
thought he was gonna be like giving you the safe like no like like do do the do the smart do like
the conservative thing like get a degree get a get a stem degree so you have something to
fall back on like that would be all be fine but no don't don't yeah don't follow your dreams go to
art college like come on come the fuck right on well anyway uh yeah anyway basically no
yeah for real I do I know someone who's going to art college and they're like dude am I eight for
going to art college and was like I don't want to say yes but yes I don't want to say yes but
almost definitely yes yep yep sorry sorry about that but uh that's that's how it is
get fucked art college students do this yourself they did they asked for it they wanted it and
they got it uh awful anyway I want to move in with someone because I don't I mean I don't like
my my my prediction is that like I will have like a bin sized patreon by the time I'm like uh
ready to move which not sustainable from when I hear yeah yeah yeah um my fucking I need I need to
do something like I really need oh I okay my patreon has been staying pretty steady for a while
which like on the one hand is good because it I'm not scared that it's going to go away
but on the other hand it's not good because it's stable at like a level that's too too low to like
completely support myself comfortably yeah so I really need I don't I really need to like do
something like I think I just need to like increase my output for a while like finish up
champion fast because like every day that goes by the champion isn't done I want to kill myself
and um and then I think I'm gonna like I think I'm gonna start like kick starting uh like while
I work on vapers three I think I'm gonna start kick starting like paperbacks of like vapers one
and two yeah and oh I got merch I got merch did you see my fucking pin no dude I put a I put a
picture in the discord oh I did see that I did see that yeah yeah yeah I got I got a hundred of them
what yeah I got a hundred of those and they're gonna feed they're gonna be uh kick starter
rewards I want that I want that I want to dude I'll fuck I'll give you one what fucking yeah yeah
I mean I I've got a hundred I'm definitely gonna keep like you know I'm gonna give one to Jackie
I'm definitely gonna keep one for myself I'll probably put aside a few to just like give to people
and then I'll give I figure I'm gonna give the majority of them away well I'm gonna give as
many as I can away as like Kickstarter rewards and then I'll I'll probably won't get rid of all of
them and then I thought maybe I'll start I'll start kick starting my I'll start kick starting my older
comics and like maybe get a little bit of like buzz because like you know that's how you get famous
as you make money in comics like that's how people notice you is if people fucking fund your kick
starters um so maybe get a little buzz but by that and maybe start going maybe start going to cons
maybe start going to like smaller cons and like boot and like we're like like manning a table and
like selling pins and selling merch and like selling prints or something all that shit that I never
wanted to do but like whatever I I won't do that too but sounds it sounds like cool to me not like
that it sounds kind of you know you know I go back and forth on it sometimes I think it sounds
like fun and it sounds cool and I'm like oh I'm missing out like that's what that's what like
that's how your that's like how you have your fun and like make comic friends but then other times
I'm like oh what a fucking hassle nobody's gonna buy nope nobody's gonna buy my shit so why do I
bother yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah that's me I'll uh I I almost feel like don't get me a poop up pin
and then I will I will kick start I will kick your start um cool yeah I mean well one one way or
another you're getting one thank you thank you uh I've been pretty good about the Patreon pledges
I feel like like like every once in a while they like might my pledge won't go through but then
like the next day I will get it to you uh yeah and I don't want to increase it all but I'm gonna I
plan to like I don't foresee ever unpledging so you're welcome thank god munchie you're an angel
and if people like you it's people like you that fucking I'm the reason I live I yet live
people like you are the reason my heart beats yeah yeah in in multiple in multiple senses um
um I uh shit I was gonna say something oh yeah you're my bread and butter yes
you're yep yep yep you're my steak and potatoes my kidney beans and rice my shrimp and grits epic
epic epic I want fucking Radcom 3 so bad I want it too I mean like we've been saying like we've
been saying here today the PCP has felt a little like distant recently like it's felt it hasn't
really felt like there's been much like camaraderie and like I miss that you know what I mean yeah
yeah yeah so I don't know maybe it's maybe it's foolish to think that like that kind of that
could be recaptured by radcon 3 but like I I hope I would like it honestly I would like it very much
if you want to make if if you want to like if if we want to go into google doc stuff this and like
write up like it like a like a contract if if you wanted to I would be fine with like maybe like
once a month just like not record anything and just like hanging out and like doing something yeah
they're just together yeah I would be fine with that is this is this obsession is this obsession
with like we not doing anything unless content comes out of it like surely that's insane yeah
like surely which we're fucking we're off our our rockers okay like like on one hand I like
to like make things like I do like like right away it's cool it's it's it's satisfying it's
satisfying when like doing a thing leads to content like it's satisfying to put it out and
be like yep here's a thing here's a thing that was made but like it can't like surely surely
everything's not supposed to be like that yeah uh yeah god the the fucking I think it was something
like like we would do something to end next but I think I think it was like us staying up for two
hours talking about how gimp is cool like what did you said something like yeah I wish that was
recorded it might have been something else but I thought like no I don't want that to record that
should have been recorded this that that was for us that that was for us this this is our time this
is our time god damn it yeah this isn't this isn't it's not for show this isn't for this isn't for
this isn't for the pcp wiki archivists to like make a page about and like speculate about or
anything yeah uh such a shame fuck I mean such a shame yeah but you know it if if you if you want
to I'd be fine just like get into a call sometime yeah um I would I would like that with you I would
like that with like a bunch of pcp maybe I would like to I would like to like hang out with like
you know hippo and like mage maybe we should like start like a new group like just we spend
off into like p like like pcp2 real friends yeah wait wasn't that didn't we talk about that one time
oh yeah wasn't there like an idea to like split the because like the pcp was too much of like a
formal thing and it's like we need a second pcp for us to just actually like be friends that was
like a couple days before frog fractures or maybe afterwards and and and yeah it was around that time
tensions were yeah tensions were so fucking high dude it was insane yeah yeah I feel like things
things have cooled down things have cooled down since then but now it's just kind of like dead
I don't feel so I I I like the pcp I like I like the podcast part and like the group part I'm
I'm down I'm I'm I'm the people who like I think give a single shit about like preserving
the podcast part and I mean I like both
do I do I care about the podcast aspect of it or I don't know but like the idea of us being like a
league of gamers that like oh hardcore together I don't I don't really care about the podcast itself
but I like I deeply care about the idea of all of us as like a league of allies like a league
a league of content creating allies who create content together yeah yeah like yeah that's that's
why yeah that's like that's what we were meant to be and and you know maybe maybe fucking hanging
out in ways that like aren't specifically for the purpose of making content would fucking facilitate
us being a league of content creators in like an indirect way you know what I mean I think that like
like I think the problem with the pcp isn't it like maybe a little bit but not people are like
look a lot of people are like complaining about the wrong things like I don't think the actual
structure of it itself is the problem but we're just thinking about it like we're not thinking
about it right we aren't being real people we're being weird and that's fucking up the experience
for ourselves like yeah like like like if it was just like each week we just pop and like do a funny
little podcast because I like doing the podcast I think it's funny and I think it's enjoyable to
get feedback yeah it's scary and yeah I think if that was just that we didn't like like I'm not even
one of these people who's like yeah we shouldn't have done the patreon because that makes it too
formal like it it's not Nate does all the fucking work he does yeah I don't like for like after the
patreon started I was kind of afraid that like it was gonna get really like what's the word like
tense about it but like it didn't yeah like nobody really like it's not enough money that anyone
really cares that much yeah and uh I just like think like we just need to stop acting the way
we are about it we just need to like remind ourselves like yeah we're friends first we don't
we don't need to record everything we can just have fun and exist like like we should have a sort of
avenue like like the PCB headquarters will be great for this but in the meantime we should have
like uh were you there for the the PCB congress that was like less like like less no I Nate
Nate told me that that was coming and then I fucking forgot and missed it well that that was
like the first I mean it was still like about business and the PCP but we didn't have to
record or anything it was just us talking about like real shit and sure there was a yeah there was a
like a while back when like it was up in the air like where we were moving like we had just like
an informal call with like me and Jackie and Digi and Nate I think was there and maybe DeVoo I don't
know and that was fun like that was that was it was just casual like I mean yeah it was it was a
it was like a formal call for like a business reason I guess you could say but yeah it wasn't
recorded and it was good yeah anyway I think we gotta have something like like that maybe not we
gotta but I think like like Jesse and all the people who are like nay saying about the PCB I get
it like I'm well you know I don't want to say I get it and be like no you fucking don't know like
no worries well I know where he's coming from yeah I know where he's coming from yeah and
I agree we need to stop being so like dependent on creating content constantly but I don't think
that's I think we we are the kind of people who just like to create content I don't think yeah
necessarily pushing ourselves so much to do it it's just kind of natural and we we we need to
push ourselves not to is the thing at least maybe a little bit I think we need to and I think we'll
get into the groove of it dude just not dude dude yeah what yeah like I'm thinking about it
and yeah what if we just had like maybe like a bi-weekly or something just like a fucking
not yeah just like a fucking like a pc pizza party or something where we all just like fucking
showed up and just like hung out in a call and maybe played video games or didn't and it doesn't
matter or something yeah something like like it's not streamed it's not recorded that sounds really
good and you know what you know what I've been feeling I I'm gonna push for it too because I've
been like I don't know like I haven't I don't know whether I've been the only one feeling this way I
can't imagine like I can't be the only one that's been feeling like kind of isolated and like we're
not really like in touch with our fucking identities as like as like a group of content creating
friends anymore you know uh so yeah I'll push for I'll push for that too yeah that sounds cool and
good I like it offline I have I have friends offline and uh yeah I am basically the native of that
group I am the one who like anything yeah like sustain it uh so yeah like like like every month
or so I will like I will like plan a party at my house and I will like make a whole like
invitation with like a ton of fucking it it will literally be like a Nate best guy ever
every video we have a ton of fucking like flash and fluff to it like a whole bunch of
fucking reaction images in the background just like yeah I'm like like a whole like dedicated
like like a fucking like like paragraph like this week it's for mitzvah themed I'm going to be I'm
going to convert to Islam because I love Islam so much bring your Quran so you can beat me to death
with them please god I love I love Jews so much all right and I'll just say like yeah just bring
pizza like like bring money for pizza or something and we'll just hang out and uh like usually I'll
stream that but not because I feel the need to it's just like all like none of my friends are
like content creators or anything we just you know the thing is kind of cool and so you know yeah
yeah uh so yeah uh we uh do like like I'll just organize that and then uh it will be great they'll
come over and we'll just hang out we don't have to like like and and like last time we like spent a
lot of it like off the air just talking about real shit and it was fantastic uh and I loved doing
that and I don't do it a lot just because you know I'm I'm working a lot and we all are working but
we can make time I truly believe that all this can make time for this and I think I yeah I 100%
agree because like yeah like like like if I'm like in the middle of work I don't want to like
take time off like when I'm trying to work to do this but like if it's if like I know it's coming
in advance and like it's like a thing and like it's planned like a couple hours or whatever is not
like a huge it's not a huge ass and like it's worth it and like it's just something that I want to do
I think us like the problem isn't that we are doing the the podcast but the problem is that we only
talk through the podcast yeah yeah the problem yeah the problem is that that's it yeah and that's
not like a real thing yeah like that's like that's not that's not the real shit like you get here on
the rowdy fuckers cop kill is patreon.com slash rowdy fuckers cop kill yeah I mean I don't know
like what the fans think but like I honestly come out and say I don't know if I'm friends with a lot
of people here I mean I would desperately like to but we just there's no I can't just say like
hey you just want to talk and hang out like that's just yeah I agree like I like we taught like we
talk in the pcp but outside of it it's like like you know like I have so much like like I have so
much shared history with like digi and jesse and hippo but we don't yeah but we don't like hang out
or talk and like that makes me real sad and like I think I don't know like I don't know if they feel
the same way maybe they do I don't know either maybe it's maybe it's maybe it's selfish to kind of
hope that they do feel bad about it but like that would make sure make me feel better if they did
and um yeah let's all be friends guys like I never talked to I'm just gonna name drop people
because you know real shit I never talked to like jesse or devoo or or uh tom or mage or anyone
and I would like to but what am I gonna do just ask them to hang out they're busy and
we right right right like that like that's how like that's how it feels but it shouldn't feel like
that yeah do you know what this is really refreshing because I've been thinking about this
and I've just been feeling like it's my problem but it's not my problem it's everyone's okay oh thank
thank fucking christ yeah I think about this all the time thank god okay okay good I mean if we are
alone in this then this pocket's gonna seem really weird if someone else is watching yeah
oh Jesus like imagine if nature's like like Nate's like life like I imagine like Nate's just
like talking in chat about this like right now in like the future he's like talking to PCP chat like
like dude what the fuck like at Nate at bed and munchie what the fuck why why are you talking about
this shit no one cares this we we're all best friends we all talk all the time without you guys
we all already have our own like get together each week what's going on
oh no this is good it's good it's good to get all this out it's important
yeah and you know we've been yeah I think that's really all like yeah we just go we just we just
gotta be friends we gotta be more friendly and yeah you know what I really regret that I like
I for the spicy bro pact I didn't get digi in there I'm like really good friends with a digi at
least I perceive it that way I've known him yeah I've known him long a second to Tom I never talked
to Tom and uh like you know I like to change that Tom if you're listening let's let's do something
uh yeah I'm really I think I really like digi I really like talking to digi uh he should be a
spicy bro we were gonna do the spicy bro pack but we didn't have time to the anime expo which is a
shame uh but you know next radcon I desperately want to get Nate and digi in there and yeah like
like spicy bros is like my way of like like it's almost like my way of like coping with like the
pcp it's like it's like if I was just about someone you can tell like I like we are actually friends
like we are actually like good friends together like that's why I'm with you because I want people
to know that it's like not we we just aren't in a chat together we just aren't in the pockets
we are like good friends and I fucking love you know with munchie yeah munchie I can I consider
you a really good friend of mine yeah I could say you're a good friend of mine too yeah okay I'm
glad it's nice it's nice it's nice to hang out yeah um but I mean did the the spicy bro pack video
ever come out oh no but I am the that's gonna be out before it's not gonna be an investigator situation
I am like like working on it and making good progress uh okay I remember you mentioned you
were working on it before and then I like didn't follow follow up on that for a while the intro
is fucking very very nice yeah is it very clean it will get it will literally kill you if you
aren't careful it may legitimately kill you okay good like I'd say like since you guys are fans of
the piece of the reference cop killers if you're watching this then lower your volumes and like
don't look at the screen only only the ratifuckers cop killers loyalists who have made it this far
into episode five spared my well no well yeah we spared your rat oh fuck and you know what yeah
you know I'm not even gonna remember I'm not even gonna remember that tip like I'm still gonna I'm
still gonna suffer your wrath even though I had the option not to it's like like like like there's
like a song that will play and like there'll be like a little bit like of a slow just like like
buildup and then like the moment you hear like the do then you will literally die you will cease to
exist you will like like because when that starts then then the visuals happen and then the audio
happens and you will be dead you will die gotta say I'm feeling gotta say I'm feeling pretty excited
about it then been looking forward to seeing that for man it was I mean I want to see the video
that was just really fun yeah no that was just a great it was just a great fucking time that was
that was radcon yeah yeah it was radcon too because you weren't at radcon one oh man because Victor
wouldn't get me the fucking video for a while but then again I I know I know like I remember I
remember that whole fucking push pull of that situation I don't know I mean Victor is by
bro too so I don't blame him he was doing shit yeah yeah yeah yeah still still still yeah
spicy bros gotta look out for other spicy bros but man I want to talk to fucking Victor again
god damn it yeah that's that's even harder because Victor isn't even in the pcp
no like um you know it's really it's a real bummer and I'm gonna make myself maybe sound like a big
fucking loser right now but like it's real sad that I feel like we don't like we're not like
really close in the pcp because like the pcp is like my only friends yeah the pcp is like my is
like my whole fucking friends group and now to feel to feel like to feel like oh it's I feel so
isolated from it and to feel like oh it's so like it's it's gone it's gone kind of silent and like
or not silent but like I'm no longer in touch with it it's like oh no yeah no oh god yeah I have
offline friends and I have other online friends but I do couldn't I I do consume not pcp media but
like I do consume being in the pcp way more than the other people uh yeah I mean I doubt any of
my other friends will be watching this but if you are I do enjoy talking to you it's just you know
I I like the pcp and also it's kind of my work now a little bit I guess yeah a bit it's just kind
of natural uh chat even though he he me and Ethan are best friends chat to Ethan I he doesn't watch
the pcp you're not watching this but shout to Ethan uh Ethan's Ethan I want you to know there's a
highest compliment I can give I literally look for girls that are modeled after you are personality
but I don't want to be gay so I can't date you that is not a joke that is legitimately how I feel
oh god um wait Ethan is Ethan in he's what he's been in a video or two right yeah yeah he's been
he's been in this he's been in listen buddy he he does he does all my streams with me
yeah okay I thought I thought he's been around I've heard I've heard him around a little bit yeah
yeah he's uh a fucking hippo was in oh yeah he's in armory treable uh hippo hippo's armory
and he said quote he's a good boy wait he's in what video armory treable uh the homestuck podcasting
oh oh oh which I have not wait hippo was in an armory treable oh he was in act five specifically
for visca uh yes uh yes of course up to his old up to hippo up to his old fucking tricks I love hippo
me too man me too hippo is I wish I wish I were I wish I were fucking
hippo's one of the people that when I think about the fact that like we don't actually
talk that much I feel like oh no yeah yeah yeah yeah we we gotta talk like and even like it's not
even just that like it's being recorded like that's like a weird thing but like due to the
effects we can't talk about like shit there's a talk about like oh oh fucking oh I I I love
star trek so much oh her funny you know a chucky cheese oh yeah yeah yeah it's all like it's all
like done with a purpose but like we don't who fucking needs who fucking needs purpose purposes
for the week yeah and and none of this is like anti-pcp at least from like my just no my stance I
am not against doing the podcast fans no I'm gonna drop out no I'm not again I'm not against it but
it's a bummer that like that's all that's been going on lately yeah exactly yeah that's how I feel
it's great uh yeah so just I don't know if anyway I think like did you and Nate listen to the last
one I think so if you listen to this I I love you guys yeah yeah you're good you're all you're all
you're all a bunch of cool guys I mean well they listen to that one because it had because it had
fucking uh pony shit in it but then again maybe they'll listen to this one expecting it to have
to have more pony drama which of course it can't because we haven't found the legendary
frog fractions to yet yeah yeah yeah I mean I think that's all I really have to say about the
pcp I think I don't know man just uh just what we've been saying I love I love them they're my
they're my best friends and um they're my best friends and uh I hope that the reason why I have
not been hanging out with y'all more is not that you all secretly hate me and are conspiring against
me uh I can only pray that that is uh but that is so yeah like people like people like
monkey I like I think I would have a lot of fun with if we just talked yeah yeah he this little
secret little secret inside the secret inside munchies paranoia I secretly believe that both
monkey and jesse hate me though I have no evidence I just suspect that that is the case I have no
reason to believe that I secretly who do I think secretly hates me well I'm pretty I'm pretty sure
tom hates me but um that's that's for reasons um um mom I think I think monkey just pretends to
hate me or maybe that's but maybe that's just what I tell myself to feel better um maybe maybe he
keeps you as a friend as like a size situation yeah yeah but like a reverse size situation
where he says he hates me but he actually likes me yeah yeah I'm sorry sig I'm not I'm not and and
then jesse I feel like me and jesse never I don't think jesse hates me I'm not sure I think jesse
like probably like I think jesse probably I feel like maybe me and jesse kind of feel the same way
we're like we like each other and we think each other are cool but we don't really know what to
say to each other I think I mean that's how I feel about him and I feel like it's reciprocated
but I guess I don't know because I've never like brought it up or anything and I just have no idea
what tom and mage feel about me like what's what's whoever I mean I have no reason to believe negative
uh I wonder if I don't know yeah I don't know I don't know I wonder if you are in like a good
foot but we have not talked since ride con two we we hit it off I feel I feel I don't know if
davoo's gonna like like fact check me here but I got to I think we hit it off pretty good
me and davoo me and davoo have like talked a little bit in the chat because like I was
asking him about like his housing situation after I moved and stuff because I was interested
because I was like interested to know how the whole like moving back in with his parents and
getting his girlfriend over there and like getting there in place like I was I was a bit invested
in that narrative so I tried to follow through on that um I wonder if I wonder if mage is like I
wonder if mage would have any has any interest in like in like fucking getting our old things
going because like I felt kind of bad because she would like half the time she would ask me if I
wanted to watch anime and sometimes I'd be like no I don't feel like it or no I don't feel like
spending the time only once in a while would I be like yeah sure let's do it I wonder if maybe
she eventually was just like well he more often than not says no so maybe he just doesn't doesn't
want to or maybe she just found something better to do yeah yeah yeah yeah we just we gotta do
I think also a little bit this this might seem contradictory to what I was just prescribing
but I think the like didgy with funky social social media podcast like jesse and hippo
doing that shit I think a key to helping this would just be doing one-on-one podcast with more
people maybe maybe not like that wouldn't solve it but I think that would like okay there was a
there was a kick for that for a while like there was like like monkey and mage made one and that
was weird and random and I didn't listen to it but I was surprised by its existence was it oh was it
oh well that's too bad um yeah there was the pody cast and the pony cast and that was all
that's all I guess the pody cast is still going um I wouldn't be I wouldn't be a verse to do in
more like one-on-one oh yeah and then me and divu did uh uh uh destructive criticism which
everyone hated uh everyone hated because I was mean to some video game which fuck those guys
their video game was gay it was just it was just another game made again I don't feel
bad about anything I said um but it was good but it was good fucking like doing a thing with
divu because I'd never like one-on-one it's good like I like fucking talking with the pcp guys and
and getting getting to know everyone because they're my friends exactly like I've known
all of you for like what like five years no I've known did you I've known did you for five well
well what was the first brony con that we went to was it brony con 2014 13 I'm fairly Jesus christ
okay so that's like four years then Jesus fucking christ my life my life munchie where is it gone
and like we haven't we just I mean okay you guys have talked way more than I have like like I'm
you know I don't I don't want to forget my place here I am the new guy I am like you know
I'm I'm I'm not bonafide pcp original member here but I guess I I I mean but we were talking
we were talking about you and we knew you even in the early early days yeah I mean the first words
you ever spoke to me you the first words you did ever speak to me was I've heard a lot about you
so I guess that means I had I had oh man nostalgia I mean where were you were you going
somewhere with that no no I just oh well yeah it's just like I feel like we like we like I feel like
we know each other less than we should for being in this stage of our like time wise our relationship
not not just not just me and you I feel like me and you like know each other way more than we
know me I mean I mean I think I think at this point I would say that I mean other than Nate but
like that's a different thing like me and you or like you're you're the one that I'm like the closest
to in the piece really like you're you're yeah yeah I mean I mean I mean I mean like I lived with
digi and stuff well I mean I lived with digi I don't mind I'm not gonna get mad we would we would only
hang out occasionally I don't know I mean I mean I don't know no I think I think I think you're
by you're my pcp you're my pcp bestie I feel similarly I feel and I'm not just saying that you're
not you're not just you're not just saying that you don't have to say no I'm not just saying I
by far know you know most oh and I enjoy it the most so I mean like I mean like I mean I don't I
don't do anything like I don't do anything like rowdy fucker cop killers with anyone else so like
you know what that there's there's your there's your evidence my my my my pcp tier list for who I
know and like love the best is as follows uh you then digi then Nate and then I forget the rest
um yeah mine would probably be you I mean Nate is like off the list Nate's Nate's like a different
league yeah um there'd be you yeah probably you digi oh and then and then hippo and then and then
hippo I can't I can't forget hippo well probably you and then digi and then divu because like I
lived with digi and divu and I was closer with digi than divu but you know we were still roomies
and then you know I don't really feel like I know hippo much better than I know like
Jesse really you know yeah you know I have hung out I have hung out with Tom like at his house a
couple times really oh yeah yeah I did I did like twice I think maybe three times yeah yeah um he
he just invited me over to like for with some of his friends for like game night one time my tire
exploded one time I popped a tire on the highway driving to his house and my dad had to come out
and rescue me but it didn't work and we and we just called AAA and then but it got fixed early
enough that I still just like on my newly replaced tire I just like kept going and like went to Tom's
awesome yeah so actually actually I probably know Tom like pretty well well I mean not not that well
because you know we don't actually talk that much but like tier you know it would probably be it
probably be you and then either like digi and then mage and then Tom and even though Tom even though
Tom hates me and Tom probably Tom probably thinks that I hate him but I don't um yeah anyway and and
like yeah and keep in mind I I want everyone to be a tier that's what I want this is not like yeah
I don't yeah yeah I yeah yeah this is not a who do I like the best this is like a how how well
exactly how fucking up on each other's dicks yeah and I want to be up on everyone's real bad
it would make me real happy yep hippos minecraft stream is the closest thing that I think I like
like we have to like just a hanging out because even though it's a stream it is I've actually
been me just off the fucking rails and we just hang out I've actually I've actually been meaning
to like pop in to definitely should wait are you like I'm actually a stream kind of guy I stream
a lot at least relatively are we okay are hippos streams like on like are you on there on voice
yes obviously oh can I yeah can I get in on that well I mean ask him but yes okay yeah I guess I will
I will ask him when do you when do you all do it it's usually minecraft so you'd have to get that
but uh we do I mean I have it I think we like it's not like a schedule it's just like like basically
every week or every other week we it's either on Monday or Friday like pcp time
oh no I just realized that I hate minecraft and I suck at it uh Nate has that didn't play it before
he went on stream so okay okay I guess I guess I'm good then yeah it's great uh hippos brother's
there too and he's a nice guy you mean hgb guy oh cool that's that's Henry yeah he's he's cool
he's not like gay no no he I know he's cool he does he's um he's he's you to be he was he was
your um uh uh fungus you're uh yeah yeah he was my he was my amungus and I know that he's the by my
p yeah finally if you can hear people in the background just don't worry about it stop listening
fucking okay not you yeah the fans I would never call you an idiot you fucking baka yeah
yeah um um yeah uh yeah I'll fucking do a minecraft stream I I do have a minecraft account I own
the game I just need to like download or something yeah it'll be great uh yeah that that's where I
truly realize that me and Nate are like good like like like if we actually want to we could totally
do a one-on-one podcast Nate if you're listening I'd be down but I don't know what we could do
yeah um yeah man me and Nate really should do another show you should we just we just uh we just
hate each other so intensely it's just such a barrier to things like to progress you know
I would just be so I would just be such good friends of this guy if only I didn't fucking hate him
yeah yeah yeah true just shame that's how I feel yeah that's how I feel about everyone
in the pcp yeah uh you know the pcp I think I said all we can the pcp's been one community
we've grown pretty distant from but I think there might be another community that we've grown even
more distant from for maybe one or two reasons yeah maybe maybe yeah and I think I've even I've
even been like noticing I've been noticing some of them like on Twitter and on social media and
stuff and we've had some we've had some run-ins with I don't know what what we what we've done
you know yeah and and what could we possibly have done we're just living our lives yeah
we're just being nice guys just just loving our friends just just just just just passionately
ranging about how much we want to be good friends with everyone just you know it's it's weird to
think about that that we can have any and somehow and somehow they find fault they somehow they
find fault with us somehow for that year 11 more like 9-11-2 am I right bros swing on with that
fucking door dude all right so he's so not 11 years into our fucking I think it's I think it's
finally time I think it's finally time to delve into frog fractions to and get into this fucking
and get into this fucking pony business from last time it's fine it's finally time for frog
fractions to not frog fractions to yeah it's time for this the actual sequel to the frog
fractions where we'll delve into the mysteries we delve into the mysteries of what happened and
who's a fucking asshole and who's retarded and who and who fucking hate and who fucking hates
our guts for no reason and talk about what a bunch of stupid shit boys they are and just and just
how I'm like see the tile screen like immediately like alt tab out and just like open up youtube
yeah yeah um I think I think I think clicking on the store is going to be our transition into
like next time on rowdy fuckers cop killing yeah I do I do because like I just next time
yeah join us next time when we fucking talk about last join us next time when we talk about last
time yeah all right here we go