I don't give a fuck, bitch! Welcome back to Rick's D Minutes. I'm Digibro, and with me is the best guy ever.
You sound like that thing Gibb made. You know what I'm fucking talking about? Yeah, I'm the best guy ever, guys. What's up? What's going on?
No idea what you're talking about. We watched the new Rick and Morty. That wasn't enough of a description, yeah. Okay, me, Rick and Morty.
It's episode 4, season 3 about the, what the fuck were they? Vindicators. It's called Vindicators 3, The Return of World Ender. What was the episode?
So, this episode I was not that into. Yeah, I'm totally with you. I thought this was pretty weak. First of all, I was very confused.
Because the whole early part of the episode, they keep insisting that this is like the return of the vindicators.
Who have never been characters on the show. Now, I was unsure, because I haven't rewatched season 2, and I was like, did I just blank out on an episode of these guys?
I was thinking that the whole time too, yeah. Dude, I fucking wanted to pause the episode and go look it up, but as it went on, I was like, I don't remember any of this.
So this couldn't have happened before, you know? Yeah, that was confusing. I liked a bunch of these characters.
Million Ants is like the coolest guy ever, and I would just like, I would remember Million Ants, so yeah, this obviously is the thing they're doing.
We haven't seen this before. So I don't know if these guys are meant to be a parody of the Guardians of the Galaxy, or like obviously the name is...
Not the expendables, the fucking suicide squad, that's what I was thinking of, but they're more Guardians of the Galaxy.
Yeah, I think the idea is that they're a parody of Guardians of the Galaxy, but they're not like a on-the-nose parody. None of them are anything like the Guardians of the Galaxy is what I'm kidding at.
Except for like the main guy. I have not seen Guardians of the Galaxy, but I got the feeling that the main dude was supposed to be like Star Killer or whatever his name is.
Star Lord.
He just seems like the main guy.
How have you not seen the Guardians movies?
I don't believe that they're that good. How could any movie be good?
They're fucking fantastic, Nate. They can't be true.
I would give each of them a 9 out of 10.
That's pretty damn good.
Yeah, I cried in Guardians 2. I saw it twice and cried both times in the same week.
Like a bitch.
Alright, I believe you. Well, I don't need to see that anymore, because I just watched the Vendicators 3 Return of Worlds, and it was everything I could hope for.
I don't know what this episode's like going for, honestly.
It wasn't going for anything. It was just trying to be like, oh, look how silly Rick's being.
It was, look, Rick's being silly episode with a little bit of like the relationship drama that we've seen like a thousand times already.
It really had nothing new to offer in most departments.
This is very Rick and Morty du jour. Like this is the most, it's a lot like Anatomy Park or like M Night Chameleons, but I feel like this is the first episode where I've become concerned about there not being B plots in this show.
Yeah.
Because like the worst Rick and Morty adventures have always been matched up with at least semi-decent B plots.
Like in Anatomy Park, for instance, everybody criticizes that episode because it's just like a straight up Jurassic Park parody.
But the funniest part about that episode is the Jerry's parents fucking some, like having a weird like threesome relationship with a younger black guy.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
That's by far the funniest thing about the episode. So this one we're just kind of trapped in this very one note repetitive adventure story that I don't know.
I had no interest in the whole time.
I hate to say it, but I mean this episode gives me the feeling that we've kind of hit the wall.
Okay, like I'm exaggerating, but like this gives the impression to me that like, okay, we've kind of had Rick and Morty run its course now and we got it like we understand what it's been doing and it has now accomplished it.
So like what, like this was just like Rick being a little bit of Rick, Morty being a little bit of Morty in ways that we see every single episode with like, like this was very much like a flash episode.
Like I felt like the animation was like a little bit next level on this episode, like everything that the ghost train thing was cool, a million ants when he did like his actions things were pretty sick.
I don't know, like this episode felt very attractive looking, but then just lacked like a script.
Like I left a couple times, but this did not feel as like biting as I was expecting.
I don't think I laughed the entire episode, you know?
I got a couple troubles. The first time that Noop Noop like backs up Rick, I don't know, that got a laugh out of me.
The whole like, like when you said about the animation, I think this show is always about on par with animation, but what was not as strong and this is like the directing.
Because in Pickle Rick, a lot of my laughs were just at like violent moments.
It was just at like the timing of a scene of like Rick just suddenly like fucking carving somebody in half.
This episode has one incredibly violent scene that just felt like to me, you know, like when the when the first guy dies.
And it's just like this way over the top violent scene.
And I was just kind of like, what was was that necessary? Like why? Why are we going for that level?
Like it just wasn't funny, you know? It was just really violent.
And I was like, okay, it's fun, I guess, you know?
I've seen the hyperviolence from every other episode of the last season and a half, so it's not like impressing me at this point.
I felt like I almost felt like when that guy died specifically, it kind of felt like they cut his arc off too soon.
Like I didn't, I don't know, like they really threw all these characters to the fucking wayside.
Which in a way, I kind of respect that they're like, yeah, we don't give a fuck about our characters that we came up with.
They will just kill them off instantly. Like that's kind of cool.
But on the other hand, it feels wasteful and sort of almost a disrespectful way to their own characters.
I don't know, I'm exaggerating a little bit.
Disrespectful is a word I would use for that guy in particular.
Because we didn't, like, what about that dude warranted such an extreme death?
Like it wasn't cathartic. We didn't hate this guy yet.
He just seemed like, I don't know, kind of a milk toast douchey guy, I guess.
We didn't, like, they kind of hinted at like maybe a pedophilia thing that they didn't deliver on that.
They kind of hinted at this other thing.
They hint at a bunch of little things, but then basically he just becomes a horror character and gets himself killed.
It seemed like they were going for a horror thing with this, but the episode doesn't...
It's not a horror episode.
At first it's like, oh, okay, they're going to do a saw thing.
It's going to be scary. It's going to be about these guys getting killed in horrible death traps.
But I don't know, after the first one, it's like you see it coming.
They really do not build up the tension in that way, and the characters really have no difficulty solving the problem.
It really is just window dressing for these characters turning on each other, which is what Rick planned all along.
But I don't care about these characters. We don't know them, so where's my investment in them getting dismembered?
It's like that Morty kind of respects them.
But of course, meanwhile, we're finding out that they're bad people, which I guess proves Rick's point.
But yeah, it felt like...
A point that's been proven, this is just stuff that we've seen before.
Even Morty is like, Rick, you've made this point before.
It's like the show is almost self-aware about the fact that this is a repetitive episode, but it doesn't do anything to change that.
I agree completely.
We've got the undercurrent of maybe Rick somewhat cares about Morty, but then...
That's never been done before. What an amazing plot for an episode.
It's kind of funny when they flip it on its head and it reveals that it's noop-noop that he cares about, not Morty.
But the scene before that already proved that maybe Rick cares about Morty, because that was Rick's theory.
Was that he cared about Morty and that's why he did this.
So yeah, again, it's been done in better ways, in better episodes.
What the hell was with logic showing up at the end of the episode?
I didn't roll my eyes. It's not an accurate description of what I did.
I just breathed out a little bit of my soul.
I guess it was fine.
Is celebrity cameos what Rick and Morty needs?
The Joel McHale thing already crippled that episode and was just a massive source of unfunnyness.
This show has had tons and tons of celebrity voice actors in it.
Almost every episode has had somebody like that.
Stephen Colbert has been on the show.
Well, never have I ever been annoyed by it except for that one time with Joel McHale.
And now this is happening too.
It's just logic though. It's just logic to the episode.
I don't think it was funny. It's just logic here.
It wasn't funny at all. Even his song.
I listened to that twice to try to get the humor out of it.
It was really like he just makes some vague references to like, oh, he's singing about noop-noop or something.
The thing about the song is that the end of Guardians of the Galaxy 2 has like a big ending song where it's just like describing the Guardians of the Galaxy.
So I think this is a straight parody of that.
But again, the episode is so like lacking as a parody of Guardians of the Galaxy.
Like it has nothing to do with it.
So bringing that in at the end, like suddenly an on-the-nose parody after a whole episode of nothing even resembling Guardians of the Galaxy is really odd.
It kind of is like the Fury Road parody that just didn't really do anything with it.
It just was the setting for it.
And then like within that episode, they do things like have that king at the end that has nothing to do with Fury Road.
And it's like a totally separate thing.
Yeah, like they're really not getting...
Yeah, like wastefulness.
Like they're using this setting and then not really utilizing what it provides.
They're just doing something else.
It's just like an atmospheric thing that doesn't actually add anything to the narrative they're going for in any interesting or meaningful way.
Yeah, I didn't get what they were going for with the characters, with the vindicators.
Like I didn't understand...
Is the joke just that they're all kind...
Because first of all, they never came across as like these like Paragons of Justice kind of guys.
The main dude is like, yeah, I drink and blah, blah, blah.
And like, I don't know, they're all kind of assholes from the beginning to Rick, you know.
They're very like...
They're just kind of snobby, you know.
I think we're just supposed to take Morty's...
I think what they were going for is that we would just like accept what Morty says, at least for the start.
But I mean, yeah, like it's obvious.
Whatever Rick says is going to happen is going to happen.
So I don't know, did not really have an effective arc in that way.
No, there was no like reveal.
There was no like, oh, this is taking apart the trope.
It's just like, no, it's just an episode about Rick being an asshole and...
To be fair, the twist...
The one thing that was good about it was the twist...
Okay, there were some things that were not terrible.
But like the best thing about the episode was the twist where they get to the bad guy, he's been defeated already.
And then it turns out that like the supervillain beyond him was in fact drunk Rick from the last...
From the night before.
Like that was a good idea.
And I was like, okay, this makes perfect sense as a villain that they will have to confront.
I like this.
Of course, they have to slip in the like obligatory scene like, oh, by the way, he forgot his portal gun.
That's why he can't use it.
Like they have to explain, which felt a little forced to me.
But you know, what else can they do?
Or else we'll just use that.
So the idea of having Rick fight a version of himself drunk from the night before is a good idea, you know.
But the only thing was like it wasn't even a fight.
Like there was no difficulty solving any of these issues.
It's just that the people are completely incompetent and get themselves killed.
I really think like if they had actually played out the saw angle that's referenced and like it actually was a horror thing
and the horror puppeteer was Rick from like a drunk Rick from the night before, like now that's actually pretty damn good.
And like it really would be an interesting thing that like he is doing all these and they frame the deaths in a way that's not funny,
but actually like horrific and everyone's like sad and crying and very upset.
And Rick's just like, I don't know, sorry dude, I was fucking drunk, what can I do?
I feel like there was more potential there than the angle they took here.
But yeah, just kind of fell flat the way we were doing it.
I also, I feel weird anytime Rick and Morty tries to do witty dialogue,
which this episode is full of quips and one-liners and references to the fact that they're making quips and one-liners.
And like it's okay for Rick to do that sometimes, but like when they make him just like the sarcastic asshole character,
I'm like that's not really how I see Rick, I see him more as like an unhinged drunken madman, you know?
Like you watch the early episodes, particularly the pilot, and like he's practically not saying words half the time, you know?
He's a babbling psycho who occasionally like busts out some really intellectual stuff
and like I think we've seen him closer to that for like Pickle Rick.
He's, you know, even though he's doing like this sarcasm thing at some points, like he's also just going totally out of control as a Pickle Man.
Yeah, he's fucking insane and it was great. That's the good stuff.
Not like this like super forced like Jew joke with like, oh they just go on about, I'm totally not anti-Semitic.
I swear, I'm totally non-taking aside at this point and everyone has to react to that.
Like, I get it, like you're making a joke about even referencing it.
Gee, just not, did not get a laugh and it just kept going on and on.
Right, my favorite, like what I love about the Rick and Morty humor is just like yelling Pickle Rick, you know?
Oh, it's Poopy Butthole.
The hybrid shit.
You know, having characters sit around going like, oh, maybe you should get your nickname back from the blah, blah, me and then, you know, ah, no.
Stop, this is faggy. I don't want this.
I kind of, like I sort of enjoyed the dynamic.
Like, I thought the quips worked in the way that like it was a way, like this is what makes it good.
Like just doing quips is boring and gay.
But when like there's a character who's like role is to like be the guy who's like, whoa, nice one dude.
Like at least I was like, that's kind of funny that like this is the dynamic happening here.
That's like beyond, that like sort of is the lampooning.
I didn't think Rick was really like hitting them with these strong zingers though.
Like I didn't laugh at anything he said.
Like the other guy backing him up is a funny idea, but like they've done that before with stronger jokes in this show.
Like when my favorite is in the episode with when we first get introduced to the Council of Rick's.
Rick's being held captive by the evil Rick and he keeps making all these quips and like this like, what was it?
Was it one of the mortis who was something that was like giggling at the jokes and this guy gets it and he's like,
that thing just makes that noise every 15 seconds and he's like, oh yeah, that's right, that's right.
Way funnier version of the same joke.
Yeah, I felt like Noop was supposed to be like a meme character, but he'd left no real impression on me.
I feel like Noop Noop and the lady who survives at the end are going to like come back or something.
I don't know.
Noop Noop just stuck me as like a shittier version of Mr. Poopy Butthole.
Well, he looked exactly like him, which can't be a coincidence.
There's got to be something going on there.
Yeah, I don't know, just really disappointed, watched it twice.
Like I kind of liked it better the second time because I didn't have the sense of anticipation that wasn't delivered upon.
I just kind of enjoyed watching it and I don't know.
I really liked the tangible details of the like superhero squad in the sense that like there was a ghost train conductor.
That's kind of funny.
Million ants.
I really, really like million ants.
He's fucking awesome.
I think my favorite line in the whole episode is when he says, I have only lost 400 ants and now my queen has repopulated.
So I am back to a million ants.
That's the funniest line in the episode.
I just feel like again, because we don't have a B plot, this got strung out a lot longer than it had to be.
There was a way more setup than usual of like the whole, you know, Morty kind of forcing Rick to get into the situation.
Then we have like a lot of scenes of build up of like Rick's an asshole to these guys.
They don't like him very much.
Rick and Morty in the room talking about it, getting emotional about it and like just it kind of went on and on and on.
And then we get on the adventure and we get the saw set up and I'm like, okay, now we're in the episode.
Like now the plot has kicked in.
I get what the gimmick is cool.
And then it doesn't really do anything with that.
And then it just kind of goes to a dance party at the end, which in the dance scene, logic aside, I like the stuff Rick says.
Like, you know, just like half the people I end up getting high with later, you know, there's gear over there.
Like, I like that, but...
Dude, how shitty was that like after credits gear had seen?
Like it's fine that he's trying to get laid with it, but then like it just like so flat that he's like, oh, there's danger.
I'll go change.
Wait, why is he going to change?
Let's go see what's up.
Oh, he left his thing.
There he is running away.
Oh, he tripped and fell down and that's supposed to be funny.
What the fuck?
Like that's not funny in any way.
That's like the cheapest, shittiest joke in the world.
I expect better.
I expect better writing.
Yeah.
So that was disappointing in a big way.
The funniest thing I thought was kind of, I don't know.
I just like at the beginning when Morty pulls out his like 10 punch card stamp thing that like, but what's funny about that is it's like a funny way to like force the adventure and move the plot along.
That amused me.
And like the fact that that's never been referenced before and comes up, you know, just as like an established thing.
Of course, Morty gets a stamp every adventure.
And on this, you know, that was funny.
That's funny.
So that's the kind of thing that I want to see happening as much as possible.
Like actually funny stuff that's sort of world building in this ridiculous way, which this episode lacked.
Yeah.
I would say this is probably one of the worst episodes, if not the worst episode of Rick and Morty.
It's up there.
And frankly, it makes me a little concerned about the future.
Like I've seen there are episodes that I think are weaker, but I can remember at least something that jumped out in it, you know.
And this one, there was just nothing that I see myself like reflecting on and thinking, oh, yeah, that was really funny.
That one joke was really good.
I'll just be like, oh, that was the episode that was kind of boring and and had a really weirdly obtusely violent scene right in the middle that I just found jarring, you know.
I just keep thinking about the scene where like that guy like instantly panics and flees and dies and just like how tremendously unfunny that whole sequence was.
It really is.
Nothing caused that.
I felt like this was sort of like the first half of a two-parter that we'll never get the second part to.
Like remember at the beginning, there's like those guys that are going to like turn the whole world sterile.
Yeah.
And then like there's no reference to that ever.
Like that could have been the setup for a joke paid off later in the episode that nothing came of.
And I don't know, it just kind of felt like a lot of that stuff.
It's just so far under the standard of this show, you know.
Yeah.
Less inventive than usual, less interesting, less engaging, less funny, less memorable shit, less tight of pacing.
I mean, we're getting this right after Pickle Rick, which is fucking great, you know.
Some different person.
Oh, I've got to say about it.
I ain't got much else.
I have nothing else to say about this episode, only that I really hope this doesn't, I don't know, like two of the four episodes have had an air of less impressiveness to them this season.
Of course, the other two were like some of the best ever.
So like maybe there's nothing to worry about.
I mean, I just hope they step it up.
I would put like episode two of the season, I would have put on par with the worst episodes of later ones.
You know, it still has moments.
It has good things going for it.
And it had a beat plot that was pretty good.
Like even without Jerry, we've had beat plots through these first three episodes.
Now that we're like doing one with no beat plot whatsoever, it really felt like it's strained to fit the time.
Like they spent way too much time on this adventure for the amount of yucks that could be garnered from it.
That's, I totally agree.
I think that, yeah, I think that was a big, that makes a lot of sense.
That adding that might have really helped this thing out.
By the way, did you see the preview for the next episode?
Because now that I remember what it is, I'm actually kind of hyped for it.
I don't.
I didn't wear it.
It's like, it's like a Jerry Rick episode.
It's like those two guys having an adventure together.
And I got to say, I'm kind of excited for it.
I think it could be dope.
Could be.
I don't know.
We'll see.
Yeah.
All right.
That's it, everybody.
See you next week.
You sound so excited.
All right.
Bye guys.
See you later.
Kill me.