Fuck me and my fucking asshole, everybody! We're back with more Rikstie Minutes! Me, the best guy ever, and Digibro!
Fuck bitch!
We're on episode 7 of season 3.
You got it.
Of this shit.
Yeah, there was no episode last week. That really threw me for a fucking loop. I was not prepared.
But boy, did we get a doozy this week.
Yeah, this episode.
It was the one.
This one was heavy.
It sure was, dude.
I was going to watch it again for this podcast because there was so much going on, but I kind of couldn't bring myself to.
Really?
Because I did not, like, I mean this episode is fun and entertaining as they all are, but it also, it's got stuff to say.
No doubt about that.
It leaves you on kind of a down note, and it's one of those episodes that I had to, like, stand outside and have a smoke with that chaos, chaos song stuck in my head.
Yeah.
And be like, God fuck, man.
The world.
Yeah, it's some heavy shit, dude. It's got so fucking real in multiple dimensions, in multiple ways.
You know, in Rick and Morty continuity terms, and in real nigga shit terms, you know?
Well, first I want to say about this.
This show, I kind of like the way that Rick and Morty will abuse its premise.
This show, basically because of the fact that this is a nihilistic thrill ride, that this show doesn't give a fuck about anything, and it's already established literally everything is possible.
Because we're in the multiverse, the infinite multiverse, every possibility will happen, and the show really takes advantage of that in this episode.
Because everything about this citadel is like, why would it be that way?
Right, right.
But then, like, if in the infinite multiverse, every possibility will happen, then, like, it's all justified.
Like, there's just a reason.
There's a reason that one Rick is just like that.
I don't know what that reason is, but there is one somewhere out there.
Of course, of course.
Yeah, there's no doubt about it, and it's just used to such a great effect, and they're using them to tell...
I mean, you know, it's been said, but really more than any episode before, to use the multiple clones of Rick's and Morty's in the way they're used in this episode is absolutely fantastic.
It's brilliant.
I don't know if I've ever seen a story like it before, but I fucking love it, especially with the obvious racial parallels going on in the episode.
Right.
It's fucking intense.
The racial parallels, but that don't necessarily, like, reflect any one racial thing going...
You could call it a class divide, instead, if you wanted to, you know?
I mean, it's definitely... it makes a lot of different, like, commentaries on real-world stuff, but none that's specific enough to, like, say, oh, they're doing that.
It's all, like, just... like, a vague gets into your mind, you know?
Yeah.
That's what I think is powerful about it, is that it never made me think, oh, this is, like, a parallel for, I don't know, Black Lives Matter or something, which, like, another show would do.
It's more like... I don't know, it spoke to something more fundamental to me.
I felt the same way.
Like, this is how it's always been, and always will be, you know?
I thought it would have been so easy for them to... honestly, my sensors were in full gear, looking for, like, SJW cuck shit.
I really was.
I was on the lookout, knowing, just as I was going through the episode, and I was not... I did not find myself in any way, like, able to contest in any, like, you know, just... there was nothing to object to in the story that was presented here.
Everything here was perfectly logical for the universe to do.
It's funny you say that.
Uh-huh.
I would say I was on the opposite side.
Really?
I had an eye out for pushing a, like, conservative agenda or, like, liberty.
Because, like, I don't think this show has ever come off as being on the side of, like, social justice, you know?
Like, Rick is not that kind of guy.
You know what's interesting about that?
That actually tells me something, I think, because I have been aware of the discussion going on lately about Dan Harmon, sort of, like, erring on the side.
I wouldn't even say that he's, like, on the social justice warrior side, but he's, like, had some pretty, pretty... pretty much discussed comments about how, like, Trump is, like, a literal Nazi.
Or I can't honestly remember the exact quote that it was.
I wouldn't be surprised if that's the case, but Dan Harmon also himself is a... like, Dan Harmon... there's this... I haven't actually seen this, I'm talking about the second hand, so you're getting some real tertiary knowledge here.
Okay, okay.
There's a documentary about Dan Harmon and this tour he did that Victor Washington told me about.
And, like, Dan Harmon is apparently, like, he's self-aware about this fact, but he is a terrible fucking person who everyone hates, including himself.
I know that, I know that.
Basically, he's a mess, like, he's an alcoholic, and he just has lots of, like, weird, like, pride issues, and he just kind of, like, flies off the handle and, like, gets mad at people really easily and all this stuff, and, like, he's just really hard to deal with.
Okay.
And he knows this fact, and, like, but that kind of perpetuates it even more.
Like, he sees himself as a bad guy, so he doesn't, like, try to be a good guy, but because he's self-aware, he can also write that into his characters somehow, you know?
It's amazing.
Like, Victor was even saying in the documentary, they say, like, everyone thinks community, for instance, was, like, canceled for studio, like, that it wasn't popular enough, but apparently it was partly because, like, Dan Harmon's shitty to work with and people can't survive, like, the process and stuff like that.
Fascinating.
But Harmon aside, who does, you know, he can err somewhat on the side of that stuff, but, like, then you look at Justin Roiland, who's just a fucking maniac.
And, of course, would absolutely despise a social justice-y.
I mean, this show's kind of made fun of social justice warriors before, in some ways, you know?
So, like, if anything-
I never really bought the argument that people were making, that, like, when you're in sort of the, I don't even know if Dan Harmon is in the LA bubble or whatever, but when all the people around you are perpetuating the notion that, like, someone is a certain way, or, you know, like, the alt-right is full of, like, actual Nazis, or just, like, that the country is being consumed by, like,
Nazi propaganda or something, like, I could see why someone would say something that could be interpreted.
Maybe it's our fault for being so reactionary to the things he says for assuming that he's a Nazi.
I don't know the full context, and maybe I'm the one who's in the wrong.
I mean, hating Trump doesn't make you a fucking liberal cuck.
That is very true.
That's very true.
Plenty of conservatives hate Trump and might even think he's a fucking Nazi, but-
And speaking of Trump, this episode, I mean, I didn't think this going in.
But as soon as I was done and I just started looking up a little bit of information, what people were saying about it,
the Trump parallels were everywhere.
Of course. Of course they were.
People are so fucking stupid about this shit, man.
Like, this guy is not Trump.
Like, this is a Machiavellian, like, evil genius mastermind.
Is that what Trump is to you guys?
Is it really? Do you really see the connection here?
No.
What the fuck? That's so stupid.
No. This is obviously about the elite class.
Exactly. Exactly.
The ruling class.
That's why I said, like, this felt to me like it was speaking to all time.
Correct. Correct.
Like, this is not about current events, you know?
Like, this is- it's- that's why we keep getting the refrain throughout the episode, like, same old story.
Morty's killing Morty's.
Right.
Same old story.
Rick's killing Morty's.
Like, this is the same old story that has been told for all time.
And, like, the behind-the-scenes Rick council is all corporate people.
It's all leaders of corporations.
Like, they're the Illuminati, essentially.
Exactly. That's right.
You know?
And, like, to me it had more parallels to, like, I don't know, like, the way the room is designed
and everything felt like a Greek society thing or just, like, this all- I felt timeless.
It felt like this is how it's always been.
Well, of course.
Because, like, again, I think the- what I said before about, like, race is the obvious
thing to go to when you watch this, but I really think it's more about class.
This is really a class divide that we're seeing here between the bourgeois and the- the bourgeoisie
and the proletariat.
And, I mean, the thing is, like, there's a lot of free radical thinkers out there who
talk about how the biggest- and I agree with this notion that the biggest problem facing
us is that everyone tries to make everything a race thing, but it is a class thing.
Like, the real problems in our society are more based around class.
And, like, impoverished people of all races have the same issues.
Exactly.
There might be more impoverished people who are black, but, like, everyone who's impoverished
is facing these issues.
And this episode kind of tackles that in that it's not just morties who are in this lower
class.
There's- there's ricks who- who have been put into, like, a low-class situation and they
are also fighting against it.
And it's, like, it's everyone.
It affects everyone.
Like, the- the broken system.
The- the difference between, like, ricks and morties, like, that does make sense on a racial
basis, because, like, they're- like, here, like, there's an obvious biological difference.
And then, of course, you've got, like, my favorite character in this episode, like, Cop
Morty, who's a fucking- like, we'll get to that guy.
He's my fucking hero.
Only in a sick, disgusting, twisted way.
But, like, but yeah, like, you've got him and then- but parallel to him is, of course,
the factory worker Rick, who, like, despite having- you know, he's just as brilliant as
every other Rick, it's the system that has put him into this slave-wage job and has,
you know, oppressed his individuality and his ability to be himself.
Because by surrounding yourself by innumerable other ricks, you rob yourself of anything
that makes you special as an individual.
And, uh, I mean, that's just one of the many themes that this episode touched on.
Man, there's a lot in this fucking episode.
There's a lot.
This episode bounces all over the place, because it obviously wants to make as many statements
as it can about this world, that this little world is introduced as it can before it leaves.
And, I mean, this episode is a clusterfuck.
Like, let's not- let's get that out of the way, too.
It is totally a clusterfuck that all works.
In the best- it's beautiful, organized chaos.
Like, it all swirls into meaning in the end, and it's- like, that- that final shot of all
the devastation that has been wrought in, like, one day on the Citadel, just specifically
by- I mean, mostly by the villain, but really, more importantly, by the system in place.
That- now, that was fucking- I- I don't want to- over you, but-
Gazomp Kutzwerk- I mean, that's the wrong word, but I feel like using it anyway.
I'm using it as a meme.
I'm using it as the meme version now.
Come to mean masterpiece, but like- It just means good.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's been- B-Tongue ruined it.
It- we ruined it, to be fair, but he used it right.
Um, yeah, it was just- it was just a- a climactic moment.
It was fantastic.
So, yeah, this- this episode is this cap- we- we finally have the return of the plot thread,
the one important plot thread we've been waiting for the whole show, which-
Okay, so the first time I watched Rick and Morty Season 1, I was watching it on the Adult Swim website,
which accidentally played the episode's out of order.
Um, it goes- it went episode 1, 10, 11, and then played the rest.
So this was the- Okay, okay.
The second episode I ever saw was the Council of Rick's episode,
um, which establishes its character, so I- like, all through the show,
I was expecting there to be like an ongoing plot line.
Right, okay.
Because I'd seen that episode, um, but it never- you know,
obviously it didn't get brought up again in season 1, because it was actually episode 10,
never got addressed in season 2.
Like, we still have the Council of Rick's, but this evil Morty that was revealed at the end of season 1 episode 10
has had no callback until the end of this episode twist, which was fucking awesome.
You know, I-
Because I didn't see it coming at all.
That's- that's interesting, because as soon as I saw that there was a Morty candidate running for office,
I immediately knew where it was going.
I didn't at all.
That's interesting.
I had no idea.
It's good to know that I am that much smarter than you.
It feels good.
Well, after he- after he gave his speech, I thought something was up.
Right.
Like, there's- he's too good, um, and- but I was- I didn't figure out that it was going to be him
until the fucking song started playing, and I was like,
oh, you motherfucker.
Well, see, to be fair, I- I do get where the Trump parallels come from in one dimension,
because his whole thing was that he was just an absolute, like, populist,
just telling the people what they wanted to hear,
and totally, like, abusing the weaknesses of democracy,
because he has his own private agenda.
I would consider that- I would say he was more like Obama to me.
Hey, that's a good point.
That's a good damn point.
Everything he says is, like, like, every word out of his mouth is change and hope.
Yeah, you're right.
Like, that's how Obama won, was he just kept promising that, like, you know, he-
he prayed on the fact that people thought the last eight years had been bad,
and that if we change something, it will be good.
Not to mention that Morty is basically from the, like, repressed minority, you know,
quote-unquote, race of this world.
Yeah, exactly.
Frankly, Obama is a perfect parallel.
I saw him more as first black president.
Yeah, well, sure.
Because, like, like, we've said that the racial stuff in this episode is not too direct,
but, like, the most obvious parallel is Morty is- Mortys are black, you know?
Yeah, of course.
And, like, so for him to be the first Morty president is, like, okay, this is first black
president, you know?
Like, to me, it looked like a big Obama parallel.
And, you know, a lot of people would say when Obama got in office, it was basically,
you know, like, nothing really changed.
Yeah, especially now that we can look back at his legacy, we can bear witness to, like,
the dealings he made with the financial system and, like, the elites at the expense of the
lower people.
Not to mention his record number of deportations of the immigrants that everyone thinks for
some reason that Obama was a champion of, but actually wasn't.
And not to mention the countless drone strikes that he, you know, did way more than any president
in history.
If anybody, if you're really woke, you know they're all the same.
All of them are the same.
SUFO is the only political party that knows the truth.
Shut up, fuck off.
So, yeah.
Yeah, I would say, again, I don't think it speaks to any one situation or candidate.
Right, right.
The whole system.
This is what the system is.
This is what it means to have a system.
Correct.
Is that the smart people are going to abuse it.
And the other, like, anyone underneath them is going to be just slotted in somewhere.
You're slotted into society wherever you happen to fit.
And if you're not satisfied with that, you are just going to have a shit life, you know?
Yep.
And yeah, this, it's, for me, the most, like, what I was kind of stuck on throughout the
whole episode was just, like, looking at a rick in a position they're in and going,
like, how does one end up, like, how does a rick get here?
But then I thought about it and, like, how does any of us get where we are?
It's just the circumstances of our birth, right?
You're right.
I wouldn't say that, like, you might think, okay, we work, we're in a, I don't want to
say an intellectual job, but a job that involves thinking.
Right.
Like, we analyze things, we pull it apart.
We're obviously not as smart as scientists.
We're not as smart as others.
But then you have to wonder, well, some of those scientists aren't really that smart.
They just study more.
They just have an aptitude for science, you know?
Sure.
Well, what about a guy who's a blue collar worker who might be smarter than us, but he
just doesn't want to do fru fru bullshit on the internet.
He'd rather fucking do something meaningful that helps the world.
You know, like, like the dirty jobs mentality of, like, this is a job that has to get done.
I'm proud to do it.
So, like, when you think about it, people, you know, the fact that they're all rick,
it's not about being rick.
It's about what happened to rick.
That's exactly right.
What happened to rick within his life.
You know, the first rick we're, like, introduced to in this episode is one called Simple Rick,
who realized at some point that his daughter was the most important thing to him and never
became a super scientist.
And so they captured him and replay his memory on loop and extract his fluids and put it in
a candy so that you can taste what it feels like to be a simple person, which when they
bring that back at the end of the episode, that was one of my biggest, like, standing
ovation moments of the season so far.
It was incredible.
And I knew it was coming.
That one I did see, like, as soon as the guy came, like, the Willy Wonka rick came in
and was talking to him, I was like, what is this guy's angle?
And then as he's taking him out, I'm like, oh, no.
Oh, no.
You hear the voice over, right?
It's like, you know, this rick staged an uprising.
I was like, oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Fuck.
It was fucked up, man.
Cycle never ends.
That was some 1984 shit right there, like some real fucking big brother shit.
Yeah, there's a lot.
The cop, you want to talk about cop rick and morty?
Yeah.
I mean, it was cool that we see a rick as, like, the plucky up and coming, like, youngling
to the experienced savvy morty, who, you know, is basically more or less turned against
his own kind.
You know, again, if you want to make, like, the black parallel, he's just, like, a black
cop.
He's, like, ten penny from San Andreas, from GTA San Andreas, who just, like, hates the
people that he, like, is forced to protect and just wants to, like, I mean, with our
guy here, with our cop morty, he just doesn't give a fuck, and he is just completely jaded
to the system.
And, like, as we see throughout the episode, we'll just happily kill morties, who he views
as, like, unworthy of, you know, participating in the system or whatever, because he has
to, you know, they work in morty town, or, like, morty slum or whatever it's called,
just dealing with the dregs society.
And, yeah, like, his jaded attitude.
And then, of course, there's a little bit of sort of redemption at the end of the episode,
where there's, like, that little spark where he thinks that, like, his partner's unwillingness...
I think he was just...
Yeah.
I think he was fucking with him.
I mean, obviously, he turned...
He does try to kill, you know, like, Goodrich at the end there, and fails, so...
I think there was a spark in there.
I think...
Well, you know, because just based on all the stuff we saw this episode, it feels like
everyone here is miserable, trapped in this system, except the people at the very top.
Everyone's just fucking forced into this role they don't really want.
I feel like Cop Morty's, like, cry of desperation was real, but then also was his attempt to murder his own partner
to get away with being a corrupt cop, you know, perpetuating the system.
And that's the crime, man.
Perpetuating the system is the one crime that's...
It's, like, the biggest...
It's the biggest problem, you know?
You can't enable the shit to continue.
And now we're just talking about, like, real-life shit.
That's where it's...
That's the thing this episode felt like real-life shit.
That's why I got fucking emotional after watching it.
It was like, I don't know if I want to watch that again, because it fucking was hard, you know?
I had to watch it again because the narrative was so great, and I loved all the characters.
I would say this is the roughest episode of Rick and Morty for me, like, so far.
I mean, there's been some rough ones, but this one's, like, ooh.
Like, because there's no real levity in this episode.
Like, it's funny, it's entertaining, but it's more of, like, it's funny in more of a, oh, shit, kind of way, you know?
Like, it's never, like, ah-ha-ha, funny joke.
It's more, like, oh, you fucking bastards.
Like, again, the Rick cycle where the...
When the guy is then hooked up to the chair to be the new source of candy.
Like, that is a dark, dark joke.
That is a bleak joke, you know?
So there's never a moment of, like, just a fun, ha-ha joke.
It's all, like, oh, you know, damn.
And there's lots of, like, really good dialogue in this episode.
So there's one Morty who's been literally programmed...
He's an experimental Morty programmed to be dramatic.
Like, he's programmed to be...
As he puts it, to make you sad and kind of bored.
Which is fucking hilarious.
But then, like, his line where they're, like...
He says, like, I want, you know, I want the system to be fixed on the Citadel.
Like, I want things to be good here.
And the other kids, because he's at a wishing well,
we have to throw in something important in order to get your wish.
And he says, I want things to be good here.
And they're like, you better throw in something really important.
And he said, well, I hope so.
And he jumps in.
And, like, as soon as he said the line...
I hope so, but I doubt it.
Yeah, I hope so, but I doubt it.
And when he said the line, I knew what he was going to do.
And it was just like, oh, fuck, that's such a...
Ah!
It was fucking powerful, man.
That whole thing, incidentally, was a parallel to the film Stand By Me, if you're familiar with it.
Yeah, I caught that.
Yeah, yeah.
I caught the...
That was Stand By Me.
The cop thing is probably...
I mean, there's multiple stories that are like that.
The one that comes to my mind is Training Day.
You know, because it's the same kind of...
Like, the Rick Cop is not just a starry-eyed...
He learns quickly, he's quick on his feet, and he will shoot someone if he has to.
And he did.
He has the power in him to do that.
And when he fucking kills his partner at the end, and he's just like, same old story.
Rick's killing Morty's.
And it's just like...
You know, like...
Yeah.
It was fucking brutal.
Oh, then, of course, we haven't talked about the campaign running Morty.
The other kind of wage slave Morty guy.
He was sort of the other kind of tied into the main plot there.
So, there's just another guy sort of similar to the Candy Making Rick, as I gave them a little name.
So, campaign Morty there.
Campaign manager for the Morty who's trying to run for office.
And of course, I mean, we're gonna get to it, but I love the whole...
It's just so brilliant to me.
This is the exact perfect way for evil Morty to seize control through this kind of system.
Like, there's no way...
I mean, I would have been hugely, like, eyebrow raising skeptical if this Morty had, like, somehow through force taken over the system here.
And in fact, my one curiosity at the end of the episode was, through what exact force is president Morty,
evil Morty, controlling the ricks that just, like, assassinate a bunch of the business leaders of the world,
like the Illuminati members?
Is it just his presidential authority?
I guess that's pretty good.
I would assume they just worked for him already.
Like, he's offering them something, you know?
Yeah, he must be, he must be.
We don't know what his angle is yet.
Right, we don't.
Like, because I couldn't tell if his aim is to perpetuate the system, but under Morty rule,
or if it's to change the system in some way to benefit himself.
It's hard to say, because at the end, like, the council, the Rick Business Council,
are all people who say, you know, we were the real ones running things from behind the scenes even before.
So for Morty to assassinate all of them means that now there is an opportunity for a full stop change,
since both the real council of ricks and the, you know, CEO ricks are all dead.
But who knows what he's trying to do?
We can at least infer from the way that he has gotten into this position,
and killing these people, you know, the way he did,
and being willing to manipulate the system in this way,
that he certainly does not mind sacrificing pawns on his way to the top.
And he, I mean, the main thing that's been brought up about this Morty
is that he has this weird, like, receiver thing under his eye,
which makes me think that he's either doing this all under, like, either a Rick's command,
or maybe he's a Rick in disguise, maybe, like, there's something about this Morty
that he's not quite just Morty.
That's true. That's true.
I really hope that he's not. I really would hate it if it turned out that there was a Rick behind all this.
I want this to be the one Morty who has some special spark that makes him, you know, equal to a Rick in his own way.
I mean, I don't know what the receiver thing is, but maybe he's a robot or something.
Yeah, maybe.
There's something about this one that he can push things into his eyeballs.
If you remember, I think the quote-unquote evil Rick that we first met him under,
that turned out to be a robot, as I recall, so, like, we don't actually know who his Rick originally was.
So maybe they're, like, so his Rick is unaccounted for, and, you know, there's always a Rick to every Morty,
so that was certainly something that I want to know about.
Yeah, there's a lot going on with this guy, and I don't know if we'll get any more answers this season.
They might be playing the really long game with this particular mystery, you know?
But just, this was so satisfying the way they doled it out.
Like, yeah, I was waiting for it for a long time, and I was, you know, just desperate for it.
But, like, to then have it sprung upon you in such a brilliantly written way, in such a satisfying way,
kind of makes it, maybe not completely worth it, but, like, just now that we've got it feels so much better for it.
Yeah.
It's good stuff, man.
Well, is there any other things you have written down or anything?
Any other stuff you want to address about this episode?
I think there was, actually.
Oh, oh, I remember.
The one other thing that I'm interested in is I'm really wondering what is going to be the event that,
there's got to inevitably be a clash with Evil Morty here, and I'm just really excited to see our Morty,
who has been previously established, at least possibly, to be the most Morty Morty, or the Prime Morty,
or whatever it was.
The Good Morty.
The Good Morty, yeah, that's a fair way to frame it.
I'm very interested to see him do something, and even in this very episode, like, at the very beginning,
you know, you can just feel Morty beginning to strain at the bonds of, like,
when they're like, yeah, you know, he's talking back to Ricksmore,
and the whole, his increasing nihilism as we've been going through this series,
just showing a maturity of the character, I'm very interested to see.
I definitely have the feeling that the final confrontation of Rick and Morty will be between the two Mortys.
It seems that way to me, too.
The Good Morty, the ultimate Good versus the ultimate Evil Morty, and, you know, and maybe Rick,
I don't know what Rick will do, but like, that is definitely going to be what he comes down to, I think.
He'll be busy.
I think they're building up both of these Mortys to be, to have a showdown.
And you know what's great, you know what's great about this?
While Rick is, like, a master of, like, technology and time and space and a literal God,
like, what's the one thing that Rick is just bullshitted dealing with?
It's dealing with people.
And that's the one thing that politics, like, politics is control over people.
That's the one avenue that Morty could excel at that Rick just has, has no luck with.
So by, like, controlling the counsel of Rick's and, you know, playing his cards right,
I totally can understand how a Morty could actually get this kind of leverage.
It's been shown to us in a thousand ways how Rick is a total fuck-up at managing his relationships.
So it just, I'm just so satisfied with it.
And the fact that it is relevant to our culture and even our current political climate is just like a cherry on top.
And it's fascinating and great.
It's brilliant writing.
All right, everybody.
Catch you next week.
Hope it's as good as this one.
Doubtful of that, but we'll see.
Doubtful, but, you know, always hope.
It's been, it's been a bunch of good episodes in a row, I think, so, yeah.
Looking forward to it.
Bye, everybody.
Bye-bye.