Hello Pizzanos, what's going on? It's episode 3 of Motherfucking RickstieMinutes with BestGuyEver and Digibro.
I don't give a fuck bitch!
Yeah, that's my guy. And alright everybody, it's this episode that's gotten a lot of publicity.
A lot of dank memes coming out of the woodwork for this one. Pickle Rick. Pickle Rick everybody.
Fucking Rick. What were they thinking?
Genius. Genius is what they were thinking.
How high do you even have to be to come up with Pickle Rick? It's absolutely absurd.
So let's talk about the premise of Pickle Rick.
Alright, they literally just came up with like let's make Rick a pickle and then they made an episode about it.
And it's great because these people are good writers and they don't fuck up and everything is perfect.
I think with this episode what they were going for is because I feel like this show has gotten really into the habit of trying to fuck with the viewer's expectations.
I think they seem to have a firm grasp on what people think Rick and Morty is and how they can fuck with you in that.
So with Pickle Rick, they wanted you to be deeply concerned about this.
It seems like a stupid meme that this seems completely retarded. Why is Rick a fucking pickle?
The way that Morty reacts to him at the start of the episode is just like, what? Why would you do this? This is a stupid idea.
Because I can tell, I can just see Justin Roiland walking into the room and going, Pickle Rick! We're going to make him a pickle!
Rick's going to be a pickle and everyone's like, no, no, that's stupid. He's like, ah, no, Pickle Rick!
And then they had to do it.
I have no doubt that's what went down.
I have no doubt either.
Yeah, but it's just great.
Yeah, I feel like that's exactly what they're going for. Everyone in the episode is reacting to this with exactly like the dry, you know, exasperation that you would expect in a situation like this.
And then it's a fucking great episode anyway.
You know, we can even read in, like Rick himself says, he says this ironically because he doesn't actually mean it, but he says, I did this to challenge myself to see if I could turn myself back.
And I feel like the writers did this to challenge themselves of like, okay, let's take one of the stupidest ideas that Roiland's ever shouted at the top of his lungs while walking into the room and see if we can actually make that a cool episode.
And they did. They succeeded.
Yeah, that's interesting that you frame it as a challenge because I think of it more as just like an expression of just like how superior the people making this show are compared to the rest of the landscape.
Because like, you can have, so you can have like a good premise, you know, you can go on and you can have yourself a good premise.
But if your writers are shit, if like the team doesn't have its act together, it can easily be garbage. There's so many things you can fuck up.
These people, they simply know what the fuck to do to make a good show and there's almost no premise that they can fuck up if they put the effort in, which they clearly did here.
And it was great. It was a great episode.
Yeah, I mean, I feel like you can watch the train of thought unfolding as this goes on of like, okay, Rick's a pickle and there's literally no one's around to do anything about it.
What is like the natural course of events is going to happen? Like something has to get him off the desk, a cattle come in, you know, something's going to have to get him off the porch, a rain's going to come in.
Well, if it rains, he's going to fall down the drain. Well, if he goes down the drain, what's going to be down there? Cockroaches. What can we do with those?
And then from there, it's just like building up this. It's like spore almost, you know, it is just like spore. Yeah.
I mean, what I what I loved about this episode was and Rick and this is like the general thesis I was thinking about for this episode.
What would it make me think about Rick and Morty? Rick and Morty like better than almost, I don't know.
I'm not going to say better than any other show, but like it's so great at being logically consistent with like the just what it's having its characters do and like the things they have at their disposal and like the laws going on.
So OK, when I first heard about a pickle, Rick, I thought they would do something like have him like hop around, be like a pickle man who could just like, you know, I don't know, roll and do things like that.
But a pickle doesn't have fucking muscles. It can't move. So like right from the start, they establish Rick cannot move anything except his face and tongue.
That's the entirety of what like like the tools in his toolbox to deal with the situations that he finds himself into.
And like I was expecting them to fuck that up and like I'd see him like inching like a worm or like wiggling around or something, but they never do that.
It was even fucking with my brain at first to like when he was laying there and I was like, can't he just roll?
And I'm like, well, I guess he wouldn't like that's the expectation, right? That's exactly it.
We've watched so many of these fucking cartoons that would make us think that like a pickle can. Yeah, of course you can roll.
It's a pickle. Why it's going to roll. But like, no, he's got no fucking muscles in his body, which you can tort his mass to make him roll.
So like, yeah, it just it's exactly how it should be. It's exactly how it should be.
And then, you know, and then just because Rick is such a fucking genius, he can cocks these amazing situations to give himself fucking limbs and like powers and weaponry and all the shit he needs to get through.
Oh, it's the best. And like that moment where where he like plugs like the brain plug into his fucking, you know, pickle brain.
And I was like visceral. And I was like, yeah, that's just what you have to do. God, I love how Rick is not afraid at all to get his hands dirty.
And like, like so many people you got disgusting man. I know it's a nightmare. It's a fucking nightmare. It was it was hard to watch for me when he was in the with the cockroaches and everything.
Like licking the things fucking brain. I was just like, why? Why do I have to look at this?
You know, just to be just just to be have the appearance of fairness, though, the one thing that I thought was a little bit ridiculous is how he puppeted the cockroach with his tongue by touching its brain.
That's that's the one thing that's like, all right, I mean, is there any way that would it was awesome? Like it was done with great effect.
I was I got over that quickly. It was not a big deal. I mean, the fact that he like the moment he because I didn't know what he like, I thought he was going to have it somehow.
I don't know. Carry him transport. No, he bites his fucking head open. And I was like, oh my God, what are you doing?
I just love what like a fucking badass Rick is. He's not like Doc Brown, who was like this clumsy, you know, the characters based on like clumsy weirdo science man who doesn't really get his hands dirty just because of the nature of the show.
But Rick is a fucking murdering monster. He'll just go he'll genocide a country. That's what I think we do. Whatever.
I think I can say officially that they are trying to make Rick and Morty the most violent show of all time now.
Like, you think so?
Like, I mean, the show has always had some violence. But like you look back at season one, like episode one, they kill a bunch of bug men.
There's some green blood here and there. Like, there's a little, you know, there's like there's a little violence here and there.
There's moments of some of some violence when Rick blows up the king. But most of them are like green or blue blood. You know, it's not a lot of like humans getting eviscerated horribly.
And season two kicked it up with the purge planet. That was where it was really like a season two is pretty fucking violent overall.
But purge planet was like another level. But this season, every episode has just been a fucking bloodbath. Like insane amounts of violence going on in this show now.
You're not wrong. You're not wrong at all. I think, I suspect that there, I think that it just kind of happens to be that way.
Maybe there is an intention. Maybe they are going in that direction. Like, but it seems to me like they perfectly make sense for the premise of each of the episodes.
So maybe they do just have an inclination to write more violent stories. But like they were just doing a, yeah, go on.
I think Adult Swim has kind of had like a long standing desire to have the most violent show on television.
Like if you think back, like they had that Korgoth the Barbarian pilot, which was just nonstop violence. Metalocalypse was really fucking violent.
In spite of not even being an action show, managed to have like insane violence in every episode, you know.
Yep, and it ruled.
Most of their shows have had like insanely violent episodes where they'll just be like blood literally everywhere.
There's that one.
I think of like an Aquatine Hunger Force when the fucking spider like just collecting everyone's blood.
That was the episode that made me stop watching Aquatine. I never was real. I was never a big Aquatine guy at all.
But that's when I'm like, this show is definitely not for me.
That's the only episode I loved of Aquatine Hunger Force because there was so much blood. It was awesome.
I just never laughed and then I got grossed out. So I'm like, why the fuck am I even watching this? There was no reason.
Yeah, well, I mean, we haven't even touched on like the other half of this episode.
That is also legitimately great and makes, I think this is for the first time, makes Daughteru, whose name I forget.
I think this is the most I've ever liked her as a character. They're really finally digging down and we're exploring her character more.
Just for the one line where she's like, one of my favorite jokes in the episode.
From that scene anyway, everything involving Rick was hilarious and awesome.
Like I was laughing constantly at everything that went on with Pickle Rick.
The other scene is much more serious. It's like this actual deep seated psychological thing going on where like they literally just go to a counselor
and they spend the whole episode just like having a family meltdown essentially or mainly Beth who won't open up and be honest with their feelings.
And they're just getting royally fucking owned by this counselor, which I knew was going to happen.
Like the whole episode, I was like, they're going to get fucking owned by this bitch.
Which is appropriate because like we understand all their nuances. We know what's going on.
So they can't like hide that shit or right. It's good.
And so that's all going on.
But my favorite line, my favorite joke line for that is when Summer, who the whole episode we have known that she apparently huffed pottery,
glaze or something. That's part of why they're here because Morty pissed his pants at school and she huffed pottery.
And it has been assumed that this is because of their family situation.
And the funniest part is that there's this reveal that it really wasn't about that at all.
Summer just wanted to get high and Morty is just an idiot.
So that reveal was probably my favorite joke in the episode when Summer's like,
I'd like to be thought of as someone who just likes to get high.
Yeah, Summer fucking killed it with that line. That was great.
Her fucking voice acting was amazing this episode.
The line when the teacher comes out of the room and she's like, none of us have ever eaten poop.
Like however she says it was just like spot on. I fucking loved it.
That was great. I will say though, I think the poop jokes just kind of fell flat for me.
I got it the first time and then they just kept doing it.
That was fine. I just didn't care.
Not as funny as the number of times they used it, but whatever. It wasn't a big deal.
Well, the reason why Rick is a pickle, of course, is because he's trying to get out of this counseling thing.
That's what's revealed. And so there's this plot setup.
I mean, I assume everyone is watching this in the episode.
But nonetheless, there's this. He's got this thing set up where he's going to...
As soon as they leave, there's a timer and it's going to inject him with human serum, whatever.
He's going to turn it back to a human.
So that's the undercurrent going on through the episode.
And Beth takes it away from him because it's immediately obvious what he's trying to do.
And then her and the therapist and the kids are exploring how they know that obviously is what this is.
And yet Beth just can't bring herself to fucking question her father in the slightest.
And I forget how that resolves. Did she actually... Did she challenge him at all at the end?
I think she did a little bit, but then immediately gave it back to him.
I honestly don't remember how that resolved.
She kind of just like... The ending of the episode, they're both clearly shook by what they've experienced at the psychological place.
The only thing she says is like, you shouldn't have lied to me.
She almost doesn't. He says, I'm sorry I lied.
And she's like, oh, it's okay. Well, you shouldn't have lied, but it's okay.
She barely concedes.
It's really him who does the apologizing.
Even she can't get past it, even when he can admit some truth.
And it's great that even throughout the whole...
At the end, she is resistant the entire time.
Beth is the one who's fighting the therapist the entire fucking session.
At the end, after the therapist does her monologue, it just lays out exactly what Beth's problems are.
In no uncertain terms that we basically already know.
The kids are just like, I liked her.
Can we go back?
That was great.
Their faces at the end of the episode was like, that hit me, man.
The way that the other two were trying to be so casual, and the kids know that these two are shaken by this.
And they're trying to break through the facade like, hey, can we be honest?
Can we go back?
I kind of liked it. It was kind of enriching.
That's almost a little bit too real right there.
Because every day, people out there, we all do it.
We all lie to ourselves about the way that we kind of wish that we were.
We trick ourselves.
I'll give you a real example right now.
I tell people that I go to the gym three times a week.
I often miss Fridays because I just get caught up doing stuff.
But I still tell people that I go three times a week.
That's me kind of lying to make myself feel better about it, even though I'm not being the obligation I've set for myself.
I mean, that's a small little thing.
But these people are lying about like, Beth's whole life has been destroyed.
And her kids, their lives are put in danger every moment that Rick is around, more or less.
Because he just doesn't give a fuck.
And it's like the ultimate danger to the fucking universe.
And especially the kids.
And she just enables and enables and enables because she is personally fucked up by her abandonment issues from him as a kid.
And the fact that she isn't willing to deal with her issues and is just pushing them off,
well, the kids are like, no, mom, please, we should go back.
You should go back.
This is how we all get better as people and healthier and become a better family.
She's just pushing it away so she doesn't have to take responsibility or confront like her own issues.
That's real shit, man.
That is real shit.
And that's why this is the best Beth has ever been.
I really liked it.
Yeah, that was great.
And the fucking speech that the counselor gives at the end.
I mean, this is awesome.
It's some very real shit.
She hits them with, there are wrong and right ways this scene could be done.
But it just feels very matter of fact to me that like she says she is not like making fun of them or anything.
It's not like she's this huge comeback.
She just like lays out exactly here's what your issues are.
Like, you know, anybody in my field would know this.
Like this is not like me being magic rocket scientists.
It's just like, this is what psychology is.
You avoid it because it's not interesting to you for the same reason that like normal shit is not interesting to me.
But like, it hit me in a very personal way because this is one of the most relatable problems I've heard on this show.
Let me describe what I've done today.
I've, right before we did this podcast, I was doing another one that I had to do for Patreon.
And right after this podcast, I will be doing another one that I do with Monkey Jones every week.
And right before I did that other podcast, I had recorded a vlog and was working on a different one.
Like I've worked on like five projects today.
What I haven't done is clean my office, which has not that dirty, but there's a little bit of stuff around.
Haven't really eaten.
I should have made myself a sandwich, but it was going to take too long.
So I ate two frozen waffles instead and now I'm still hungry.
I should have fucking paid this goddamn $350 I owe to the state of New York for a speeding ticket that I got in May.
And I need to pay in within the next four days.
The reason I haven't done that is because it would require me to go to the post office, which is right up the road.
But that would be not working.
It would be boring.
It would be normal work upkeep shit.
It would just be daily life shit and daily life shit never takes precedence in my mind over doing something interesting.
The only times I go do this shit is when I don't have anything scheduled or planned.
I don't have any ideas for videos.
You know, like it's the days when I'm not feeling creative that I go and I finally get the other shit done.
I go and clean up the house.
I go, oh, I don't have an idea for a video.
So I guess I'll like, you know, brush my teeth.
That's never going to happen.
I'll go pick up the trash, you know, like that's the day that that shit gets done because, you know, it just doesn't feel like an adventure.
And I want everything to feel like an adventure.
I want everything to be larger than life, never to just be like normie shit, you know, even though you need the normie shit because your mind cannot handle not being kept up.
That's why you need to keep a clean space because you feel better and you do better work.
You know, if you dedicate that hour every day to fucking developing an environment that you can live in, you know, and don't have the looming stress of, oh, God, will this fucking thing get to the courts in time for me to not owe the government whatever
like interest on this shit, you know, because I have just been holding onto these envelopes.
They've been sitting on my desk like in my line of sight for two weeks now, you know.
I know the feeling well.
I had been putting off getting car insurance for a while and I finally got it.
But it took me months to just get around to doing it, even though like every day I didn't have it, I was at risk, you know, it's just like, it's so true.
That's such a relatable thing.
Every fucking person in the world does this shit.
And especially now that like, I don't know, we're all consumed by like fantasy of like Hollywood shit and anime and all this magical shit that we wish would happen in our lives.
We just want to, like every movie is the most interesting portion of those characters' lives and we all want that to be happening to us all the time.
And you know, people back in the old days, like, they didn't know what they were missing.
So day-to-day life, you know, maybe it wasn't so bad.
I think there's lots of people, it's like she says, some people can handle work and some people can't.
And I think most people, like what we define as normies, what we insult by calling normies are people who can work.
People who like can do something every day because they know it's the right thing to do.
They know it's how you live.
They know that's like what's normal.
And then there's people like me who are just like, I could never work.
Like, I've gotten to the point right now, I don't know if I could work a normal job.
Like, I don't know if that would be possible for me because I've gotten so used to this manic lifestyle of like constantly making new things.
And what's the phrases that Rick says?
It's like, he creates-
Oh, wubba lubba dub dub.
He says like, I'm a scientist, I create, destroy and mutate or something like that.
And I'm like, yeah, like, that's what's on my mind.
Like, if it's not creating or making something new, then what's the point of it, you know?
But the point is obviously, you don't become a fucking psychopath who goes around putting your life at risk every day
and murdering people constantly.
Yeah, he's a little bit out of whack.
You know, I remember when you were first starting your Patreon years ago and shit.
And I remember, you know, when you left your job and stuff.
And you, even back then, you were, you know, saying the sentiment that like, you know, you just don't feel like that's right for you.
And you know, that to me has been like a big strength for you personally.
And that way you are like a Rick.
And that you are just wired for this lifestyle.
That just really seems to me, you know, when I was a kid, I used to think that like everyone could do anything.
And if you're not, you know, like excelling at just the shit that everyone needs to do, then you're just not trying hard enough or something.
But as I've gotten older, I've really started to realize that there really are different kinds of people who are built to do different sort of things,
especially as I've discovered what I'm actually good at.
And, you know, and I, yeah, I don't know, man, she's right about that.
And, you know, one other point that I really liked about just the therapist in general, I really liked how it would be so easy for a show like this to just like,
you would think that like a nihilist framed show or like a show with themes of nihilism about it would, would like, it would be so easy for it to shit on the idea of psychology in general.
Exactly like, like Rick does and just be like, this is total fucking bullshit, man.
I decide my own destiny, you know, there's nothing controlling me.
I'm controlling my own thoughts and mind and all that shit.
But the show really does take a more mature stance at it.
And even though like, you know, jokes are thrown in, of course, it's a comedy fucking show with like the poop stuff and whatever.
Like, despite all that, she is absolutely like a professional at her craft and has real things to offer these characters.
And it's obvious and the characters understand it and accept it in the form of Morty and Summer.
Whereas our, our less mature people who are just pushing away their problems, the parents, those are the problem people who don't understand the real benefits that could be here.
I just appreciate that, that, that feels refreshing to me that they're not just like shitting on it.
I feel like I've seen that a thousand times.
I think my favorite part of it is the way, the favorite, my favorite part of her speech and how it's framed is that like,
she keeps saying like, you know, to Rick, like you have this amazing level of intelligence.
Like she recognizes like, Rick, you are smarter than me.
But this is what I do is like, understand how people think.
I know how you think.
Like the fact that you're smarter than me doesn't preclude me from like this specialization that I have,
which is to understand how your mind works, whether I actually like understand the concepts that you do or not.
Which is something I find really interesting about psychology in general is that like, it's in some ways an equalizer.
Like we're all humans at the end of the day.
Like how the human mind works is not something that you have a better grasp on just by having a higher IQ.
Like your IQ doesn't affect your emotions.
It doesn't affect the chemistry of your brain.
It's just like how much shit you know and can know.
And that's clearly, you know, what Rick's strengths are in as opposed to self-awareness and that and other kind of shit.
Yeah man, it's good stuff.
And it's funny, I just watched all of the Sopranos not too long ago, which has, I didn't even know this at the time,
but before I started watching it, the fact that Tony Soprano goes to a therapist, a psychiatrist, yeah.
Like is a big undercurrent throughout the whole thing.
And there's a lot of like dream analysis and, you know, he spends a lot of time talking to her and understanding his motivations for why he like lives this gangster lifestyle and stuff.
And it was really interesting there and it's really interesting here.
It's good stuff.
Yeah.
I mean, the only other thing I wanted to talk about was kind of just like the progression, the specific progression of like Rick in his journey
throughout, you know, like acquiring the materials he needed to do the shitty comedy, the gigantic action battle scene at the end, which was fucking dope.
So just like the way that Rick, I feel like we've already blown our load here, but nonetheless, like the way that Rick starts out as an immobile pickle.
And then like you were said, like the cat kicks him off the table or whatever, rain comes down, he gets flushed down the drain into the sewer.
He then lures over a cockroach with like spewing brine.
So he's like using pickle special abilities in order to do that, which was dope.
The only special ability a pickle has, which I'm glad they didn't try to like stretch that, you know.
Yeah.
There's one thing he could do and they used it and then.
Oh, how about, how about when he gets hurt later on and in order to bandage his wound, he uses like mustard and hot sauce and then staples a pickle to his wound to hold him like his pickle guts.
It was fucking genius.
Like just from a burger that was sitting there.
Holy shit.
That was amazing.
They just commit so hard.
Close my pickle hole with more pickle.
It was fucking great.
Well, while like, of course, you know, while he's fighting this guy, Jaguar, Jaguar, whatever, who fucking just like burns it's shut or whatever.
God, it was fucking great.
I don't know.
Like I didn't, there was nothing particularly amazing about like, okay, well, once, once Rick like controls these cockroaches.
So he lures over the brine, he bites his head, snaps his neck and then starts puffing his brain with his tongue.
He then like, then we kind of accelerate to, okay, now he's just gotten to the point where he's building like some machines out of like the various limbs of cockroaches that now that he can move himself, that he can get, get a hold on.
And he eventually makes like this battle armor that he can use to fucking chop up these rats in this like amazingly gory fucking fight.
It was so dope.
I got it was the best.
The fucking shit he says to the big rat at.
Yeah.
Classic.
Like I didn't even give you a name.
I could have called you scar.
I call you nothing because you're nothing to me.
You aren't even worthy to be my adversary.
But like even the fact that he's addressing the rats, like that rat instantly has character to us as the viewers.
Yeah.
Man, it was so good.
It was so good.
This was a.
Where the fuck was he by the way?
Like what, what was this cartel place he was in?
Like I assume because they say like there's lines like this country is a prison and stuff like that.
That's right.
I'm assuming he's in Mexico and some kind of drug cartel place.
Where is their house?
Like do they live in California?
Like why are they so close to the border?
Because Rick says he's five minutes away by helicopter from his daughter.
So.
I guess.
Yeah.
I guess they must be.
Are they like right on the border of Mexico or something?
Based on the clear like Latin influences on the characters and shit.
Like yeah.
I guess they must be close to the Mexican border.
Oh yeah.
I forgot about that.
They're just piling up.
I guess they're close to the Mexican border.
Yeah.
Or something like that.
I don't know.
Maybe there's a Mexican installation in the U.S. somewhere.
I don't fucking know.
Yeah.
Something like that.
Well, that's that was cool.
The the fight I really liked after I just want to mention like how amazing that mouse
muscle exoskeleton was.
God, it was so fucking sick.
And I loved that like it's not like he constructed like human anatomy out of rat parts.
Like he clearly still had like rat legs and rat limbs and they didn't.
I love how you could see the the tendon moving independently of the arm.
Of the bone.
Yeah.
I noticed that straightening out.
That looked really cool.
That was fucking dope.
And then the subplot with Jaguar was kind of funny.
It's all right.
Didn't have a big pay off.
Wasn't that great.
The fight scene was the coolest part.
I think I'm hoping they because they brought back Jaguar for the after credits scene.
That was funny.
Right.
I'd feel like maybe they were doing that so that that wouldn't have to happen later
because like Jaguar is a surviving character.
So he could come back.
But I don't think he's that funny or memorable that he should come back.
You know, I think that ending gag was all the payoff that character will ever need.
He could show up in like the background or a crowd or you know, whatever.
We'll probably get murdered somewhere in the background of another episode.
Probably.
I mean, he's really tough.
He fought toe to toe against Rick and came out came out alive.
He fought toe to toe against Rick as a pickle with rattles.
Oh, yeah.
Well, yeah, but he was rocking it.
Oh, man, dude, how sick was his fucking like laser gun?
We're using like individual batteries for the fucking charges.
God, damn, that was awesome.
Well, all right.
Well, that's it, man.
I mean, we kind of went in a circular circuitous route there, but that pretty much covers the
whole episode and how fucking great it was.
I give this like a big wreck.
I'm going to give this like a strong nine.
I feel like maybe a mid to strong nine.
It's very solid.
The only complaint I would have is that like the subplot that's in the psychology office
is just very like, you know, it's just like one location with flat shots, you know, like
it's not that interesting to look at.
You know, I hear what you're saying.
I just like that as is a juxtaposition.
I felt like this was intentional to like the crazy environments that Pickle Rick is going
to they made it deliberately drab to juxtapose like the insane life Rick has, especially
as Pickle Rick versus them.
So, you know, I thought it worked, but, you know, I understand your criticism nonetheless.
Yeah, that's it.
See you later.
Oh, fuck yourselves.
Bye-bye.