Hello everybody and welcome to another episode of Rick's D Minutes. We're back with the finale
of season 3, episode 10, the Rick Churri and Morty date. The last episode of Rick's D Minutes
for the foreseeable future. Yeah, possibly for years. Could be years until the next one.
Unless we decide to like go back and do the other seasons at some point. Which we could
do. Feeling masochistic. Maybe as like a batch we could do the season or something. But in
any case. It could be more interesting because those ones already have commentary and stuff
that we could go through. Right. Which I have not watched any of but would very much like
to based on what you've told me about them. They're really fun. They're worth watching.
But anyway. Let's get into it. So, Rick Churri and Morty date. Oh, I'm Digibro by the way.
Oh, that's right. I can't use Kyver. There you go. Yeah. And yeah, this is the season finale.
Kind of sprung on me out of nowhere because for some reason previously on Wikipedia it had
suggested that this would be a 13 episode season. So, I really thought they were like
going all out and making it a longer one. And considering how much
plot development happened this season, it felt like that would be the case.
Yes. But then suddenly it was just, oh, episode 10. That's the last one. It's just fucking over.
Did you feel, I don't remember where I read this. But somewhere I think I read that
Justin Royland specifically said like, yeah, we were supposed to do 13. It got shrunk down to 10.
Sorry about that. Next time we'll try to do better. If that's the case. I have the feeling
that there were a lot of production mishaps on this season. And that that contributes a lot
to why it took so fucking long to make. Because there was a definite sensation I had from this
episode. And this is skipping right to the end. But the last scene sort of restores things
to normal. Like they were in season one sort of gets us back to the status quo.
And Beth says like outright, it's basically going to be like season one except more streamlined
from now on. Indeed. And I couldn't help but think that what happened here, like what happened with
this whole season was that by the end of season two, they'd written themselves into this place
where it's like we are now going to do a continuous narrative with this show. Right.
And I think maybe in the process of trying to hash out what that continuous narrative is,
it became apparent that this was not a good idea or that they didn't know how or that there just
wasn't a way. And so they went, yeah, let's let's just address all the open ended things
this season and then just kind of wrap back into something normal that we can continue with,
you know, that's how it felt to me. I would be inclined to agree. And especially the whole
ending scene feels extremely tacked on to the end of this. I mean, what's fascinating to me
about this episode, correct me if I'm wrong, but I feel like this is the first episode of
Rick and Morty where the B plot has been a thousand times better than the A plot. And it was it was
so unusual for the show to spend so much time on this, this whole like presidential like
breakup, you know, like bad feelings thing. And then like, and then we get to the thing that
actually matters. Like last episode, we were like, Oh man, will they ever address will we ever see
an addressing happened in this episode and we're past it. It's done. The questions are answered in
the trash. It goes amazing and not in a good way. I kind of feel, yeah, it's a weird feeling.
I can easily imagine the writers with this story seeing it kind of spiraling out of control and
getting to because like, if you look back at what Rick and Morty was, what the successful formula
was like season one was not great because it had an ongoing plot. It had little tidbits of like
emotional stuff that carries over. Like, you know, in one episode, they ditched their universe in
another episode, it's confirmed that they are still in the ditched universe. There is a continuity.
Bro, that's abnormal in some way. And then by the time we get to Rick has overthrown the government
of the entire cosmos. And like, there's all this background shit going on. And now Beth,
what if she goes and has her own adventure? And I have the feeling someone had to go like,
we can't write about Beth and her adventures because this is going to get so unfocused.
Oh, they fucked up so bad. The correct way to handle that we already addressed. At least I
think we did last episode. You just go have her do her adventures. And then like in a season or two
or whatever, you can have an episode about that Beth. And then it blinds everyone. We're like, oh
my God, we totally forgot about that. But this has been the fake bet the whole time. This recontextualizes
everything I thought. Like everyone would have loved that. It would have been super cool. But
they're just like, no, too much work. We can't do all that. We just want to address it. But yeah,
I mean, but then if they leave that open thread, then it's just one more thing they got to worry.
I guess there was something cheap about like, and I'm not celebrating that they did this
necessarily. But I couldn't help but feel like the ending of this season was their way of going,
just put it all back to normal. I don't want to do this anymore. You know, fuck, what have we done?
And just seeing that, you know, that several episodes have commented on the slowness of the
season coming out, the fact like the conflicts and getting it made, like it's pretty clear that
Dan and Justin have, I've only been picking up like random things like tertiary knowledge about
this. But people have been saying like that they've been addressing a lot of issues like apparently
Dan Harmon hated the episode we hated. The vindicators. That's right. Yeah, the vindicators.
And good man. He's got good taste, obviously. Yeah. And so it makes me think, man, it must have
just been fucking chaos putting the season together. Like I'm thinking that they hit
simultaneously the most ambition they wanted to have with the show and the least they could
actually do with the show at the same time. You know, that's the kind of feeling I'm getting.
But this is all speculation. And it's interesting because this show has absolutely blown up this
season. This has been the season post season two. I mean, it was a long time after post season two
into this, but now people are really paying attention to the show just in time for it to
stumble a little bit, stumble along its way. Not completely, obviously. Some of these episodes
were fantastic. Yeah. Yeah, I don't know. Maybe it's unavoidable. But I don't know. Is this still
going to happen? You think as the show clearly is taking on an even bigger role than it had
previously. The funny thing about Rick and Morty, and this was already the case in season two,
is it's too big for itself. Yeah. Like it's too successful because it's on fucking adult swim.
Right. Like it's never going to be a like high budget production. It's always going to be like
this weird off kilter passion project. And the fact that it has this kind of attention is kind of
like strange. It's almost like with my little pony friendship is magic, a show we're both very
familiar with where the show suddenly erupts in popularity right around the time that the actual
lead writer is leaving because like it sucks to work on the show. And then you get this weird,
muddied storyline and production where as the show is getting more popular, it's also getting
worse. And I feel like we're seeing something similar here. I don't even necessarily think
the season is worse, but like there's clearly been issues with the production where like the
popularity of the show is taking people from the show and leaving them not able to actually
make the show that will satisfy its new, huge audience. That's my question. Do you think we'll
finally see a stoppage of the leak of talent from Rick and Morty because it's so popular now?
Will they finally recognize like, okay, that's it. Does it make more money by being more popular?
That's a good question. Is adult swim like able to pay these people enough to keep them, you know?
How have they made all these like spin off like games and shit and all these like shorts and
these 3D, you know, whatever, like all the spin off stuff that's come from Rick and Morty. How the
fuck was it all financed and like where those just if all those make money, then like, okay,
maybe they can pay for themselves. But how do they get people on these projects to make these?
I don't know. I guess it's all part of the zeitgeist that's carried Rick and Morty to the
popularity set now. And I'll say I'm going to, since we're talking about the meta of the season
anyways, to talk about the content of this episode. For the most part, yeah. And I don't hate this
episode. I thought it was fine, but like it's not the one that has the most deep shit to talk about.
Season three as a whole. Compared to the last season finale, like, Jesus Christ.
I almost felt like this one was deliberately retarded. I got a little bit. Like just because
it was so like, so dumb with the president thing, like, like going above and beyond to make the
president this petty idiotic character and to focus so much on this dumb story almost felt like
they were deliberately making sure, you know, like, okay, we're not doing that again. Season two
finale was a fluke. That's not where this is going. We're restoring normalcy. We're going back to
sitcom roots, you know, who's felt like a sitcom episode. Like this episode, in some ways, it felt
almost family guy-esque to me. Yeah. Yeah, totally. But then to be more kind to it, I would compare
it to an episode of the Venture Brothers, like just that kind of sense of irreverence. But while,
you know, applying the unique brand of this show to a sort of classic scenario, like working for
the president, you know, which feels like an old school sitcom premise almost. But yeah, it's
and I think it's a goofy fun time. I enjoyed what I got, but it definitely was weird to see this as
the season finale. Well, that's the whole thing. I really feel I have no way of knowing this is
true enough. But I really think this is just like one of the episodes, considering we know so much
about how many problems that we're just getting this made. And the, you know, we, I wish I had
actually looked this up, but I know somewhere, Justin Rowland said, like, yeah, they fucked up
and they couldn't make as many episodes as they wanted to. I really feel like this was just going
to be an episode in the series. But then they got to the crunch time and they're like, oh, fuck,
we need to make this the season finale. And then they, like they either slapped on the Beth plot
into this and the whole ending thing where they wrapped all that shit up. That's what it feels
like to me. But that's not to say that I didn't enjoy the president stuff, because I did. It was
good and fun. I just the whole time I was sitting here knowing this was the season finale and was
like, okay, ready to be impressed. Here I am sitting here looking for that good shit. Oh,
there's Beth things going on. Something interesting is going to happen with that. And it did. The
Beth plot was interesting. But like so much more time was devoted to the president stuff.
And hey, the fight, the fight that Rick has with the president was like dopey shit. And like,
I love that they incorporated all the things that have been brought up so far about the White House,
you know, that they go through all like, because you don't have to question all this crazy shit
that they're that's happening underneath the White House because we've already established
before that all this shit exists. Have those all been mentioned or have they been shown before?
I thought that about some of them. Remember, he at the beginning, he's talking about how like,
oh, don't go into the like the Lincoln slave, whatever. And like this other way, he's like
him. Yeah, the like Coke room, which they fall into the Coke room. Right. Right. He's faced
a bowl of coke. So you know, like, that's true. But some of the stuff that would have been harder
to explain, I guess, I really like seeing it's like the present the battle president aesthetic.
I was I like surprisingly a lot. He had all this tech, like, my favorite was when he pulls out
like his watch and points the laser at Rick and then an orbiting satellite shoots the laser down
from space. The hammer of dawn from Gears of War. That's the one. That's the one. Yeah, it was
fucking great. And like the little the little twins that he just blows the whistle and turn to monsters.
Yeah, it was good shit, man. That whole fight was great. Yeah, that was by far the most entertaining
part up until that point. It felt a little slow. But the fight was the the Rick and Morty genius
of lots of things happening really fast without explanation. But you kind of get it, you know,
like racing just just a little bit ahead of your able ability to parse the information,
you know, you have to be an intellectual to like Rick and Morty. There it is. There it is. Yeah.
So that leads me into what I really want to talk about meta wise, which is that I hate that the
show has gotten popular and I hate watching it with the world. I couldn't agree more. I know
this is this is this is the most hipster I'm ever going to sound. But I miss when Rick and Morty
was just my show, you know, I know exactly what I feel. And it's not even that I got in on the
ground floor of it. Like I found out about it like throughout season one, I was hearing the
early review saying like this is the best show on TV when no one was talking about it. You know,
film crit Hulk was I think the first person I heard it from. And, you know, I watched I caught up
in between seasons one and two. I got everyone I knew to watch it because I thought it was great.
Watch the commentaries, watch the episodes like four times, you know, and then season two rolled
around. And when they when they were the leaked episodes, I was way excited about them. Like I
watched each of those leaked episodes, you know, multiple times. Yep. And then it came for where
the show was actually airing. And I was watching it week by week. And first of all, I think watching
anything week by week will always make it worse. And this is I've stuck to I firmly fucking believe
in this. And every time I've tried to challenge it, I've come up failing. Like no matter what,
if you watch a show week by week, it will be worse. Because every time it falters a little,
it's a much bigger deal. You know, I marathon season one the first time. And it was just amazing.
Of course, it was just perfect. And I marathoned it like three more times. And I could eventually
pick out which episodes I thought were weaker from the others. But like it never felt like a big
deal. This season, when we got to the Revengencers episode, it was like, this is real. Like for a
whole week, it was like, ah, you know, I legit was not excited about doing this podcast for a lot
of the podcasts run after that episode. To me, like it was always scary. Like am I going to go in and
watch a shitty episode of Rick and Morty and have nothing to say about it? And and and then deal with
the comments who are never appreciative of what we have to say about the show. Like I very quickly
abandoned reading the comments for 60 minutes because it's a lot. It's they're weird because we
get lots of people who don't really know who we are because they're just like looking for Rick
and Morty podcast. I enjoy that. But yeah, I know what you mean. Yeah. And it's it's just been a
it's been a weird experience keeping up with the season. And like I feel like after season two,
which I think everyone agrees was overall great. Like even though for me, I felt less enthusiastic
about it than I was about season one just by way of watching it week by week. I still ultimately
enjoyed it a lot. I think after season two, everyone felt really entitled to great Rick and
Morty. You know, I hear what you're saying. And when season three rolled around and anything wrong
with it got picked apart to shreds because the people like me who loved the first two seasons
and wouldn't shut up about it like idiots like I feel stupid because all I did was rave and rave
and rave about how this show is so perfect. And now every time anything slightly imperfect happens,
everyone like, oh, the female writers. Rick and Morty wasn't the greatest show on television
this week. So, you know, so I mean, these female writers are just such intellectuals. We can't
understand what they're going for. And then people people who fucking rag on the Rick and
Morty fan base, which I as as is always the case, I've never seen the annoying fans. I've only
seen the people complaining about the annoying fans. You know, like I've never once, unless one of
the people who's making fun of them like literally reposts their shit. And then I see it and I go,
yeah, well, that guy's clearly a fucking like retarded, like literally retarded, you know,
like posting that like Facebook group of the people who see themselves as ricks. Yeah, right.
And are like favorite people in the world. And it's like, okay, these people are clearly not
indicative of most of the people watching this show. Like you can't say, oh, the Rick and Morty
fandom are so like, no. Well, you know, that's it's selective reasoning. Because, you know,
of course, you're gonna with people who want to defend the like the fandom, they'll look at the
people they like best and be like, Oh, those are the guys, they're not the real ones. Whereas if
you're on, if you're like looking for a reason, if you hear one person be annoying about Rick
and Morty, you're just gonna be like those fucking fans, they're all like this is the worst.
I don't get that. Like when I see an annoying per idiot, like participating in a fandom, I think,
wow, that's an annoying idiot, you know, has nothing to do with the show they like, because
guess what? Every show has annoying retarded fans. Like I can't name a show that doesn't have any
annoying retarded fans. So this whole position, like it's somehow Rick and Morty's like specifically
has this problem. It's like, no, it's just a show that people are talking about right now. So
those people boil to the surface, you know, it's just the nature of anything that gets too popular.
People will like it. There will always be someone who likes it to an obnoxious degree.
And just be big on the train for a burp. Nothing matters, Morty. Belch every God's not real burp.
I'm gay, Morty. Suck my dick. Yeah, it's inevitable. It's a nature of fandom.
I will say the most gratifying thing about the season was listening to the dick show and hearing
him reference Rick and Morty almost every week. Oh, that's cool. Not even anything specific,
just referencing the fact that he's watching it. And I was always like, yeah, Rick and Morty.
How nice for you, did you? How nice. I'm glad you enjoyed that. That's the best thing about watching
this show for me. You know, now I'm starting to get why people wanted to hear this episode of
60 Minutes come out. Because yeah, I feel a bit of emptiness after watching this episode. Just
and again, I think it is, I wouldn't frame it as entitlement to a good episode, but
heightened expectations certainly are there. And I mean, this was definitely a case where
about four minutes into the episode, I went, oh, okay, you know, maybe not even that far.
Like it was that feeling of I loading up the last episode thinking like, what's is it going to be
a big is it because I haven't heard anything. Nobody's been freaking out. Everybody's been
telling me when are you going to do the last 60 minutes? Nobody's been saying it's a crazy episode.
It's just been when are you going to do it? So I start watching it in a few minutes and I'm like,
oh, it's not going to be anything. Like if this is not going to be a big season closer episode,
you know, it's fine. But it's unfortunate that just like a standalone episode like the like the
toxic episode was like, in my opinion, quite superior to this one. This is like the whole point.
There's this joke of the president is jealous that Rick broke up with them or something. They
have a big president battle. There's some cool stuff that happens. And then Beth immediately has
confronted the issue that was set up last episode about if she's a clone or not. So both the one
was kind of not that interesting. And the other was like kind of kind of a premature ejaculation
on like a thing I was expecting to be a part of the narrative. And just like I was really
looking forward to going into next season as well and thinking about like, ooh, what does this
indicate that this is clone Beth or this is real Beth? What can I learn from this? They didn't have
to go that way. But I was like expecting that. And this really is just like blowing their load
immediately. And it's a little disappointing. So and I do. Yeah, the whole president plot. I mean,
this episode is kind of a sequel to the show me what you got episode season two, which was at
a perfect place in that season. Episode four, we've already been hit with some really heavy
sci fi stuff. Later, we'll get it with some more emotional stuff. But right here, here's a goofy
fun episode about saving America, bringing back which the president himself is not that memorable
a character from the episode. So like bringing him back, I had to kind of take a second and
like I remember thinking, oh, I guess president's still black in the Rick and Morty universe.
And then I remembered that it was a character that they had before. And I was like, oh, right.
Whenever I think about a situation like this, like, so yeah, this is this is basically them
saying like, OK, we've got this character, let's recycle him and do something interesting with
it. And they manage that reasonably OK. The problem that happens every time is that
I always my favorite example to go to is the party God from Adventure Time. The party God in
Adventure Time was the best character ever conceived because he was a giant floating wolf head
with the backwards baseball cap, who supercharges I think Jake at some point, so that he can go
like save. I was going to call him Morty fucking. What the fuck is the kid's name from Adventure
Time, Finn? Yes, thank you. And he just shows up at one point completely out of nowhere. He
does this magical thing. It's hilarious. And then he leaves. And then way later, like seasons
later in Adventure Time, they like made an episode developing the character of the party God. And
it was like, what the fuck are you doing? That that's like that's that's just such a misunderstanding
when he was a character supposed to be that exactly that is a one off joke. Rick Rick and
Morty's definitely had some of these issues. And I would say it's done reincorporation really well.
I think Bird Person was reincorporated well, like fucking the first time that the first
time that Gear Guy was brought back and Rick like replaces eyes with his balls. That was great.
The second time Gear Guy is brought back this season was terrible. And it was like, why do you
keep bringing back this character? Like why did it have to be him? You know, why is he there?
They're getting lazy, dude. I mean, I'm not saying that the show is like lazy itself, but but that
is a lazy idea to do. Exactly. Like we didn't get we didn't get a wealth of great new characters
this season. No, we did not. No, we did not. In fact, I can't think of one I particularly cared
about. A lot of people like that guy. What was his name? Cougar or Jaguar? That action guy. He was
he was pretty cool. Just whatever. He served as part of the episode and I don't ever really care
about seeing him again, though. So yeah, that's fair. Remember unity? Remember fucking unity from
season two? She is like, that's like the best character ever. I fucking love unity, not to
mention like the incredible relationship. It's like the best episode of the whole fucking show.
It is. It is one of the best. But like the ending is legendary. Yeah, I would say the first three
episodes of season no episodes two and three of season two are like the two best. What was the
other one besides the unity episode there? Episode two is the one with the fucking when they go to
Blitz and Chits. Oh, yeah. And and they meet the fart cloud. Yep. That's that whole one.
Wait, is that the same episode? I think so. No, yeah, you're right. I think it's got the it's
got crumb crumbopulus Michael in it. Yep. Yep. Yeah. Anyway, I can actually remember that name,
by the way. I could not have remembered that. That's a sanity. Yeah. I don't know what else to
say about this finale. It was kind of underwhelming. It was a, you know, the season was okay. I would
say this would not be I don't think the season would have disappointed people if it hadn't taken
so long to come out. Yes, it's important. And I hope I I wish upon a star that next time I'll
somehow be able to watch it weekly, but I know that or not watch it weekly rather, but I know
that won't be the case. Yeah, I'm going to end up having to and it's going to perpetually ruin
this show for me as this happened to every other show I've ever watched weekly.
You know what? I do want to I want to challenge you. Don't you think that our enjoyment of
Aromanga Sensei was heightened by the fact that we had to stew on every episode in between them
and just just get ready enjoyment of our reactions to it. Exactly. That's what that that's what was
all about. That's what it was all about. Incidentally, Made in Abyss Weekly will probably finish that at
some point. Indeed. Indeed. Very soon, I think. And if anybody cares who listens to this show.
By the way, let me let me let me shout out two jokes that were hilarious and I love
do it quick because I got a poop. Okay, we'll do. So remember when when the President is growing
back in size and they just give him the shirt because apparently he needs to swing his dick
around. Hilarious. I laughed. Good. Good. The other one was when it just went when the President
is like ordering this guy to clean his room and he's just like, I don't think you even know what
Secretary of Interior means. Just small side. I laughed. That was a weird one, but I did think
it was. Well, you know, Rick and Morty is a pretty intellectual series. You know, not everybody's
going to get it. You know, you got to you got to think about it. Oh, and also when when Morty is
just like, I don't know, Commander in Queef want to count my pubes, I laughed. I laughed. That's
it. I got nothing else. All right, everybody, see you in the future. Possibly in years like nothing
matters. Yep, we're all dead universes. Choices don't matter. Consequences don't matter. Kill
yourself. Do whatever you want, everybody. That's that's my thing. Bye bye. Oh my God,
I almost forgot to add the last thing. Hey, everybody, best guy ever. World famous Rick
and Morty analyst here. Yo, you know how Minecraft was in this fucking episode? Oh,
I thought it was really dope how like in real life, like the President's portal like had to be
lit with a fucking lighter like in Minecraft. I am a Minecraft specialist. Thank you very much.
I'll see you next time. Bye bye.