Hello everybody and welcome to another episode of Rikstie Minutes. It's me, I'm Best, I'm Best, and we got Dig.
I don't give a fuck, bitch, doing this show the only way that you should, which is under the influence of alcohol.
Good, good. I'm keeping it sober, I'm keeping a clean cut over here, because that's just the kind of fucking dude I am. What can I say?
So what do you think of this episode here, Digi?
It's alright. I like the concept, and there were a couple of lines of dialogue that were rewarding to me on a meta level, more so than perhaps much of the episode.
I feel like while I like this as an episode idea, it's weird that they framed this as a replacement for dimensional cable, because I don't think it was really that similar.
Maybe they just did that to assure us that they weren't going to do one this season.
I suppose so.
Because I was expecting, because in season two when they did it, Rik did a fourth wall break and said we're doing it again because everyone loved it last time.
I didn't think they'd do it a third time, because A, they've done it twice already, and B, the response to the second one was not nearly as favorable as the original.
So I was thinking that if they addressed it all, there will be another fourth wall break, and we got that at the start of the episode.
And that was really gratifying for me on a meta level, the fact that Rik said we're doing this instead of dimensional cable, and I went, oh, like, of course.
But then I think that accidentally set me up to expect it to be anything like dimensional cable, which it's really not.
Instead of crazy vignettes where they just spitball lines and then animate around them in a very appealing aesthetic kind of way, like with the two brothers.
It's just called two brothers.
That's classic shit. Everybody loves that.
And this was just a bunch of mini Rik and Morty adventures just smashed into one thing, and they were all new.
They were all original. They were cool.
But yeah, it came away a bit lukewarm.
It's a bunch of episodes that were decent.
That's even selling it short. They were good. Some of them were quite interesting and quite funny, but in the end, we're just left with a bunch of shallow experiences that were kind of cheap fun.
Yeah, but the weird thing about it is that they're not going...
This felt more like a story episode to me.
With the dimensional cable, and granted, the first dimensional cable did have one of the most gripping narrative moments in the show with the family.
But the dimensional cable itself is like a totally ridiculous unscripted goofy shit.
And I think the reason the second one wasn't as well received was that both stories were...
The dimensional cable itself was the same as before. It's just a bunch of retarded bullshit that's hilarious.
But then the B plot was also really dumb, and so it didn't have the impact the original episode had.
This one, though, if they had never mentioned dimensional cable, this would have just seemed like an episode of Rik and Morty.
The point is this idea that Rik has been taking all these memories from Morty, some of them by Morty's request,
and some of them because Rik got rid of them on purpose for his own reasons, usually which are hilariously petty.
Probably my favorite memory is the one where Rik just says a word wrong.
He says taking for granted, everybody.
As opposed to taking for granted, and Morty calls him out on it, and he erased that memory from Morty's mind.
There's also one where Morty beat him at checkers.
While he was drunk, he wasn't even probably trying, and he still erased that memory.
I'd be interested to know the creation process for this episode, because later on, Rik repeatedly says several times,
Stop thinking of this as a lesson learning thing. Stop thinking of this as a normal narrative episode.
This is a vignette episode. Stop taking it so seriously.
He was quite clear to make that point, but it manifests.
The resulting we get of these micro episodes are good, but they're less out there and wacky and fun than the crazy shit you saw on interdimensional cable.
That's the thing. They're less weird than a normal Rick and Morty episode a lot of the time.
Even though these are the ones that are supposed to drive him literally insane, that's what we were promised at the beginning.
Usually it's just that Morty accidentally got someone killed in some kind of horrific way, and that's why he had the memory erased.
While those stories are funny and fun, they're not so weird that it doesn't feel like a normal episode of Rick and Morty.
Here's the other line that was deeply satisfying to me on a meta level, which is where at the very end of the episode,
when Rick and Morty are both calling Summer a bitch for no reason, she says,
no wonder you're arguing constantly and always behind schedule.
They're like, would you say it? She's like, nothing.
I was like, ah, there we go. That's why this episode happened.
Because Justin Roiland wanted to do another interdimensional cable and some more unscripted bullshit,
and Dan Harmon wants the show to be a serious drama show.
If you go back to the original episode, Dan Harmon wrote the half of the episode that was a completely serious story that was heart-wrenching,
was written by Dan Harmon, and the other half was Justin Roiland doing improv in a booth.
I think that maybe there was disagreement about how the second one had gone,
where maybe, now I haven't listened to the commentaries on season two yet,
which I've been meaning to do this whole fucking time when I've never gotten around to,
but I should, and then I want to hear the commentaries on this season,
because I've kind of followed the production background of Rick and Morty a bit,
not only through having listened to the commentaries, but also when season two was airing,
and I don't know if any of this has happened for season three, I haven't paid enough attention,
but when season two was airing, for the first episode and the last episode,
Justin Roiland, like, periscoped and live-streamed the parties that they threw.
Oh, I remember that, yeah.
Yeah, and during those, during the first one was one of the most fascinating things I've ever watched in my life,
specifically because of the fact that half of their people were being poached actively at the time.
Right, right.
They were talking about how their lead guy, their lead writer for that season,
had just been poached by Disney, and Justin Roiland was saying,
like, if the show goes downhill next season, it's because we lost this guy,
and he said things like, you know, everyone was saying that, like,
because Justin does so much on the show is why it takes so long to come out,
and like, just not having enough talent on the show is why it's always behind schedule,
and why, you know, and like, because the talent that is there gets poached by better networks
who can pay them more, you know, and so they all leave, so no one stays on the show for long enough.
So, like, if Rick and Morty were to go downhill, it would be because they couldn't spend two years
letting Justin and Dan do everything on the show, you know.
Now, obviously, the season's been pretty great, so they've found, they must have found someone.
They've just strapped some shit together, yeah, they're working that out so far.
But, like, hearing them mention the idea that, like, oh, you two argue constantly are behind schedule,
and the fact that it was directed at Rick and Morty, like, themselves, like,
because if it had been directed at more characters, I'd assume the whole cast,
or everyone involved is always arguing, but, like, framing it that way made it,
like, Justin and Dan are arguing all the time and always behind schedule,
and, like, it's easy to imagine.
Of course, that's exactly what it comes off as, yeah.
I'm saying people, like, just in the last episode of this podcast,
I was talking about how Dan Harmon is known for being impossible to work with
and a total piece of shit, and Justin Roiland's fucking crazy.
This is a guy who, last year, just leaked all this, like, information about a show he was trying to,
like, he was working with Fox on.
I don't know if this has been canceled by now, or if it's just, you know,
I don't know how far along it ever was, but he just, like, leaks all this information about his own show
that he had been selling Fox.
Okay, cool. This is news to me, but all right.
It was, he got really shit.
Why would you do that? Who was the point of that?
He got shit-faced and leaked all this info, and he was, he posted,
he posted the text logs he was having with, like, the lead writer on the show,
the guy was, or producer, who was telling him, like,
what the fuck are you doing? And he was screaming all caps at the guy,
this is new media, you motherfucker, like, stop living in the past.
We're in the future now, like, Twitter is the future,
like, you can't hide shit behind corporate backgrounds and stuff like that,
like, he's just out, like, he's doing what I would do, basically.
Yeah, but he's doing it while trying to make a pitch to Fox or whatever, so, like, not...
I think they already owned the show, like, it was a show that's in pre-production
that may or may not come to exist.
Okay, it's just like, oh, look at me, I'm such a rebel,
while I work for a giant corporation making their cartoon, like,
it seems like a double-stamp, but okay, whatever, that's fine.
Well, I think he saw it as a promotional thing,
like, let's promote this show in a very modern way
by releasing all this information and just being transparent about it,
which is how I think, you know.
That makes more sense.
But the point is that Justin really doesn't play by the rules,
and he's insane, you know, he kind of comes from the internet.
He's originally an internet guy, like, he's from Hollywood,
but he's from the Hollywood internet, you know?
What even is that? What is the Hollywood internet?
Like, what sort of things do Hollywood internet people do?
Have you ever heard of Channel 101?
I am aware of the Channel 101 stuff.
That's where Rick and Morty comes from.
The original short was on there.
But Channel 101, like, was supposed to be...
The idea of it was that it was, like, people who work in TV.
Like, it was people who were, like, sick of the restrictions
of what TV made them do.
And so they went and made this other place
where they could break copyright law without getting punished.
They could, like, basically do whatever the fuck they want.
It was, like, a guerrilla filmmaking thing.
But, like, everyone involved with it was people who...
Like, Dan Harmon was involved with Channel 101.
Like, these were all people who worked in TV,
but were, like, looking for an escape on the internet.
It just didn't blow up that big.
The only show that I think anybody really knows is Yacht Rock
and Cautionary Tales of Swords, which are both amazing.
Of course, of course.
But that's why those shows have a little bit more production
than the average YouTube show,
because, like, it was a channel they were trying to launch online,
which Dan Harmon tried to do recently,
like, his show Harmon Town,
which was the Dungeons & Dragons show.
Do you know about that?
Oh, that's right. I know of it in general.
I haven't seen any of it.
Yeah, they just animated, like, over a...
Like, they played D&D live in front of an audience
and then animated the campaign.
It's alright.
It sounded like a terrible idea.
Okay, nobody understands that D&D is the most boring thing
in the fucking world if you're not actually playing.
But it's all comedians, though.
Well, okay, if they know what they're doing, it's...
It's alright.
Is this that show that you see the fucking trailers for
on, like, YouTube ads and shit all the time?
Because it looks like the worst thing ever.
Are you implying that I watch YouTube ads?
Well, I mean, I skip them as much as possible,
but I see that on mobile.
The point is that it was on this new...
Dan Harmon and a bunch of other people tried to create,
like, their own Hulu, like, a subscription service
to watch, like, specific shows.
But it went as well as Tidal did.
Right.
Trying to do the same thing, which is,
you can't take people away from the websites they want to use
and make them pay to watch content
that they don't even know what it is, you know?
Yep, I hear you.
No one's gonna download Tidal so they can hear
the new Kanye West album if they haven't already heard it
and confirmed they liked it.
They just want to pay for it normally.
But anyways.
Like, there's a reason I didn't buy 4.44, Jay-Z.
I downloaded that shit because I can't buy it anywhere.
It's only on fucking Tidal.
Who's gonna do that? Not me.
Well...
Not that it matters to him. He has a little money in there.
In any case...
Okay, so that's all cool.
But I just did want to say about all that whole point
basically tied into that meta comment
that Summer makes at the end of this episode here.
And, okay, so, like, yes.
That is the lampshade hanging.
Sort of explain...
Possibly, as you just placed it forward.
Explaining, like, why this episode seems to be disjointed
and have, like, a half that's, you know, story-based,
that doesn't really go anywhere,
and then the other free-form thing that also feels kind of awkward.
So, okay, we've got this basically explanation,
but that doesn't retroactively make the episode more entertaining
or, like, more good.
It just gives me sort of a sense of satisfaction.
It is an interesting thought about, like,
why this production is...
Why it took Season 3 so long to come out.
You know, why they released the April 1st episode
that took another three months for the episode.
For the season, you know, like...
Just the idea that Dan and Justin fight all the time
is entertaining to me because I can easily imagine it.
You know, like, these guys are insane people.
And, um...
I don't know if that's why the episode itself
is like how it is, but it would certainly explain
why, like, I could easily imagine Justin being, like,
why not do another interdimensional cable?
Like, why not? I love it.
You know, and Dan being like,
we didn't go...
We're making it emotional, you know.
Fucking Dan.
I don't know, man.
I almost feel like it's a waste of time
to even go into any of the details of the episode.
Like, the moon thing, kind of funny, I guess.
Yeah, I don't even blame them for that
because of the fact that, like, I loved the second
interdimensional cable, but that one did get a lot of flag.
Like, I know people who think that episode's bad.
And, like...
I can't imagine why.
I guess Monkey said...
I think Monkey's dissed that episode before.
Really? But what's his argument that it's just too redundant?
It's just the same idea again?
I think just because, I mean,
the Jerry half of the episode's not that funny.
That's true.
I'll give him that, but...
And the skits aren't as memorable as the first time.
I just feel like I could watch an infinite number of those.
That's what I was gonna say.
They don't all have to be as good as one another.
I will watch as many of those as you make
because they're fucking hilarious in concept alone, you know?
I feel the very same.
But, you know, I could see why
that episode was pretty criticized,
so I could see why they'd not want to take that route again.
Yeah, I guess so.
I don't know, man.
I got nothing to fucking say about, like, the individual.
Like, oh, it was so funny when the worm came out of Morty's mouth
and they were like, lol, it's poop.
That was great.
Just pinch it off, dude.
You know?
Okay, I got a laugh out of that,
but then, like, I don't know, like, the joke dragged a little bit,
and I was like, okay, I get it.
Let's wrap this thing up.
The Moonman joke dragged,
and, like, the high point of the joke of the Moonman thing
was, like, uh...
Huh.
Okay, I get it.
Yeah.
It's good.
You know?
I agree.
There was no real massive peek.
Lol, he's jacking the dude off when he thinks he's torturing him.
Kind of funny, but, like, it's...
I don't...
Yeah, they weren't that funny.
They weren't that funny.
The funniest line in the episode by far to me
is immediately after Rick and Morty accidentally mind-wipe themselves,
and after Morty's first memory, he says,
I guess we're kind of like the men in black.
Yeah.
And he asks Rick if he remembers men in black,
and Rick says, I've only got men in black, too.
And he says, well, then you get the concept, and he goes,
well, actually, it's mostly random callbacks to the first movie in there.
Like, fucking...
I lost it at that joke.
A couple more at the end of the episode.
All the jokes that really made me laugh weren't even in the memories,
except for when Morty beat Rick at Checkers,
and that made me laugh.
That was good.
I went back and watched some of those, like, really fast clip show things that went by.
Yeah, like, there was some...
I like when they can cram.
The fast ones were better than the long ones.
I know, they were.
They were.
But then again...
You know, honestly, some of them felt like they were legitimately, like,
rejected ideas from the show.
Yeah, yeah.
Like, that Moon Man one could have been a full episode if they wanted to be.
Or just, like, all of these were just things that they thought of for, like,
minor subplots and then didn't do.
And then they just went, like,
let's just fill an episode with all of our extra bullshit that we thought was kind of funny.
You know, the way that at the beginning, like,
Rick is like, oh, we're doing a clip show, but they're all new clips.
Like, oh, these are ideas we threw away,
but at least they're new.
Here they are, everybody.
You know, we got them on the table.
The way he phrased it made it sound like it was stuff they'd thrown out, you know.
You know what?
I'm just gonna pin this one on the fucking women writers.
Those goddamn fucking women writers.
You can't trust them as far as you can throw them.
Why they gotta ruin Rick and Morty in every way like this?
Actually, my favorite scene is when Morty's gonna kill himself,
and Rick is, like, inspired to join him in a suicide pact.
I do like that.
That's just such a Rick moment.
Like, that's what I love about his character,
is the idea that he'd be like, you know what?
I am down to kill myself.
Let's do this, motherfucker, you know.
Yeah, I like that reckless side to it.
And then Summer coming in just like, oh, you guys are doing this again.
I was like, ah, you got me.
Yeah, we all got cucked.
I wanted to see him fucking die.
I really like this idea that Rick,
because he's so insanely well-prepared and has so much shit set up,
and generally is only kind of afraid of death.
We'll just let these scenarios play out.
Like, you know, he openly says this isn't the first time we've done this.
Like, we've literally gone down this road before,
just because he can write all his memories after it's over, you know.
And the fact that he has set-ups for even if him and Morty accidentally wipe,
like, even this has happened before.
Even them forgetting it happened has happened before.
That's right, that's right.
There's preparations for it, and I...
Yeah, that's what I love about Rick and this show.
That's good stuff.
And, you know, just the idea of...
Yeah, like, it makes sense that it just reinforces the whole thing.
Like, not only is Rick able to go to infinite realities,
and like, just if everyone dies here, he'll just go somewhere else.
Everyone's fine, like, so, you know, his detachment has begun at that point.
But now, even though he's able to just remove memories from himself
and anyone else and replace them, it's just another layer of, like,
yeah, like, why would I give a shit about anything?
I can just wipe those memories.
Nothing matters whatsoever.
Yeah, exactly.
It's all just entertaining, you know.
And I think this episode was helped for me also by the fact that I actually...
I watched the first 15 minutes, and then I had to stop
because I had to do other shit, and then I watched the last five minutes just now.
And I really think the last five minutes saved the episode.
Like, I think up till that point, I thought it was okay.
And I was like, alright, there's moments in here I like, but some of it's dumb.
The very end, I thought, is the best part.
Like, just when it actually, when it stops being just a clip show
and becomes about them, you know, doing the suicide pact
and, like, this meta idea that they've been doing this before
was way funnier than any of the actual stories they told.
That's true.
Yeah, I don't know, man.
I was just pretty disappointed overall in terms of the laugh-o-meter.
Yeah.
I don't know.
The stories were not that good.
They really felt cutting room.
They didn't feel original, and, like, they felt like stuff
that wasn't supposed to be in the show, that you watch and go,
oh, that should have been cut.
Like, I know why you guys didn't put that in the episode
because it wasn't that good, you know?
Yeah, I don't know, man.
And maybe that's why she was, maybe that's also part of the reference
to them being behind schedule, is like, they don't have time,
so they threw in an episode of, like, you know, half-complete shit.
Who knows?
Yeah, we'll never know.
I can't wait for, I cannot wait for the commentaries for this episode
because I think this episode, while by itself is not that great,
will be far more interesting to hear it talked about
than it will be to have watched it.
That's a great point.
I would love to hear the commentary on this episode.
Yeah, yeah.
More than any other episode so far this season.
Yeah, and I have a very different kind of engagement with this show, I think,
than this, you know, this is, I think we should address this, Nate.
This has been a weirdly controversial podcast a lot of the time.
On occasion, that's true.
I think it might just be because, like, people watch this who,
maybe there's a lot of people who watch this who just are Rick and Morty fans,
like, maybe these episodes get found, I have no idea,
because they do get pretty high view counts for views, shows on this channel.
They get more views than any other thing on this channel, it's true.
Yeah, which is really weird.
But the comments are often, like, aggressively against us,
and they have bigger dislike bars than our normal videos.
So I think people come in here just looking for Rick and Morty reviews,
and when we, for instance, of the last episode,
went on a seven-minute rant about whether or not Dan Harmon is a liberal cuck,
we got a lot of flak for that.
Rick and fuck off, that's the good shit, that's the good shit.
Yeah, no, but that's sometimes, I mean, for one thing,
in this episode, the whole time watching the episode,
I thought, I'm gonna have nothing to say about this.
Like, I wasn't even sure if I was gonna be able to do a podcast
until the meta thing came through, and I went,
well, I can talk about that for 20 minutes, you know?
And that's filled up 90% of the time we've been talking right now.
Yeah.
How worried were you?
I'm never worried.
I have developed a level of confidence that can talk for any amount of time about anything.
I'll find a way.
Yeah, that's how I felt.
I was just basically gonna reiterate how unfunny,
I don't wanna, like, oversell how unfunny this was.
It was like, I did get some chuckles, I got some smiles,
there were some goofs in there, like the fact that the Moonman winked.
This is like a strong six episode, I think.
Yeah, around there, around there.
Like, I actually, I watched it twice, actually,
just because I had time while I was editing some other shit.
And the first time, I liked it more the first time,
because I just let it wash over me,
and just let the memes fall where they may,
and was like, yeah, pretty positive.
Then the second time.
Yeah, I'm imagining watching the whole Moonman section again,
and like, no, it wouldn't be worth it.
It's not that funny, like the payoff wasn't that good.
The idea that he was literally a smudge on the lens doesn't really make sense
with what we saw in the beginning.
He moves, he moves in like the first thing,
so like, it makes literally no sense,
but that's kind of what makes it funny, that it makes absolutely no sense.
I don't know if that makes it funnier to me.
Oh, he literally was a smudge on the lens, that's predictable.
Rick and Morty really does a good job of basically explaining everything
and never contradicting its own logic,
and that definitely does contradict its own logic
in a way that one could criticize.
I just think that like, it's a wash, like who cares
if that like doesn't make sense in this particular case.
But, you know, it's a fair criticism.
If I was the mysterious Mr. Enter, which I am,
I would deduct massive points for that tragic logical break.
It would be a big problem for me.
There's also stuff, probably the most predictable joke in the entire show,
and maybe it's fine that it's predictable,
is when Rick types in like twisty ties or whatever into his magnet
and gets a bunch of them, which I thought that was really funny.
And then as soon as it shows Morty typing in,
and I went, he's typing in tits.
And then a bunch of chicks with huge tits fly into the house,
and I went, yep, you know, like,
I think it was less funny because I knew exactly,
because it was obvious.
Like, what, if it had been anything else,
it would have been funnier because I didn't predict it.
But it was exactly what I thought it would be.
They're going pretty, okay, I noticed that specifically
all those women were also redheaded.
So like, it's clearly like a Jessica thing
that he was doing at that moment.
They're really going hard with the Jessica thing.
Like, honestly, that kind of like,
it's been annoying me a little bit.
Why is Morty so into this one girl?
Like, wouldn't he just fuck anyone?
What's the deal?
What's the deal here?
I honestly feel like it's kind of a feminine perspective here.
Like, you know, as a guy, I'd fuck anyone.
I'd fuck anyone.
How is that a feminine perspective
that he is more in love with Jessica?
I think it's just that they're taking that direction.
You don't think it's more feminine to be fixated on,
like, one person and have that kind of,
because the men sow the field.
The men sow the field.
The women...
I don't think so at all.
Whatever, man.
You're like denying the existence of sluts right now.
Like, what are you fucking talking about?
We're having the exact debate right now
from Eyes Wide Shut
between Natalie Portman and Tom Cruise.
I haven't seen Eyes Wide Shut.
You should, but that's exactly the debate
we're having right now.
One of my favorite movies.
Everybody watch it.
I highly doubt that that is at all involved
in the intentions.
I think they're trying to make Jessica
a more important character
because she's going to be relevant.
She has been getting more scenes.
That's true.
Because if you watch...
If you go back to season one,
Jessica...
We mentioned this before,
that she was kind of a non-...
She's just a girl who Morty has a crush on.
Every once in a while,
they feed you a little idea
that maybe she could like him
in that classic 80s movie kind of way,
but it's not that important.
And in the episode where Morty gets a sex spot,
he doesn't seem to give a fuck.
Granted, in the last episode,
he objectively fucked a bunch of mermaids.
He sure did.
He's not a virgin.
So, like, I think in season one,
the idea was more Morty's this dorky virgin
and he likes this girl
because he's just into her.
But at this point,
I think it's more that he legitimately
finds her more attractive than anyone else
and is in love with her.
But why?
I've never heard a reason like why.
Because I think they want to make her
a major character.
Well, that would explain it, I guess.
Even though that's not really...
She hasn't done anything other than be hot.
And he's fucked countless mermaids less.
Some people have...
Some people just have one person there.
My fucking brother, Victor, chased his...
The girl he's now dating,
he chased for six years
because he literally couldn't find anyone else attractive.
Oh, boy.
We're gonna get into serious red pill territory
if I go down this road.
Let's not dig too deep into that.
Happens to some people.
Happens to people.
They just have a single target sexuality.
You know?
I can't relate.
Because someone is so...
Imagine...
Okay.
Imagine, Nate,
like you've probably never met someone
who just seems absolutely perfect.
The closest thing that I've ever met
is this girl in college who was just super hot.
That's the closest I could get.
But imagine you met a girl who's so perfect,
like so insanely attuned to everything
you've ever thought or wanted,
that after meeting her, you think,
there's no way I can ever be happy with anyone else
because she's just that perfect.
Like, I've seen the top of the mountain.
How could I settle for sitting on the side of the mountain?
Okay, you know what?
When I find myself in a situation like that,
here's where my mind goes.
Okay, I know for a fact that nobody's perfect,
so what's wrong with me
that I think this person will complete me?
What do I need to fix about myself
that I need this addition in my life?
This is a good defense mechanism for that.
Yeah, I think so.
Because it's not a good position to be in
if they don't love you back.
No, it leaves you vulnerable, dude.
It leaves you vulnerable.
You can't be doing that.
Some people, like my brother, get lucky
and they eventually do love you back.
That's a rare thing, man.
It's a rare thing.
Yeah, it's a rare thing.
But you know, I get it.
Like, I get why if someone,
like if the only thing you find attractive
is like a red head with tits this size
and like everyone else you fuck is second best to that.
Like you fuck some girl who might be a 9 out of 10,
but is that going to distract you from the 10 out of 10?
You know, like you're always going to be thinking about the,
especially if it's within grasp,
because Jessica's kind of within grasp.
That's true.
Like, I'm sure in Morty's mind,
he thinks like she lives near me.
It's not like, it wouldn't be weird
if we got together, you know?
You know, I feel like it's a little bit
that they want to have their cake and eat it too,
that they want Morty to be woke as fuck
and you know, like this increasingly sociopathic guy,
you know, who's also gotten some morals and shit,
but then they also wanted to be like a naive kid
with like this innocent crush.
I think they want to have it both ways a little bit.
I think that's always been the case in this show.
Yeah.
Like, I think it's, it kind of bothered me in season two
when some episodes Morty was like this hard ass
and then other episodes he's a fucking retard.
Right, right.
And, I mean, that's always the problem
when you've got a bunch of writers in the show.
That's sort of the problem of like the archetype
of what, of the character that Morty is based on
versus like the character progression
throughout the show, you know?
Yeah.
And I think season three's done a much better job
of keeping him consistent.
I agree.
Like, he's, he's felt pretty consistently woke
throughout the season.
I haven't really felt like he was just a naive retard
much this time.
It's just the Jessica thing really,
I guess that stands out to me now.
I think that's why, that's why I think she's supposed
to be a major character.
Like, I think there's going to be some kind of development
in that relationship.
And that's why they want us to keep it in mind.
And if that's not the case, it will be weird.
Like, why bring her up so much
unless you're going to do something about it.
I agree.
Because I don't remember her coming up that much
in season two.
She definitely did not.
The most that she ever did was like,
the most important Jessica has been before this season
was like that episode where he like made her fall in love
with him.
And then she, you know, was just mind controlled
to love him.
She was fairly relevant in season one.
Like, she's probably mentioned in more than half
the episodes of season one.
But season two, I don't remember her being a big deal.
But I haven't rewatched season two.
I've seen season one like four times.
So, I'm a bigger expert in that.
I forget.
Cronenberg is season two, right?
No, that's one.
Fuck.
Okay, I can't keep it.
That's like episode six.
That's where they killed the family
and moved to the other universe.
Okay, well whatever.
All right, well, good tangent.
See, that's the kind of quality you get under 60 minutes.
That's the good stuff.
Yeah.
An episode that neither of us had anything to say about
turned into one of the longest episodes of the podcast.
Is that true, really?
That's how we do.
Yeah, normally these are under 30 minutes.
Oh, that's cool.
There you go.
So, there you go.
Enjoy your various pills of wokeness and sleepiness.
And specifically that like, you know,
that shack like asleep and then woke with like the glowing
eyes.
Yeah, that's the one.
All right, I've had to piss for 25 minutes.
Okay, sounds good, my dude.
We'll see you guys next week with a new episode.
Bye-bye.