Fuck me and my fucking asshole, it's, we're back with Rick Stieman. It's everybody season 3 episode 6. Rest in Rick
Laxation. I am the best guy ever and here's Digibro.
We're back. You sound, you sound like you're toxic Digi. You're, I am quite toxic. Toxic animal. Yeah, I'm the toxic Avenger.
This is good episode, man. Yeah, real good episode, real good. I really liked it. This took me back in a way to
what I think is a
lot of the best Rick and Morty episodes, which is take a just really interesting fucking sci-fi
concept and see what you can do with it. Yep. Yep. Which I don't feel like we've had as much of this season.
Maybe the first episode with the whole
Yeah, yeah. Going into like his memories and shit, but the start of season 2 was a lot of this.
Like the, this reminded me of like the planet that was a live episode kind of with the
The usage of the concept and seeing where they could go with it. Planet that was alive as in the
What was her name? Fuck. His girlfriend, that lady? Yeah, the girlfriend. Yeah, okay. I'm with you. I'm with you.
Yeah, this was uh, this is really great shit. Uh, there's no like, there's no like evil foe
to conquer in this episode. So there's no need to like worry or there's none of this shit. We're like, we're, we're second
Guess like, why doesn't Rick just do this? Why doesn't Rick just fucking do it?
No, it doesn't fucking matter because the conflict is internal this episode exactly where it should be for this shit
It felt tight and it's
I kind of love when they
I can call it an excuse, but I think it's clever writing when they put the characters in a situation where they can't
solve it because of just like personal like mental limitations like in this case the
You know, this could be resolved easily if they were whole but the fact is that they're not and that's the whole problem, you know
Yeah, um pussy rick
You know won't go through with what uh other rick would right of course toxic rick
and I mean what makes it interesting is like these are
Like they're approaching it on a level that makes sense to all of us like we can all imagine what our
Toxic sides are and it's really interesting when when you get to the end of the episode where it turns out the toxic parts
Everyone it defines for themselves what their toxic parts are that may or may not be what the rest of us think they are
And that was a fucking great twist. Yeah, it was awesome. It was fantastic
It because it made me realize, you know, like this whole episode
These are the obviously toxic parts of rick and morty that we're seeing the idea ricks a violent
Maniac who thinks he's a god and just you know, it's completely full of himself
But when we find out that this is what rick thinks are the toxic parts of himself
It really recontextualizes it quite a bit that like even he wishes he wasn't like that
But he also wishes he wasn't uh, he didn't have like love and feelings like that, you know
Like he'd like to be a nice polite regular dude, but he still wants to be a cold
asocial, uh, you know
Psycho and it's great and it's great that since like morty kind of like those are the other
The traits that he would consider positive about himself
Like he wants to be that american psycho like a a moral, you know, unfeeling
Cutthroat businessman kind of guy that that rick identifies as like that's what he wants to get rid of
But morty wants to keep those things because of his deep deeper insecurities and it just makes it it's making it so that
None of this is like an objective stance as to like what is actually good and bad about a person by couching it in this
This is how the individual identifies as their bad points
It gives it this great air of subjectivity where it's just
We just get to more understand the characters themselves and how they perceive these things as opposed to like, you know
Dan Harmon making a stance about like, oh if you have feelings if you love your week, you know any of that that bullshit
It's not making that point at all. It's just talking about the characters. It's uh, it's great. It's much more interesting
Smart shit. I will say one thing if I have one complaint or doubt about this episode. It's
Would morty really be this good just by losing his toxic side that did occur to me as well
Yeah, like just by not being such a huge
coward
You know, I mean one of my favorite moments in the entire show
Is in the entire episode is when morty just like confronts rick
He like tells him like you are not fucking getting in the back
It'd be real dangerous for you if you fucking went back and got like our shitty sides
And then as he's walking away fucking football just arrives in his hands
And he fucking tosses his back and keeps going like
Yeah, like the levels of absurdity as to how perfect morty's life has become because he's lost his like are comedically
Just just fucking perfect like they're way over the top and they're great. I love how obnoxious he is
Yeah, and that the episode's willing to just dwell on it like just really like go
They go so hard on like the cornball
element of it like he's just telling stupid jokes that aren't funny and like
For a second I'm like groaning and then I'm like, oh, that's the point, you know, like you got me you mother fucker
I constantly felt that way throughout his scenes and I sort of felt like um
uh
the the elements that propel him to such levels of success are just his absolute confidence and
You know, really that's that that can that can make a huge difference in somebody's life
And you can see like toxic morty, which is his complete like
Disgust with himself on every possible level
Uh, yeah, leaving leaving, you know, healthy morty quote-unquote healthy morty to be just this fucking
Powerhouse of confidence. Yeah, like I can see why he'd do well, you know, when he goes it becomes like a broker or whatever
Uh, yeah, yeah, it makes sense. It makes sense
How my favorite character in this episode is um, what's a random random slut
Big tits make what's a bar. Yeah, I fucking love her. I felt it. I felt a certain
Tingling in my loins when I gazed upon this character
The line where he's uh, when she's like, should I leave and he's like
You're free person do what you want. She's like, I choose to stay
That got me
Yeah, she was a bit of a delight. I liked her a lot
I knew I I was really happy because like I knew that they were gonna end up trapping her in the machine
But what I was really hoping was that either she'd escape or just be like like a badass down
Like I knew she was going to be in the end after credits
Yeah, yeah, like no question after she got trapped in there
And didn't like like I would have been really bummed out if they'd like killed her
You know, and this is I've I've been saying all season that the show has been
writing right on the line between being like overly gross and like and
Inacceptable and like there's still an insane violent scene in this where all these little kids chop off a clown's head
And it's fucking
Horrible, but it was great because it's a character. Nobody cares about it's just a one-off gag
And it's it works really well
Like if this girl had gotten killed that would have been like this is like why why she was likable
I liked her don't kill her
I'm glad this show still has that sense of knowing like when to push the violent button and when not to
And um, you know, it's continued
There's only been like a couple places where I thought like the aforementioned one of the avengers episode
I was like, uh
We have to kill that guy so gruesomely, but it wasn't a big deal and I didn't like that episode anyways, so yep
Yep, you know, but here I felt it was done. Just right, you know
Okay, can I just bring up so people have been making a there's been a contention this whole season that we haven't addressed on this show yet
The issue of the quote-unquote female writers. Are you aware of this? You aware of this meme that's going around
Yeah, I don't like I mean didn't the show always have female writers
I honestly don't know. I thought that I should prepare, but then I also didn't uh, so I have not looked into this at all
I don't know comment people give me give me like reasons to take this seriously
I don't know what this means every time it gets brought up. It's like it's completely inconsequential because
Everyone agrees pickle rick was an amazing episode. It was written by a woman
and then like
So, you know, where do we go from like what what is the side you're trying to take here?
You're trying to say the female writers are good or bad because
We've already proved they've done like the both the best and worst episodes of the season were written by a woman. So
Where you know, I mean all I can tell people make of this is just show me an itemized list
Show me the correlations here because uh pickle rick was perfect
This episode was fantastic
And then the the avengers one and the the mad max one like those are pretty lame overall
So like I don't know if these were like diversity hires that made the show worse
I don't know prove that to me in some way. I don't know do do the work for me people
That's what I'm asking of you. It's I think they're just trying to make it a meme
But like the meme can't stick if the if some of the best episodes are written by women
Like you can't meme it if it's just not even true
I think so people disliked pickle rick just for like they didn't pay attention to how good the episode was
And instead focused on like the memory of it like oh pickle rick
So funny except that episode was fucking great. So, you know, I don't I don't know what there is a complaint about
Um, well, anyway, I don't know
I just thought I'd bring that up like people have been saying that for a while
And I didn't really know if you had any insight to to bring to the no
Like I said, the first thing I heard about it was well pickle registered by woman and I was like, well, okay
Well, there's no problem. I guess women are the best writers then as it turns out
I don't know. I feel like yeah, maybe people are just out to
which hunt on the show for
Seemingly having more women than it had before I don't fucking know
I know everyone who works on rick and morty gets fucking poached. So like
If they hired more women, it's probably because they ran out of whoever was writing the show before, you know
And the new hires are just as good as the old ones. Who the fuck all the goddamn men are ascending too high in the patriarchy
We have to fill these slots with the the lowly women. Hey, what can we do? Uh, so, hey, can we talk about how?
fucking uh, I don't know spine
Shatteringly intense the opening scene of this episode was because I I fucking loved it. It was the coolest thing ever
I was not in control that situation at any point morty that that really fucking got me that uh, that's
Oh, that's another thing
I've I mean we've this has happened many times throughout this show
But the way that this show will have like full blown
Lovecraft shit happened to the minds of these characters and then find a reason to just wipe it under the rug
You know like we had the roy game in season two
Where morty experiences an entire lifetime as another person
We just had in the last episode the whole mind meld for an epoch thing right and now we've got this like
Deep trauma to the point of we're never going on another adventure for both of them for even rick
But then they go to a spa. They're like, you know, well, you're just gonna work through that stress
It'll be fine
That was great. That was great. And I yeah, I just love seeing like the alien spa and all the stuff they were doing there
And I don't know. It's not a major point, but seeing like
Once we saw like toxic rick and toxic morty trapped in the tank and just realizing that they're like in this world
Uh, I don't I don't know something about that was just really cool being in this
like seeing sort of like the uh, sort of the anthropomorphization of like the inside of like this toxic tank
Or or something like that. I don't know something about that was really dope. I really like I really I love this
idea just because of the fact that they they go to a spa
And detox which is like in in reality a load of horse shit
Yeah, like detoxing is not like a
Thing that works as far as I'm aware. I'm pretty sure it's like bro science, you know, it's like a meme to me
Yeah, so like especially the like, oh, I'm going on like a three-day detox right to like swallow a fucking rope and
Then shit it out over the course of three days, you know about those ones like
You know, that's what they're making fun of here, but it's a sci-fi version where not only does it work
But it's like literally everything toxic about you psychologically removed like just such a good idea
And then to make a whole story out of that idea is
It's genius. Yeah, it was great. It's just really smart and uh, you know seeing, you know, uh, uh clean rick
Or a healthy rick, you know being guilted into into bringing back him and and even being guilted like oh morty
We got to reabsorb our darkpots. They're they're part of us morty. We can't we can't live without them. That's uh, I really loved
That rick. I loved fixed rick because they didn't make it
Oh, they didn't overdo it. It didn't make him like a like an actual total pussy. He's just like a reasonable guy
Who's very interested in science, you know, like he just wants to be a scientist man
Like that's that's the rick's perfect vision of himself is just a man who wants to do science
Just a reasonable guy who who wants to do that, you know
And like that's what he would consider an idealized version of himself
But but that that idealized version is such a moralist that he can't stand to leave behind
You know a part of himself that he feels he wronged by you know doing this too. So
By the way, a detriment to himself. He's so self-sacrificing. Yeah. Yeah that he would help this other person
Whereas morty sees himself a perfect version of him would not sacrifice anything for anyone
Yeah, yeah, it's true. It's true. It kind of just shows that uh
Deep down morty is kind of a worse person than rick, you know
At least in the way that like he wishes that he could be you know, he wishes to be this kind of a moral guy
Which I totally relate to I I'm totally in agreement with morty. I would I wish I was that
American psycho morty
I've said many times that my favorite thing about rick is that underneath all the psychopathy
He is a moralist and now we've been made fun of on the previous episode for suggesting that rick was a better person than
Jerry we have because ricks ricks killed so many fucking people and all that shit, but rick also
has
Created entire worlds that run perfectly fine. He's you know create his amount of things
He's brought to the world is possibly
Greater than the amount of destruction he's caused and I mean I would say it probably more likely evens out
Considering that on the council of ricks. They said he was like right in between being a full evil and a full good
He's like the perfect middle ground
Um, but you know a middle ground as a rick is not oh, I don't kill anybody
But I also don't really contribute to society. It's I kill swaths of people
But I also like create entire
Utopias and shit and you know occasionally help people so
Like I do think there's a moral center to rick that's always been there
And whereas morty has you know, he's just an idiot who's been strung into this world where he's developed this nihilistic
Personality and doesn't care about anything for real. So like you know
It's a bit of a bit of a give and take there. It's it's interesting to and I really don't think
Toxic ricks point should be discounted like you you've got to imagine yourself in ricks perspective here
Everyone around him is a fucking like worthless piece of protoplasm
Like he is a literal god compared to these people with with his abilities
Like to even give one ounce of an iota of a shit about any of these creatures that you know
You have access to infinite alternate versions of like
Frank like the the moral labor enacted to do that is frankly more than any of us could possibly imagine
In any of our lives because we're like a lot of us only act kind because we have to act kind or society will destroy us
rick is above society in every possible way
He chooses to act morally none of us ever have to like with how about the great with great power comes great responsibility
Considering the incredible power rick has he is goddamn saintly because he could just evaporate our universe if he felt
And granted he will do that sometimes if he flies off the handle like
We're not saying that he always makes the right choice
But the fact that he ever makes the right choice is almost shocking exactly
You know like like again back in episode two with the the road warrior world
Like if he wanted to he could have just killed everyone and left
But he just didn't I don't know didn't feel up to just murdering everybody that episode
The people the people making those kinds of points
I think should listen to bill burr's comments on tiger woods like all these all these fat middle-aged pieces of shit
Like waddling out when they hear that tiger woods cheated on his wife
They waddle out to their fucking sedans, you know, they're fucking honda civics, and they're like, oh, absolutely
Reprehensible behavior from tiger. Oh, it's absolutely disgusting
Meanwhile, they have never once ever had to face the kind of challenge that tiger woods did at his peak when he would walk
Off the club and there'd be a fucking busload of of fucking uh,
Swedish cheerleaders wanting to fuck him all at the same time
When have you people ever faced the kind of challenge the tiger or rick has never once in your fucking life?
So I don't want to hear you commenting on this shit like oh, why doesn't he just be perfect all the time get fucked
I don't have any sympathy for these people rick is uh rick's uh
He's a he's a complicated man
I like how many times have you crushed an ant in your life at least once probably that's what human beings are like to rick
There's a context people it's a context
Yeah, there you go. Here you go beautiful beautiful rant there. Uh, what the fuck was this episode about again?
I don't know toxic. Uh, hey, uh, how about I was pretty cool when they made the whole world toxic
Uh, that was that was kind of cool
Uh, what did they I all I can remember is them the the children murdering the clown
Oh, the priest the priest being like, uh, got we steal money from you. God's not real
Ha ha tip. Yeah, and then everybody starts fucking and then the people from like
Subarrows and some salad place like switch places for some reason. I was trying to interpret with that joke man
I didn't really understand that one
I think like the fat people went into like the mexican restaurant and then after it went back
They went back to like the salad place. I I don't know. I I lost track
Yeah, I wasn't paying it. It wasn't mexican. It was a subarro. Oh, oh, yes. It's subar right right
Oh, hey, one other cool thing about this, uh, the fight scene between ricks was pretty fucking dope
Especially when they like murdered each other and they had to like
Regrow fucking body. Yeah, that was fucking awesome
Uh, the coolest thing ever
Which is another one that has
Like that's a thing a lot of the coolest tricks in this episode are things that have been done before
Like that is something we've seen we've had a
In episode one when morty knocks over the like the tank with an alien baby and it like grows all the way into old age
In a second. Yeah, we've had rick. Don't think about it morty. Yeah
Yeah, we've had him kill other versions of himself and take their bodies at the start of the season like
We've seen a lot of rick using weird
Regrowth and rebirth techniques, but it's still cool
But I do think this is one of those things where it's like
This show has a limited number of seasons that it can still be impressive like this, you know
Like if we see this another time, it's gonna start to be like, okay, I get it rick can science himself back to life
You know, uh, how many times are we going down that road because I thought it was cool as shit
But I didn't have that shocking like hanging in my psyche like that scene from episode one did with the alien
Don't think about it because I couldn't help but think about yeah
Yeah
You know, this fight kind of reminded me, uh, you know for obvious reasons of uh, you know that fight
I once I first saw it on youtube as the most cartoony anime fight ever between uh, araragi and uh,
Vampire girl where they just pop each other's heads off repeatedly and uh, you know what i'm talking about
If you've seen this I don't think so is it recent it might be from the third keys in monogatari film
It was basically the coolest thing i've ever seen in my entire fucking life and uh, makes me understand why people watch that show
So I gotta fucking do that sometimes
Yeah, yeah
A lot of people would say you should watch the films first because they are technically a prequel to everything else in the series
But aren't prequels supposed to be watched after you know, uh, whatever
I mean, I mean they the book was like the second book, but it's taken them the longest to adapt so yeah, right
Well enough about bullshit anime, uh
This I mean and nothing else. I mean we pretty much covered everything that was great
Oh, hey, how about the uh, the additional little extra layer of character that was added to jessica?
And she like actually seems to have some feelings. Yeah, what's up with that? I don't know man. It seems like it's going somewhere
I mean I can't I can't really remember how she's been treated because she wasn't around much in season two
And hasn't been much for this season so far like she was mostly a plot device in the first season and
It kind of felt like the way they were treating her was she has no personality whatsoever
She's just a prop in whatever the scene is. Yeah, like so
I can't remember if there's ever been a hint of this before the idea that she might have cared about
but
Yeah, other than when she got like love potioned in the uh
Other universe, right? I honestly feel like it's a little bit out of nowhere
Like I she did go on a date with him and I'm sure she was impressed like she said like I think I'd be too boring for you
So that that's an admission that this guy seems to have a lot going on
So she's kind of into him in that way. I think she was
You know, that might have been an excuse or something. Yeah
I think that was a nice way of putting it that she's probably true. I don't know. I feel like they're going somewhere with her
I expect to see more of her at some point
But like Morty wants her bad and she is at least a little bit into him. Just just fucking do it guys just
I wonder if they're trying to set up like because there's a lot of stuff this season that feels like it could be continued on
I wonder if they're trying to set up for like the long haul
Like this isn't going to be stuff that's resolved this season
But it'll be like new overarching stuff for the rest of the show that'll like slowly develop
I almost feel like every episode that we've seen so far has introduced a character that like could come back for like the season
Finality of this like in in this episode. There was uh, you know, the the big tits McGee
Uh in pickle rick. There was like the the that machete guy, whatever his name was l t gray that guy
In episode one there was bird person and what's the face of those guys were obviously kind of like more important characters
I don't know. Oh and uh like bucket head uh x husband of summer
I guess or whatever just seems like there's a bunch of that
I'm wondering if we're gonna
I don't I almost feel like they're setting up for like some big event where they all get together and for like revenge or something
I don't know that that's my prediction
We'll see we'll see I don't think anybody who shows up in an ending gag is going to show up again
I feel like they do that to resolve a character so that we know they won't be back
I know what you're saying that that would make a lot of sense. Then again l t gray
seems
I don't know the fact that he's still out there, you know makes it like I can't see big tits McGee coming back
Because what would she do? Yeah, but but l t gray if that's his name. I I don't know if that's his name
I can't remember
We all know who you're talking about though. Yeah, we'll uh
We'll see man. We'll see as it goes great episode
Really good. Last episode was really good. Pickle rick was really good
Well, let's let's keep this episode one was really good. There's only really been two episodes that we thought were weaker. So that's not bad
That's not terrible. Yeah
It's going it's going okay. I mean
And not even that we thought were terrible just that we're not amazing like below average rick and morty episodes
Which is a dissapointment, but more or less. Okay. Yeah, I was a force on when I was like
but yeah, I mean I
There's episodes of seasons one and two that I think are worse than the others. So this is not new
I don't expect to show to bat a hundred at all times, but it is definitely fucking still solid. Absolutely as long as they keep
Bringing in new ideas. I just I hope they stay away from like if there was like another mr
Meeseeks episode or just anything like reusing old ideas
Even in small ways would be that would be an indication that things are starting to dry up
But as long as they keep doing stuff like this
Yeah, this is good. Like this is just a new idea. That's like that's the kind of stuff that we I promise we will see that if
Dan or
or
Justin ever left the show. Oh, yeah, for sure. You know for sure
They'll laugh on those tangible details as hard as they fucking can if those guys leave
Which I mean Justin voices half the characters and Dan voices the other half
So like they can't it would be real hard to do the show without the moment
Yeah, that's true. Well, we're here's hoping good so far. Keep it up guys
All right. Yeah, peace
Kill me