Fuck me and my fucking asshole, what's up everybody, it's Riksy Minutes, I'm the best guy ever here with Digibro.
Hey, I'm still alive.
He sure are dude, so we just watched episode 5 of season 3, what was this one called? The Grand Adventure of Jerry and Rick?
The Whirly-Durly.
Of course, of course, who could forget such a wonderful name.
Yeah, so this was way better than the last episode, right out of the gate, a thousand times better.
Oh yeah.
We got a lot of flack for not liking the previous episode.
We sure did.
It seemed like. Some people really enjoyed it.
And so many people were just like, guys, you fucking tools, obviously it was a Avengers reference, therefore all your criticisms don't make sense and are invalid.
Okay, literally what the fuck is the difference between an Avengers reference and a Guardians of the Galaxy reference?
Literally what? Because the Guardians of the Galaxy are a part of the Marvel Universe, they're another five person team, and they're in the fucking new Avengers movie!
So what the fuck is the difference?
I think what they were, it doesn't make any fucking difference, but to these incredibly pedantic people, it's that these guys form up as a team when called upon, like the Avengers do, they're not always a squad.
Who the fuck cares?
Yeah, I know.
It doesn't make any difference.
What the fuck effect does that have on the episode?
Zero. Zero.
It's nothing.
Which, and I know you haven't seen the Avengers either, have you?
No, I haven't.
Exactly.
So it doesn't fucking have affected anything.
I have, and I still, I don't give a, it makes no difference.
Well, it's just that thing.
Like we say something that's like, not even like wrong, but like slightly maybe a bit incorrect, and so that may, allows there to be a justification for why we're just totally invalid.
Our entire point of opinions can be thrown out at that point.
I don't even, I can't even like process the idea that it's less correct to say it's a Guardians of the Galaxy parody than it is a Avengers.
Yeah.
They're literally the same thing.
You got what?
But they're in space, yeah.
You got, like the dude who's like the human guy.
Uh-huh, yeah.
You could say he's Star-Lord.
You could say he's Tony Stark.
Either way, it makes just as much fucking sense.
Yep.
You're right, dude.
Is the pile of ants supposed to be the Hulk, or is he supposed to be-
Like Ultraliter, that other guy?
Vision?
No, Tree-B-Oh, Groot.
Groot.
Yeah, Groot.
Yeah, there you go.
I don't fucking know.
Is he supposed to be Groot, or is he supposed to be some of it?
It doesn't matter, because none of them are a direct parody.
That was my whole complaint.
Anyway, forget about that episode.
Yeah, that one doesn't matter.
Let's move on.
So-
This one's great.
Yeah, this episode was really great.
It was fucking great.
I loved it.
I'd say I loved it.
It was everything I wanted.
This felt like a season one episode to me.
Yeah.
It really took me back in a way.
In a way that I really wanted.
In a way that was good, refreshing.
Yeah, and some people were asking me, because they preview the shit out of the episodes
before they come out.
I ignore all that.
Because back in season two, I followed Rick and Morty on Facebook and shit.
And in season two, I was watching all the trailers beforehand and shit.
And all it did was make it so I wouldn't laugh at that joke when it happened in the episode.
Exactly.
You know?
Because I've heard it too recently or out of context.
And so it happened in the episode and I'd be like, oh, this is the part I saw in the
trailer, so I don't laugh at it.
The worst example of that was in season two and Morty turned into a car.
Oh, yeah.
They had already spoiled that.
And had I not known that, that shit would have blown my mind to fuck.
But I knew already.
So it wasn't that- there was no impact.
So I tried to ignore all that, but people bring it up in our comments anyways.
And people were asking me like, oh, are you worried?
They're bringing back Jerry next week.
But it was Jerry and Rick.
And that, as soon as I heard that, I was excited.
Because what I'm sick of with Jerry is him and Beth.
Oh, yeah.
That dynamic is played out.
Jerry and Rick, you can do anything with.
You know?
Yeah.
So I thought, oh, no, that sounds awesome.
Yeah, I'd love to see Jerry and Rick.
It's a great combo.
And it was.
And so it was.
It was a good combo.
It was great.
You know, just like bouncing.
Rick is just the guy with no filter who will just tell you what's up.
And, you know, we just really dive to the heart of Jerry's character here.
And, you know, there's that scene later on where he just, like, spells out exactly what kind
of a guy Jerry is.
And it was fucking devastating and fantastic.
And that's the kind of shit I love.
That scene was great because it put words to, like, what our problem with Jerry is.
It's everyone's problem with Jerry.
Everyone knows Jerry is shit.
But, like, sometimes, like I've seen in our comments, people being like, why are you
guys so harsh on Jerry?
What the fuck?
You know?
And we're like, well, that's the thing.
Like, Rick kind of spells it out right here that, yeah.
Like, Jerry himself is not a great guy.
And not just because he's an idiot, because he just manipulates people to get what he
wants.
He's constantly in this, oh, everyone beats up on me.
I'm the victim.
Even though he's the one who, like Rick said, it's his fault.
Beth's unhappy at this point.
I mean, it's both of their fault equally.
But, like, he wasn't a good husband for her.
So it's not like because she's breaking up with him, he's the victim here.
It's like, no, you were both bad for each other.
That's exactly right.
And you know what's fascinating about this to me?
It really reminds me sort of a dynamic of the worst kind of, like, YouTube commenter
versus, like, a YouTube creator, just as an example in my life.
Like, Rick is a guy who goes out and creates things.
You know, he doesn't need society to give him anything.
He creates value in his life and in those around him.
Jerry, on the other hand, is a parasite.
He's a little scum-sucking shit who can't do anything for himself.
He's like a YouTube commenter.
He's like a whiny, entitled YouTube commenter who just, you know, wants stuff,
give to him for free, and when he doesn't get exactly what he wants,
he'll bitch and cry and complain and pretend that he's been bullied in some way.
Not that I really have any experience with this, but just in my experience on YouTube,
like, you see that shit around.
Like, Jerry is the worst parts of humanity.
Like, the people that I want to all die.
And I only respect the people like Rick who just, they do things.
They create, they add value to the world so that the people like Jerry can live better lives.
But they don't deserve better lives.
They just happen to be there in the warm glow of the genius and the power
that is the Rick Sanchez's of the world.
I mean, someone like Jerry, he really preys on our humanity.
Oh, yeah.
Like, this is where...
He's a moral parasite. He's a moral parasite.
Sometimes when we look at Rick, like, there's clearly elements of Rick that are monstrous
and are not advised, that are not good for him or for anybody.
You know, like, this level of, like, detachment from emotion is not a good idea.
However, there are also elements of Rick that are there to protect us,
that we should incorporate into our lives.
Like, being able to, like, see through this kind of manipulation of someone like Jerry.
Because the average person, like, yeah, was gonna feel sorry for him.
And, like, that's how he'll fuck you.
You know?
That's how he'll...
I really love how he brings up specifically like Jerry.
Like, it's not like there are no victims.
You are the predator.
Beth was your prey.
You used your pathetic little, you know, whiny existence as a way to entrap Beth
to, like, suck the life out of her.
Who, you know, is a far more capable person than Jerry.
He's the parasite.
He is the bad guy here who just used this kind of emotional manipulation in his life
and does constantly that we see every fucking episode that he's in
to just, you know, be a baby, prey upon people's, like, desire to...
You know, like, even in this episode, like, he just fucking is so pathetic
that nobody feels like killing him.
They're just like, this is not worth my time.
It's not worth my time.
And that's what he does with Beth.
And, you know, it's great to just see it spelled out so black and white.
And you know what?
Just to get a little more...
Actually, you know what?
I don't want to say that.
Never mind.
Well, to go further into the episode, there's an opportunity here
because I've been complaining about how I wanted Jerry to just be out of the show.
But I do think there's ways to use him.
Like, the reason I wanted him out, I wanted him out exactly this way
where he's just not in the house having the same bee plots he's had before.
We just don't want the same story again and again.
And this isn't the same story.
This is new ground.
But there's a huge opportunity at the end of this episode
where Jerry seems to kind of learn from what Rick accused him of
and the fucking other dude.
You know, like Jerry gets his shit rocked emotionally
and he actually seems to reflect on it a little.
And it seems like throughout the season, Jerry has kind of been like
taking in the criticisms people have had of him.
You know, like as it's gone on, he's kind of reflected.
And I'm wondering, what if Jerry actually, actually develops as a character?
You know dude, it reminds me of when I was a young lad
and not doing a lot with my life before I had my shit together.
Like my parents would just bring up occasionally how they needed to throw me out.
Not that they would, but like they're just like,
Nate, you're living here, you're just being a bum.
What are you fucking doing with your life?
And that was entirely fair.
And like throwing me out would have been a fine and reasonable thing to do.
And that's kind of exactly what happened to Jerry.
You know, you got to fucking nut up in a situation like that
and face your shit and recognize that like he's just being placated
by continuing to live with Beth and like continuing to receive,
to continue to suck on the teat of sweet life
that comes from these better people in his life.
I actually know a guy, now that I'm like thinking about it
and hearing it like through this episode I'm realizing
I know a guy who's just like Jerry, who has a victim complex.
He's constantly blaming the circumstances surrounding him
and other people being an asshole.
But he himself is a vindictus shit who like the second,
the second he has the power and situation he takes advantage of it.
Just like Jerry does this episode where when Rick's retarded
Jerry's just beating up on him ruthlessly
even though he would never, you know, at all other times
he's crying victim because of Rick's actions.
I knew a guy exactly like that
and he got kicked out of my group of friends for being that way.
He pissed off everyone I knew so many times
that we eventually just had to say you can't come here anymore.
Like just like Jerry.
So it's kind of the inevitability with someone like this
because they are so sure that everyone else is the asshole
that they will never process the fact that they are the real asshole.
That's exactly right.
And the best you can hope for in a situation like that
I think is that like you kick this person out
they finally have to face the real consequences of their lifestyle
and their attitude and actions
and like hopefully they'll become a better person
and then like get a decent group of friends elsewhere
or like maybe get a family that like they've actually
formed a real bond of respect with.
And you know what, maybe years later
they'll be, once they become a good person
they'll be able to come back and be like, hey man, you know,
hey ain't seeing a while, you know, I'm not a pathetic piece of shit anymore
I really became a good person, yeah I'm doing my own thing now
don't need to, you know, drag everybody else around down with me
I've got this other thing that I've developed in my own life
you know, my own situation, my own friends, my own circle
that I built up with actual positive character traits
and then you can have that kind of relationship later on, you know
but I love, I love it
when people have to face their shit
that's fucked up about themselves personally
and get over it and yeah, it's what this episode was
and it was fucking great.
I love that the scene of Rick hammering Jerry with all of that
is immediately followed by a scene
of Jerry being repeatedly slapped in the face
by the testicles of a monster that he's riding in the sack of.
Yeah, that was fucking great.
That's what I love about Rick and Morty
that's the kind, that's the Rick and Morty I want
I can deal with all the clever, the clever bickering or whatever
you know, like the last episode I was complaining
that too much of it was like the snarky back and forth
the Rick and Morty stuff that makes me bust out laughing
is when they hit you with some, some deep real shit
and then follow it up with a amazingly timed dick joke, you know
The show really needs to keep that going
if it doesn't, like yeah, it starts to feel like
like a Marvel movie I guess
which I don't want, which I do not want
this, yeah, I want to keep that raw shit
keep it flowing guys
Yeah, it was fucking good, not to mention the fact that
during that scene where Jerry's just being
emotionally devastated by Rick
and he's crying, he's just like literally being
eaten and devoured by a monster and is fucking dying
That's great, you know, you gotta die
and you gotta deal with your shit to become a real boy, Jerry
Oh, it was good, hey, but you know
there was a bunch of other cool stuff in this episode
How about that immortality field?
That was pretty fucking dope.
Yeah, cool idea
There's a, there's a manga that is kind of all about this
like exploring this idea
There's a manga called Immortal Hounds
which takes place in a world where
there's like a society where no one can die
and like people who can die can, because of like a disease
So like the police are just hunting those people down with impunity
because like they don't want to spread the disease
of being able to die
So if you can die and they can just shoot anybody
it doesn't matter, because if you're immortal
you'll come back to life
and if you die, oh well that guy had the disease
so fuck him, you know
So it's just like constant violence
and people shooting each other
and the thing is that in Immortal Hounds
it's not that you heal instantly like you do in this
it's that when you die you heal
So if you say lose your arms
then you'll just be without arms
until you bleed out and die and then you come back
So it does a lot of interesting things with that
This is a less interesting usage of the concept than that
but that's also in that case
it's the entire series about that
Yeah right, the fact that you can insert that into one episode
as like a set piece is great
and it's really cool and yeah
it's used to what little, you know
like the effect that they could cram into this episode
I think my favorite part of the whole episode
that wasn't directly related to Jerry's whole shit
was just at the end after like, you know
the shit goes down and the immortality field goes away
and the little kid who had been murdering his sister for fun
over and over shoots her again and he's just like
Liz? She's fucking dead
and the thing about that scene
that scene is close to
this show, I've said this before
this show is always writing on this line
between like just glib violence
that I would find disgusting
and violence that's fun and breezy
and this is like right on the line but I think it's fun and breezy
whereas in the last episode the one guy getting horribly fucking
murdered for no reason was just kind of gross
and it was like why? Why did we need this?
Like what did he do that was so obnoxious
that he deserved to die so
bizarrely? In this episode
it's just some minor little background character
but the fact that earlier in the episode
Jerry had said that's just bad parenting
either way
that makes it hilarious that it happens
That's exactly right and beyond hilarious
it's actually kind of making a point
that I actually like a lot
it's like yeah don't live in a fucking fan still world
like Jerry's just like this is
the fact that Jerry immediately recognized
that this is like stupid and irresponsible
and was 100% right
yeah it's good you know he's got a little bit of wisdom in him
he's not a total fucking idiot
it's good that was really good
yeah it was a good moment
Kill more children Rick and Morty
we gotta yeah and it's
you know they managed to make
horribly murdering a child funny
yeah
um
what
I'm trying to think of
I'm trying to think of anything other than
the crazy trippy scene to talk about
but we have to address it because it's just
this episode they go through
a wormhole and just there's
this total mind fuck scene where they get
like mind melded for an epoch
or something but it's a fleeting
high so it's like waking up
because I know this feel
of like I've had those dreams
that last like days
and it's like you've lived this other life
and then you wake up and for like
five minutes
you feel like this incredible
dysphoria between like your mind
and body having like having to remember
who you actually are
and like where you really are
but then it just goes away and you forget about the dream
and it doesn't matter anymore and like
that was this moment of
I have um
something I've always been really interested in
is like these kinds of time accelerations
like people who've experienced
an incredible amount of time would have such
a different perspective on
everything you know so like
in that moment after it
happened they have such this incredible
understanding of one another
that could have been I mean
that was a whole epoch of experience
of them being a completely different person
but they forget about it so quickly
that it already doesn't matter
you know they lived
an infinite number of other seasons
of Rick and Morty that we'll never see
that's an excellent way to put it
in which Rick and Jerry
have a great relationship
doing weird trippy shit
like fucking and also turning into
animals and killing each other
and evolving and shit
and then at the end he's like
already he just doesn't give a fuck
after like one second that's fucking hilarious
that's great
that's the great juxtaposition there
of this shit happening and them just not giving a fuck
like that's like the good kind of nihilistic
stuff this does
it's like a fucking funny joke
that makes me laugh and go ha ha
that's good that's the good shit
while also being
while also not only being
a like high level concept
but also one that you can understand
in one sentence
like Rick explains he just says
whatever it's called
is a more fleeting high
salvia you know like
immediately we get why they're coming
down like what just happened
and why it's not affecting them anymore
is all set in a couple lines
while you're imagining this much bigger
concept that they've actually explored
that's classic that's what I love about Rick and Morty
that's like my favorite thing about the show
is that
and
then also one of my favorite scenes
is so we've got a B-plot in this episode
about Summer accidentally turning herself
giant
it's definitely the less interesting
part of the episode but I'm okay with that
I'm okay with B-plots in general
I think it makes sense when you're trying to
split up a story
and have more than one thing going on
and we get this fucking hilarious moment
when Beth turns herself giant
and it's talking to Summer
and you can't understand what either of them
are saying like they're having this big
emotional moment but it's just
like
that was fucking hilarious
by the way do you think this was an attack
on Titan reference
it just kind of looked like it
I know it's kind of recent
I didn't even think about it
could be for all I know
what do you think of Morty vindictively
fucking over
the guy who
for hurting his sister's feelings
I enjoyed
seeing Morty in that role
of like the like it makes sense
that like this guy is seeing the shit now
like he's in a place where he can easily
do this kind of stuff when he wants to
just like threaten people and
do you think Morty will eventually become
Rick
that's kind of what seems to be implied
sort of
in season two we were constantly given
in fact ever since season one there's been this idea
that he is the good Morty
he's the smarter Morty than
the other Mortys
in season two he always has
these moments where like he tries to be
like more Rick like but he's
still so stupid that he gets himself
fucked over anyways but now in season
three sometimes
Morty doesn't fuck up
this episode Morty had all the power
Morty tricked Rick
into going on this adventure
so he could get rid of Rick
like Rick the concept
of this episode is Rick thinks he's
taking he thinks Morty is so worried
about Jerry so he takes
Jerry on a fake adventure to placate
Morty but Morty is actually
just wanted to break from
hanging out with Rick and so tricked
him into taking his dad
instead yeah Morty doesn't give a fuck
about Jerry he doesn't give a fuck
about Rick he just wanted Rick out of
his hair and then he's mad
and you know and he's
smarter than his mom in the situation they get into
you know he's the voice of reason there
and I'm just like Morty was completely on
top of his game this episode what the fuck
you know he's really getting his shit together
yeah there's no doubt about it
yeah it's an interesting idea
I've never been sure if I wanted
that but now if it's
like this I kind of do
well you know I was thinking so we've seen
all these multi-verse versions of Morty
but have we ever seen like older Morty
like what he'll be like as an adult no
I don't think we've ever explored that
we've never really got into like
future or past of the
lines of the characters which is probably smart
in terms of wanting to be able to keep writing
the story without fucking up too bad
like all the different ricks
the different dimensional ricks are always
an old man you know yeah by the way
quick aside so in this episode
we learned that Rick's got
a ton of cybernetic enhancements
all over his body and that's really
cool and I like that
it's interesting but
it's kind of weird that that hasn't
ever come up before and it strikes me
as like okay he's been
in a lot of situations where it'd be really
useful to have used those and he just never
did so it's it feels to me like
someone just wrote that in this episode like
they thought it would be cool well when we finally
see him use one he like
opens up this massive gun
to shoot a suction cup at
somebody so I think maybe they're all just
weird stupid prank
well he does that but then he also
blasts the guys head off like with the same gun
but yeah it also had like the suction cup thing
um yeah
I don't care at all it was cool but
yeah it doesn't matter
my favorite joke
in this episode is
Placated Rick
like the fact that
the idea that
in order to prevent
international terrorism when you get on a plane
they just inject you with something that makes you
a fucking retard
with no controversial opinions
or intelligence
and that and that they did this
to Rick like he was not prepared for it
and now he's just completely helpless
and he's talking like a baby
and it's fucking hilarious like Jerry beating
up on him while he was retarded was the funniest
shit in the world to me yeah that was
good that was good shit
um well
fuck anything else I mean we
oh you know what one other aspect of this episode
is like
Beth's just like need to like
be in charge of shit like she's doing this
weird you know what she's doing her weird like
hoover like lull epic joke guys
um but then like this is a bizarre one
yeah I thought it was
kind of cool but then like so there's the whole thing
that she's kind of like vying with Morty about
how like she needs to like be able to solve
these issues without her dad
and it seems like it all really just stems from
the need to like like Morty sums it up later
on the episode like yeah like just stop
stop sucking up to your dad like stop trying to
just like make his life great and be super
you know
and whatever like conciliatory to whatever
he fucking needs
I feel like uh what's great about this
situation with Beth is that now with Jerry
out of the picture we're getting to look at
the fact that Jerry wasn't all her
problems yeah you know like
up until this point it's been
like all of the bad things like
all of her emotional issues have been blamed on Jerry
and now that we see that with him out of the picture
she doesn't just immediately thrive
yeah she's not suddenly like a badass
who gets to do anything she's just
horribly emotionally damaged
weirdo who
you know like instead of going
and doing something scientific with her time
is like building a hoof statue
it's like what she's
she's broken you know which is interesting
uh uh because you know
Rick brings up you know when he when having the big
fight with him and Jerry uh how
how Jerry ruined this
his daughter you know like this is Rick
Sanchez's daughter she could have done fucking
anything and instead like he knocked her up
this fucking piece of shit
worm loser whose only skill
in life is making people pity him
which I'm sure is just the worst thing
Rick could like possibly have to deal with
um oh god
the fact I'm just thinking of like if my
daughter married a guy like Jerry
like Jesus Christ that would be
the fucking where I would want to murder him
I would want to murder that man it would be
a nightmare but it's also partly Rick's fault
because he wasn't around that's very true
that's a very good point like
that's the one who created the emotional vulnerability
that probably left her open to just like
fucking around with this kid and she was
a little baby yeah so uh
that sucks though you know I do wonder
did she you know the
the fact that you brought up before like the fact that Jerry
disappears and it doesn't immediately solve all our
problems did she does she really have
like that much going on for herself
like I know she's Rick's daughter but it's
not like she's some kind of super genius
in her own right you know
maybe that's Rick she's been a little yeah
that's him being a dad you know just being a straight
up dad there
I don't know something to think about I'm
going to be keeping that in mind and like see if
she shows burgeoning potential of
I don't know magic science powers
or something I guess I don't know
yeah
well that's uh that's all I've got to
say about this episode really strong
you know not not as like
it's not one of those like brick
shitting incredible episodes that like
is just so perfectly crafted
like episode one yeah
or something or or one that's
like super unique like pickle Rick like
this is very this is like standard
Rick and Morty in a good way
the last episode was like if you took
just like the
like the bog standard of the show
but like below like without actually
having anything that stands out
this is an episode that's like as good as what
should be the average for this
show I completely agree that's a good way
of putting it I should be like this should be
the minimum and above and beyond
should be the maximum I
very much agree I'd give it like a strong
eight or something like that
yeah agree all right
well that's it everybody thanks for listening
rikstymids back next week
hey I don't give a fuck bitch
I don't care about anything
bye bye