I don't give a fuck, bitch. Welcome to episode 2 of Rick's D Minutes, the show where we talk about each episode of Rick and Morty as it comes out.
We had our first episode of A Distant Pilot as it was with the show itself.
Yes, right.
And now we're here. The show's actually airing. I'm joined by Best Guy Ever here.
What's up?
Oh, and I'm Digibro. This is, you know, it's not on my channel, so I should probably introduce myself as well.
Oh yeah, good idea.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, this is fucking episode 2 of season 3.
It's finally here.
The fucking warm-awaited.
We've been waiting for it and now it's out and I watched it and it was good.
And they put it right on adultswim.com so everyone can watch it, which I really appreciate.
Yeah, that's really cool.
Yeah, it's great.
It's great.
I watched all of season 1 the first time on adultswim.com, but I don't think they were doing them like simultaneous release before.
This, I don't know if this was simultaneous, but it's the next day and we watched it there, so that's pretty cool.
Yeah.
I'm fucking adultwim.
It's the way to go.
Any what's up.
Yeah, pretty cool episode, I thought, to start with.
Yeah, you think so?
What did you think?
I was actually a little bit underwhelmed.
A little bit underwhelmed.
I thought it was a little...
I would say underwhelmed is a fair, compared to the opener.
That was so amazingly great.
Okay, like obviously it was not as good as that.
Yeah, I don't know.
What do you think?
Go on about your feelings in general.
Alright, well my big thing about this episode is that I feel like this, in some ways, is making fun of the biggest criticisms that this show has been getting.
You think so?
Yeah, because what I see when people who don't like Rick and Morty talk about, particularly the fans of Rick and Morty,
everyone makes fun of them for just claiming that the show is super deep just because it's nihilistic.
Like the parody that I've been seeing around of the show is that Rick just goes,
nothing matters, blah blah blah, and the fans go, oh it's so deep.
And in this episode, it kind of lampshades that because that's literally what Summer does in this episode.
That is true.
She becomes this really edgy nihilistic edgelord.
And that's her whole character in this episode is that she becomes obsessed with nihilism and not giving a fuck and senseless violence.
And she just embodies all the criticisms people have about Rick and Morty.
And then the episode kind of looks at her and goes, yeah, that is shallow.
She's just acting out.
It's so funny.
Before I watched this, I happened to be on TV.
I was just looking for a download.
I didn't find one, so I just went here.
But on the TV board, where I thought there might be one, it was just full of those.
It was just completely full of that exact criticism.
That's a big one right now.
It definitely is.
I mean, at least from the shit I was seeing, they were just taking that at face value and being like, lol, nihilism.
Yeah, and nothing beyond that.
And that's true that it definitely did lampshade that.
I just didn't feel like it had any real counterpoint.
And not that the show really needs to defend itself on that front.
I just didn't find its argument.
Like, what's the resolution there at the end of the summer?
She's just like, eh, it's kind of like the exact same point that was made when Morty was like, yeah, blah, blah, blah.
Nothing matters.
Come watch TV.
Just like, yeah, just don't worry about it.
You know, it's fine.
Things kind of matter.
Things kind of do matter a little bit.
I mean, I won't say that this episode had a strong message.
I don't think it did an amazing job of proving the critics wrong if that's what it was going for.
But I feel like what this episode was trying to say is like, okay, that's not what this show is about, though.
Like, yes, we go over the top with edgy violence and dark brutal humor and nihilism.
And yeah, we know it can look goofy, but the show is about this emotional side.
You know, like, it's always been like, what has made the show so endearing and interesting is not that it's nihilistic and full of violence.
There's plenty of shows like that.
If I wanted that, I would have them make Corgath the Barbarian into a full show.
Did you ever watch that?
Of course.
It was great.
Like, yeah, it was just fucking violence.
You know, that's all it was.
And it was a fun time.
But like, the reason people get attached to Rick and Morty the way they do is not because it is senselessly violent and nihilistic.
It's because there's this more interesting human story going on underneath it.
And like, the fact that it managed to, what I was impressed with this episode, and this is the only thing I would consider like absolutely impressive about it.
Like, otherwise it's a pretty standard Rick and Morty episode.
Yeah.
But it's just the fact that it did manage to make like what the kids were going through and the wife feel like emotionally poignant on some level.
Like, yeah, they're going through this like, this hardship of the breakup and like, you know, their parents are getting divorced and they're really trying to deal with these emotions.
And like, it was believable from them.
But at the same time, managing to just shit on Jerry relentlessly.
Like, everyone else, the way everyone else is dealing with the breakup is taken very seriously.
The way that he's dealing with it is just completely shit on and they don't care at all.
And I thought that was like such a weird dynamic that worked really well for me.
I really do like the way they unequivocally accept the fact that Jerry's a fucking pussy loser and there's no redeeming qualities to him.
That's just, that's not open for debate.
It's a closed issue.
That is not what these kids are hung up about.
Like, they're having trouble dealing with, like, in fact, what they're hung up about is that they're frustrated with him.
Like, neither of them is mad at the fact that their parents are splitting up.
They're mad that Jerry's not doing anything about it.
They're mad that he's hanging around and being a namby-pamby piece of shit and like trying to, and he's not committing.
He's not fucking committing to shit.
He's just being a little bitch trying to hang.
He's being a fucking orbiter of this family is what he is right now.
It's very embarrassing and he needs to, to, to nut up already.
And I think that's a really kind of fascinating dynamic for a family breakup in a show that like,
the kids are, like, they're mad at him for the same reasons the mom is.
And they're just like, dude, you need to either get the fuck out of our lives,
or fucking nut up and do something about this, you know?
And like, when they see that he's not gonna nut up,
and then both, their conclusion is, oh, I guess you are a huge pussy.
So, you know, maybe stop hanging around us.
You know, like, god damn, it's so brutal to Jerry.
It really is.
And the way that it delivers that to me through like, Morty's whole quest
of getting over the fact that his dad's a pussy,
like, I like all that stuff a lot more than I like those like,
and I know it was obvious on purpose,
but like the super on the nose joke of the like, you're a pussy.
Or like whatever that whisper was.
I get it, that's fine, but I'm just glad that we were away from that really fast,
because it's way more interesting to explore the issue through the lens of the other people in his life,
specifically, you know, Morty and the gang, who are the interesting characters,
as opposed to Jerry, who we all know is shit, we all get it.
I'm satisfied with the amount of Jerry that was in this episode,
because I expressed a very strong desire that now that we're kicking Jerry out of the show,
we commit to that, that he's gone, and we don't focus on him too much.
And like, the way he was presented in this episode,
it felt like he was not really a main cast member anymore.
Like, it felt like he was just there, he was around a little bit,
because we needed a little bit of him, but like, the show is unequivocally shitting on him at this point.
He is not a major character.
He is there to be shit on by the show, you know?
I'm still a little bit wondering if that was like the gag of this episode,
to shit on Jerry intensely, and that there will be some change to that as we go on through season three,
but you know, there's no way to know, there's no way to know yet.
So, how did you feel about the overall Mad Max parody world?
I felt it was, you know, I really liked the Purge episode.
I thought that was a really great episode.
You know, this was a fine like parallel for what they were trying, not a parallel,
but it was a fine, you know, representation of like how Summer was feeling
in the kind of world she wanted to live in right now, where she, I don't know,
where she like has control over things in her life, as opposed to her parents' life,
or you know, her parents' relationship, where she has no control over it.
So, here's her, and the same with Morty.
Like Morty is able to find a way to have power over something in his life by coming out of this place.
You know, the setting itself was cool.
I like the characters that were there, I guess.
You know, I didn't like Buckethead Man, just like, he was weird.
I didn't like his voice performance.
Yeah.
Like, he felt he was weirdly in between trying to be like, I don't know,
like he was a little too deadpan almost.
Like, he's saying all this shit that's like supposed to be this like, you know,
like he's supposed to be talking like one of the people in these movies,
but he's got like a totally normal guy voice,
and they didn't like play it up enough in either direction for it to work for me.
I was not happy with his voice performance.
His performance here makes me terrified that there's intentions to make this character like important,
or recurring in some way.
No, he'll never show up again.
Yeah.
I don't know, man.
I hope that's true.
Like, the fact that nothing bad happened to this character at all in any way
makes me think that he's being set up to come back and just like, like, oh my God.
Honestly, this might be the worst scene in any Rick and Morty episode I've ever seen.
That like mustache conversation about the helmet.
Like, I know later on, it got to the point where like,
acknowledges that it's a shitty conversation,
but that was like a minute of my time being wasted on discussions about this fucking dude's hair
and like the obvious relationship they were building up between him and Summer.
Oh my God.
Like, that wasn't clever.
That wasn't witty.
It was just boring.
It wasn't that long, so I'm not going to like dwell on it ruining the episode or anything,
but man, did I not give a shit about that scene.
Yeah.
I mean, that character to me, what I felt like while watching it was this sounds like an act.
Like, this is clearly a guest star.
Yeah, exactly.
Like, he had that guest star feel and I felt like this seems like a dude who probably like isn't in voice acting much.
Like, this is a normal actor who's doing voice acting for the first time.
I just looked it up and it's Joel McHale, the guy who played the main character in Community.
Well, there you go.
That's the reason why he's so weird and sucks and filled up the script because he's a famous actor.
Great actor.
Great in Community.
Sure.
Not exactly known for his voice acting.
He has been in Bojack Horseman and a couple of, he hasn't not ever done voice acting.
I mean, he could be the best voice actor in the world and the dialogue written for him was terrible because they were trying to fill space.
And like, I know, okay, you know what?
This is good because it makes it seem less likely that it'll come back a lot, but it does.
Like, this character was weirdly protected by like an aura of like, nothing bad's gonna happen to this guy.
I could just tell, I could just tell immediately from the way his dialogue was written that this guy was like special in some way and he didn't earn that or deserve it in any way.
No.
It was weird and uncomfortable and I hope they don't do it more.
I thought he was a boring joke.
Yeah.
Like, I got what the joke was and I thought it was boring and I didn't think he, he was definitely the weakest element of the episode for me.
I feel like this, the thing about Rick and Morty is that it does lots of parodies and it usually either does them in a way that's like, so, like, like they take the original concept and they do something even more inventive with it or take it beyond the impossible.
Like when they did Inception in like episode two.
Yeah.
With, you know, the, like, the Freddy Kruger meets Inception.
That's genius.
Right.
You know, what if Freddy Kruger got into the Inception world?
Like, that's a good idea.
Sometimes though, they do a parody and they like seem to deliberately half-ass it because they're like, look, we're not really here for the parody.
Like, it's just, you know, it is what it is.
It's there.
And sometimes that doesn't work as well for me and this is one of those cases where I was like, like, they didn't even, I'm glad they at least didn't like mention that it's a Mad Max world.
Like they usually would.
Like Purge Planet.
I don't know.
They continually are like, this is the Purge Planet.
But that's what was so funny.
Like they just used Purge to describe everything in that episode.
Yeah.
That episode totally worked.
That was great.
I'm glad they didn't say like, oh, we're in Mad Max world this time because like it was such a boilerplate, like, Mad Max world.
You know, like they didn't do much as a Mad Max concept.
Well, that's the weird thing though.
It was so obviously Fury Road that I felt it was weird that they didn't mention that specifically.
I felt like it's, it's, it's got literally everything that Fury Road had.
Well, it's got the, I mean, it also has the Thunder Dome.
So that's Mad Max.
Which is Mad Max in every way.
They did name-drap the Thunder Dome at least.
So, you know, which they say, oh, don't you mean the Blood Dome or whatever.
He's like hilarious joke, guys.
Hilarious joke.
I don't know.
That was all right.
But yeah, it, it felt like a, you know, like you said, this is a good idea for like taking
Summer to a nihilistic world.
Yeah.
That part of it's good.
Like the world in itself, I felt like this was one of the weaker parodies that Rick and
Morty has done.
I agree.
Of like a, of a, of a world just because the characters didn't feel right.
Dude.
They didn't feel like, like the mustache guy did not feel like he was in a Mad Max world.
And like, I, the only part that I thought was genius was the very end when the, they
used the crystal stone and it becomes just modern society and it immediately ruins it
for, for Summer.
That was good stuff.
And that was the only part where I was like, oh yes, like this is a great idea.
But they could have done that with other settings other than Mad Max, you know.
And you're absolutely right about that.
But like, okay.
What was the, what was the deal with the fact that there's just a king in Mad Max world?
Like, how does that in any way make sense?
There's nothing about this that is at all reasonable.
They're, they're just like, is a king who like, he's the same slave.
Well, he was the same.
In Fury Road, there's a king.
In Fury Road, what's his face?
Mortan Joe is like their warlord God King.
Like this is just some like, some like, oh yeah, that, what is that?
Yeah.
Total, that was like total left turn.
Like they just went from Fury Road world into like medieval world.
How did that happen?
And why?
And what the fuck?
So it was that the arm that Morty had had a vengeance because it had, it had its village
burned down.
Right.
The behest of some king.
And yeah, there's just like a king in a castle.
Like that was also really weird.
I don't know.
I haven't seen all the Mad Max movies.
I don't know if that's a thing in the first one.
Like I've seen Road Warrior and I've seen most of Thunderdome and all of Fury Road,
but there's no kings in any of those, you know.
I'm looking at the environments they're in right now and it's like just a fucking fantasy
castle place.
It just, it's so not Mad Max.
Again, yeah, maybe I'm missing something.
Maybe this wasn't a Mad Max, but it feels bizarre and weird and I hate it.
That is a strange thing.
Yeah, but I mean, yeah, there's definitely elements of this episode that are less strong.
It was just not.
Yeah, the king guy.
He didn't do anything with him.
Yeah.
There's, okay, but here's the thing, like all that stuff is kind of not that important.
You know, those are like, yeah, okay, it's not the best, you know, but it's fine.
It's serviceable.
One thing that did actually actively bother me throughout this episode is that the way
this plot played out should not be possible with Rick's powers.
Like, there are so many moments he could have just shot a portal gun and it would be over.
Oh, yeah, I hear you.
I hear you.
Like, why does he need to hatch a scheme to steal this rock?
Yeah, that's the thing.
They could have just grabbed the rock and left.
Like, that's something, we just, in episode one of this season, Rick destroyed the world
government while simultaneously kicking Jerry out of his house, all in one fell swoop.
And he did it like, he's the biggest schemer in the whole world.
And he has to like, fumble and bullshit his way through trying to get this rock.
I don't understand why he didn't just kill everyone.
Um, yeah.
Like, this is a guy who doesn't, he like, at the start of the episode, he's like, about
to leave a summer on the planet.
And he tells Morty like, you've got infinite sisters, but you know, I don't want to hear
you bitch.
So I'll save this one.
And then 10 seconds later, he sees like this big rock that he wants and he doesn't just
murder everyone and take it.
Like, really?
Yeah.
That seems like something he would do, you know.
Explain that away with the one line of like, there's too much heat on it.
Uh, yeah.
Pretty weak excuse.
No.
Pretty fucking weak excuse.
Too many, like there's, there's also a moment where they try to excuse where like, when
he's in the car with the other two and he says, you know, I've got a portal gun and
I could just leave you guys here and I'm like, yeah, but you could also just shoot the, like,
couldn't you just teleport them?
Like, I know you can use this for more than what you're doing right now.
Like, it just felt very forced to me that Rick had to be in this scenario where he has
to like, oh, I got to sneak around and I'm like, you don't have to sneak around.
We know you don't have to sneak around, you know.
Again, I think everything in this episode is facilitating something that I do like.
I like the story with Summer and Morty.
I love the Morty's arm subplot.
I thought that was the best part of the episode.
That shit was hilarious.
Yeah.
I liked it.
Um, yeah, I don't know.
It was one of those things that I did enjoy it as it was happening.
It just kind of fell a little flat for me in terms of the humor.
This whole episode, I found pretty darn unfunny overall, like compared to a normal episode.
I don't know.
I felt like the wit was just dulled down in general, maybe for this like cameo of this
other character going on or something.
But I liked what they did with the arm.
I thought it was funny that there'd be a sentient arm that just goes on a rampage to
get vengeance for like it's burned family and I really like the way that like the relationship
between Morty and the arm develops and how it like becomes more and more.
Cause at first it's just like a gag that like the arm remembers fighting.
So it punches out Rick and it's just like a really strong arm and then it goes and just
murders everybody.
And then as Morty like comes to understand this feeling of brutality and like wanting
this as a way to vent, like he can communicate more deeply with his arm and then like the
arm goes on this whole journey to resolve its own conflicts that have been established
so who knows how long ago and like, you know, the scene where Morty drowns the king and
like he's just like talking to Rick while drowning the king with this big beefy arm
and the arm goes away cause it's satisfied, but it's not, he's not actually dead and then
Rick helps them to like finish the job.
That was great to me.
That was a good ending.
And I love the fact that this whole thing kind of hinges on this like incredibly vague
notion of muscle memory, which is not a real thing and like that's like the joke that this
is all propped on.
Now that's funny that I like a lot.
That's great.
That's my favorite thing.
The arm thing is the best part.
And again, I like Summers, I like the Summers development again, seems like an answer to
the criticism of the show that like, oh, it's just nihilistic bullshit and like that's
literally what she is and she just becomes this like total hard ass who's murdering everybody
and then like, you know, cause it felt like this is a natural progression for Summer.
We've seen her continually get more and more into this work, you know, but she's gotten
to a point where it's self-destructive and not really smart and you know, Rick is, Rick
is, will never take these two as actual pupils.
That will never happen.
He will give them advice along the way.
He will give affirmation when they do something that he thinks is cool and he will give consternation
when they're in his way, but he will never just tell Summer like, hey, um, you're acting
retarded act this way.
He'll just watch and be like, oh, she's going to get herself killed.
Fuck her.
You know, like his attitude towards her is really funny to me that like when he sees her
like, oh, I'm going to hang back and fucking fight these guys.
He's just like, well, fuck her.
Let's get out of here.
You know?
Yeah.
Classic shit.
It's, it's fun.
This show walks such a tightrope for me where like, uh, I think I discussed this on the last
episode that like I'm not really big into like glib violence most of the time, but this
show manages to do it in just such a way where like, I don't know, it never like offends me.
Like it can be insanely turbo violent, but I always feel like there's something behind
it.
You know, it's a combination of, uh, you know, because this is a cartoon, I feel like
they can get away with that stuff.
Like I'm never like disgusted or anything on like a super deep level by the shit I see.
I mean, it's actually sometimes like, uh, like the, the rape of Morty, like that or
the almost rape of Morty.
Now that's a disturbing thing.
But that's supposed to be disturbing.
And it was great.
And they did it just right.
It's not glib at all.
Exactly.
It's almost the attitude.
It's the attitude that frames everything.
Yeah.
I don't think they've ever done a violent scene where it was like the wrong person dying
for the wrong reason, you know, like if, if they just, for instance, like had Jerry just
like blow up or something grossly like that.
And then everyone was like, oh, well, fuck him.
It'd be like, really?
That's how you're going to.
Yeah.
But, but shitting on Jerry constantly is fine because like Jerry does deserve it.
Like he is a shit, you know.
So like there is satisfaction in watching the whole show piss on him, but it does so in
a way that's not like cruel and unusual.
You know, like the dog eating his welfare check at the end, like he gives it to the
dog.
That was funny.
Yeah.
He just pussies out as he always does.
Of course.
Like on the, if, if you're thinking of it like at first something, okay, this is like
cosmic level of like fucking with him.
But like then it's, it's him who ultimately does it.
Like if the dog had just come up and eaten the welfare check, it wouldn't have been that
funny.
It's just like, okay, whatever, we get it.
You're shitting on Jerry.
But the fact that he gives it to the dog, it's just like, what are you doing?
You fucking pathetic idiot.
I think about this a lot.
I think about the fact that I could totally stomp a dog to death if it ever attacked me.
I think about that.
Cause people always talk about dogs.
I love to do that.
I could, I love dogs and would never want to do it unless necessary, but I could totally
stomp a dog.
I could, I could beat a dog.
I'm just saying.
Jerry, you could have beat that dog, you pansy bitch.
That was, he could have taken him.
I know he could have.
Yeah, that was, that was good.
That was good shit.
That was like, that was like the good answer to like the first joke that was like the little
you're a loser or whatever.
That didn't make me laugh.
At the end it did.
So you know what?
Even that joke, I suppose did have like a payoff to it at the end.
So fair enough.
I didn't completely understand the scene where Summer gave him the skull.
Yeah.
I wasn't sure what they communicated to one another.
I didn't know what Jerry was getting at when he was like, like, why is he like, like, is
he just getting blackpilled by his divorce now?
And he also, yeah, go on, go on.
I thought maybe he just didn't understand and was just like, okay, whatever, you know,
but like, but then he said something like something was going on there.
Yeah.
I didn't get it.
That scene was confusing for me.
I'm legit.
Yeah.
I watched it twice and I am baffled by what the fuck they attempted to communicate there.
So did you like the little robo morty becoming sentient and wanting life?
You know, that was pretty fun.
I like it.
Yeah.
I like the, that's another one of those things that this show does an amazing job of, of like
just throwing in like high level sci-fi concepts that other entire shows would be based on
and just having it as like a one off gag in the background.
Like, you know, this idea that, that Rick's, which I mean, granted, they've done this exact
joke before when he built the butter passing robot.
Yeah.
You know, what is my purpose?
And it's like, you passed butter and that was probably a better executed version of
the joke.
Better and speedier.
Yeah.
But this was still.
All right.
Yeah.
I liked it.
What I like about this joke is mostly the part when they all leave and then the mom's like
confused about the two different versions because she's like, why don't you go run
in a stream?
And he's like, no, what the fuck are you talking about?
I didn't like that.
And I, you know, I just feel a need to say like, okay, she's like, she's, she is, there's
something wrong with this lady that she's not asking questions about what's going on
here.
And I suppose that I, this, this has been well documented by now that she will just
excuse anything that her dad does, she just will tune that shit out.
She's, she's hashtag damaged for sure.
Yeah.
And she's an alcoholic.
Well, that's true.
I'm sure that's related.
Yeah.
I really love her.
I love her character.
I can't say that.
I love her.
I want more out of her.
I, I like her in her position in the story as this like poor, poor woman who's been so
emotionally manipulated by her, her evil father, well not evil, but you know, basically
evil.
Yeah.
I like that a lot.
But even Jerry, I think has more character to him at this point.
She hasn't like, like she's more character, but yeah, you know, he's always been like
the guy who you're like, oh fuck off, you know, you're right, you're right.
But, and I don't even know if I necessarily like want a character arc for fuck what's
her name?
Uh,
Slipping my mind.
Daughter, for daughter, whatever her name is.
I don't even know if I want her to have one.
I feel like she actually does belong in this story as the rock.
Like she's, she's something that Rick does seem to care about sort of and like at least
in, in the idea of her, he wants to protect her in general and, and that's good.
And then she can, you know, sit here while her family does crazy stuff around her and
be the alcoholic who's totally oblivious to the things happening.
I don't know.
I appreciate it.
I feel like this show is in some way running into a danger of like this, because we are
presented with this idea that like, yeah, Rick will look out for her at least, but like
he has abandoned one of her in season one when he just like left that universe behind.
So like, I don't know, sometimes the show is fond of her.
He's like fond of her, you know?
Yeah.
I feel like this show runs into problems with consistency on like what Rick will do or can
do.
Like the fact that he couldn't get them out of the situation much more easily in this
episode, especially when he seemed lucid.
Like there are times where Rick fucks up, but it seems like he's just literally like
in an, like a insane episode, you know, or like his mind has, is not working right.
And that's why he's not doing it.
And I'm fine with that.
I'm okay with like Rick's got space dementia.
That makes sense to me.
Or Rick is just a drunk, you know, or high.
I'm okay with that.
But when it seems like he's completely right of mind, he's in his normal good sense.
And yet he's like not able to solve what seems like a basic situation or like he's making
different moral decisions from what he did earlier in the episode.
It's just like, yeah, you're playing a little too close to the fire there, you know?
I hear what you're saying.
But like, so Rick has always had like, it's been his modus operandi to like involve Morty
on these like extremely like pedantic adventures to get like little knickknacks or whatever
the fuck that he's trying to do for whatever.
So like, you know, there's, there's, I'd say like last episode, there was an absolute
like power level spike in, in Rick's like mental abilities to like, like he's unmatched
completely on every level.
No one can do anything to this dude.
He just completely decimated the entire universe with sheer mental power.
And like, there's no way anything can compete with that, like if he stayed at that level
all the time.
So I think that the only way they could do that was to like elevate him to that status
for an episode.
And now we have to swallow a pill that like, okay, we're going to dial this back a little
bit.
I just think there's a way to avoid ways like there are stories you can write with him in
like situations where he just like, isn't aware, isn't paying attention, things like
that.
I think so.
Like, I mean, if you look at episode one, like in that whole episode, he's just fucking
insane.
Like he's, when he makes Ricky like, when he makes Morty wear them, he makes him wear
the boots, the gravity boots, like doesn't explain them properly and stuff like that.
You know, and like, there's, there's lots of times where Rick, like you said, pedantic
adventures, but usually it's like his inattentiveness, like in the big party episode where he makes
Morty go get the Klaxian crystals and he's like, Morty, you got to get these crystals.
It's super important.
Morty has to go on this whole trick and he comes back and he just snorts and it's just
like, it's just crack, you know, with a fleeting high.
And like those moments sell me on like, Rick is just like on a different plane when it
comes to like how he thinks about like risk and reward, you know, this episode didn't
sell me on that.
This episode felt like Rick was completely in his right mind cause he was like the straight
man this episode.
Yeah.
Rick was the straight man in an episode and he still fucks things up, you know.
Usually when he's the straight man, he's like completely in control and like, you know,
no Morty, I have a portal gun, dumbass, you know, Rick.
So basically, I guess there, there's sort of a rule, I guess, about that that like Rick
cannot be placed in a situation where he has a clear goal and clear methods of accomplishing
that goal.
He just, you can't ever put him in that situation because he should just be able to solve it
immediately.
It has to be vague.
Yeah.
It has to be some like weird thing.
Like when he, when he had to build a business that uncursed items that were cursed by the
devil, like that's perfect.
That's exactly what this guy should be doing.
And the scene where he just like gets tired of it and burns it all down.
Yeah.
That's a Rick move, you know.
Exactly.
And I understand why it happened here is cause this episode's not about Rick.
This is not a Rick episode.
It's completely about Summer and Morty.
And so I understand why Rick takes a back seat, but I just think they could have done
it more carefully.
Like it was a little too blatant.
Like I'm looking too hard at Rick's plot line and going, what, why is this the B plot?
This doesn't make any sense.
You know.
Yeah.
I hear you.
Um, okay.
Hey, let's talk about, uh, how do you feel about like specifically the, the underlying
plot thread of the divorce?
You feel like that's moving along?
You feel like we're going anywhere with that in general?
Yeah.
I feel like the kids resolved their feelings for it and maybe, maybe this is the last we'll
see of Jerry for a while.
That's what I was wondering.
Yeah.
Um, it felt like a natural progression from the previous episode and it felt like the
show was really trying to reassure me that like, look, we have things to say about Jerry,
but we're not bringing him back.
He's not like still a major character.
It felt like they were bending over backwards to reassure me.
Look, this is just about the kids dealing with their feelings towards Jerry.
He is really gone.
That's really a thing.
Like, look, they're not trying to get him back.
They've all come to terms with me and gone, believe me.
He's not coming back.
And I'm like, all right.
All right.
You've convinced me.
I'm glad.
I'm glad you've convinced me.
You know.
That farewell scene with Summer, I think if I understood what was going on, what was intended,
I think would have been a good sort of farewell scene for Jerry for a while and we can just
leave it at that for, for a good while.
Unfortunately, it was confusing.
Yeah.
Tell me in the comments what the fuck they meant because I do not understand what was
going on.
So Summer gave a, you know what, never mind.
Yeah.
Just tell me.
And there's plenty of moments at this episode that I thought were pretty cool.
Summer shooting the car and flipping over her and then Rick just being like, OK, that
was cool.
Yeah.
I love when my favorite Rick moments are when he just appreciates the world around him
and what other people are doing.
And the ending scene again, like where the whole society turns into just like modern
society.
Now granted, I thought the actual conversation between Summer and Buckethead guy was weak.
Like I didn't think it was funny.
I got what they were doing, but it wasn't like funny joke wise.
But the entire scene as a concept was definitely a great idea.
Like I laughed really hard just when I saw her like driving up to the place and I was
just like, oh my God, they fucking did it.
Yeah.
I think this, yeah, like that character really fell victim to is nepotism the right word?
I feel like because he's buddies with this guy, he gave him a role and gave him a whole
bunch of lines and made sure nothing bad happened to him and gave him a bunch of silly stuff
like, oh, you're mustache.
You're such a weird, quirky character.
Like that really kills a great actor.
But this character sucked it.
Not cast Wells here.
He was written poorly and yeah, acted badly and everything about this character was really
annoying.
Yeah.
He, this character should have fucking died by the end or something.
Fucking Summer should have blown off his fucking head at the end.
Like that would have been, I don't know, cool or something.
That's a little unnecessary.
All right.
I guess that's unnecessary.
It was funny enough that Rick took the stone and damned that whole civilization back to
what it was before.
I'm just annoyed by the fact that nothing bad happened to this character and I could
sense that that was going to be him from the second he was like revealed to be, I don't
know.
He was just obvious that this guy was like above everybody else.
It annoyed me.
He felt protected by fucking plot armor.
That's what he felt like.
I felt plot armor on this character and it annoyed me because he wasn't funny and nothing
good came of him other than being married to Summer for that one joke that dragged on
too long and got annoying anyway.
Well that's about all I have to say about the episode.
You said all you had?
I think so.
Overall, I thought it was good.
It was not like a great Rick and Morty episode.
It's not one that's going to keep me rewatching it the way the first three episodes of season
two did or the first episode of season three.
It's just one of those like, yeah, all right.
I won't skip it in a rewatch of the show, but it's not incredible.
I agree.
I think I like it a little bit less than you in general.
I really thought, I don't know, something about the humor wasn't doing it for me as
much as consistently and really all this is relative to Rick and Morty being the best
show ever.
It just didn't live up to that bar for me on that front the whole time.
Some of it was great, like we said.
I'd give it a okay.
It was okay to good, I guess.
A light okay, decent good, whatever, something like that.
All right, that's it folks.
Come back next week.
See you then buddy.
Bye-bye.