I don't give a fuck, bitch. Welcome to the first episode of Digibro and Best Guy Ever. That's you.
Dickin' Boardy Time, baby. Yeah, baby, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're talking about Rick and Morty, everybody, season three. Season three. You know, the season
three premiere came out on April 1st on Adult Swim. It was a big deal. Everybody was excited about it.
And we're thinking about maybe talking more about the rest of season three. So here we are
starting things off with that episode. Rick and Morty is like my favorite show ever.
It's just rewatching that episode again just now. It's really hard to argue that that show
isn't like the most dense with high quality content show anywhere right now.
I mean, that's what I love about it. It's so fucking, it's so dense. It's so dense.
Every single shot has so much going on, yeah. It's fantastic. I was a huge fan of the first
season, watched it like five times. Still haven't really rewatched season two. I intended to do
that before three started and three seemingly had snuck up on it. But then it hasn't actually.
It was just a weird April Fools thing. Confused the shit out of me because I was in Atlanta
when it came out. I didn't get the chance to see it. And then every week I was like,
why am I not hearing about the new season of Rick and Morty? Sounds like you were out of it.
I thought I was just missing episodes and no one was telling me somehow. And I was really confused.
So let me just talk about how great this was as an April Fools episode.
So April Fools every year is terrible because everyone tricks you and says like,
hey, I'm going to do this and then I'm not going to do it. And then you're disappointed.
Am I the only one who loves April Fools? Yes. We were all complaining about it,
but me and the rest of the PCP were all shitting on it. I love April Fools because people always,
well, it depends on who it is. Some people just do some bullshit, but I love when people pull out
all the stops to do some crazy shit. That's what makes it good. If you follow the old web
comment XKCD, every year he would do some kind of like insane shit, like turn his entire website
into a fucking text adventure game or something, like some crazy programming shit. Well, that's fine.
It used to be that websites would really go all out and make like a crazy thing for April Fools
Day. And it was always exciting to see like what everybody was doing that day. And I historically
have always made April Fools videos. Well, what you're describing is the good side of April Fools,
but there is the downside, whereas people say like, oh, I'm going like, oh, Half-Life 3 is out.
Wow. I'm so excited. Oh, it's not actually out. Okay, fuck you. But what, I mean, but this episode
is exactly that. Watch the fucking calendars, people. That's all I'm saying. Everyone loves
fucking Rick and Morty. Everyone agrees. It's fantastic too. Like on April Fools, get this like
loop of the new episode that is so legitimately good and well crafted and has, even the episode
itself has a ton of Mr. X as Rick and Morty episodes tend to do. Like this is exactly what an April
Fools should be. We're getting more. We're not being cheated or lied to. We're just getting extra
stuff. That's what you should celebrate about the day. Yeah. I mean, that's the best way to April
Fools is to make an actual surprise. Surprised by people by giving them more shit, by making them
happy as opposed to pissed off. That's what I like. Though personally, I think you should just
know what day it is. It's not hard to know April 1st is coming. I don't know. Maybe because I make a
big deal out of it, like I always have plans for April Fools, so I know it's coming. But that just
means one day of the year, you just be like, oh, everything's a lie today. No one is telling me
the truth today. That's just annoying. I don't want that. Maybe it's a nice change of pace, I guess.
I fucking get pissed off by it. But anyway, forget that. To me, it's like the classic festivals
like the masquerade. No one's themselves today. It's an escape from the normalcy.
And again, I think it's been hurt by the fact that the internet is now real life. There are
real life repercussions of changing everything. Where 10 years ago, YouTube did a thing where
the entire front page, everything linked to Rick Roll. YouTube could never do that now because
it would hurt too many people's careers. That's true. It would be a huge fucking deal. Now,
April Fools is always like some lame shit you have to actually go find.
Yeah. It's like, oh, I already know what it's going to be. I know it's April Fools' day. You
can't fucking trick me today, you know? But I miss when sites would do, I mean,
fucking 4chan still does, like, they'll have a song looping in the background of the entire
fucking website. And you know what, that is annoying, but 4chan is not really essential
for anybody. So that's more okay. It doesn't really interfere with your day.
Anyway, Rick and Morty. Yeah, I feel like that's an appropriate interlude to discuss
Rick and Morty anyway. Well, I don't know how long we plan for these podcasts to be,
but we can go on as long as we need to. There's a pilot episode and we don't know when we're
going to be covering the next one, when it will be out. No one knows when the next episode is
going to be out soon. And I mean, this episode, like the biggest question on everyone's minds is
because it was like season two ended on a huge fucking cliffhanger. How are they going to start
off? You know, they have to open season three with something kind of epic. Yep. And the show
opens up by lampooning this. Of course. It starts off with this joke that they're all in a shoneys,
and oh, who wants to hear about how I escaped from prison? Like, that would be stupid. And like,
it's like, I'll even admit, like, even though I knew I'd heard spoilers for this episode before
I watched it, even though I knew that I still had that reaction of like, oh, you motherfucker.
But then, of course, when it turns out to be a lie, that's like, oh, okay, that's exactly that
April Fool spirit I love. They act like they're fucking you over, and then they give you everything
you want it. And it's so great. Oh, and the actual shit that Rick does, it turns out it was all part
of his fucking plan. And they do this whole rigmarole with all this new technology of like,
mind transferring we haven't seen before. Oh, it's the best. Yeah. So this episode continues
the sort of trend that I saw happening through season two, and especially with the ending of
season two of I feel like Rick and Morty owes a lot to Game of Thrones. Yeah. Like, I think the
way that this show uses like brutal violence is sort of like, because we are now in a, in a culture
where that's like a normal thing on mainstream television, like, like insanely violent scenes
has HBO become mainstream television, or is it just the popularity of the show? Like, yeah,
because HBO now is way more easily accessible. Well, it used to. Torrents are a thing. Well,
yeah, but it, you know, Game of Thrones is the most torrented show of all time. I believe it.
I believe it had like millions and millions of torrents. Yeah, okay. So everyone's everyone's
seen it. Everyone has seen Game of Thrones. It's it's that's the culture where it now is like
that this kind of hyper violent, like crazy dark shit is what gets talked about. And I mean,
the ending of season two was clearly a Game of Thrones parody. It was a red wedding. Yeah, it was
the red wedding like redone in Rick and Morty. And I just love the way the show. It totally like
gets into the headspace of like, who is the audience of Rick and Morty? Like,
what kind of cultural stuff are we? Because like, a lot of the show is in reference to
like, cultural touchstones. Yeah, like, there's lots of movie parodies. There's like a whole
episode on the purge planet. It's like, right, which was great. What would it be like if there's a
planet that does the purge and the way that Riley and matter of fact, we address like what a real
purge planet would be. I mean, in their lampooning way, it's great. It's wonderful. And so when they
do like a red wedding scene, like they know exactly how the audience is going to feel at every step
of the way. And the moment that like really got I mean, that episode is fucking amazing. A lot of
shit happens in that episode. But the moment that got me the most was right after bird person gets
shot. Yeah, then Rick screams like bird person, no. And literally he said that while I was saying,
no bird person. It's like one to one, me and Rick saying it at the same time. And I'm like,
because they knew that that's what the audience was going to do. They knew you were going to yell,
no bird person, you know, and so they they matched it. And it's like, they totally get
the ebb and flow of your feelings and stuff. And like, it's well written, man. It's well written.
There's so many like, there's so much stuff that they've allowed themselves. This show does what
like my little pony fucked up with its background characters. Oh, yeah, you're right. It makes you
care about them in a real way. I mean, in all fairness, it was one episode that was garbage that
pretty much ruined that whole thing. But what I mean is that like in in in MLP fandom, for anybody
who doesn't know, because we're a few years out from it, and people probably don't know what we're
talking about anymore. The fan base of my little pony, like really ran with every random fucking
background character that was in the show. They all had like fan made backstories and like people
had all these ideas about them. And like they each one was a popular character in their own
right, because they would show up in the background all the time or have like one line here and there
and stuff like that. And so all those background characters became kind of famous. And eventually,
the show writers became aware of this. And they kind of tried to do something with it. And it was
terrible. Granted, some people don't agree. Some you know, there were some decent things like the
way they handled the fact that Bon Bon had like two cannon or like there was a fandom name and a
real name. They made her a secret agent with an alias. Like that's one clever way to handle that
kind of a thing. But there were many things that were bad and shitty episode itself. The episode
was garbage. So yeah, yeah, like and just the general way that they tried to like they're trying
to pander to the audience. But it's like they're trying to give us what we are saying we want.
Yeah, Rick and Morty knows what we want and gives it to us in ways we don't expect, such as it's
got all these background characters who people just naturally started caring about people love
bird person. People love, you know, all these random weird wacky characters. That fucking
half dude whose name I forget. Squanch. Squanch, yeah. Squanchie. And instead of like giving us
some fan service episode, or it's like, Hey, it's all your favorite background characters.
They murder all of them. Yeah. And it makes it even more memorable, because it's like instead of
just like, Oh, here's bird person again, we know you love bird person. Here you go. Have as much
bird person as you want. No, like the second or third episode he's in, he gets fucking shot and
dies. Yeah. And it's like, because they know you actually do care about him in this weird way,
this guy with like two lines, but he's such an endearing character that when he gets shot, you're
like, Oh, no, not bird person. But it's, it's also that like, they can get away with that because
it doesn't it never feels too dark because of the fact that they're all just dumb background
characters. Yeah. Like a guy, you see a guy get shot whose name is like Schmoopy Doop or something,
or Poopy Butthole. Poopy, Mr. Poopy Butthole. Yeah. You know, like, like it's the scene is like
drawing out like this pathos and everything. And it's everyone's crying, it's like that. Like,
on some level, it hits you emotionally, because you kind of care about Poopy Butthole. Not to
mention, but it's not like they murdered your favorite character who you really care about.
And a lot of that has to do with the way that Rick himself is such like an anti social,
you know, whatever, misanthrope. And I'm using that word right, the one who hates people. Yeah.
Yeah, I was wondering if it's the one who hates men. I'm not saying that. It's the other thing.
But like the way he doesn't give a fuck about anyway, about anyone and the way that he does
react when bird person dies, and like continually has this relationship with him. And he talks about
like, Yeah, we fought in the war. It's like, we're buddies to actually have that character care about
someone makes us care about them to and makes their death all the more impactful. So from that
perspective, too, it really works. I definitely think that like, because Rick is presented as
someone who's like, so yeah, over the edge and like doesn't care about anything. Yeah,
anytime he emotes, right, it feels serious. Like it's that much more impactful. Like when he
like the fucking self an episode. Yeah, after dating that girl and having been like cut off. Oh my
God. And I do Jesse freaks out about that episode. That one's devastating. Oh my God. Just because
it's like Legion. No, whatever. You just like, oh my God, it's like, yeah, he does like that.
My favorite thing about Rick and Morty and I know Tom, Tommy Oliver had a problem with this
aspect of the show. He thought it was ruining Rick showed so much emotion. That's my favorite thing
about the show is that there is this like, like at heart, he is highly empathetic. And the reason
that he the reason he acts this way isn't because he hates people. It's because I think he cares too
much about people. And he knows that like, the universe is an unchanging, unfeeling, you know,
like monstrous place, like caring about people is just going to lead to pain. So don't do it.
It's like he's a man who's gained the knowledge of a God and is, you know, aware of how insignificant
everything is. It's really fucked him up. Yeah, he's like, you know, how can I bring myself to
give a shit about people when I know what's going like that they are nothing, you know, but then
like he can't help himself because he is still human. That's true. So like sometimes he has,
he can't help but care, you know, and like if he really falls in love, like he did in that episode
and loses out and and I mean, it's not even just that it's also he's drunk and yeah, it's too
emotional, you know, and like he's fucked up on drugs and shit. And it's like, yeah, that's the
moment when you're like he could have easily killed himself that if he hadn't passed out. He really
tried he really put his best effort really like did it and just failed. The fact that he didn't
push out he went all the way and really tried to do it. I mean, it's been said, but that's such
intense moment, great scene. And yeah, and then when we see like with this at the end of season
two, when he's like, what are you in for? And he says everything. It's like, you know, I've
like he finally realizes, you know, I can't bring myself to say I don't care about my family.
But of course, of course, all this, I mean, you know, we were saying this to but all this,
you can you can compare to is in parallel to how like him turning himself in at the end of the
second of season, you know, to supposedly save his family and like, you know, give them back
the life that he stoned from it was actually I mean, and it's kind of ambiguous, but it seems
like it was actually all part of a plan to depose Jerry as patriarch of the family and become like
the ruler and get more to exclusively because he's so evil and fucked up. That's the thing about it
is that with Rick, you can never say for sure. And I mean, I personally think that like,
I think that he is ultimately empathetic because we've seen him do it in moment like
when he tried to kill himself, no one was there to witness that there was no benefit to that.
When he goes back, like the first moment we really see Rick act that way is when Morty gets like
almost raped by the Jellybean King. And Rick, when he realizes that Morty is upset, he like changes
gears and like tries to comfort him and like leads him and then he shoots the Jellybean King just
out of anger. I love the fact that he murdered that guy because he deserved it. He didn't push
the out. Well, that's that's one of my favorite scenes in the show because the fact that it's like
it shows that Rick like on even though he doesn't care in general, like he saw something happening
right in front of him to someone he does kind of care about. And so he was like, well, I can do
something about this. I can kill that guy. You know, that kind of speaks to a fundamental like
psychological, you know, facet that humans have where we're much more empathetic about things
that are directly in front of us as opposed to like news that there are billions of people dying
elsewhere. Well, because it just when you hear how big it is, you're like, I can't do anything about
that. But even it's interesting. It's just like, oh, well, I literally know I can do something about
this because it's right in front of me. It's interesting to me that even a character like
Rick, who is the smartest man in the universe, even he like retains that perspective, that very
human perspective. And that's the thing, like when you meet first meet the Council of Rick's and
everything, it's established that he's like right on the edge between like being the evil.
If you're slightly more evil than him, you're an evil fucking master villain. But if you're
slightly more righteous than him, then you're like a little bit like he's right in the perfect
interstice to be the most interesting Rick, which is why we follow this right. Right. Right. It's
really he's a who's a real reflection of humanity, like a certain perspective of what a human being
is. You can see in that. It's real cool. So I this episode accomplishes a lot of things that I
wanted to have like, okay, after season one of Rick and Morty, like my biggest thing that I wanted
to happen in season two was for Beth and Jerry to split up. Right. Like because the way I saw it was
like season one was constantly suggesting it. And like this is a show that has plot progression.
So like, let's do it. Let's do away with this nuclear family dynamic. Like, you know, because
the first season was constantly bouncing between like home life and crazy sci fi A plot. Yeah.
And like, it did sometimes feel a little restricted by the fact that it had to do like normal shit.
The cutaways to the Jerry and Beth bits are almost every time the worst part of the episode.
Yeah, even when they're good, like even when they're good, the Gazorp is or stuff with them is
actually great and is probably the best part of that particular episode. But not every time they
are, you know, in general, they're the weakest part or the the the TV episode. Did I say Gazorp
is or I meant to say Mr. Meeseeks. I meant to say Mr. Meeseeks. Oh, yeah, that's fantastic. Yeah.
Yeah. Like, so it's just that it felt very explored in season one. So I was really hoping
that season two would like start off with them getting divorced. Yeah, it didn't happen. Instead,
season two went even heavier on the divorce element. And like, again, it had ultimately the
episodes were good. But I was just like, I get it. Yeah, like, I want these two split up because
this is going to go on forever. And like, I feel like we've done everything we can with it. Yeah.
So the fact that this episode, a big part of it is getting Jerry out of the picture. And like,
the way that Rick talks to Morty at the end is obviously meta. He's like describing to Rick or
to Morty, like, we have done this as writers, we are writing Jerry out of the show to get rid of
him because we're sick of him. I still though, in the context of a character saying these things
to Morty, it's just so so wonderfully black and dark and evil. It's great. It's fantastic. It's
like your father was your father crossed your father and the entire galactic government crossed
me. So I got rid of them both. That's what a fucking badass. That's so sick. God, I love Rick.
What I love about this show is it's never content to just be status quo. Like,
like, um, I mean, that's what most most episodic comedy shows like this, you know,
they have to have this baseline thing they can always return to this sense of normalcy that's
kind of in the background. And it can be hard to change that and break away from it. And like,
I was really scared that after season two, like, are we always going to have this Beth Jerry thing
going on? Like this is getting tiring, you know, and they did some like, like episode two of season
two where they had Jerry in the daycare was fucking genius. Yeah, that's a great one. That's a great
way to do a Jerry B plot. But like, um, you know, Jerry's a he can't develop as a character because
it would defeat the point. That's right. He's a character who's like inherently static. And
he's boring now. So let's get rid of them. And they did, they cut him out. And I'm like, I fully
expect him to not show up throughout season three. Yeah, I think we'll a little undercut what they're
going for here if he just was back. Exactly. And, uh, and then they're also doing away with the
Rick Federation thing, because obviously that's limiting in a way that like it always puts Rick,
like there's there's a definitive opposition he has. Yeah, that's always around. And it's like,
we've explored a lot of it. And I mean, it's not that they couldn't have done more with it,
but like having it there means like there's certain rules we've established like Rick can't do this
because the council will intervene. There's certain things that like we've made it. So
if, if this or this happens, we have to involve these characters. And so I see the writers going,
all right, that's too limiting. We want to do crazy or shit. We want to make it so Rick can do
those things. It's very exciting that they're changing things on such a level. That's really
is a good sign. So now we've taken out like the entire power structure of the universe.
Yeah, the galactic government and the rest of the things. Yeah, right. Like from here,
the show can go anywhere. And there's nothing that's, there's no like system that was in place
that's going to hold it back from doing my only kind of fear was that they really had established,
like those were, as you were saying, like they were the highest level authorities that existed.
And it's a little hard to imagine like what could easily replace those. It's going to take
some creativity. So I highly anticipate what you say. I wouldn't be surprised if we got like,
you know, Rick forming a new government himself or something. Well, there's no Rick would be.
I mean, he might do that just to like deal with the problem and then divorce himself from it because
he can't be involved in bureaucracy. Not at all. But like, yeah, just like he did with the with
the devil shop. Maybe it just turns the fucking whole world completely anarchic or the whole
universe goes to anarchy or something, you know, like, you know, that's maybe this whole season
is just like batshit insanity all the time. The only reason I think they won't go that way is
because that is a little bit harder to write for than I expect them to go for. Yeah. I mean,
there is a bit of a formula here that I think they generally want to stick to.
Yeah, I'm just really curious where we're going to go with with no Jerry and no, no Rick council,
which like, you know, it's it's almost sad because like the Rick council is such a cool
I know I loved it that I could have watched it forever. It's such that at the same time. Yeah,
it's really ballsy to just kill like to take this great idea and say we've done all we want to do
with it. Let's just like make sure you know as a viewer that it's gone. You know, they really
hammered in those points. And I just love I mean, this is just a compliment of the entire show.
How logically consistent everything is like with Rick having an interdimensional portal gun,
of course, there would something like the Rick thing would develop and the way it impacts his
character. Because he has the portal gun, he developed this, you know, lack of care about
anyone and anything in his life because there's literally infinite copies of him. It doesn't
matter what he does at any point. And these ricks are going to form the Federation to live their
like own outside existence outside any kind of like galactic government that existed. It's just
and and everything's just so consistent and wonderful. And it's just why the show is so good.
And continues one of my favorite things about Rick and Morty is how breakneck it is. Yeah,
like, there's the scene where the the Rick Council breaks into the alien thing and just
Rick himself gets shot in the face immediately. Yeah, like our Rick, we see get fucking shot
in the face. And it's like, whoa, you know, but you also kind of know that he just left. So it's
just like, you're barely able to keep up with the things that are happening. It's like, people are
getting shot, people are taking a shit. It's a wild ride, you know. Yeah, take a shit. That was
that's a great recurring thing. I think he's using that as like his I need to leave this room
now and go to other stuff. I got to take a shit. And it's just because no one would question anyone's
saying that. And it's the the great way they use the dialogue and such a snappy pace, like he walks
into the room and is like, whoa, you can't be in here. This is the room where if you press a couple
buttons and knobs, it like teleports the entire Citadel. He's like, well, he probably shouldn't
have designed it that way. Beep, beep, explosion. Yeah, plot moving along and break that immediately.
Like the very first thing you see is it's just a shot of the Citadel reappearing inside what
is clearly the world government. It's just like, yeah, everything's done now. Like what in that one
shot, we totally understand that both of those governments are just gone. You know, it's just
like, well, moving along. And they spoon feed you a little bit, but they're just like, you know,
oh, no, we teleported here. Everything bad's happening. I that's great. It's it's really good.
Yeah. Every all the ricks getting shot, the brutal and more ricks and Morty's getting killed left
and right. And again, it's all like a pre-established background character. So like you care a little
like rest in peace, hammer Morty, rest in peace, hammer Morty is just some weird background like
gag like what if one of the Morty's is a hammer. And this one, we see the Rick wielding the hammer
Morty like beating people to death with it. And then it gets shot like so it serves it's one other
purpose it could have. It has two purposes, one to be a random background gag to die used as a
Shekhov's gun and then to just get killed. It's like perfect. That's all we needed from him.
He never has to show up again. Doesn't have to be like once per season. Oh, here's hammer Morty.
Yeah, like don't don't you don't want to be pulling like a an adventure time style party
God and like try to make this ridiculous character that should show up exactly once
into like a regular character. Yeah, that's the mistake. And they don't do that here. Thank God.
How about that Sejuan sauce? How about well, how about the whole memory sequence where I mean,
I had to watch this twice to really understand what was going on. So he does this whole thing
where so he's been captured and they're trying to extract memories from it. And he's got this like
so Rick immediately figures this out and the way he plays them and you know, they do the fake out
where like they're exploring his memories. They're like, Hey, you better go to the place
where you invented your interdimensional travel gun. And so that he thinks they think that he's
leading them to that. And we see in the midst of that we see like his wife the mysteriously absent
wife mother of of Beth character that everyone's been wondering about. And then like it plays you
the whole way. And then when you get to the end, both the like the way that he came up with the
portal, the interdimensional portal gun and the mother character were both fictional. They were
not real. So they got played and we got played at the same time. I mean, I was suspicious of that
memory because it seemed way too straight like straightforward, right? Yeah, wife and daughter
died. And also why would Beth have gotten blown up? Well, interdimensional, you know, went to
another one, I guess. Yeah. I mean, that was as soon as that happened, I was like, Well, what the
hell? That's not the real story because Beth can't be dead unless he was going to rebuild her. But
like, I mean, we've already seen Rick abandon one Beth and just get a new one. That's true. You
know, we've seen that in the show. Yeah. Incidentally, they we get to see the new the world, the Cronenberg
world that was abandoned, which was great. I love that. The Cronenberg world comes back. And once
again, we bring back the Cronenberg world. It's a great reference to an old joke. Immediately all
three of them get frozen, probably dead. So we don't have to go back there again. Yeah, I am
content to know like, it's good to know what these characters are doing because they were these were
the characters that we grew up with through all season one. And yeah, to see to just see them,
they're doing fine. They're doing fine. Don't worry about it. It makes me happy now. I bet they'll
be okay. I know that actually freezing did like totally will actually kill you, but it's magic
space gun. So in the first episode, someone got frozen and immediately fell and broke to pieces.
They didn't fall and break to pieces. So maybe they're okay. Yeah, by the way, can we talk about
how how great and like, so the thing that we're wondering is so Rick's got his plan, but what
are like Morty and Summer going to do? I mean, I personally was wondering like, what agency
can like Morty and Summer do to like get involved in the plot again? And the idea of digging up the
dead Rick and finding his portal gun that gives them an end back into like actually doing something
relevant in the story, just a really good use of these like dead bodies in the background in the
backyard, really, really good stuff. Yeah, the portal got smashed so they can't use it anymore.
Well, but but that was great because you know that it was a great way to give you something to do.
Yeah. Yeah. I think I really want us to like, I think the number one promise this show made in
season one that hasn't been delivered on is the evil Morty and this, this general idea that I
think our Morty is special, you know, and like Rick says so in that episode as kind of like a
haha, we're buddies kind of thing. Yeah, like as the show goes on, we more and more see how
our Morty is like growing ever more cynical and more understanding like how he literally tried
to kill Rick this episode. He did his best to murder Rick. But like, you know, other Mortys are
presented as like significantly more retarded. Yeah, that's true. Even when we were first introduced
to there being more than Morty, it's like ours is supposedly the good Morty, the one that's like
they tell of in legends, you know. True, true. And in this episode, he himself is like, oh,
my lawyer is a fucking Morty. Like, obviously, this is unfair. So like even though our Morty is
still like an idiot in some ways, like he's definitely smarter than he's supposed to be.
He's developed a lot as a person and character. And while it's mostly made him into like a
cynical asshole, he still cares about summer, though, you know, he's he's become cynical
and the way that he tries to pretend that he doesn't care about Rick anymore, specifically
to protect summer show some real maturity and development. And I'm interested to know if we're
going to get like, if Morty is going to become, you know, more of a hero or if he's going to
keep growing as like a, you know, I kind of want to see him get out of this phase he's in of like
really like depressed kind of, you know, like he's really upset with like, like what's going on
with Rick and everything. Like it's kind of breaking him down to see this nihilist. Well,
ending the episode the way Rick chose to is not good for that for healing his mental faculties
at all. I'm just wondering if we'll see Morty evolve more or if he'll if we'll bring back the
evil Morty finally like that's gotta happen. That's the number one thing we all want to see.
Everything else has been brought back. That's right. The show has never like had a promise
that it didn't deliver on right. So that has to appear at some point, you know,
they've got to be these guys are way too smart to not do that. There must have been a plan for it
in the in the cards. Maybe they just haven't figured out how to work it in yet. You know,
the only danger is once that happens, like I'll still love the show. But I'll I always want
something to look forward to, you know, they got to give me something to establish more
shit. Now, you know, there's definitively this feeling of like putting a lot of stuff behind
us and being like, OK, we're tying up all these loose ends so we can introduce new shit. Yeah.
But there's still some loose ends like, you know, Evil Morty and stuff like that. But yeah, tying
up the whole Beth and Jerry thing is I'm so glad. I was just like, oh, thank you. Yeah. I'm glad they
did it like in kind of a glib way where they were like, look, we know you get it already. Like
they've we've already seen like if they made a whole episode about them like finally getting
divorced, it's like we've been boring as shit. Yeah, like we've already seen that character
arc happen. You know what? This this is not do it flip. And the way they did it quickly was
really good because it actually made me like Jerry. This is probably the most I've ever liked
Jerry. He's just like, you know what? This is it. I'm actually taking action in my life. I'm
saying it's me or him right now, which is entirely appropriate to do because Rick is a fucking monster
more or less. And yeah, just really the right way to do it. Yeah. Um, what else happened in this
episode? Why don't we talk a little bit about the sage one sauce? Because that is relevant.
That's important, I think. And the discussion that's gone on around it is is, you know, we did
a little research. I really feel like it's worth talking about. Nate was telling me that, um,
the Shazwan sauce that they bring up in the episode. It's a meme. Yeah. Yeah. I guess there was like a
campaign because they're making they're remaking Mulan. Are they really? That's why it was a
campaign is that there's a Mulan remake. And so people were saying bring back the Shazwan sauce
for the Mulan remake. Wait, I think you're confused because that's what it said on that
article we were reading. Oh, really? Yeah. Okay. Okay. I mean, I know there is a Mulan remake
coming. So like they were saying, Hey, Rick and Morty talked about how great the Shazwan sauce
was for the fucking 90s. Bring it back. It's perfect timing, I guess. Yeah. And then we read
an article about how it wasn't coming back and that there were people who are arguing that it
was a problematic sauce. Yeah. It was a problematic sauce. It was a cultural appropriation of Chinese
culture because of the Shazwan. Okay. First of all, do you people even fucking understand what
America is? America is a place where you bring stuff and you make it appeal to people and they
buy it because they like it. It is inherent to the foundation of the nation that we combine
things. If you think that it is a wrong thing to do, okay, first of all, there's a couple things
we were thinking about might be the actual argument here. If you think that it is wrong
for other cultures to like eat the foods that you invented in your culture, first of all,
you are 100% wrong. I don't respect your opinion. Go away. If your argument is that it is somehow
like it's like evil to misrepresent a culture by like having something like a McDonald's dipping
sauce that is supposed to be like a quote unquote Chinese sauce, but it like isn't spicy enough.
It isn't like real Chinese. I would say I still that is that is fundamentally flawed because
it is on the individual to realize that, okay, this doesn't actually represent China.
This is a fucking sauce that McDonald's is selling to represent like a movie that we're
making in America. It's not fucking China. So what is the actual arguments that there's something
like harmful about this sauce? I do not fundamentally understand this idea of cultural appropriation
being bad in this context. Do you have anything to add to this point, did you?
It's fucking McDonald's. I know.
I because I really hilarious to me. I don't want to fuck around on this issue. I want to
actually address people's real concerns and respond. I like, I mean, this is this is what it
always is. Yeah, it's always it's it's just that it's so unimportant. Yeah, who the fuck cares?
It's like what what Chinese person is like upset that their culture is being besmirched by a
McDonald's dipping sauce. McDonald's itself is an affront to all life and culture as it is.
Yeah, like the entire existence of McDonald's is an evil skirmish. American American like
burger culture is like poorly represented by McDonald's to begin with. So really,
we should be more insulted than anyone. Exactly. Like it's just literally who gives a fuck. Just
give me the fucking Shezwan sauce. It's fucking hilarious. Stop being a fucking show. Jesus Christ.
And you know what? We might be making a mountain out of a molehill here because we only read like
one or two articles. But the fact that there's any discussion like just the fact that I typed in
Shezwan sauce Rick and Morty and the first the first article was sorry, Rick and Morty fans,
but the problematic Shezwan sauce isn't coming back and I immediately burst out laughing when I
read that headline. Fuck you guys. Fuck you guys. I don't give a shit. I don't know how we got onto
that from a Rick and Morty discussion, but it's funny. They made it about that, dude. The people
out there made it about that. Bring it back. And I love that that like, you know, that Rick
went out of his way to do that in his memory because of course that's something he'd care about.
That's that's what I love. They make that kind of like super obscure cultural reference.
I totally get it. Like they make it out like, oh, haha, it's Rick being silly. But I'm like,
nah, man, like I would pretzel pub chicken sandwich from Wendy's. If I had for some reason, I was
going through like memories of 2009. I'm getting a fucking pretzel pub chicken. There's there's like
some mushroom burger at Wendy's every once in a while that I always am on the lookout for and
is gone most of the time. Cheddar and mushroom. Yeah, like mushroom cheddar burger or something.
I want that. That's see, that's my one dipping sauce right after the pretzel pub chicken,
they brought in that sandwich was also great. Yeah. And then they they kept they kept they
had like a revolving door of sandwiches ever diminishing in quality.
Well, the point of it is that's hilarious. And you know, it's a fucking joke. I don't understand
why anyone would even be mad about in the slightest. So let's let's all suck it up. I mean,
if you're gonna be mad about the sauce, just be mad about the Mulan movie in the first place,
which I know, I think they would be, I'm sure they would be, they'd make the same argument that
no, it's watering down our culture. And you know, the thing about that is almost every time one of
those things happens, the actual culture loves it. Yeah, like most of them are like really happy
that their culture is being represented at all. Do actual Chinese people get really mad that
like Mulan exists and is like, Oh, this is a shitty Americanized version of our culture.
Like they got things to do. Yeah, I don't want to speak for them. But I don't think they would
consider it a big fucking deal. I've seen it all the time. Yeah, like Japan, for instance,
where like, they get really excited to even have reference to Japan in an American film, you know.
And they they appropriate Americans and Japanese films are the most fucking
flanderized, like misrepresented. We're literally all blonde cowboys who scream,
fuck and shoot guns. Yeah, every American character in Japan. So like, you know,
oh, but you know, but racism is prejudice plus power. That's the issue. That's the fundamental
disagreements that we have here. Anyway, anything else about this Rick and Morty episode? Well,
there's that little teaser at the end with bird persons back, you know, that's that's a little
something. I don't know how I feel about that. I know what you mean. It's a little bit disappointing.
Kind of liked that bird person was gone. Like I like bringing back Tammy as like an evil. Yeah,
she's alive and relevant. Yeah, like she I mean, she's kind of like an archvillain now. She's kind
of like the big bad. She's she's the one who initiated all of this. Yep. And, you know, I don't
know what she's working for now that the world government's gone. Shit. And can we just reflect
on I believe the first word we ever heard Tammy say was wasn't she said like, Yeah, I love Bukake
really into Bukake. And she is our main villain. Yeah, love it. Love it. And she's great. She's hot.
She fucks. She fucks. She fucks birds. Yeah, it's a little bit. It's a little bit disappointing
that they're kind of going back on that and just reviving him like that. But I mean, he's evil
now. And I mean, they might make it like, I don't know, it kind of reminds me of like when a chef
died in South Park, and they brought him back as like Darth chef, but just for like a second,
you know, I don't know what they're going to do with this Darth bird person. Yeah, yeah,
like we'll say seeing it and especially like just doing it as like a really tired reference to
Star Wars was like, Oh, I don't know, man. Like, yeah, yeah. But yeah, I don't know. He looks kind
of Borg ish too. Yeah. Yeah. Cyborg, dude. I will say hopefully it'll be good. Yeah, I'm not that
worried. These guys are good writers. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's the thing. There has not been a bad
episode of Rick and Morty. Agreed. There's been a couple. Yeah. Yeah, there were there's a couple
like that night chameleons and raising gizorp is or are probably the two worst episodes. And those
are pretty fun. Agreed. I mean, fucking, I don't know. Chameleons has the the fucking. Yes. Wait,
which one's that again? Yes, the one where Jerry gets trapped in a simulation. Oh, yeah,
recognized that it's a simulation. My man. Just his favorite line. My man. Yeah, like that even
like half of that episode is amazing. Yeah, still the worst episode of the show. It's hard to fault
this hard to fault Rick and Morty. Yep. So yeah, we'll definitely be looking forward to the rest
of season three. No doubt. I got to rewatch season two soon because I still have like the first
three episodes because they were leaked, I watched them like over and over and over again. Yeah. And
the rest of them I watched on TV and never saw again. So like got to get got to get my season
two knowledge up to snuff so I know all the background characters and lore references
where you know that I could look out for when season three gets underway because I'm sure
I'm sure any surviving character we're going to see again. No doubt. That's very much a Dan
Harmon thing. You haven't seen any of community. Have you? I watched all season one. Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I didn't watch beyond that because I got bored. It definitely gets better in season two.
I like season one quite a bit. All right, that's cool. But yeah. I mean, a lot of the arc structure
of Rick and Morty, the meta-ness, all of that is extremely like community. Yeah. Yeah. And obviously
they can do even more on this show because it's fucking you can do literally anything. Yep. And
it's always willing to just... What I love about Rick and Morty is that it's not even that it's
pushing the boundaries, it's that it's just past all of them. Like it represents that we're kind
of in an era where you can literally do anything. Yeah. You can go as violent as you want. You can
say whatever words you want. You can fucking present the most insane concepts you've ever
heard of at the drop of a hat and just keep going. There's no like hand-holding. You know,
and I mean, you could argue that the daily life scenes are like to give retarded audiences like
something to cling to. But even then, I just feel like this show can do literally anything. And
it's like where is the line anymore? Like what's holding it back other than it has to be 22 minutes
long? Yeah. That's like the only real thing. And I really do trust these writers to whatever
they choose to talk about. They will do it in a hilarious, intelligent, and like well-thought-out
way that fits cohesively into the overall structure of the show. So just one of the best fucking shows
I've ever seen and definitely airing right now. Yeah. Absolutely fantastic. Cannot wait for more.
Please give us news about when it's coming out, people. All right, y'all. Join us next time
whenever that is. Whenever it is. Yeah. I mean, maybe we could like try to maybe do some back
episodes while we're, you know, if we want to make this like a weekly show. Yeah. Yeah. Leading
up to whenever the hell the actual show starts. It gets a good 24 weeks if we want to do it also.
Yeah. So yeah, I mean, we don't have to do every episode. We can just do the highlights.
I'm down. All right, everybody. See you then. Goodbye, moon man. Goodbye, moon man.