Hey, hey, hey, hello everybody and welcome back to Rickstie Minutes. I'm the best guy ever and this is Digibro.
Hey, I don't give a fuck, bitch. What's this? Episode 9?
This is episode 9 of season 3. That's right, my dude.
Awesome.
The ABCs of Beth. The ABCs of Beth.
This is our first, man, this is a game changer. And then in some ways, there's a game changer here.
This is probably one of my favorite episodes of the show.
I thought you might go that way. That's interesting. That's interesting.
Because this was probably the biggest core plot development we've gotten in outside of the Council of Rakes and all the sci-fi stuff for the home life.
This is the biggest development we've gotten since the first TV episode.
Absolutely correct. You know what's interesting? I think I'll probably have a slightly different interpretation of that about that same exact idea.
But why don't you tell us about it, did you? What went down?
Well, basically we learn about Beth's past and exactly who she is, which is something I think this show, I don't know if it's ever done a really great job of characterizing Beth.
I couldn't agree more. I couldn't not agree more.
I've always liked her, but she's always been kind of in the background.
The main focus has always been her relationship with Jerry and how that changed her.
But this is the first time we learned exactly what she would be without Jerry or who she was before that.
The thing about Beth is that while Beth was a better person, a more interesting person than Jerry,
her entire character arc depended upon Jerry and Jerry is the worst.
So in what way could we possibly care about Beth considering that's the crux of her character.
There was just no way. There was just no way.
And that was a problem I was feeling throughout this season, which is that with them finally having broken up, Beth has not had much to do.
She's just kind of been on this downward spiral of being weird.
Most of the times we cut to her, she's just being fucking weird.
But then in this episode, we get context into that weirdness that maybe she's just always been a fucking weirdo.
Maybe dating Jerry was just a way of putting on a facade of normalcy in her life.
I feel like they were building to this episode with this season so far. I think that was inevitable.
Yeah, I think if we were to sort of figure out why in terms of her characterization, why this is.
Yeah, I would say it's because Jerry is gone. She no longer feels this need to, I don't know, be a placated mom kind of dude, I guess.
Something like that. I honestly feel like that's giving it maybe a little bit more credit than it deserves.
But nonetheless, I certainly enjoyed what we've seen transposed, fucking happened this episode.
That's the word I meant to say, happened.
Transpire.
That's the word I was looking for. Thank you.
So, yeah, this is an episode about, really, it's a, what was the B plot?
Right, Jerry.
Jerry and the fuck.
Fuck this alien girl.
Which was hilarious.
He was fucking her. He was fucking her. He knew she had two vaginas. That's cool. That's cool.
I like, that was a great subplot, but obviously the less relevant half of the episode.
Of course.
So, basically, we learn this interesting back and forth that Rick was, in many ways, a terrible father.
But also because he, like, I guess from a young age, he had already corrupted Beth to be just as bad.
Or she just naturally is, she's pretty, she, as he put it, you were a scary fucking kid.
And everything she ever wanted from him was stuff to make people like her.
But it's very apparent that the reason she had those issues was, like, out of abandonment issues over her father.
But, like, to this extreme degree that is clearly, like, something's wrong with her.
No doubt. No doubt.
You know?
Like, it's not just the daddy issues.
Those are, like, just the catalyst for releasing what is already psychopathy.
Yeah, it kind of seems that way.
Though I kind of want to give her a break on that a little bit, because I really do feel like, I don't know,
I really do want to attach it to, oh, okay, you know what, I don't want to give her that much of a break,
but I really want to come down on Rick for just being clearly the worst.
Because all the things that he, when he goes through, they go through, like, this, not montage,
but he just pulls out from this toolbox all the things he had made for, all these, like, crazy, goofy devices that, like, a child might want.
And then they get, like, darker, just, like, a sentient switchblade.
Like, okay, that's kind of weird, why would you want that?
But, um, like, those are things I could really see most kids asking for,
but the thing is, parents know better than to give their children them.
And they know, no, that's when you have to be a parent to tell them no.
And, like, I almost want to blame it fucking all on Rick.
I don't really know how responsible that is.
You have to say it's all his fault, because he's the fucking parent.
She was a kid.
Yeah, yeah.
Like, and obviously he was just placating her because, like, I can easily imagine that Rick, in the brief moments he was around his daughter,
she would ask him for something and he would churn it out in a couple of seconds, hand it to her and fuck off.
Right.
And be like, this is enough, you know?
Which is why he creates an entire other universe for her, which she grows up to believe is, like, was just in her imagination.
Yeah, that was good.
He creates a whole world for her to enjoy.
And, like, it's really, I really love the scene of Rick, like, going through this world and, like, explaining about how, like, carefully he constructed it to be perfect for her.
That was one of the best things in the episode.
I loved it.
Yeah, that it's just such a weird, like, obviously he's at fault here.
Obviously this is all a bad idea and Beth is right, but he really did try his hardest.
Like, he did the best that Rick could as a broken, terrible man to make a perfect place for his daughter.
But just the attention to detail, I mean, like, that is something that I absolutely would have noticed that, like, well, okay, dude, so, okay, you made the grounds squishy great,
but there's a river right there, she could easily drown.
But no, it's fucking breathable water, it's not a problem.
He thought of all, like, the reasonable things.
And the only problem is that, you know, like, a kid lived there for a million years and fucked the whole place up.
So, well, the biggest problem is that the entire conceit is wrong.
Well, you know, it's no way to deal with your children problems.
It's like if somebody, like, didn't, wait, I'm trying to think of a good analogy here.
Like, if you wanted to build a better toilet and instead you built, like, the greatest sink in the universe,
like, it doesn't help the problem that you need to shit, you know?
Yeah, I suppose.
That's kind of what he's done here, is, like, the problem is that she needs her dad,
not that she needs this, it doesn't matter how perfect you made it,
it doesn't matter that you were the most considerate person in the world about how you designed this place.
It was the wrong thing to make in the first place.
Very true, very true.
And that's sort of the argument between them, and I thought that was really great.
Yeah, Rick, Rick should take some more responsibility, I think.
But on the other hand, so basically all their grievances are like from when she was a kid,
these days she's a pretty together person, for the most part, until she has some of these moments later on,
where she really, she lets the facade fall away and she embraces her monster mode, which I enjoyed.
I mean, I think that's probably the real reason she's been with Jerry all this time,
because now that we're looking at it from this lens of, because we've seen that in the alternate universe,
where Beth and Jerry weren't together, they both become way more successful,
but they also go insane and go down like a crazy rabbit hole of depravity and end up together anyways.
In this episode, we get the sense that if Beth had never had Jerry around, would she ever have gotten anyone?
It's the only reason she ever got someone to be around her, because he was so weak-willed
that he could put up with the fact that she's an insane person.
Here's this woman who's like a psycho bitch, and who would possibly want to be with her other than the weakest man in the world,
and there's a reason they were together for so long.
She's afraid to have to be by herself, because we see now what happens.
If she doesn't have Jerry, she ain't exactly getting out there in the dating pool and making new friends.
She's just being a fucking insane person in her house, building statues out of hoops and shit.
And of course, there's just the practical fact that she got knocked up, and then had some kids,
and that's going to fucking weigh you down.
Yeah, that too.
I was just before we recorded this, I was watching a video by a guy called The Matching Ties Network
called Harman and Jerry and Rick.
He was basically creating the idea that Dan Harman writes a ton of himself into Rick and Jerry,
and apparently in between seasons two and three of Rick and Morty,
he married his longtime girlfriend and got divorced in the span of about three months,
and up until the start of season three, the way Beth and Jerry's marriage was always portrayed
was that they weren't just staying together for the kids.
There was other reasons. There was this deeper connection between them.
There was some destiny shit going on, a little bit.
But then you start season three and they immediately get divorced,
and so I have to wonder if this is also Dan Harman exploring his own divorce in this season.
What an excellent point, and I think it probably is.
It's interesting to see that change in mindset that maybe by the end of the season
we'll find out that they do need to get back together, who knows.
Maybe they'll just keep exploring being separate for seasons on end
and we'll just have this broken home that we're following,
which honestly is kind of a great idea.
How many sitcoms have we seen about a dysfunctional but still together family?
What if we just have a show about a family that's broken up
and everyone's slowly getting jaded to crazy space adventures?
We're at a point now where Jerry is dating an alien of his own accord.
Was it just me or was that...
I mean, I know that the Earth had been enslaved by aliens,
but they're basically all gone and it's just human society again
and we're pretty much ignoring that.
But there's just an alien and nobody gives a fuck.
This is just common now. This is the life everyone's involved with.
Did they go... When they ate with the alien, was that the same diner
that we went to not only in the last episode
when Rick had to kill the alien that wanted to die,
but also the start of the season when they were just in a family diner?
Is it the same diner?
No, no, no, no. That was a different one.
That was Chonies, Chauncees. That was definitely a different one.
This place was, what do they say, Mexican something?
No, this is like a Japanese place.
No, okay, that was different because that place was like...
It was like a taco place.
Right, there was sushi here.
Yeah, that's right.
You should know that. You're the biggest.
There's a lot of restaurants in the fucking...
in Rick and Morty now that I think about it.
It's true.
And you hate restaurant scenes. God damn it, this is the worst.
Zero out of ten.
This is exposition, yes.
But no, it's great.
Jerry's subplot with the alien chick was fucking hilarious.
It was pretty good.
It's just such a Jerry...
Well, what made it work for me was the fact that Jerry has telekinetic powers as a result of this.
Which is fucking...
That moment when they walk into his house and he just like...
Not only is everything nice, but he has telekinetic powers.
I was just like, whoa, hold on.
I love that. I loved how they rolled with it.
But I must admit, I thought there would be like...
The other shoe would drop on that somewhere in the episode
and just was never mentioned again.
Never came up again.
But I don't know, it wasn't that big a deal, but I did expect something.
Whatever, who cares.
That was great though.
Why didn't he use it to help on the hunt?
Why didn't he fight with psychic powers?
Maybe he wasn't getting enough pus.
He didn't have enough juice left, he wasn't getting enough.
They were hunting too much.
After they feast, they hunt, and then they hunt to celebrate their hunts.
This episode had so many fucking zingers in it, man.
I don't even know where to begin, but there's a few that I can remember.
I'd have to watch the episode again and write them all down to get all the great ones.
But two of my favorites, at the beginning of the episode,
when Beth says something about the generation gap,
and Summer's like, our generation gets traumatized for breakfast.
Yeah, that's the one.
That was great. That was a dope summer line.
Yeah, which is totally accurate.
And then later on when they're chastising Jerry about how they say,
they're like, we chose mom, we made that very clear to you,
both at the breakup and in your weird Facebook post,
the comments of your long Facebook post or whatever.
That was great.
Because it creates, you can imagine a whole other scene
that's left out of the show of them going on Facebook
and seeing Jerry having typed this wall of text about the breakup
that no one cares about and them leaving angry responses.
This kind of shit happens in my family.
Of course.
Someone gets upset and goes on a fucking Facebook tirade
and everyone else blasts them in the comments of it.
I've been through that particular drama, so it's too perfect.
Blinds are like that, man.
I know what you mean.
The thing that was the funniest to me in this episode
was just how gross everyone was willing to be all the time.
So first of all, there was just like the Jerry scene
where he wants them to know real explicitly
how much he's fucking this bitch.
Is that relatable, did you?
You gotta let everybody know how much you're fucking.
Are you getting anything from that?
Okay, anyway.
But later on, the running joke of the dude in Fruppy Land,
just insisting upon explaining to everyone in extreme detail
and displaying for them the fucking ritual of him impregnating
these fucking monsters and devouring the bodies.
His insistence upon explaining this to everyone
every fucking time, I laugh my ass off.
That was the funniest thing this episode.
What made that work for me so much is that like,
because Rick and Beth do that thing where they rapidly extrapolate
that that's what's going on here.
They immediately figure that out.
Oh, yeah, of course.
While I thought that line was funny because of just what they're saying,
I was a little bit annoyed by the overly meta.
When this show does that thing where everyone's just too far ahead of the story,
and I'm like, okay, they don't have to all be maximum nihilism 24-7.
But then to then be explained over and over again made it way funnier.
Oh, it was fucking great.
It was fucking great.
And he does it.
He fucks it right in front of them.
It has a baby and he eats it in front of them.
Even Rick is like, dude, please stop.
No one, like, this is too much.
I don't want to think about this happening.
Oh, it was great.
God, I fucking love it.
I love that he just books right after that.
He's like, all right, I'm done.
That was fantastic.
Oh, man.
It was great that Rick, you know, again, like, he's a god.
He just like, yeah, okay, I don't want to be here anymore,
so I'm leaving and then he does.
And then Beth has to go and, you know, bumble fuck around
and try to deal with the situation on her own.
Yeah, it was great, man.
It was great.
Should we talk more about the Fruityland plots,
the whole, the things that went on there?
Yeah, it's an interesting, I love the,
I guess it all really culminates in the moment
where Beth realizes that she is her father.
Yep.
Because she, just as Rick will not take responsibility
for the fact that he made Beth this person,
she will not take responsibility for the fact
that she made Tommy this person.
True.
By pushing him into the honey.
And all, all he wants is an apology
and she would rather murder everyone
than give that apology.
And yeah, and then she like realizes,
she kind of has an awakening moment of like,
I need to stop lying to myself
and admit I'm a fucking monster.
Yeah.
Just like Rick, you know.
Especially that coming right up to the scene
where she's like, no, I'm going to go prove
that I'm not a bad person, that I am a good person.
And it's like, you just found out,
objectively not a good person.
You're kind of a fucking monster.
It's great.
And I mean, they still rescue the dad
because they're like, you know,
we can do some good here.
Like does the world really want Tommy back in it
at this point, considering what he is?
No.
They should have just left him there.
Like fuck it.
Then again, would it be?
They did just leave him there.
They cloned him.
I think she murdered him also.
I mean, the guy's got to be dead, right?
That was implied.
I assume she killed the real Tommy
and they cloned him into a new one.
Of course.
Yeah, that's fine.
That plot line's resolved.
It's all good.
Yeah.
I also liked the, this was a very subtle detail
that I thought was really cool about Fruity Land.
So like at one point, Rick's like talking about
like how, you know, how hard he worked to making,
how hard he worked to like make Fruity Land and stuff.
And like, you know, they use the magic chalk,
like chalk zone to like, you know, draw a thing
and then walk in and make magic doorways and shit.
I thought it was really cool that this is just one
of those subtle details.
Like at one point he's just like,
ah, I collapsed a whole quasar to fucking
and Beth just cuts him out like,
dad, I don't give a fuck about how you made it.
Like just take me there.
I don't give a fuck.
And he's just like, ah, fucking bitch.
And then like later on in the episode,
he's like, okay, you know, we left that guy's dead.
Time to like pull the plug.
And then he like, he makes a gesture as if he's going to like
snap the little piece of chalk thing that he's got.
But then Beth stops him and I was just like,
hey, that's cool.
Like, so that's, so basically we're learning that
it's a pocket dimension maybe contained within that thing.
Or that's like some power source to it or something.
I don't know.
I just thought that was a cool little detail.
I liked it.
Always in with the details in this show, man.
Yep.
Lots of great, lots of great stuff.
I love all the inventions that he gave Beth
and how long they let that scene go on.
Yeah, yeah.
Like he just lists this shit for so long
and it was like each thing's funnier than the last.
It's one of those, it's one of those Andy Kaufman jokes
where they just keep going and the joke is that
it just keeps going and you need to get comfortable
with the fact that this is not stopping anytime soon.
And I think it, I think it worked really well
because I felt like it kept giving slightly different angles on it.
Like it wasn't just Beth as a psycho.
It's like each item you can imagine it's particular use.
This was a great way to like in, like in my mind,
I'm crafting a flashback that is not actually being shown,
you know, and there's the stage play flashback,
which is also fucking hilarious.
They're just like literally describing what happened.
Like in no uncertain terms.
I think Rick's just criticizing the screenwriting.
Yeah, that was great.
That was great.
I also really liked when Beth just walks back in,
you know, after covered in blood after killing everybody there
and she walks in on Rick, you know, tune his guitar, do do, do do do
and then later on he's like they do a musical montage
to the do do in my butt.
Oh my God.
The musical, that was the moment where the episode was like,
this is now one of my favorite of the show,
because we just have like, we have this really emotional dialogue
and then the emotional montage is immediately do do in my butthole
and I was like, done.
10 out of 10.
Every daughter's a butthole in her dad's butt in one point in his life.
Yeah, it was good shit, man.
It was good shit.
That's kind of humor I can really resonate with.
Yeah, that's my kind of humor, right?
That's what I come to Rick and Morty for.
Everyone's always like, anyone who criticizes this show
and they're like, ooh, it's just a guy burping
and talking about nihilism, no.
What makes Rick and Morty funny is the do do in my butt song.
Agreed.
That is like, the fact that they put that as the cherry on top
of the inner depth, you know,
that we get this beautiful episode with all this story
like fucking deep shit about the relationship of these characters
and the big climactic sign off of it is the do do in my butthole song.
That's why I love this show.
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
Which I barely heard the lyrics of because I was laughing over the entire time.
I went back and listened to it again.
Yeah, it was fucking great.
So let's talk about the ending.
So after that scene that, you know,
Beth's come to a realization that she's a fucking monster
and Rick's just like, she's like, what should I do, Dad?
You know, got no more excuses to hang around here.
There's nothing to hold me here.
What the fuck do I do?
And Rick's like, fucking peace out, dog.
Peace out.
I will make you a clone.
It will do everything that you did in your life.
You got no attachments.
You can be completely free.
No moral ramifications of any kind.
What are you going to do?
And then they don't answer it, but it's obvious.
It's obvious that she's gone.
That's okay.
That was, yeah, it was a weird scene that they didn't show that because like,
it definitely feels super stilted when she comes back into the room.
She's acting like a clone.
Yep.
Like she's acting.
She's acting a lot like the summer and Morty bots from episode two.
Exactly.
So I was thinking, okay, it's a clone.
We're about to get the reveal, but then there is no reveal.
And I don't know if that's just to trick us for now.
Like, or just to leave the question unanswered.
Like we won't really know unless we see Beth off somewhere else later.
You know.
I think that that is a almost guaranteed to happen.
I just, okay, just like narratively as, as the narrative genius that I am,
I don't see how they could get away with putting that in this episode
and then not having to pay off like at some point in the future.
I expected it to be at the end of the episode and like the after credits thing.
That's the thing.
If that's what they did this, I don't think there's ever been a time in this show
where they set up something like that, that didn't pay off within the episode.
You know, I guess you could argue that.
Evil Morty thing, but like that was a, that was like a setup for something later.
So yeah, we all knew that.
That was like, that was like an ending like clincher thing though.
And like we never knew like what this, like what was going to be the relevance of that
until much later.
This one, it just feels like, like the way that they ended the episode is clearly meant
to suggest, hey, she didn't clone herself, but then you have that or did she in your mind
and like, I don't know, maybe it pays off next episode.
If it doesn't pay off by the end of the season, I'm going to get real skeptical.
But if they suddenly in season like four brought in this other Beth,
it would be a fucking pretty big sledgehammer to the face.
I will say that.
You know, I think it would be like, oh, you motherfuckers, you held off for that long.
You know, my genre savvy-ness just to me, it almost gives me no way to believe
that they are, that she didn't leave.
Knowing the show and knowing how these characters operate, I cannot imagine a world in which
they wrote it that summer or that Beth indeed stayed.
And maybe that's how they're going to fuck guys like me over who think that we know everything
about the show.
Maybe it'll happen because this show, I mean, there's no way that they just go with the
obvious thing on its face.
Like there's that kind of show.
And then there's a more complex show that would do something on top of it.
And then there's like double triple layers on top of that where they could interweave
plots and double back on your expectations and totally surprise you out of nowhere.
And Rick and Morty sometimes transcends to that level.
And the biggest way they could defy all expectations is to indeed have Beth not leave after setting
up that whole scene.
So we're just going to have to find out.
I guess we've got nothing we can do.
Yeah.
We'll see.
And we will not be able to save 100% sure until the show is over.
That's true.
Even then.
Yeah.
Even then it's up for debate.
Well, I guess that's all I have to say about this episode.
The ending gag was hilarious.
It was.
The fact that Rick went and fucked Jerry's girlfriend.
Oh, that was the best part of it.
That was the best part.
And yeah, the meta about like nobody uses answering machines before.
You can keep it, whatever.
Got to chuckle out of me.
But I did have one final point I wanted to make about this episode.
And it was just that.
So you were quite positive about all this Beth development happening.
I for one, as a portion of that.
Okay.
I felt a little bit deflated by this happening.
And it's just because.
Okay.
So in this episode, we have Beth finally realizing things, all these things about Rick and herself
to be fair that we didn't know.
But everything about Rick, we have all known since episode one.
There is nothing new on like the realization of this whole Rick situation.
So to me, it's a little bit of a mixed bag only because this is something that had to happen
inevitably in order to make this character at all interesting, but because it took so long
and it's been so much dead weight basically having this character along doing nothing for so long.
Like it's happening now.
It's like, okay, great.
But it's just like, okay, finally, finally, it's out of the way.
It's like a bowel movement.
You know, it's finally gone.
It's out of the way.
But man, that shit stinks.
And but I'm glad it's beyond this.
I don't know.
I don't want to shed it too much.
It's just, I wish this had happened sometime sooner or that Beth had just been more interesting
leading up to this point in some way.
Yeah.
But she really hadn't been.
Honestly, I think if you went back, she was most interesting in season one.
And definitely least interesting in season three.
So like, I think the problem has really been with this season not finding anything to do with her
because it was so much more interested in exploring Jerry's side of the breakup up until this point
and how the kids were dealing with it and just exploring Rick's being Rick, you know,
or doing weird stuff.
I kind of feel like why wasn't this episode just earlier in the season in a way,
but maybe it would have felt like too many like relationship episodes in a row.
I don't know.
But like it definitely feels like maybe it would be like maybe Beth's character won't
be as bad going back through the season now that we know this about her.
Yeah.
Like you can kind of put together a little bit more why like she's acting this way.
Because I think I think they probably had this in mind from the start of season three.
Like the way she's been acting this season is clearly indicative of this character.
They're painting in this episode.
I don't know how true I would say that is in the other seasons.
Yeah, I'm with you on that.
But like it'd be worth going back for a look.
But like, yeah, I see where you're coming from.
I do think it's unfortunate that it's taken this long for Beth to have a moment where like,
oh man, she might be cool now or I'm a lot more invested in her than I was before, you know.
I certainly feel that having this episode end.
But additionally, I do want to say there's a lot of hype here for Beth going out
and like becoming her own woman and, you know, doing stuff.
But like Beth's not that smart.
I feel like there's a little bit of an exaggerated sense of like how cool things are going to be
with Beth now that she's out there.
I feel like she's just going to go like she's she's no Rick.
She is no Rick.
You know, she's not like a God genius or anything in the other alternate world.
She just became like a fucking famous horse surgeon.
You know, what's been holding her back there?
I don't know.
I mean, Rick has implied that she could have been a super genius.
But I don't know.
I don't know what she's going to do.
I mean, we've already seen Morty and Summer just by proximity to Rick gaining a lot of his like abilities.
You know, like they wouldn't survive very long by themselves, but they do have a lot more skills
than a normal person would.
You're not wrong about that.
Yeah.
So, you know what?
I'll withhold judgment on that.
Maybe they could do something interesting with her.
So, yeah, go to it, writers.
Make her interesting.
And I'll tell you the first thing they got to do is not have her stayed here.
She needs to have left.
Go be an adventurer.
Go do something cool.
That's what I hope is revealed.
And I think it will be this season.
That's all I got.
Alrighty.
That's a fuck, a fuck, a fuck, fuck.
Bye, everybody.