Hello everyone and welcome to a special, I guess a bonus episode here on the Pro Crastinators channel.
Today, me and my airmanos are going to be talking about a little story you might have heard of called The Triflers.
That's right, it's the world famous earth shattering book by our friend Mumkey Jones here.
And we're just going to talk about it. I just read it on the plane from Anime Expo and I finished it.
And I'm bursting with things to say about it and points to make and brilliant bits of rhetoric to expunge for my being.
So that's why I'm here. I don't know what their excuse is for being here.
Oh, Mumkey for book sales. For book sales, of course.
Yeah, I'm just here to sell books. I don't give a shit about you guys.
Jesse just read it last night, right?
Last night, I bought it months ago. I read 10 pages. I got to the part where Don gets locked in the freezer and that's where I stopped.
It's like 10 pages to half way through the book.
That's pretty far. I couldn't pick the book up anymore because I just hate Mumkey so much.
Last night, because Nate had posted about it on Twitter, I'm like, oh god, everyone's still reading that damn book. I better finish it too.
And then it was said that we do a podcast today and I was told that we might get a new member of the procrastinators and I had to put a stop to that.
Because every time we have a guest on the show, he becomes a real procrastinator. That's how I ended up with Mumkey in the first place.
So no more new procrastinators. I had to put a stop to it. I said, god damn it, if it'll stop someone else from being on this podcast, I will read the book tonight.
Well now we're going to start all these rumors. We might as well save who this mystery man was who we wanted to prevent from joining the show.
It was our good friend and horrible collaborator, the mysterious rhinoceros.
He'll never be a real member.
There but for the grace of god. There but for the grace of god goes a new addition to our merry brood.
So I stayed up all night reading the book. I pulled a Mario Quintanilla only instead of teaching I was learning.
We should say that Tom wanted to be here but he's out of town right now so he couldn't.
That's true. In all fairness, he's the one who read it before any of us.
Not before me. What the fuck are you talking about? I read it first.
Oh shit, you're right. I totally forgot because you don't matter.
But Tom's the first real person. He's the first real person who read it.
So we're all up to speed. We've all fucking read this book and we've got the author here.
So let's just dive the fuck in.
I don't know. Should we just talk about our general thoughts on having finished it?
I've certainly got some strong feelings.
Why don't you go ahead since you're like swimming at the fucking...
You were remarkably affected by it it seems on Twitter.
Real quick before you start, I do want to say that since I was a young boy,
my dream of being an author was to like go on book tours and shit.
But now just sitting in my bedroom with three of my friends online,
my stomach is in knots and I feel physically ill.
So maybe I don't have what it takes to go on a book tour with all these fucking people.
Well, that's what Maddox was like during his first book tour as I remember in some interview.
But then he became the God we all know today. So don't worry about it.
It's all part of the growing process.
As long as my fall from grace is 15 years out, I think I'll be fine.
You know what? In all fairness, I should say,
Monkey, is there any sort of preamble you want to give?
Anything we should say before diving into it just since you're the main man?
I mean, I guess I'll just say we're going to go into heavy spoilers probably,
but really that shouldn't bother you too much.
And if you've already read it, then you should especially enjoy the podcast.
And yeah, I'd say if you can, I'd say go read it before listening to this.
If you can, go buy it and then read it and then come listen to this in that order.
That would be best. But if you want to listen, hey,
you're going to get some interesting shit out of this anyway.
So right off the bat, it's very interesting the way that you've structured the book.
I'm just going with the super basic details here,
but the way that you structured it from the perspective of multiple different protagonists,
they all count as protagonists, right?
Is that accurate? Is that the book lingo to use here?
Whatever, it doesn't matter.
The point is you've got Don, you've got Mason,
and you've got Mario as the main guys who are speaking here.
So you've got Mario, the school shooter,
Don, the sociopathic manipulator evil character,
and Mason, kind of the didn't do nothing good guy.
Ganky.
Sorry about that.
Yeah, you should be sorry. This is professional work we're doing here.
So, I mean, immediately, it took a while for me to figure out
kind of what Don's character was going to play into.
She's kind of like the main driver of everything that happens in the story,
for the most part, except obviously some shit goes down with Mario.
I mean, the book begins with we know he's the shooter,
so it's not like that's a spoiler or anything.
We know he's doing the shooting, it's just building up to that point.
And so it's kind of learning backwards how things got to that point,
and really what Mario might have done it regardless of what happened.
In fact, he probably would have, but it's the way that Don manipulates him
and encourages him and makes things worse for him
when it was entirely possible that things could have gone better.
I have a gigantic written-up analysis of Don's character here
in this notepad document that I wrote while we were waiting to get together here,
just going into specifically the ending and why she is writing,
because for her part, Don's input in the story is from the perspective
of a letter written to her mother after all the shit has gone down.
And so I put together this whole big analysis of like,
okay, so Don is a sociopath who manipulated all these people in the triflers
into doing some fucked up shit.
But it's very interesting because every account that we've got here
is in the form of sort of a journal entry or Mario's manifesto,
or in Don's case, it's that letter written to her mother.
But the thing is that we learn at the very end of the fucking book
is that her letter was written, and I actually suspected this from the very beginning,
Don's letter was written with an agenda.
It's full of at least several notable lies, and it's possible the entire thing was a lie.
So just for example, because Don's one of the characters that I am the most fascinated by.
I kind of relate to Mason the most, of course, as I'm sure everybody does.
And do you relate more to Mario?
I mean, I don't know if I relate to any of the characters in the story in the slightest.
Mason's a totally normal kid, except for the fact that he's got severe depression.
The one who I felt like I understood the most was probably Don,
though because of the twist at the end, it's hard to say,
because it's hard to say how much of what she portrays about herself is actually what she's like.
The character that's portrayed in her story felt like someone I went to high school with,
but a more clever and more sociopathic version of that person.
But seeing the big twist at the end kind of puts it into this perspective
where she has to be a lot smarter than the character she portrays.
Because I think that the character that I was reading out of Don,
some of the stuff she would focus on in her letter is like,
you have to be a fucking retard or some kind of weird autist to focus on these things.
But then you see at the end, well, okay, if it's all for a purpose,
then maybe she was doing that just to fuck with people.
Well, see, it's interesting, and I could tell that what Munky was going for
was trying to make Don, at least in her own eyes,
seem like she's the smartest dude ever and that she's got all her bases covered.
But I actually made a list of all the ways that she is weak and has made mistakes
and all her failings.
A categorical spreadsheet of her failings.
I did, because I have great hope at the end of the book
that Don is not nearly as smart as she thinks she is.
If the story that she wrote is mostly true,
then she definitely is not as smart as she thinks she is.
Well, I'm aware that it's entirely possible.
Literally everything she wrote was a lie or fabricated,
which I found very interesting,
and I suspected that from the beginning when she insisted that everything is 100% true
because nobody ever is, I don't know,
she's too smart to realize that she isn't coloring things with her own bias.
So that stands out to me immediately as something notable.
So at the end, when she has the big bait and switch where Truman,
probably the worst character in the book in terms of the worst person,
the worst person, because he's just such a weak, disgusting piece of shit,
possibly even worse than Don.
I will say, you don't really hear from him until the very end
where we get some parts from his perspective.
And I loved his character once we did just because he...
I think of all the characters in the story,
the one that you did the best job capturing is the semi-retarded beta male orbiter.
He was perfect as that.
I actually have some criticisms there.
I thought it went a little too far.
Like the childish writing, the spelling mistakes,
he seemed like he was literally retarded.
That's the thing, he probably is literally retarded.
Wait, isn't that the whole point of the book is that every character is literally massively retarded?
Well, there are plenty of mental illnesses to go around,
but I think only Truman descends into actual much dumber than the average person.
The thing about this book is that all the characters really did remind me of people I knew in high school.
And him especially.
I had a face I could put to that guy.
Yeah, I read Truman's lines, I see Jesse Wood's face.
It's just a one-to-one correlation.
Bam, got him.
You got me.
Bury me with my money.
But that aside, at the end,
as soon as the shit went down,
we're going all over the place here,
so eventually we'll probably flesh out the plot more.
But at the end, after Mario has gone off to do his shooting spree,
and Dawn has kind of,
she's gathered the trifles the day afterward for a meeting,
the way she is described,
and this is why I'll go through my list,
but this is one of the many ways I don't think she's as smart as she pretends to be.
Or she thinks she is.
Because according to her letter,
the day after a school shooting,
Chao's uncle, Tao,
brings home a fucking dude for them to do their evil human experiments on.
And it's like, how could he possibly think that was a good idea?
And of course, it's all a cover for smuggling out Truman
and explaining how people died,
and not pretending that it wasn't her.
I mean, it's, yes.
Yeah, I remember Digi pointed out almost immediately
when I went to his house the first time,
like, that's just the plot of a Serbian film.
Dawn is clearly writing out the plot of a Serbian film,
because it's even the same name as the character.
Yeah, the guy who he captures
is literally the main character of a Serbian film.
Like, it's literally that character
is written into her story.
So she has, like,
that's why I'm inclined to believe
that that's the only part of the story
that's like an outright lie,
because of the fact that she's basically
just borrowing from a movie she saw,
like, you know,
it's just so blatant that, like,
which leads me to believe that, yeah,
she's not as smart as she thinks she is,
because this one little chunk of story
is so incongruous with everything else
that sounds realistic,
and then this part just sounds completely batshit-insane,
and also it's named after a movie character,
which surely the police could figure out
before too very long.
And that's totally in character with her,
because at the end, we see that in her notes,
she's thinking of just naming herself after Lily,
which is Mason's little sister,
so obviously she is just pulling names
for things she knows for all kinds of stuff,
so totally, totally consistent with
the shit that she does.
Yeah, fuck Don.
You know, just for the sake of clarification,
so Don is basically the ringleader
of the triflers,
and as the story progresses,
she makes it quite clear,
who's goal in life is to
not really go out of her way to hurt people,
but what she's going to do with her life
is perform a human experimentation,
like the Nazis,
and sort of test the limits of
human pain endurance,
and what they'll do before they accept death,
and just all that kind of stuff
that's not particularly useful,
but she's very interested in,
and she spells it out quite clearly,
that there's no moral implication to it.
She doesn't give a fuck if she's hurting people.
And we'll do whatever it takes to get there.
So she kind of harangues the whole
all the triflers. She gets rid of
guys like Mason, who are a moral impediment,
who would stop her through,
and that process of doing that
was to me, by far,
the most disturbing part of the entire
book, but like way worse
than human experimentation, kind of because
I mean, maybe it's just me being selfish,
but whole like, kidnapping people,
chopping them up, making them kill themselves,
that kind of stuff, that almost seems
cartoonish to me, whereas
women, you know,
false rape allegations, doing the kind
of things that she's done, I could totally
see happen, probably happen every single
day, ruin innocent men's lives,
and terrified me to my core
that it could someday happen to me. So
I'm totally, you should have seen me on the plane
as I'm reading this book, surrounded by a grandma
and some, and some
some hot little number on my other side
as I'm just, my face is going,
ugh!
Sitting on the plane
raping this grandma, thinking, oh, I hope
she doesn't falsely accuse me.
Exactly, exactly.
Yeah, I mean, that part of the book had the most impact
by far, not only because it
felt more real, but also just
it was such a perfect
like, because the thing is, to me
at that point in the book was
where I was starting to get bored
and particularly
of Mason, because Mason's
thing is that he's kind of a normie.
Like, he's not a normie
normie, and this is another character
again, while I don't connect with
Mason personally at all, he was another one
I could put a face to from my high school
years, because like, there was always
like, that guy who hangs out
with kind of the freaks and weird...
And that face is the face of Davoo.
Not at all.
And of course, Mario would be monkey,
of course, of course. Yeah.
Well, I imagine Mario looking like
a munchie, actually.
Wait, that cut out, looking like who?
Like munchie, but like a short
version of munchie.
Half Mexican, yeah, it's the whole thing.
But anyways,
Mason, you know,
I knew kids in high school who kind of like
hung out with the freaks and weirdos
because their life wasn't really
like, normal, but
it's not that they thought the same way.
You know, like, Mason doesn't have
any like, mental disorders,
he just has a shitty home life.
So like, he connects with these people
who are much weirder than him
because he doesn't feel normal
because his home life is so shitty,
but like, the way he actually acts
is not like these other people who are all like,
you know, actually crazy.
But like, as you go through,
I kind of got that point, at first,
like learning about his home life and stuff, I was like, okay,
you know, I've seen this story before.
I know people who've been through this.
But that was the point of the character.
Eventually, though, it kind of starts to get to like,
okay, I get Mason,
because he doesn't really have a goal
the way that Mario and Don do.
Just by the end, baby!
Yeah, well, that's the thing.
At some point, I'm like, okay, I'm kind of sick of hearing
from Mason, and it's right as I'm starting
to really get sick of him,
that the tables turn on him,
and he gets written out in a big way.
And like, the second that thing happened
where they say like, the police go to pick him up,
I immediately flipped through the rest of the book
to see if Mason's name was at the top anymore,
and I saw that it wasn't, and I was like,
fuck!
Just that realization that his story
has just ended, like,
75% of the way through the book
was probably my favorite moment in the whole book.
It was by far the best.
Most disturbing, terrifies me to my core.
Yeah, that's the real shit.
Turn your fucking audio down.
Well, let's see here.
You know, if you like, I would love
to go through all the reasons why I think
Dawn is a piece of shit retard, faggot bitch.
By all means.
Okay, just dwell on that for a moment.
Okay, so I wrote this down,
so forgive me if I'm just reading off my page here.
The content of her letter.
What utility is served by Dawn
sending the letter? Why would she do it?
Ego and nothing more. She's still human
and has weaknesses. Now, I'm aware
of the list that is composed
by Truman.
There are exactly four reasons given
to why she would do it.
I divide them into two categories.
One, emotional reasons
that add risk to her doing so
and add nothing other
than fulfilling her own ego.
And those are freeing Mason
and taking credit for the Ricardo Fire.
Why in the fuck would Dawn do
something that in any way
makes her life more risky
just to help Mason? It doesn't make sense.
But putting that aside, there's also
two good reasons to do it.
I thought it was being implied,
especially through Truman's dialogue at the end of the book,
that Dawn actually did like
Mason. Like, she's actually
in love with him, I thought.
Unacceptable. There's no way that this...
If she loved him, she... Okay, I mean
that is unfathomable to me.
Any feeling she has
cannot be equated to love.
I think she lied
about the sex being terrible
and that she actually had
a thing for him. Because Truman's getting...
Truman keeps saying how
she'll get like...
Oh, she's getting way into writing
about him or that she's ignoring Truman
and stuff. Truman who she's obviously using
and doesn't give a fuck about.
Here's where the black pills come out
because love isn't a real thing.
Especially... What does that have
anything to do with...
You're saying that she likes him.
What does it mean to like someone?
To be willing to frame them for rape
of you or her little sister
or his little sister and send them to jail?
She needed to do that to get out of
what she... She needed to get him out of the way
but then she still cares about him
enough to free him.
That seemed obvious to me.
Mumki, do you want to pitch in on this?
Do you have an opinion?
I mean, of course I do have an opinion
because I know what happens
but I don't like to
answer questions in terms of
people trying to like
translate the book or interpretations
because it ruins people's
interpretations so I'd rather sit out on that one.
That's fair.
Well, okay, I guess we'll just have to have a disagreement there
but I don't see how you could possibly claim.
Was either of those an interpretation that you had not even thought of though?
Like...
Is the possibility that Don
is in love with him intentionally
written into the book as a possibility?
Even Al can see there's a possibility.
I just find it ridiculous.
Because I think a lot of the last part
of the book is clearly
throwing in lots and lots of implications
so that you can come to different conclusions
but without it being
ever, you know.
Like, how much of the stories lie,
how much of this and that. There's deliberately no answer
but there's lots and lots of implications
that could drag you in different directions
and I just thought there was a lot of implications suggesting
especially in what Truman was saying
about Don writing the letter
that she is in love with Mason
and won't admit it because she's too proud.
What...
Okay, here's the thing though. I literally don't care
about the answer to that question.
Whatever her feelings are
we're done with her feelings.
Her feelings don't matter anymore.
Not interested. She has done these things
I'm just trying to explain that this is why
I mean I'm not saying it was a good idea
for her to...
What's the relevance here?
I'm saying this is why she incriminated herself.
It's not that it was a good idea to do so
but she wanted to get him off the hook
because they're already after her.
That's fine.
She's not as the bad guy
but so why not just stack the extra allegations
on herself and let Jason skate
if she likes...the Mason skate if she likes him.
Well that's fine but she is now
unleashed what she must have known
would be at the very least a vindictive agent
someone who's not going to be too thrilled
about the shit that just went down.
I don't think she's smart enough
to realize that he would like
become a fucking...
Vigilante hero, man.
Exactly.
Yeah okay maybe
but see that's exactly what I wanted to get to.
In this way Don has shown that she is weak
and that she has flaws
and that she is not an impenetrable
logical fortress. I mean that's obvious.
She has these kind of flaws.
It just gives me hope.
It just makes me happy about the ending
because we've got, I forget what the guy's name was,
Grimes, the crime guy.
The true hero of the book, the only character
who I found remotely relatable
especially is Ron Clacker
who's going to bring justice to the world.
He has a lust for justice.
He's going to take her down
in the sequel written by me.
I can't wait, I can't wait.
I actually would kind of love
a trifle sequel written by Jesse
about like Mason and that agent
trying to take down Don.
He teams up with Truman Sinclair
who was the real mastermind all along.
He was playing that bitch for a fool the whole time.
Now he's just using her.
Now he's got this hot blonde girlfriend.
He just wanted her to be blonde the whole book.
That was the whole plan.
That was the gambit.
He's portraying himself like a humble beta orbiter
but in truth he's the fucking Omega male.
It's all part of his
Machiavellian schemes
to slam that plus.
When a beta goes that beta
it goes all the way to Omega. His power
circles around and becomes infinite.
My god, yes.
It's kind of like retard strength only socially applied.
Same kind of shit there.
I read the ending as
personally I don't feel I need a sequel at all
because in my mind I now know
that it was clear all along
but I know that Don has flaws
and that there are two hot
male heroes on the case
to take down this weak
cowardly woman. And if Ronda Rousey
can't take Jesse
then we know
that Don cannot handle these two men.
Two men.
I would kick Don Bracken's ass.
She's like a 15 year old girl.
I'd throw her in the fucking toilet.
So yeah, I mean
my impression of Don throughout the story
is that the way she's meant to be
is just extremely pretentious.
Like she really thinks she's hot shit
but it's constantly evidence
that she is not.
Not just in her actions
that she's petty and retarded.
Because she's a fucking teenager
and she acts like a teenager.
The things that she thinks are a big deal
are just not.
She's so obsessed with those swearing.
And I knew girls like that in high school.
I knew people who were like
swearing is for
uneducated people.
I know that kind of pretentious bitch
and she totally reminded me of that.
So the whole book I always saw her as
this grating pretentious asshole
who was just
who thought she was hot shit
and the only reason that she succeeds
is that everyone around her is even more retarded.
That's right.
In that moment when she meets
the detectives
you definitely have this sense of
these people are fucking adults
and they're way beyond her
and they're going to
there's gonna be a way
they can get her.
The end of the book doesn't really leave her
in the context of winning this one.
She's got all these things she's trying to do
while she's on the escape
but none of it is very convincing
that it's gonna work out for much longer.
They've figured out
who she is.
They're gonna chase her down. It can't be that hard
to catch this girl
who has no fucking idea what she's doing.
She thinks she does but she's a fucking idiot.
That's what I love so much about her.
The fact that she...
Just to go back on that
because I love shitting on this fucking bitch
as I'm sure everyone does
she just represents everything evil.
Forgive me for getting a little redpilled here
but she's like evil femininity at its worst
or at least she uses the tools at her disposal
particularly with Mason
and manipulating Truman
and the whole fucking thing there.
The way that she's so
cataclysmically does not
understand Mario
does not know that one of her pawns
is about to go commit a fucking
school shooting tomorrow.
That's how you know she...
She sees herself as in control
but she does this thing
and this I can relate to
because I kind of do the same thing
which is that when things
don't go your way at all
you just reframe it as though
but she does that
so much that it's obvious
that she doesn't really have any control.
She finds out that Mario's doing this thing
and she's like oh well
okay that's fine
I can plan...
it's actually like this
this all works out.
This is exactly what I had in mind
this is okay
but the reality is that her plans are completely fucked
and that she's getting foiled left and right
and having to change everything
and you can do that for some time
but how long before
it just pulls
the rug gets pulled out from under her
This bitch didn't even think
she was so
fucking dense. She didn't even realize
that Joe was in the restaurant before the thing got burned down
didn't have any idea
that there was a possibility that somebody would be there
and that's just one of her many
many mistakes along the way
and yeah she doesn't know what the fuck's going on
Well you know we're talking about
what a monster Don is
but we're not talking about
the other actual monster in the book
that committed the shooting
Mario who is
just as much if not more of a retarded faggot
and represents everything wrong with the
entire world all at once
he's a stupid
like uncreative, unoriginal
he only speaks in like
4chan copy pastas
which...
I'm not sure
he just speaks in
monkey videos
is what I'm trying to say
two of my videos are just
direct cold from Mario
I recognize a few passages
of just being your videos
well you know if we're segwaying from Don
he's basically a mumkey jones fan
is what he is
he's mumkey's entire fan base
in one wretched body
well you know the thing is
even though I'm fascinated by Don
the great thing about that is
the reason I even wanted to do this
and I was tweeting about this before
Don is pure evil and is basically
irredeemable by her own account
maybe she's
talking herself up, she's not actually sociopath
but according to her account
she's not changed anytime soon
she is a constant evil force
Mario on the other hand
that's something we can do something about
Mario is someone who could have been saved
by society
well stick with me
I'm just saying that
Don frames herself as like
in the end of the book she talks about how
there's a passage about how
what were the trifle is, what makes a trifle
or a trifle and she thinks about
oh were they all lonely, did they all have the same fascination with the macabre
no it wasn't any of those things
it's just that they were manipulable by me
and I agree that that was the real problem here
these people had psychological
vulnerabilities that she exploited
and so the way we can help that
and we can talk about Mario specifically
cause he's obviously the biggest one
though Truman's no spring chicken either
the murderer himself
yeah like that's what opened them up to this shit
to being able to be manipulated
by things that we cannot change
we cannot change what's going on inside Don's head
she's always going to be evil
but we can help with guys like Mario
and if he just had had some fucking friends
he wouldn't have done this shit
and you know like I rewatched
Mumkey's um
Elliot Roger, notice I didn't say Rogers
Elliot Roger, I'm learning
I'm getting better
I watched that video beforehand
and it was the two questions
that he brought up at the beginning of that
why did this happen
and how can we prevent it in the future
yes that's pretty much what was running through my mind
the whole time thinking about Mario
well obviously Mario is based on Elliot Roger
and so you know
the parallel is obvious
what were you saying Jesse
well like Mario doesn't have any
real problems
all of his sadness
and depression comes from the fact that he is
an obnoxious little spurred idiot
shit retarded butt boy
who can't make any friends
because he sucks that's no one else's fault
true I mean
I think it's um unrealistic
to say like how do we help these people
oh we gotta we gotta go we gotta
find the weird little depressed people
who are mean to everyone and who suck and just be friends with them
so they'll be better that's ridiculous
some people just suck and they're evil
well even if
the answer is that we can't do anything
about it until we have some sort of
I don't know brain scanning
psychopath technology and then we can know
ahead of time what people are gonna do
I would just like to know if there's
anything we can do
and you know you're right you're right
because especially the way Don frames it
I love the way in this book the way
there are different accountings
of different events and that the way like Don
I love how Mario goes into detail
about like all the conversations he had
with Don about like oh how I want to like
massacre everyone in the school and Don was totally like
yeah I want to fucking you know hang him up
by meat hooks and carve out their innards
or whatever it was but Don leaves that out of
her story entirely yeah clearly framing
herself as like oh I would never
delve into that kind of like bullshit
I fucking love that that's that's that's
really great she's a pretentious bitch and Mario's
Mario has no reason to be he's
completely Mario is just as pretentious
and deluded I mean he has these fantasies
that he's going to kill a bunch of people
and all the betas will be alphas
now and no one will ever be depressed again
he's going to create a utopia I mean like
where do you even start with
what could fix that nothing can fix
that that's a that's a deep fucked up
idiot delusion yeah
well that's what I
you're not wrong personally like Mario's parts
are my favorite parts of the book because
they're hilarious like nothing causes
something like that that's just there's something fucking wrong
with you go to you belong in the trash
yeah I we that's not
good enough damn it that's good enough
I kind of
I kind of agree with
Jesse because like we wouldn't know
like a guy like this
it's like like Jesse just said
we can't just like find a depressed guy
be like I'm going to be your best friend
we've been at antidepressants
and you can debate about
you know the ethics or the
value of antidepressants but they don't
make an antidepressant for stupid there's no
anti-stupid look look it's like
but but he clearly
illustrates several
points in the story where I mean we're just going from
his words here obviously but there were ways
that things could get better Mario was never even
on medicine at any point there's
ways that things could have gone
differently but no one could
ever possibly recognize that
like there's no way you can know when the doctor
in the when Mario talks about how the doctor
just blew him off and didn't take him
seriously and said just go talk to your general
practitioner whatever yes Mario should have
followed up with that but there were
there were moments where things could
have gone differently if the system was
more you know like the system is always
imperfect and that's the the problem
with all this stuff is that they try to
fix them yeah well
but the thing is the problem
isn't that nobody helped Mario
the problem is that the system itself
needs fixing like it's
not that he needed fixing it's that the system
needs fixing is that you need to have the doctors
not be shit you know and stuff
like that I agree and so
yeah but
personally reading Mario's parts
if this is
my biggest criticism of this book
and this is something I told
to monkey but I tried to avoid talking about it
online so it wouldn't color anyone's perception
who hasn't read it yet
it's just the fact that
it slips into self-awareness
sometimes in ways
that I think work against the
characters because with Mario
sometimes he reads like a parody
of a school shooter
and sometimes he reads like a school shooter
and so
even though that makes this part of the book hilarious
at times it also
kind of deflates parts of it where
there's moments I love
like okay when he goes on and on about how Death Note
inspired him that was like
the perfect combination of hilarious
and also totally I could see it
but then there's other times where he
goes on a rant that yeah does sound
too much like a monkey
video but I know monkey videos
when I watch them I can tell it's self-aware
and it's not a fucking school shooter
writing it so when he
is able to have that level of cleverness
or to tell a funny joke
I think well
Elliot Roger couldn't tell a funny joke
Elliot Roger's fucking retarded
his book reads like an insane person
wrote it you know Mario
sometimes seems retarded sometimes
he seems too clever and so
when he comes down to the end where he just fucks everything up
and dies it's like this should
have been a more retarded character
I think you know
I mean I see
what you're saying I don't know if I
necessarily agree yeah there were
times where I thought
I don't think anybody who commits
a school shooting is a funny guy
because funny people have friends
and it won't happen
well but that's part of the delusion
what if the Joker committed a school shooting
the Joker
yeah I'd be all smiles
I don't know if the Joker is actually a funny guy
like
has the Joker ever actually said like
a joke that makes you laugh
I thought the Joker said what he finds funny
I would put Mark Hamill and Cesar Romero
in the funny category of jokers
but that we're getting off on a tangent about with jokers
rating the funniness of jokers
I feel that like the point of
the Joker is not so much that he's funny
to other people but that what he himself
finds to be funny is
you know
terrorism I guess whatever he does
what does he consider it
I think the Joker is a terrorist
I mean in the animated series
he's a crime lord but he's also a murderer
yeah all those things
all those good things
well uh yeah
alright that's fair you know I'm pretty good
at just diving into something
and this is probably a negative on myself as like a critic
I'm pretty easily able to get
absorbed in worlds I'm reading so there weren't
many times where I had difficulty
separating like the monkey
well I think it's I think it's the reason
I felt this way is because I felt
so strongly that these characters reminded me
of people that I've known
before that like when they did something
that was incongruous with that then it would
it would take me out of it a little like with
with Dawn because she's
so pretentious and so up her
own ass and focuses on so many
weird details in her story there were
times where I thought she was too clever
as well where like she does something that I'm
like okay I don't believe
that the person who thought that explaining
every fucking detail of her
work shift at the stupid goddamn ice cream
place was necessary is also
clever enough to write
this other sentence you know it's like can I
like like like monkey himself
is better at English
and in creative writing than
the characters that he's portraying
even though he sometimes is trying to portray
the story like
sometimes he tries to write like a retard
and sometimes he writes clever and
the two can compete is what I mean
to say you know I the only time
I really felt like that was with Truman I mean
unless I never got the sense this character was actually
retarded I definitely
for a loop got the sense that
um that that monkey had stumbled
upon a great scheme
of making his book impossible
to criticize because it's written from the
perspective of three terrible writers
yeah true true
but that's again that's what I
mean when I say that sometimes the writing was
too good like it's
it's just inconsistent where sometimes
it's like it's clever and
funny and it feels like a dark comedy which
is how it kind of builds itself and then at other
times it feels like you're just looking into
the like when again when Don goes into
like everything about her work routine it was so
fucking unnecessary and I thought that part
of the book was completely boring because
it it's not
it's not funny it's not
really relevant she's just going on
and on about everything they do
but it does get you kind of more into
like I'm looking at it and I'm thinking this
is what a fucking 16 year old would write though
like she would think that this is all
necessary because I've read lots of stuff
written by teenagers because people
teenagers constantly submit to me their
work for my review
and it's always full of unnecessary
bullshit information so reading a part
like that was more
boring as a story but better as
this is something a dumbass
16 year old pretentious bitch would write
whereas other parts where it's
like really you know there's like a clever twist
and there's like a just right timed
piece of dialogue or something that's really funny
I'm like okay that was great
oh what was the one I wanted to make them
look like you oh
got them fuck wheelchair
people oh yeah yeah that whole
big dramatic twist part
that was that was I died inside
really bad I wanted to die I definitely
felt I like how he put her
on the school shooting list by the way
like she did anything fucking wrong
fuck you Mario you piece of shit
alright what did Marissa do
what did she do she did
nothing she did nothing wrong
you're the bad person okay alright
go on yeah I definitely
um I felt far more
disturbed I guess you'd say
with Mario's chapters than with dawn's
chapters because
actual psychopaths like dawn
the job something
actual psychopaths like dawn are you know pretty far
and few and far between and
they're not as smart as they think they are and they usually
get caught but people like Mario
are fucking everywhere
um he is every
4-channer in the world he's every internet commenter
in the world and every redditor in the world
they're all over the place they're all
too stupid and deluded
to know how evil they are and how malicious
they are and they're the real
problem we need to take them out we need to put them
in a fucking meat grinder
just like you know Mondo Burger you mess with Kurt
you go in the grinder that's what I say
what the fuck is
Mondo Burger
is that the prequel to Good Burger
yeah it's the evil fast food chain
in Good Burger
that's right that's right
I haven't seen Good Burger in 15 years
can we just talk real quickly
about do you think it is
I was just wondering about this so nobody
at any point ever
like provided evidence
besides Dawn's written word
that there was actual like human
experimentation that happened in that basement
with like the first guy we know the second guy
was fake obviously but the first guy
I found myself re-evaluating
whether or not that was even true and if so
because this goes into like why
she even wrote this letter like why give them
all this material to like
look into the fact that yes I am a
super psychopathic monster
I want you to know about the fact that
I've committed these atrocities
like what good is served by that
other than just ego it was just ego
we can just write it off as we go
well that part is corroborated by Mario's part
I mean a lot of what Dawn says is
can be called true because
yeah Mario did say that they started doing that
he said something about that yeah
yeah the FBI even brings it up he says
Mario says he was responsible for two deaths
and blue bitty blue
oh shit that was two deaths
fuck okay yeah I fucked that up
incidentally I wonder about if
why the fuck did she tell anyone though
how many of the kids
videos had you guys seen
because I'd seen one man one jar before
so that was
another interesting aspect of the story
is how much of it is just real
well sometimes it's
interesting because some of them are monkey made up
and some of them are real videos
and it's because I've seen some of the real videos
that it actually enhanced
how disturbing the made up ones were
because like because I can't
tell I can't tell how many things I just
haven't seen before so as I was reading this
book probably the part that
disturbed me the most was just
monkey describing
video tapes that the characters were watching
that was extremely disturbing for sure
and again I could never tell which ones are real
and which ones aren't because there were so many
or at least a few
that I knew were real that I had seen
like one man one jar which is the one where the guy
puts a jar of bazaar and it breaks and he has to pull
all the shards out
fucking disgusting video
but like I've not seen that one
yeah it's on like porn
sites but
yeah it's
just knowing that that was real
and then thinking about like okay
well if that one's real then maybe this one's real
my mom just showed up with a bunch of food
and drinks you know what a bitch
I'm so sick of her one of these days I'm gonna kill her
and I'm gonna kill the whole world too
and make it a better place for
podcasters like me
that one moment where Don
describes you know Mario's mom
is just being such a nice lady that one time
really really added a lot
to when Mario just shows up to school with like her fucking
blood all over his hands
what did she do Mario did she deserve that is this justice
guess so
casualties of war I guess
it's kind of funny that Jesse made that joke because Jesse
does actually complain about his mom
all the time and I have met his
mom and she's an extremely sweet woman
so
that's why he hates Mario hit
too close to home hey Jesse
oh boy
like I remember
when you told me or you were on
some stream and you were saying that um
that uh that that boozy floozy
was like friends with your mom and I was like
huh I always thought Jesse's like
I imagined your mom is like I don't know
like a total bitch or something
and then I met her and I was like oh she's just like
a mid-western
house mom she's just a mom
yeah my mom
is a saint and I always feel bad when I complain
about her
yeah well that's good you see
shout out to Jesse's mom
and Jesse's mom yeah
and Jesse's whole household is nice I stayed there for a week
had a good time
aside from the shit rot that I caught
in the uh
baby Groot
the real hero of this book baby Groot
as he is the real hero of every book
ever written
uh yeah
he's gonna be a essential character in
my sequel it's gonna be a buddy
cop movie with uh special agent Dale Cooper
from Twin Peaks and baby Groot
and they're gonna take down Don
they're gonna trap her in the black lodge
where she belongs I gotta
watch the new Twin Peaks I just remembered about that
apparently it's shit so
oh no
have you been watching it Jess
I have been watching it
because Victor was just telling me
that he just marathoned all of the original
it's very
very slow and very methodical
and they're really taking their sweet time
with everything that you want to see but I wouldn't
call it bad
the people on the Twin Peaks
Reddit board are all of course kissing
every episode's ass and calling them a genius
I'm not like
I can see where they're coming from
I can also see where people would say it's boring
but I don't know I'm invested I like it
to be fair
I thought that the original series
has a lot of moments where it drags and gets
pretty boring I thought so too Victor said
he just like completely loved the
entire thing like both seasons
the whole franchise is something that you just
like you stick to the bad parts because the good
parts haven't of trying to make up for it
all right well now we're reviewing
like that we're on the Twin Peaks
all right we're off all right we're off that
now let's talk about
let's talk about Mason
just to see what we can get out of the character
of Mason so it was interesting to me
that you said did you that you couldn't really relate
to the guy because to me he was painted to be
basically the normal everyman
well I'm not a normal everyman am I
so well I wouldn't really consider
myself to be one either but just as like a moral
agent you know what's interesting actually
I would I would I actually love the character
of Dawn because Dawn is exactly
the opposite of me because while she is
an amoral unfeeling
psychopath wanting to hurt and kill people
I am an amoral
unfeeling psychopath whose only desire is to
make the world better for everyone that is what
I am this is my I don't
give a fuck who I have to crush on my way
to make their life great I will do
it and I will I will take hostages
I'll do whatever is necessary to make the world
better for everybody and
so and and you know Mason just as like
the maybe it's just
that my connection to him as like this guy
being you know strung along
by Dawn I don't know dude
this shit really gets to me any of this
kind of shit about an innocent guy
just being I
I know I'm gonna go off your red pill
migtown date we understand
I I I have such deep
fear of the of the real power
that women have socially over men and it
it haunts me it haunts me all the
time it doesn't you know why it doesn't haunt
me because I'm not a rapist
well that was
was he a rapist was he a rapist Jesse
yeah lock him up here's
an accusation no actual proof what's
that a bunch of hearsay throw him away
fucking lock him up I just fuck what do you
mean there's a little girl come all over
her that's proof that doesn't matter
if it's true or not it's still
she she she literally could have gone into
the bathroom after he jacked off and rubbed
it on herself there was no proof that he
ever do that that's ridiculous
that would never happen it would never
happen would never happen
incidentally by far my favorite thing
that happens in the book is uh is really
rubbing come all over her so let's
let's talk about that because this
that's a shitty meme that's a shitty meme
look the incident is fine
it's cool that people bring up that as
like an interesting outstanding
moment it's just me it's just me
who brings it up all the time because
it's well what I consider
maybe it is just you I mean when I sell
the book to people I tell them
there's an 11 year old rubbing come on
herself okay see
a thousand times more interesting to
me than that is just the fact
that a man is being destroyed for
having done nothing wrong well sure
that's the emotional content
of the book that's not that's intellectual
content rubbing come on your body
is not intellectually interesting it's
viscerally interesting I don't know
I don't know if I agree that
Mason is totally innocent
or totally like a nice guy
not bad at all I mean he's not
so he's not as evil as the other
two but he's pretty
annoying yeah and he's complicit
in a lot of which is
black him out he's a dumb teenager
he's pretty cringy yeah his desire
to fuck Don does
make him complicit in a lot
of bad activity what the
fuck are you even talking about it's
clearly painted in the story that
everything okay I mean the fact that
Mason take her words as joke the fact
that they're just that's true
the triflers at all
makes him a fucking retard
like all right you personally have
admitted to watching that that clip
of the guy in the ass are you
are you first of all are you as
evil as true I mean I never said
I wanted to watch that video or that
I enjoyed it in any way in fact
by society I guess
I
think that if you're too stupid
to notice that the people
you're hanging out with our weird
gross grimy greasy pieces of shit
then you're probably just as bad
yeah I mean like he
look he got played I will fully admit
he's weak I mean he's definitely weak
you're not you're not evil
but being a certain level of stupid
to me is complicit
in evil
I just think I think Mason
turned a blind eye
to a lot of things because
of the fact that he wanted to fuck Don
I think there's a lot of shit he could
have recognized he could have seen
where things were going but he let
himself be blinded because all he cared
about was how badly he liked this girl
and it's because it was an escape
from how shit his life is you know
his he hates his dad he's trying to get out
of the house he's you know trying to finish
school and all he's thinking about is like
this sort of fantasy this escapism that
he gets from imagining that he's gonna get
to fuck this girl you know and hoping
that she'll like him and like that
it's an escape from his life but it's allowed him
to turn a blind eye to all the bullshit
going on in the triflers you know oh yeah
it's not like he had any desire to like move
away and save his little sister he only
cared about fucking this guy you guys are
totally blown away
why do you keep putting words in my mouth
you just paid it that you just
when did I ever say that
when did I say that I did not say that
I said that he's so
worried about it he's so concerned
about it I didn't say it's the only thing
he's thinking about I said
that he is blinded because
his life is shit and he
can't do anything about it so he's
obsessed with this girl and
he's thinking about her all the time
and he's turning a blind eye to all the
bullshit just because he can't you know
he's doing it because
he can't get away he can't
escape yet he wants to but he can't
so he needs something to keep him
fucking sane and that thing
is obsessing over this girl but he
should recognize at some point that
A, Don is a piece of shit who doesn't
give a fuck about him and that should have been obvious from the beginning
he should have recognized that all of her friends
are pieces of shit that the kind of videos they were
watching is fucked up I mean
this guy is not into this stuff
he's admits himself you know he doesn't
find these videos interesting he's concerned
about these people but just because he wants to
fuck Don so badly he'll just
go along with all of it just keep saying yes
and that's a dangerous kind of thing that
totally happens you know
he'll go along with it is just
continue to show up to meetings and watch stuff
it's not like he ever agreed like because that's the
thing he had to go because he was too good
because he would have stopped because he has a moral
compass whereas the others are you know
too weak I found
a lot of Mason's chapters to be
pretty uncomfortable and particularly
cringy because I could
relate to them they did remind me
of stuff that I said back
when I was in high school like the parts where he's
talking about you know
girlfriend and Don and like
you know trying to like scheme his way
you know out of one relationship
it really reminded me of like the way I used
to think about girls all the time
when I was in high school so that was
really cringy of me because you know relating to it doesn't
make me not able to see that it's fucked up
and evil and stupid just like the other
two's behavior um I
what would stop stop
it's like you're putting him on the same level
as the other people I'm not I'm not
okay we're talking about look let's
put him on a scale all right I'm
complimenting
he's writing you Claude by
saying that fucking all the characters
were equally uncomfortable
which I think was the intent for different
reasons and and Nate you
you gotta understand it's like saying
you know you got you got
you got Don she's like
Aromanga sensei level bad
right and you got Mario
Kintania and he's like the asterisk war bad
and then you've got you've got
mason and he's like re-zero bad
you know he's re-zero
bad but they're there's a sky
whale of a human being I
I will masquerading as a man
I legitimately think it's unfair
to call Mason a bad person I don't
know a bad person I'm
just saying that he's a little
complicit and not totally innocent and that
I think that he's
an annoying teenager which you know
fuck and he's boring which is the worst thing
that a person can be look look
I just want to be like if you're saying that he's
I question that like I question
whether
I think he I question
whether he's also a sociopath
like Mario and Don I mean
you could almost call the book two sociopaths
and a psychopath I think I think Don
is the psycho but I but I
you know Mario's obviously a sociopath I
you know I wonder if he really
gives a shit about anyone but himself
because all of his writing and everything
his narration is all very focused on
himself what house
how are things going to turn out well for him
he doesn't really go with a teenager dude he's
15 exactly all
just like sociopaths yeah
oh wait he's he's a he's a he's a
whether he really even cares about his sister
or whether he's just you know he wants
to help her to feel better about himself
or something because he the way he
literally antagonizes dad doesn't
give a shit about his girlfriend he doesn't
really give a shit about Don other than he's
infatuated with her because he wants to fuck her
and that puss it's ridiculous
to say he doesn't care about his sister he would
literally antagonize his dad so that he would
beat him instead of the sister
how can you argue that he doesn't care about
are you and he doesn't I'm just saying I wonder
I'm saying I wonder I'm
being well here's a proof to the contrary
all right fine I just
and for what it's worth the second
that Lily did something
of her own accord that
he completely turns on her like that
yeah as soon as she takes a look at pictures
he starts sounding exactly like Mario
oh yeah yeah he was mad at her
and then he got over at the next
entry what a bad person
to be mad at someone
blowing this way out of proportion nobody
saying you're a bad guy we're saying
that he turned on her like that's some sort of
like yeah he broke up all
time no one said it was
irritable you mother fucker
yeah it's normal normal people suck
normal people are horrible it's
normal for people to be shit half
the time half of their lives
what context are we coming at this from
from having normal human expectations for
characters or expecting them all to be
literally perfect paradise of goodness
look worse things happen
to Mason than he deserved but he's
not a great guy he's just
a shitty teenager like every other one
you knew in high school he's no
look Mario and Don are worse than
anybody I've ever known yes
nobody I well okay that's not fair because
I knew a school shooter so Mario
was as bad as the worst guy I've ever
known and Don's may be a little bit worse
but Mason is just like
a lot of kids I knew in high school
who were just fucking dumb burnout kids
who didn't know what their lives
sucked so they had no plans
and they just fucked around and they made a lot of bad
decisions he didn't deserve to have
the things happen to him that did but
he's not a good guy he's not someone you root
for he's just kind of a shitty
little teenager who gets a lot worse
than he deserves you know but like at
no point was I like yeah Mason
you go until the very end where he gets
like a and it's only because he becomes
the punisher yeah it's only
because like so severe
of stuff happens to him that yeah he
basically has like a superhero backstory
now and now he's interesting at the very
end but like throughout the book he's fucking
completely lame and that's kind of the point
that's why it's actually kind of cathartic
when all the bad shit happens to him
because it's like oh thank god we wrote out
the boring guy and now we get to focus on the cool characters
for a while you know
like fuck Mason
you guys are ridiculous
I disagree that his chapters are boring
I think they were
you know just as interesting as the other two characters
I thought they were interesting at first
but eventually I just
but I do definitely think fuck him
yeah when he
writes when he confesses
in his entry I mean of course
of course he's the normie of course he's got the least
interesting thing his
you know it's not like his problems weren't the worst
his problems actually were the worst
of any character and yet
he puts up with it the most
he is the best person despite having the worst
situation you know what Nate you've swayed me
what I agree thank you
thank you I mean that's objectively true
I mean again like it's just that
his problems are all real stuff that
most of the people I know have gone through
and like it doesn't
most people don't
go through most people who are in that situation
don't then get put into a far worse
one like he does and most people
don't become a vigilante superhero at the
end of their story
but you know Mason's
started Will Smith
Mason's problems were stuff that I was
like okay yeah this is what most of
my friends were going through in high school
they had shitty home situations
I mean I hung out with a bunch of fucking
you know like potheads and stuff who were just trying
to do anything to get away from the house because their lives
fucking blue you know they had shitty
parents who didn't know how to take care of
them because they had kids when they weren't ready
and they lived in the ghetto like that was a lot of
my friends so Mason to me was like
yeah I know this guy I know this story
but he's not my friend
so I don't care about him the way I care about
my friends you know I agree
he had the least interesting things to say up
to when things turned but the point of
the character is that he represents
normalcy yeah and of course that's not
going to be fascinating relative normalcy
so I don't disagree with you at all
but to say that he's like well
I mean okay we already talked about like
if he's complicit and yes I will 100% agree
his own idiocy
you know everyone's idiotic to a degree
if they couldn't see what was going on here
obviously shot him in the back
but like the
the impetus I mean obviously
if you're dividing this up by percentages
I'm just saying he's gotta be like
tiny compared to what's going on with these other people
obviously
we're comparing again
re-zero bad
which is to say 5 out of 10
you know strong 5 light 6
if you're lucky
to guys who are bottom of the barrel
worst scum of the earth
you know a school shooter
and a fucking mass killer
like these are the worst that we have to offer
any big brother who protects
his little sister from abuse from an abuse of father
I would put above a fucking like
average he's better than average but okay
did he really protect her though
or did he just get her beaten up more
oh
whatever let's move on
we know the answer to this question
how about
Doreen
Dobson I believe was the male name right
is that the
the pretentious asshole trans person
again very
character I've seen
I'll tell you man
you portrayed an obnoxious
SJW pretty accurately
with that character
like in the name I think was
Doreen and Donovan
Donovan was like
I want someone to make a Dobson joke
as in the little blue bear guy
I mean it's easy enough to make fun
of like a you know SJWs
and stuff and say
okay they're all obnoxious pretentious
shitheads but like it's not even
that I think there's plenty of SJWs
who are like fine this person
though I have this is exactly
the type who
gets on you on Tumblr
you know like this is the
the portrait of the stereotypical SJW
but they do exist there are real people
like that and well you know this is the
character I this is the character
I think I most felt the hand of
Mumpkin as in like yeah by the way
fuck these people don't like
they're totally real like
they are real and
and I thought he did a good enough job of
like making it it didn't feel like
um it didn't feel
like just a parody because of the fact that he
addressed the backstory that
that he became this way
that he wasn't always like this but like
now that he's learned the rhetoric of
this movement of the social justice movement
he's developing these feelings
so even though he still hangs out with the fucking triflers
who are like these terrible
terrible people watching horrible videos like
you know he's still hanging around but he's trying to like convert
them to his new age like beliefs
and stuff and I thought that was totally believable
like I've seen people make that transition
before that is very interesting
and that it no pun intended
right true it kind of shows
the characters like deference
to power in that you know once once
you know because in her life obviously
she's following trends that's that's what
she's all about um which
you saw like oh I can get attention if I'm trans
so I'll do that I mean just not that old
actually but that's what this character was and
not to distract from you too much
sorry but um I actually
thought I felt the hand of monkey
perhaps too much just in the fact
that the characters
like like Don goes on this whole thing about
how she's like you know oh I don't have any problem
with trans people it's just the way that this
character has to do that
that felt a little too defensive where I was
like why not just make her hate trans people
or something or like Mario when he
I think he has a part where he does
something like that with either trans
or like blacks or something he has
some kind of like defense
logic and I was like no
just let him be a fucking racist he's already
a school shooter you know
it did kind of great on me
after a while and annoy me that all the
characters sort of talk in youtube
videos yeah like
they'll be like in the middle of a conversation
and Don will just lapse into like an editorial
on you know
Mario does it too and you know it's
like I said before about not really
being able to criticize it because
I don't know if that's intentional
or if that's just the way that like Don
writes but doesn't actually speak
I mean it felt a little too
it's true it really felt
a little too editorially at some
parts I agree there were I noticed
that in moments and
yeah like she would literally in her
dialogue suddenly transform into
a youtube video sometimes and
I think that's I mean
you can defend it all you want I think it's clumsy
writing monkey was 20 that's how 20
year olds write so
you know I'm gonna blame monkey for
that one yeah you swayed
me I'm gonna blame nobody to
the one time yeah it was definitely during the
the train I mean don't get me wrong
I'm saying that because if you go read
my light novel that I wrote when I was 20
that happens all the time
characters will lapse into an editorial
because I was used to editorial writing
so you know like in the middle
of a conversation a character will like
psychoanalyze himself to explain
to another one so
you should be nisei oisin
you're a genius nisei oisin does the same
shit and he started when he was that age
so yeah he never
grew out of it they only
whatever I don't it's silly to go back to
but I'm just gonna finish my point anyway it was just that
Dorianne she was
a bitch to social pressure decided to be
a cool trans person and then
when Dawn asserts herself
as the leader of the group she
notices she bows to the
new authority in her life which is Dawn
so shows that she is a weak, spineless person too
there you go that's just the character
how about
I mean there's not a lot to say about
Chao or Chao's uncle
cause Chao's uncle first of all
but the more interesting of the two
just like a war vet who got a taste for blood
wants to kill people thinks it's really cool
those two also fascinated me in a way
and I have to ask Mumki did you have
Asian friends like that before
are you talking to me you cut out
yeah yeah did you have Asian friends
like the two
the brothers
every single person in the tribe
is based off of one of my high school friends
yeah I figured because
that particular brand of Asian
household is familiar to me
of like
the kids
the younger generation of the household
just being super disaffected because
their parents are from a completely different culture
and they just don't even know what's going on with their kids
like
there's a level of disconnect
like you can tell the mother
just literally does not understand her children
cause they are American and she's not
you know and so like
she just tries to be the default mother
because she does not understand what the hell
well when's her brother right
yeah but the brother
is younger than her I think
by a good amount and he being
ex-military he kinda reminded me
of like an evil version
of
my friend
my Asian friend Donson who has a cousin who lives with them
who's like that age and he's like
similarly a very like physically active
outgoing guy you know mostly kinda quiet
but like watches a lot of movies
and does a lot of travel and like lots of interesting
random weird things and like
this the you know
the older guy kinda reminded
me of that a little bit
like they just everything about
the way that house was described and the way the kids act
and everything I was like
yeah I've been in that house before
and to some extent like not that exact
one but it's like an accumulation
of different Asian households I've been in
and I totally got it
I thought it was cool because
the whole time I was picturing
this veteran chow's uncle as Rambo
you know the returning vet
he's back
hey man this is really bad enough Casio but I'm back
and I just wanna hurt people now
look at my fucking youtube videos guys
yeah that's my Rambo impression
that's um
I don't know I was picturing like imagine
you know that scene where Don walks into his room
to like tell him like hey let's start experimenting on people
imagine like Rambo in the corner just like
sitting there all bunched up just like
I love that she pretentiously
criticizes him for having
a pulp fiction and fight club poster
that really stuck with me
cause I would totally have
those you know like
I it was
yeah that's what that guy would have
of course he would you know like
yeah he's gonna have two
good hyper masculine films in his fucking
you know well one's a hyper masculine
film at least and the other one's comparable
like yeah why wouldn't he
it just a lot of the character details
in this book really definitely
resonated with me like every character felt like
somebody who I kind of knew
and you know uh I feel like
Mumkey's high school friends are probably not
similar from mine in
in that case
mm-hmm
I do want to mention about Chao
was that his character was an experiment
on my part to see
how full fledged of a character
I could create who has zero
lines of dialogue in the whole book
I was going to comment on that
yeah I was going to see if you guys even noticed
that he didn't say a single word
I did but only towards the end
like there was a moment where I suddenly was like
he's never spoken has he like
uh yeah I thought you did a pretty
okay job like I mean he's obviously like
the least interesting character because of it
but I felt like I understood
his character in spite of it I sort of like
spaced out
his entire existence in the story
yeah like I thought like the Chao's uncle
was just a guy called Chao's uncle
it's
isn't it fascinating though that the more active
interesting character there would be referred to as Chao's uncle
while Chao was just the non-entity
in the in the situation
and one moment that really stuck
out to me was when
after the meeting after she and Tao
you know the uncle talk
and they announced their plans to the group
and Chao just looks bored
yeah very very interesting
very interesting response I want to know what's
going on with this guy I like that because I feel
like he's just
so utterly doesn't give a
fuck that it like none of it
matters like he's just he's a super alpha
he doesn't give a fuck about anything
I mean I feel again like I've known
I've known people who are
kind of like I assume he's probably a pretty
smart guy who does well in school
and like but
but doesn't give a like has no particular
opinions about anything just doesn't care
just let's life pass by because he doesn't
he has no aspirations
and no nothing to care about
he's just letting the people around him control
and he hangs out with these with the triflers because
probably his options are
hang out with Asian kids or weirdos
because you know as an Asian
kid you're probably not going to hang out with like
Jax and all the like white kids
or whatever you know so you're going to end up
hanging out with like the either the freaks
or the other Asians and he ends up hanging out
with the freaks you know
yeah I love casual racism
Chinese people can't do anything
not being racist I'm anything being sympathetic
towards this is what like
towards the weaker race of Asians
my group of friends I was
the freaks in high school you know
and like that's who are you
saying that Asians are the freaks of society
I'm saying that
like for instance my friend Brandon
Tolentino he hung out with this guy
aren pretty much exclusively because
both of them were Filipino and
so they hung out together even though
they weren't necessarily friends
they just hung out because they were the
Filipino kids and that's what
you just end up gravitating to people who are your race
my high school is extremely mixed
so we had like probably half the school
was black half the school was white
and you know some percentage of other
ethnicities and like
the black kids all hung out together and the white
kids all hung out together and the ethnic
kids all hung out together and the only
group that was like super mixed
like you know they'll be mixing here and there
but it was the freaks and weirdos who
was a true
multicultural group because we're internet denizens
and stuff we don't give a fuck you know
we're outsiders we don't feel like we're part
of our race so that's how a kid like that
ends up with a group like that I think
yeah yeah
he was in a bit of an enigma to me um
well shit
what else we got have we talked enough about
Mario specifically because I feel like
we might have glazed over him
a little bit in our in our rush talk
about other guys I love the way
he's fat he is fat
unfortunately I think the the best thing
about Mario um in his
presentation in this book is that
this book shits on him in
a big way like
because I know he's based on Elliott Roger
and monkey's done he's read the entire
Elliott Roger um you know
uh manifesto and all that
and one of the things about
monkey's relationship relationship with Elliott Roger
is that he does make fun of the guy
and point out that he's a fucking retarded idiot
and that's a big part of this
book is that Mario spends this whole
book building himself up and having all
these grandiose opinions and in
the end he accomplishes almost nothing
you know he just he goes
in he he kills one
guy who is the guy who stopped him
who becomes a fucking martyr and a hero
for all time you know his target
as one of these people that have to be disposed
of was the hero and
save people the real the real lesson
to take away from it is thank god that
mass killers are always the weakest
most beta pathetic people in society
because if they were strong like
me we'd all be doomed
right well you know if they if they had avenues
if they had levers at their disposal to climb
social ranks and alleviate their issues they probably
would but they that's the thing I just push to
the point of desperation I love it because I feel
like most people if they heard
about a mass shooting book
they would assume it's going to
in some way glamorize it
or painted as like this big epic thing
and the book there's a lot of build up
to this school shooting so you're thinking
it's gonna be this like huge epic
bloodbath or a big action scene and instead
the book goes way out of its way to undercut
it as harshly as possible and so
if you you know let's say someone
tried to read this book thinking oh
I'm like some edge lords like oh I
want to read about a fucking school shooting yeah
and then they get to that part and it just
slaps them in the face with how retarded
a school shooter is and how badly
he fucks up you know I hope
the school I hope that edge lords the world over
read this book and realize how that's not
yeah you got to be a little bit like dawn and realize
that school shootings are highly inefficient
at changing the world and god
their beta depression
Mario's plan will finally be fulfilled
we'll have a college school after all
Mario's biggest problem to me I think
was a lack of self-awareness and even when
done clearly point out that every school
shooter is a lack of self-awareness
they don't realize it's just not realizing
that it's your fault not the world's or
or that the people who
it is their fault you're completely misguided
on who they are like Elliott Roger
there's people he could have blamed but he
didn't blame those people you know he
blamed the girls who wouldn't
sleep with him
because they literally he just never even
asked so because he never
like so Mario you know his rage is
completely misguided and the book
points that out and shows
it this book paints Mario as a fucking
idiot and it paints his
revenge is pathetic and it paints him as
a failure and I think that's
great because I don't think
a lot of I don't think there's a lot of people who could have
written that and still made it feel
real like there's people who would have
you know imagine like
a normie guy writing this book like
someone who like heard about a school shooting who's just like
some guy that read fucking 13 reasons
why or some shit like that you know and that's
the problem with 13 you know there's a
Netflix series airing right now and Victor
pointed this out that in that show
there's a character who they're building up to be a
school shooter but he doesn't have the personality
of one he doesn't act like what
a school shooter would act like that any
anyone could point that out Mario
is a completely realized school
shooter but the book still
shits on him for being that you know and I
think that's a cool aspect of it
that uh was it was definitely
one of the funnier twists in the book to
read him just like utterly get shit on
and fail horribly and it was
like ah you dumb fuck
which I mean I mean
agreed the guy who I know the school
shooter that I grew up with
who was a friend of mine when I was a little kid
um he didn't even get
to accomplish it because he made youtube videos
bragging about all his guns and how he was going to shoot
up a school and so he got busted because
he's a fucking retard so
man what about that American
hero who tackled Mario
and wrestled the grenade out of him and blew up
that's Bryce
Bryce whatever yeah and
what's great about that is that
Bryce Dallas thundercot
what's great about that part is you know Mario
had portrayed that guy as like
this asshole normie piece of shit
but he's clearly like
yeah a total hero like he saves
well that's kind of
that's kind of what Jesse says all the time
about he was spires to norminess
yeah norminess is next to godliness
when you're an outsider of society
it's easy to just demonize everybody
or view them as you know
because they're ostracizing you and they must be evil
and you know to a certain extent it's kind of like
um uh you know like
uh an outsider mentality like if you're not one
of us uh you know we're gonna treat you like
shit but at the very least
at the very least these people are they're pretty good
to each other you know they they want to protect
each other guys like Bryce
not a bad guy certainly not a bad guy
probably has parents in the
he probably has like parents in the military
who while strict with
him and therefore he acts out
they nonetheless are like very proud
people like very America's
beautiful place you gotta protect your citizens
you know I bet that's the house he grew up
see that that's the thing about guys like Mario
or even guys like you know Isis or whatever
like they they're viewing
individuals as part of like
guys like Isis
not a not a fan
of that guy uh yeah
like these they they paint
you know like they're the whole terrorist and Mario
is literally a terrorist like he's hoping to
inspire terror to make society
change that's literally what what terrorism is
and um
like you have to view people
as part of a collective because he's just
Mario had specific targets right of course but Mario
didn't care to like look into their stories
and and you can see this clearly
that he was not even interested in diving
deeper when he starts painting people
like Marissa this angel who
gave him a chance and was such a wonderful person
him that he did everything wrong to
and destroyed his own chances with he says like
I would have loved to have killed her too
but she's not at this school because it's all about
him and how he's the sad one and how
you know the why hasn't life
and that's exactly what Elliot Roger was like
that he was he wanted to kill his own little
brother who he literally
loved and who never did anything wrong
and he wanted to kill him so he wouldn't turn out
because one day he will have sex
one day he'll have sex and that's
unacceptable that cannot happen
what a fucking monster
not
a fan of that guy
um which is why you know
just on a little rant here I get pretty pissed
when people like lion eyes Elliot
or like celebrate him in any way
because he's just a monster
that no one should like
admire in any way
there's probably I'm sure there's a great deal of irony
going on here but
you know the water's getting muddy to some points
so I guess I'm just saying don't get carried away
with it folks he's not a good person
he is a literal murderer
if you saw you he would kill you
so keep that in mind
do we have anything else to say about the book?
any untapped
any um shit
monkey is there anything you want to hear us
talk about about your book?
uh no nothing specific
I was just gonna say I've been waiting over a year
to hear people have an actual conversation
about this and I thought it would
like when I was writing and I thought it would never happen
I thought nobody would read it so this last hour
has been like pretty fucking great
for me like even even the parts where you're
shitting on some of the writing I'm thinking
finally somebody is acknowledging
what I did
that's great that's great all it takes is a hero
like Nate Bestman to read your book
and bam instant well instant celebrity
yeah I mean I talked to monkey
about some of my issues with it back in
March but I again
wanted to hold off till more people had read it
because I was literally the first person to
read it because I got an early copy
um so I didn't
want to like air any of this out and like
you know when people get it in their heads
they're gonna read it that way like if anyone
listened to this podcast before reading the book
they're going to now read some of our criticisms
into it but uh but they'll also
read our more in-depth analysis
into it so you know
I just want to say that I'm uh
I'm immensely proud of you monkey
that you actually
wrote this book and published it yourself
and that you have an actual
like a real novel under your belt
that's amazing to me it's um
it's a thing that I haven't done and it's a
thing that I respect immensely far more
than any ridiculous retarded
YouTube video
of course
I would say this book
is the only thing I've ever made in my life
that I'm proud of like all the YouTube is
just like a fucking joke to me compared to this
thing
well that's nice
I'd say that just on a
I don't know a literary note I guess
this thing was an absolute page turner
and consumed it
uh voraciously
and and loved reading it and it was really
really good and
I read this book at night because
I was trying to read it before monkey got to my house
um incidentally
I read the entire book while non-stop listening
to slipknot corn and
Marilyn Manson um and I would
highly recommend you do the same so you can get into
the school shooter mindset but uh
I read the entire book listening to the
Stone Cold Steve Austin podcast
talking about wrestling
um and doing it for the working man
give me a hell yeah
I will say that I think the
early part
there's like this book has a lot of build up
and I do think it's probably
longer than it needs to be
um I think that the mid
section is the weak point when we
get to dawn working at the ice cream
place like up and like
when she gets locked in the freezer pretty much
everything from that onwards is
great like that's where the book really takes
off is after after she gets out of
the freezer and all of her schemes from then on
all of that is fantastic
um and the early part where the setting up
the characters is good but just that mid section
when she gets the job and she goes into so much
fucking detail about working there
I like had I not been trying
to finish the book that night I would have been at risk
of not finishing the book just because
I read books while I take a shit
a lot of the time I try to get through
like one chapter per shit and
if I read a whole chapter of just dawn
book and describe your workplace I would have been like
okay and my name is
Don Blackie I work at
Jerry Queen I like to be mean to people
and torture people I'm a really
smart girl
that's the whole book
I want the Jesse Wood audio
book of the Triforce
yeah that'd be great because that is Don's voice
at all times through all her narration
I wear pig socks because I'm
a girl
well fucking exposed
I
I wanted to say that I
yeah like I loved reading this
I tried my best to finish it
in one sitting but I am a genius
but I could not finish it in the four and a half
hours of my first flight so I took till I came
home from the trip I was on
it was wonderful I
was thoroughly entertained the whole way
I did not find
like I was
in hard enough by the point where she got to that
where I was totally willing
to take the journey that Don was providing
me of like exploring her workplace
because I knew that it was leading to something
and when the place burns down and you
get to think about all the details that she gave
us all going up in flames I enjoyed that
immensely and I don't know
maybe I had more patience or something for better or ill
I was I was disgusted
on deep levels but in the right
ways I was I was provoked
I was I was made to think about
real things and I'm a very
I don't know very like issues driven kind of guy
and you really presented things in a way that
that that that as you've
shown that you're quite capable of doing
you know really made me think
about the real issues going on here behind
the scenes not just a fucking
puff piece about school shooters now cool
they are you really got down to the
deep issues and I could it seemed
to me that a
lot of it came from
you know that not to go
crazy with conspiracies here but like
like you you really understood
you know like the the the motivations that would go
for a character like Mario
and and the way they're able to construct this
you know not not like a complete rip off
of Elliot or anything but like this new character
you know having all the
just a real clear understanding
of why someone would be driven at this point
I thought was fascinating especially as someone
who has probably never had anything
close to clinical depression for me
it was a very educating experience
to just kind of dive down into this world
and see what it's like down there and
to to I don't know maybe
hopefully be able to use this experience
to do what I think you want people
to take away think about how to actively
avoid this shit in the future
and see what we can do but
that's that's where I'm at it was great
loved it to summarize my thoughts
I mean I think this is a really
impressive book and piece
of work especially for having been written
by a fucking 20 year old
because again
I get inundated with people sending me shit
they've written all the time I usually can't make it
past the first paragraph or the first page
this is from people who you know
tout themselves as writers like
people who really think oh my god
this is what I'm gonna do and I love writing
and they send me something and it's bullshit
you know I expected it to not be
shit because your videos aren't shit
but when I was started reading it I didn't expect
to be like hooked and actually want to read
the whole thing and I did
you know it's obviously
it's interesting if we could get this much fucking
conversation out of it which is more than I could say
for a lot of stories and
you know
I had a good time I would say
you know weak parts aside it's still
a really interesting book lots lots to
relate to lots to connect with and
for what it's worth I'm extremely excited
to see where you'll go later because
writing unlike any other
medium is not something that anyone
is a master at young
there's never been
a like world famous author
who got world famous
before their 30s like everyone
has to work up for that
what about the famous author
Harry Potter
his series of autobiographies
sold up trillion copies
I think the only outlier would be
Essie Hilton who wrote
The Outsiders when she was like 16
but otherwise you're pretty much right
yeah authors never blow up huge
when they're young it's one of the only mediums
where like you really have to study at it
for for a long time and so
to be putting out something impressive
enough that three
relatively harsh critics mind you
are I mean
I at least I'm a relatively harsh critic
if this was interesting you'd know
yeah you would definitely know
I'd let you know so to have written that at
20 I can't wait to see what you will
be writing by the time you are 30 if
you're still writing fiction
and if you still have ideas that are at
least you know half as interesting as
this one
I can only assume you'll get better as a writer
as time goes on so yeah
you know I think I'm with didgy
on the fact that I think simplicity might be key for your next
work so when you're writing that and you say goodbye
cruel world and you're heading out to that rope
hanging in your closet that
you know just just leave it at that you know
just leave it at that
what
kill yourself I'm saying kill yourself
that's what I'm saying it's my next big magnum
but it's your suicide
that's what I'm kidding that's the joke
that's the joke okay good
bam closer
nailed it I think we should all agree
that next week we'll come back together
and review that anime snobs
book in the same way
someone should
read that and let me know how it is though
I was told it's an autistic version
of dune
that sounds like what you would write
so I'm not surprised at all by that
when did he write this when did he write it
like a year ago
oh we should have had him on this right now
to review the book what were we thinking
did he read it
I came in for the last part of the podcast
he's never going to read it because I won't send him
a pdf
what a piece of shit
well
so long
go buy the triflers on the link in the description
if you haven't read it yet and you'd like to
um
written by monkey jones
we're proud of it
and we're not just saying that
and maybe someday
we can be proud of him too
yeah
that's the whole point of my life
is to make my parents proud
I haven't done it yet but hopefully someday
well here's hoping
thanks for listening everybody see you next time
bye