Sword art online doesn't even make sense. I mean, it's online, yeah, but there's sword
art. Like, I always thought it was when I saw the dojins of sword art online, I thought,
uh, how do you fuck a sword? Like, why did the people draw sword art? And obviously it's
online, it's on dojinmoe.com. Like, what, what, why do you call it online? Why do you,
and it's art, yeah, but the sword, I don't get it, and I didn't get it. And then I heard
that there was an anime called Sword Art Online. I was like, oh, it's inspired by the, it's,
it's characters from the anime called Sword Art Online. And I just kept thinking, like,
what a stupid name for a thing to be sword art online. I mean, what could it be about?
Could it be about an artist? Oh, wait. Oh, sword art, like the art of sword swinging.
Couldn't you call it like blade fucking guy, blade nigger two, blade nigger attacks them,
you know? I mean, he wears black. Uh, welcome to the first in a 48 Pot series on why sword
art online sucks. Oh, here's pot one, the everything. Pot one, the everything, everything
sucks. There's a guy, and there's a girl, and there's a boy, and there's a girl, and there's
a woman, and there's a boy, and there's a guy, and then they're all homosexuals. Nothing
wrong with homosexuals, but I hate them. Oh, here's a lot of, a lot of, a lot of all
that stuff and sword art online. And it will fetch me my tin crumpets, just me, just me,
just think of it as, I just love a tin crumpet, swine me with a polka.
That's enough tin crumpets, and back to the review. Part two, sword art online.
It's not good.
Part three. No. No more. This ends now. I've never seen sword art online. I've never seen
Attack on Titan. I've never seen Full Metal Alchemist Brotherhood. I always thought Full
Metal Panic was part of that series, and I got confused. I'm like, which do I watch first,
Full Metal Alchemist or Full Metal Panic? I hate things that have things that aren't numbered,
but it wasn't even part of the same fucking show. I mean, people, you act like you're supposed to be
liking anime? Well, it's hard, okay? It's all confusing. It's dumb, and I don't get it. I mean,
Crunchyroll doesn't even work. I go there, and I'm looking at it, and I'm like, typing in fucking,
I don't know what I'm looking for. How do you get into new things? How do you get to a point
in your life where you're looking at new anime? What are you fucking gay? Just stick with what
you know. I watched so much Naruto, and then Naruto Shippepa do it in, and fucking it was all
right, but I couldn't bring myself to do anything else. And I wonder why that is. You know, you're
seeing a new thing, you're like, you know, when you're a little boy, and you're on anime,
anime stream, I don't fucking know, anime, lovelyanimateplace.com, and you see the top ones,
you see Naruto, you see One Piece and Bleach, and you're like, oh, people at school talk about
Naruto and Bleach, and you watch him. The asshole, but you don't realize that it's fun,
but you do it because you want to fit in. Like, I remember one guy saying, do you even know Naruto?
Like, I was pretending I did, because I'm one of those, you know, I just one of those moments
where you just say something, and he said, do you even know Naruto? Do you know Shikomaru?
And I'm like, uh, do you even know Zabusa? I'm like, do you even know Itachi?
I'm sorry, I'm very sorry. I don't know that dude. I guess I don't know it at all. And then
they killed me. They stuffed me in a bunch of trash, a bunch of rubbish, a carcass.
Yes. I was. What a carcass I was as they rolled me down the hill in a trash bin.
And I thought to myself, well, I really need to impress those guys. So I watched Naruto.
I want a rocks. Many rocks. What does he want to do with them? I want a rocks.
My Japanese man. What does he want to do with the rocks? I want a rocks.
You want to rock or you want to rocks? Oh, many rocks.
Well, the way.
You may realize that this is stupid and it's deliberately so.
See if I see it deliberate, then it's okay.
I, I don't appreciate your time and which is why I'm spending it doing nothing.
This is going on the procrastinators channel. It's a podcast now. It's suddenly now a podcast.
The Gibbon show where nothing is quite right. Now that I'm doing a show, it's time to fill the air.
I need to fill my lungs with air.
Delicious air. Doesn't it feel great to just take a big whiff of air, even though you don't need it?
It sounds funny too. It sounds funny.
Hey, let's, let's look at my DS. Let's do an impromptu game review of whatever I have on my DS.
Oh, it's Pokemon moon. All right. Here's a sneak peek of my game of the year video.
In fact, this is my game of the year video. I'm going to slip this bit out of,
I'm going to put this bit out of this video and put it into my video because I don't, I don't like,
I don't like you. All right. I wrote down some notes from Pokemon moon. Let's go to the mind of
my notes. Oh, where is it? Oh yeah. Pokemon moon. Pokemon moon is fine. The main point I have,
it's a, it says good for a Pokemon game, which means it has the staples. Cool Pokemon, uncool
Pokemon, battling, catching, bad guy gang, roots, towns, poker centers, boring characters and towns,
people, status effects, Zubat and others. But it's slightly better than the normal staples
because they have interesting characters. They got the edgelord and a goofy troop of loopy dukes
and their loopy king and the insane woman who I can imagine is actually very scary to young
children. So that's good. You know, it's always nice to know that children are scared. Then there's
the punching bag and the professor who's not a nerd and the girl and popcorn. And that's it.
That's my Pokemon moon review. You know, if I had a beer bottle, I would jangle it just to make,
give you the illusion that I was drinking, but I don't have a beer bottle. I do have these things
or cards I keep dropping on the table. That's what the cards were. That's what that was. I'm not
even starting to begin to make like a good video podcast, but you're still here, I guess. Hey,
you ever know these sunglasses that I have? Here's what they sound like.
They're sunglasses. They're very plasticky. They're very, very plasticky.
That's it. That's my sunglasses ASMR section of the video. Now we've got to have a,
we've got to have, oh, look, listen to this, listen to this shit. All right. In my hand is a special
button. It is a button that will tell me and you that we are a badass and it will give us confidence.
And this is a real thing and I'm about to press it. Here we go. Do what you love.
Do what we love. All right. What else do you want? What else wisdoms do you have?
You create your reality.
All right. Feed fear, a sucket, sandwich, sandwich.
You are a badass.
I've never been so insulted in all my life. I know my mom didn't give this to me
because she thinks I'm insecure. She just had it. I mean, she says that, but she's given me
like self-help books before because she thinks I'm still as depressed as I was when I was 17,
which isn't true. How fucking patronizing can you fucking be?
It's unbelievable. Zero, zero out of 10 on product. It came, hang on, it came with,
it came with this book. You are a badass mini book and it's not a joke. This is,
oh my God. I was about to say this is as sincere and patronizing as it can possibly be.
The guy who wrote it is called Jen Sincero. S-I-N-C-E-R-O. Jen Sincero. Okay. Maybe it is a joke.
How could it be not a joke? Jen Sincero. I'm assuming you're reading this that there,
because you're reading this, there are some areas of your life that aren't looking so great
and that you know you could be doing looking a whole lot better. This book is about getting
mighty clear about what makes you happy and what makes you feel the most alive and then creating
it instead of pretending you can't have it or that you don't deserve it or that you're a greedy
ego, maniacal fathead for wanting more than you already have. I guess it is a joke. I mean,
maybe it's like, I assumed that it was like talking like, oh, we're a self-help book and we're,
you know, you're not that bad, you're great, you know, but, and it is saying that it's the whole
book about, like, number one, appreciate how special you are. Number two, drown yourself in
affirmations. Number three, ditch the self-deprecating humor that this is the sort of stuff. Oh, let the
love in. Oh, forgive yourself. Don't compare yourself to others. I guess, no, this is very
sincere. Love yourself. It's a sincere self-help you book by written by someone with a bit of
self-awareness, but not enough. Like that they can say, stop calling yourself an ego maniacal fathead
because you're beautiful. I'm so mad at how fucking stupid this is. Do what you love. No,
well, I will, but shut up. I don't want to do it because you told me to, you fucking idiot.
You create your reality. You create your reality. What does it say?
Feed fear a sucket sandwich. A sucket sandwich, sandwich. Fuck it. Oh, oh, unacceptable.
That was terrible. Sorry for that. Sorry for that. Lemon. I can't do lemon.
How to tap into the motherload, the G word. Hang on, what? Wherever you happen to stand on the
God issue. Let me just say that this whole improving your life thing is going to be a lot easier if
you have an open mind about it. Call it whatever you want. God, God ass, the big guy, the universe,
source energy, higher power, the grand poo bar, gut, intuition, spirit, the force, the zone,
the force fuck off, the zone, the Lord, the vortex, the motherload. It doesn't matter. Whatever
you choose to call it is important. What is important is that you start to develop an
awareness of and a relationship with the source energy that's surrounding you and with you and
with you and you. We enjoy the same engine. We should give you the best pale air if you give it
a chance because you think all of us are connected to the limit of this power and some of us aren't
being a fucking, a fucking, a fucking, a fucking hippies. Oh, meditation 101, basic meditation
Fuck you. You make me feel, you make me feel, you make me feel like an actual retard,
retard. Oh, love yourself. Surrender for people who, this is like a training guide for fucking
sheltered social justice warrior people. Like, I'm reading this one thing. It just,
it just gives me that idea that people who turn to this weird way of thinking are usually very
self-conscious. Surround yourself with people who think the way you want to think.
That's a, that's a thing they say. You've got to surround yourself with like-minded people.
Obviously makes sense in theory, but like, you go too far with it and you're in a fucking hug
box. You're in a, you're in an echo chamber. You're thinking about a lot of the same, oh,
I'm sorry I'm going on about this. It's just, I don't feel any reason to keep this stupid
You are a badass button. So, and this book, so I'm reading it now just to get it out of my life.
I don't ever want to return to it. Number five, love yourself. You deserve it. I really am,
I think it's got to be a joke. Really, what it is, is that I press this thinking,
it's going to be like, whoa, cool dude, you're a badass, guitars and explosions, you know,
something cringy, but something like, something harmlessly cringy, like, dude, whoa, radical,
you're cool. Yeah, bro, but it's just this sort of sounding American lady saying sincere and very
patronizing bullshit. How to get over your BS already. Procrastination and perfection.
Procrastination is one of the most popular forms of self-sabotage because it's really easy. I mean,
I get it, I agree, but I hate that you are saying it. I fucking hate you. I want you to die.
Blah blah blah. Because it's not like I don't know how to stop procrastinating, it's that
knowing it is not half the battle, knowing it is like one percent of the battle.
Doing it is the hardest part and it's the entire part.
How to kick some ass.
I really want to burn this book. It's worth it. It annoys me just like,
what annoys me the most is that the idea that somebody would buy this for somebody
and somebody would actually have a use for it, like they would, they would press the button
and feel better. Like that is the saddest thing I could possibly imagine.
Like if you need that in your life to get through, like I can imagine someone on the
brink of suicide and there's someone like, oh he's depressed, I should get him this and he presses it
once and he just, like it's just, I would commit suicide after hearing that.
After hearing this button being pressed, I would just crumple in a heap and like, oh it's not worth
it anymore. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That was my OC dog. I don't know, he's a furry. He's gay, he's a gay furry.
So when it comes to like podcasts and stuff, usually I have a topic and a theme and or a
topic and a theme and like a thing of consciousness, a stream of consciousness,
which is what this is, this is a stream of consciousness and it doesn't have any guests
and this is a one-time podcast. It will never happen again ever. I will never make another
podcast because I have integrity. I don't want anyone to know that I did this,
which is why I'm putting on the internet for the cheap laugh and a cock in my buttock.
Just one though. I'm just looking at things on my desk that seem like, what can I fucking
talk about? I've got a camera over here, I've got a camera over there, I've got a fucking
piece of paper. Oh boy, let's talk about a piece of paper. You know, guys, we've got a piece of
paper here, let's hear it. That's not a piece of paper, that's a pad of paper. Yeah, you thought
you were just listening to a piece of paper? You've got a whole pad, pad of paper here.
It's a bunch of sticky notes. And that's that. I don't stick them anywhere, I just write on them.
Sheesh. Are you still here, you idiot? You dumb idiot?
I can't believe you even, even in the background. Like, why would you put this on in the background?
You'd be like, ha ha, Gibbs talking, lol, hippos being a silly boy.
And then you think it's buffering because like, I had silence. Because you're not looking at it,
you're like, oh, what happened? What was he saying? Did something happen? No, I just tricked you.
You're fucking, I got you.
I mean, part of me thinks, oh, this is awful, I'll never put this up, but part of
me loves it, part of me loves how terrible it is. Hey, look, we've got a magic eight ball.
Magic eight ball is something I associate with Risker, but also with Toy Story,
because it's the thing that Woody shakes and he's like, I fucking hate Buzz Lightyear and he says,
yeah, you do, or something. And it's like integral to the to the fucking buzz getting knocked out of
the room. And it's what a weird scene that is. Like, I always thought that it was really unnerving
because of it's a sunset, but it's like really harsh lighting in dark areas. And
and it's not really, it's not really clear what time of day, like, it's not really clear what
everyone's thinking. Like everyone's sort of like they're sleeping their toys. It's weird. It's a weird,
like the very end of a sunset sort of lighting, but it's darker than that. And it's all about Woody
conspiring with the with with hatching a plan to get Buzz fucking lost.
What a great movie. You know, I don't I don't care what people say about like dated CG.
Because like CG, I like old CG games. You know, it's only dated in the
that they try to make realistic humans. And you can obviously make realistic humans a lot better now.
But the toys, they all look perfect. Because they're toys. I mean, that's probably part of the
reason why they made it in 3D. Like, oh, we can't we got this new technology. But how the fuck do
we make a whole bunch of characters? It's going to be a nightmare. It's like, I don't worry,
just make them toys, just make it so that you don't have to animate their body parts moving
and breathing and all that shit. And it's like, perfect. We got it. Toy Story is great. What do
I mean? Shrek. Shrek's a good movie. Shrek 2 is one of the greatest 3D animated movies.
If you don't believe me, do you think it's just a meme? We'll just remember the Billy Maze was a
meme and he was fucking amazing. Michael Rosen's a meme and everyone loves Michael Rosen. He's
actually a very good children's entertainer. People make fun of what they like. You know,
you don't see many YouTube poops with Pootie Pie in it. Maybe a couple to ride the thing,
ride the train of hype when he was like beginning to be a thing that people would search for.
Shrek's good. I don't know about the B movie. The B movie doesn't look good, but maybe it is.
Shrek's good. I mean, the third one was, you didn't need to make the third one and the fourth one
was kind of like, come on, you've done it. You've finished. Actually, the ending of the third one
is pretty cool, but like, I think the second one is really the peak. First one's pretty great.
Second one, the best. Kung Fu Panda as well. Kung Fu Panda movies, I don't know. Nate, for some
reasons, seems to think that Dreamworks is all shit. And I don't know why. I guess he just like,
he just had that opinion from some experience and he's not willing to give any other Dreamworks
movie the time of day, like Madagascar 1. It's all right. You know, I don't know whether it's great,
but they're all great children's movies at least. But like, Kung Fu Panda 1 and 3, I haven't seen 2,
I should, because I've seen the ending of 2 and it looked great. But 1 and 3, they're really good
movies. Like, such action. You know, I like Kung Fu Panda 3 more than The Force Awakens.
Don't know what that says about me. I went, I went to see both of them in the theaters,
which is why I make that comparison. Because I don't go to see things in the theaters ever.
Like, this year, I don't think I went to see anything. What movies came out?
Obviously, I haven't gone very recently. No, I haven't seen a single movie this year.
Not one. Not a single movie that came out this year I have seen this year. That's one of the
things I've noticed. Like, people are making of the year, of the year lists of things like movies
and albums and stuff. And I'm like, I'm just rediscovering or rather discovering
stuff from when I was a kid, because that's what I like. I don't like new things.
Not that I don't like new things, but like, new things often are uninteresting.
Like games. Like, modern games. This is like a thing that people have said for a long time now,
but it still holds true for me. Like, modern games do not interest me at all. If it's big
budget, then it means it's a big no-no. On principle. Not on principle, actually, but
well, yeah, on principle. If it costs a lot to buy and it has a lot of DLC and it's one of those
pre-autobonus bullshit things, I will never purchase it. I will pirate it if I want to,
but I will never purchase it if it has all that bullshit. If it's just a game that comes out,
like The Witcher. I think I bought The Witcher 2 because I heard that it was a great game made by
great company. And if my computer could run it without exploding, then I would have played it, but
I don't purchase things that are bullshit. And so much of modern games is bullshit,
and so much of the console scene is, like, gone. Like, all my favorite characters have been
discontinued and replaced with white, boring people. That's right. That's right, I went there,
they're white. You ever thought why Uncharted sucks? Because it's not a black woman
with a dick and and three genders that change depending on what hour you're playing the game.
And it also changes the dialogue. Ooh, that's interesting. That's interesting. That's a stupid
way to make an interesting mechanic that changes about stuff. Depending on what time of day you're
playing the game, stuff is different. That's a cool concept. Too bad, no one cares.
But yeah, like Ratchet and Clank, Sly Cooper, Spyro, Crash, they sort of died before the end
of the PS2 era, but like, you know, these characters, these colorful cartoon characters,
they just got fucked in the butt. Ratchet and Clank continued for a bit,
but Tools of Destruction was not interesting because it ended on a cliffhanger and it
suffered from what I like to call, fuck you, syndrome, where it's like
the first three Ratchet and Clank games, the first one was made and it was a complete game.
That was it. You played it, that was the Ratchet and Clank one. The sequel, same shit. You know,
even though they probably knew they were going to make Ratchet and Clank 3, they made Ratchet and
Clank 2 and it was completely, perfectly its own thing. You could play one or two, you didn't have
to play both. And then you got Ratchet and Clank 3, which is the same sort of thing. It
borrows elements from one and two, but you can play it on its own. It is, from start to finish,
a complete thing. Ratchet and Clank Tools of Destruction, the first game on the PS3,
was a cliffhanger ending game, which means it wasn't a complete thing, which means they were
planning to make another three games. And obviously, once you plan to make another three
of anything, the certain parts of, like, each individual thing becomes less, like the Hobbit
movies, you know, if they just thought, let's make the Hobbit movie. I mean, when you're making,
like, Lord of the Rings, each one is a whole book, fair enough. The book has a beginning and an ending,
but it will continue, but it's not like ending on a cliffhanger that's unsatisfying. So each film,
similarly, does not end unsatisfyingly. Everything that happened in the book is satisfying that it
completes itself, but it could still continue. The way the Ratchet and Clank did it was like the way
that they did it in the Star Wars prequels, or the Hobbit. The Hobbit, not so bad, but it's pretty
bad. Like, they had the dragon at the end of the second movie, but it didn't actually really happen
until the third movie. You've got to see him die at the, just the beginning of the third movie.
And it's all, it's marketing. It's not actually a film that feels complete in itself. It feels like
you have to watch all three at once, or at least the second and third at once. And it's just dumb.
And the prequel trilogy of Star Wars, did I say the Star Wars? I just said the prequel trilogy.
The Star Wars prequel trilogy was like the first movie was like introducing Anakin. The second movie
was nothing at all. And then the third movie was like the actual important part. Like, they had
three movies and like 13% of all three movies put together was actually a movie that was important
or interesting at all. And it's like you,
they're not satisfying for a very, a lot of reasons, but like the element that I find,
and I'm referencing here is that they don't feel complete in and of themselves. Maybe the first
one does. I'm not, I'm not sure about that. I can't really remember. Like, they do kind of like,
at the end is like, yeah, the droids are dead. Hooray. It feels like the end of a new hope.
It could continue, but right now they won. The second movie is like,
the point I'm getting at is that Ratchet and Clank died to me because the first PlayStation 3 game
was a cliffhanger that was completely unsatisfying. And I didn't like the characters or the story
that much. And I didn't like the extra mini content to do that much. And I was like, why the fuck
would I buy the next games if this one wasn't good? And so I never did. I never bought the PS3
trilogy of Ratchet and Clank. And I'm sure a lot of other people felt the same, which is why the
Ratchet and Clank is not the main thing. You know, if Insomniac had come up with a better idea than
the fucking glowy blue red asshole infamous guy that, you know, that they would actually have
a game series to talk about to make the next gen thing. Like, if infamous was not crap and boring
and disgustingly shit and blue and red, then they might have stopped making Ratchet and Clank and
made their own thing, like Naughty Dog Dig with Uncharted, which is all right. I don't like it
more than Jack and Daxter, obviously, but I don't begrudge it too much. It's okay.
You know, I feel sometimes I feel like I should play all of them. I have them.
It's like the PlayStation 2 thing, like everything that was cool about it, all the
cool series that started and ended. And then the PlayStation 3 comes out with my favorite game
companies coming up with boring shit that I didn't care about at all. It just, you know,
there was no equivalence of my favorite games like Okami and Dark Cloud.
And I will say Dark Souls is probably like the best thing to come out on that sort of
Demon Souls on the PS3, but then Dark Souls was on the PC and I obviously would go there instead.
Bloodborne I have on PS4, but Dark Souls 1, 2, and 3 are on PC and I have them on there.
But like modern games aside from Dark Souls are boring and I don't like them ever.
I just don't like them. Every single time a thing comes up,
it's like whatever. Final Fantasy, I was never into it. You know, that's another thing. That's
unrelated to modern games being shit. It's just like fan things coming back like Ghostbusters,
never saw it. Final Fantasy, never played it. You know, remakes and I pressed the space bar
and I stopped recording. Reboots and remakes and stuff. There's just an ocarina of time on the
3DS or Majora's Mask on 3DS or like anything. Any big thing that has come back in like a fan way
and people like making a big hubbub about it. That's never happened for anything that I like ever.
I can't, I cannot recall a time where something has been remade or rebooted that I was into
aside from maybe Ratchet and Clank, which was a tie into a movie, but it was sort of,
there was no fanfare around it. Nobody really cares. I think that's just the thing. Like I'm in
that generation that was a little after all the classics like Mario and Zelda and Metroid,
Nintendo things, and then, you know, the PS1 games like Spyro and Crash Bandicoot and Conkers
Bad Fur Day and Banjo Kazooie and Super Mario 64 and Diddy Kong Racing and all those, you know,
ocarina of time. Everything that all the kids in the 90s were talking about, that's all coming back
now and the stuff that I'm into has yet to come back and it will eventually and all the people my
age, my generation who care about PS2 rather than PS1, they're all just not interested in anything
because there's nothing that's appealing to them. And it's a shame because it's like anything new
that's coming out has so much fanfare about it. You think about like a new game comes out and then
instantly there's porn of it. There's porn of it everywhere. You can just find every character
in every situation possible. Porn everywhere. Everywhere you go. Anywhere you want. Any character.
Pokemon Moon, like five seconds after it's released, there's porn of every character in the
whole game. Undertale, porn of everyone all the time. That's how I judge like the fan content
because I don't care about really anything else. But like when you think of like PS2 games,
I'm not sure whether I would look at Ratchet and Clank porn actually, but supposing I did,
there's not a lot of it. I don't think I've looked, but there probably isn't a lot. I have
looked at Carmelita Fox. There's a bit of that because she's a furry. But there's not a lot of
it. Like it's in that time where before it came out, before artists were making fan content of
that about stuff. So it's before the internet really was becoming big. But it's too late after
the classics because every time anybody wants a big, making a big art piece, they're like, oh,
I'll draw fucking Samus. And everyone knows Samus not only just because of Metroid, but also because
of Smash Brothers and stuff like that. Like you draw a character that was really old and has continued
to be there. Or you draw art of characters that were, you know, just, just before, you know,
Super Mario 64 stuff, fan content of that. Like there's mods of all that stuff. There's like crazy
modding communities. You all know Pan and Koic, right? Those guys, him and his buddies, I don't
really know what they're called again, the ABC crew. It just feels like, it feels like it's,
it's unfortunate because like there's old stuff and then there's new stuff and then there's the
stuff I'm into and it's all ignored by the internet in general. And I am mad about it to a certain
degree. I don't really care too much about seeing porn of my games that I like. I only brought that
up because I was thinking of Kamalita. All right? You know, some furry porn's all right.
It's just tits with fur on it. You just forget the fur is there. They didn't really draw it furry
anyway. They just draw it colored. It's like there's a boob and it looks like a normal person's boob,
but it's orange. Okay. It's a rabbit boob or a fox boob. They don't have a tail, but they otherwise
are human. What am I saying? You create your reality. I sure do. Idiot.
I just went on rants about things.
Oh, the podcast never ends and it will always remain directionless. It's the sort of thing
you would put on in the background, but you need to listen if you're trying to figure out
what I'm doing, saying and such. Since I'm in a dour mood, let's talk about a dour topic. Videos.
I don't want to. I don't want to do it. Videos suck. They're okay.
But, you know, they suck.
I'm making a game of the year. What the date is today? The 28th? All right. Well, I can't do it.
It's the end of the 28th. I've got to record me talking about Pokemon Moon and Dark Souls 3.
I've already talked about Pokemon Go. Those are the games of the game of the year.
I want to talk about all three of them in a game of the year video.
And I got to do it all at 29th and the 30th and the 31st. I'm glad there's a 31st.
Maybe I can do it, but, you know, and I don't want you to just say, oh, you can do it. Shut up.
That's also patronizing. It's like coming out to a wheelchair guy and saying,
don't worry. I still think you can walk.
There's nothing like that.
I know I can do it. You idiot. It's not like I really, really love you to say,
you, I feel sympathy for you.
If you're having trouble trying to do something, then whatever.
Everyone is. I think it's a bit redundant to say, oh, you know what, dude? I know how you're feeling.
I got stuff I want to do and I'm trying to do it and it's not working out so well.
But you know what? You just got to keep doing it and that's what you got to do.
And I'm like, I get it. I know. Thanks. Thanks for trying to help, but you're really boring.
You're really normal. You're really just wasting time.
You know, the amount of time you spend trying to cheer others up could be better spent being a cool guy,
making your own things and then using that to entertain them, just like what I'm doing.
You know? I mean, sure, if you made a podcast about complete bullshit, nobody would listen to it
if you didn't have a fan base already like I do. I'm not saying make a stupid podcast.
What I am saying is I'm an asshole who's telling you to not give me good feelings because...
Suck it, my dick.
I put two slices of bread in between my penis. Wait, no, how do you do that?
You two put your penis in between your slices of bread and then the magic happens.
Welcome to the close-up. Welcome to the close-up part of the show where I'm really close and I'm saying
Radio Shade, over and over.
Shit.
This isn't a decompression chamber more than it is an exhaustion tube. I was really
so tired that I couldn't move and I made a podcast right now.
Talking into a mic has helped me stay awake but now I'm tired again. Whoops, I should have just
started talking about bullshit, then got into an excited state and then used that to work on
something but instead I tried to make a podcast that kept going and going and here it is keeping
on going and now I'm tired again and I can't do it.
Let's see what's going on in the discord chat.
Mage is there talking about Sword Art Online. What are you doing?
You are a badass.
I can't even do a sentence.
There's anything to have been gained from this. It's that you wasted your time but more importantly
that you wasted it with me and I idiot.
I just want to play video games, dude.