It's time for another PCP interview! It's been God knows how long since the last one, I don't remember.
Like a year and a half at least, right?
Yeah, they were all done relatively within a reasonable time frame of each other, and they're not ever again.
And then I think Nate and Mumkey had one, but now it's your turn.
Yes.
And you're fucking who are you, motherfucker?
I'm Tom Oliver, and I do 3D stuff mostly now.
Tommy Oliver Says.
On Twitter.
Tommy Oliver Blogs.
On The Tumblr.
Tommy Oliver, what's your Instagram?
It's PaulieState2.
Yeah.
And then YouTube is Tommy Oliver Says.
C slash Tommy Oliver Says.
Anything happening on Facebook?
Not yet, but I'm definitely gonna move there eventually.
I consider you sort of like, the reason that I think you're like a very underappreciated valuable asset to the PCP in a backroom sense that maybe even viewers wouldn't appreciate is that you know social media,
like you know what's big, you know what's hot, you know tech, why? Why don't you know all this shit?
I'm just really interested in it. I've just been interested in technology for my entire life.
Like being a little kid when I was like, I got a Game Boy for the first time and like, can I make this do anything else besides play games?
Like I was just really fascinated.
Like I'm like, I'm super addicted to cell phones, but I wanted a cell phone before cell phones existed.
Like I was the kid in like seventh grade who had no like actual life, but got a PDA.
Just thought it was cool to have a computer in my pocket.
So everyone else, like everyone else was listening to iPods and stuff and I got a PDA and like got an SD card and put music on that,
but also like could play little video games and could do like things.
And I was like, super interested in like the Dell Pocket PCs.
They had like the little Wi-Fi dongle you could plug in and shit.
This is so cool.
Did you actually use your PDA to do like playing, like planner shit?
Like did you actually keep schedule on it?
I mean, I didn't have a schedule, but if I did, I would have put it in there.
Cause I, I never went for anything like that cause I am so bad at like,
I love writing in a planner, but I never look back at it.
You know what I mean?
Like I love writing a list of what I'm going to do today and then I never look at it.
When I do it though, it's super effective.
Oh my God, it can be.
If you fucking, like if you have scheduled time for videos and stuff and you can like pre-produce them ahead of time, that's like a huge boost.
My big thing, my hardest thing with production is that I can't start.
As soon as I start, I get in the rhythm and I'm fine.
But I will like sit for like four hours and be like, should I do something?
Oh yeah, that's the hardest.
I mean, once you're in it, the only thing that's going to push you out is if like,
you feel like this particular section is really soulless and you wish it wasn't even in your video, you know?
Like when you have those moments where you listen to a sentence and you're like,
there is no way to make this creative and fun to watch that I am capable of.
So I guess it's just going to be 30 seconds of footage from whatever show is relevant.
And that's when you want to get up and take a break and go outside and, you know.
Not exist anymore.
Exactly.
That's me for the entire editing process start to finish.
Because as soon as I get to that point, like I've been doing the Y3D anime fail series.
I did the first two.
It's been written out since, I want to say maybe August of last year.
I have like this huge document.
You read it.
You read the whole thing pretty much.
I sent it to you like a year ago.
Which document?
The Y3D anime fails like for each.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
That long ago?
It was a long time ago.
Oh fuck.
I didn't feel like that long ago.
Yeah.
And it just sits there because I don't want to edit it.
That video series.
What, how hopeful were you that that was going to be like a huge hit?
That one in particular, I didn't think was going to be huge.
I thought it was going to do way better than it did.
Yeah, I thought so too.
And I think that the only reason it didn't was like just, just didn't get spread around
enough.
And I honestly like, I kind of wished you had just made it one big video.
I mean, it probably just never would have gotten done if that had been the case.
Yeah, I'd still be working on it.
But like.
Originally it was going to just be one big video.
Yeah.
But I think the issue is that like because it's in smaller parts, people were like interested
but wanted to know more and then it took a long time before they learned anymore.
Here's the thing.
I think there's three things.
The first thing is that my channel is dead.
So like we just talked about how like only.
You should discuss that.
So explain this to me because this is something that, you know, YouTubers are always trying
to keep track of the algorithmic changes, Matt Petz, the only person who seems to completely
understand it, but he does not reveal all the whole consulting business around it.
So right.
So he's not going to just spill everything.
There's a lot of things we all know and that we all copy, but there's a lot of things we
don't know that we have to theorize about like my theory that my turntable channel won't
get promoted to music channels because it's only watched by my fans.
So like you told me about this part of the algorithm none of us knew about and it's apparently
happening to your channel.
I think it's happening to everybody's channel.
It's just like there's a lot of people complaining like no one's seeing my video or whatever.
And I found out, watching some videos, I've been doing a lot of research on Instagram because
I mean, I'm trying to use Instagram a lot now because I just like the platform.
I think it suits my current work pretty well.
But they have every, everything now has a set algorithm and how it kind of like filters
content and stuff.
And they were talking about how on Instagram, the algorithm on Instagram is that the most
crucial window for your content on Instagram is the first hour.
So depending on how well your content performs, how many likes it gets, how many comments
it gets in the first 60 minutes is how it ranks for the rest of time.
Cause most people when they open Instagram, just look at the first few things and then
check off.
So like if you, if you get a bunch of like traffic on your posts in the first 60 minutes,
it goes to the explore page and then it also can get ranked in the hashtags.
So like every hashtag on Instagram, it has the top nine posts for the day in the hashtag.
So if you do really well, you can get pushed to there and then everybody sees it.
And there's constant chances, not unlike Reddit, but unlike Reddit, it's, it is self-promotion
and not you having to like weirdly, circuitously only promote other people's content.
Another really interesting thing about Instagram is that the, uh, how big the account is that
likes your photo affects your photo as well.
So if you have like 500,000 followers and you like a photo at boost it, because what
it does is that, um, there's also the explore page.
So like if, um, it's kind of like the search function in Instagram, but before you search
for anything, it just shows you a bunch of content, it thinks you'll be interested in.
And that's based on who you follow.
So if you're an account that has 500,000 followers and you like my posts and I have
like 500, right, like a portion of your 500,000 followers will see the posts you liked in their
explore page.
Oh shit.
Is that how the, that's how Twitter works too with the likes then, right?
I think it's similar to that.
I think it has to do, I think on Twitter, it has to do with how many interactions you've
had with the person.
Like if you interact with them a lot, it shows you more of their likes or something or, or
if I don't know if like, I don't know what the fuck the logic is.
I haven't, I haven't looked into Twitter's algorithm all that much.
The only reason I don't even know about this YouTube thing is cause I, they mentioned it
in these Instagram videos, but for YouTube, it's not the first 60 minutes.
It's the first 24 hours and the first 24 hours only sends it out to 10% if you're following.
And depending on how well it does with that 10%, it'll either keep sending out to the
rest of your audience or drop it off completely and no one else will see it.
Clarify what does it mean your audience?
So your subscribers, so like it's, it's public and anybody who like searches for terms and
stuff can still see it, but it, you know how like cause, but will it be different?
Okay.
So I get the sense that, okay, I've never like not seen a video in my feed with the
exception of for some reason, exclusively super bunny hops channel.
And only this year, like will not give me every video he does, but everyone else always
has, but I think the reason is I only watch my subscriptions.
Like I consistently have for years only watched my subscriptions.
And even when I leave my subscriptions tab, most of what it recommends me is shit from
channels I'm subscribed to.
So I think maybe it just shows me, you're probably just cause you're a highly active
subscriber on all the channels you follow.
So it makes you're going to watch them.
And like the only times I ever, like for a very long time, I've had people who will show
up to my video and be like, huh, somehow missed this, didn't show up in my feed.
But like it would be only a couple of comments.
And like most people seem to see it and all the people who are regular subscribers
see it, but like the people in my discord, for instance, they are literally racing to
see who can publish my video in the discord first after it comes out.
So YouTube obviously is just going to recommend them everything in their feed.
But like, I think if you have an account that's not like that, maybe there's more of
a chance that it's, it's, you know, I mean, they keep it all close to the chest, obviously.
Right.
Cause someone like Nate, Nate doesn't even watch subscriptions.
Like he doesn't subscribe to channels.
He just goes to them occasionally when he wants to watch their videos.
Weird.
Yeah.
Why does he do that?
He just doesn't like use YouTube.
Like he doesn't like go there and, and go to the subscriptions tab and see what the
new videos are.
Like most people do, he'll go to trending and do that, or he'll go to like the
homepage and just like watch some recommended stuff.
But he mostly just, but I hate that I do it.
I hate, it just never recommends me anything I want to watch.
So I've, people have told me that if you do enough of the, like, I don't want to see
this button, it will eventually start to recommend you better stuff.
Cause like it takes enough out of your pool of what it thinks you want.
And, uh, but I'm scared that if I do that for some of the channels I'm subscribed
to, it'll just stop showing me that stuff in my subscription box.
So it's, it's a total clusterfuck.
Yeah.
I think that's one of the reasons that the videos didn't do well is because of the
10% thing and my entire channel is just dead.
And because not that 10% not enough of them are anime fans that they were going to.
So they're not going to click on it.
So it's not going to get seen by anything else.
Cause a lot of times, um, cause the first, I ran a Twitter poll trying to figure
out what the fuck's up with it.
So the first poll I ran was, have, do you know that I've been posting regularly
for the past 60, like, uh, like six months, 60% said no.
And Twitter is where I post on the daily.
So that's my most active people who know what I'm doing.
60% of them didn't even know I had uploaded.
Dude, I don't know if Twitter shows people all those YouTube links.
Cause like I've noticed that if I have a video,
why, why, because Twitter has an algorithm now too, like if you don't
turn it off, it does show best first instead of a chronological feed.
Yeah.
So it's the same exact thing.
I've, I've noticed that like my videos, cause I have all my channel set to just
auto tweet the videos and they come out cause I make videos fucking constantly
and I want to fucking just have them do that.
But, um, I've noticed that those never get very many likes or retweets unless
like there's a freak incident where someone retweeted it, maybe a few people will.
But if I like write out a tweet and put a link afterwards to the video, way
bigger chance that people are actually going to interact with it.
It's probably because Twitter, Twitter, I know Twitter actively doesn't like you
going to other platforms, especially Instagram.
I honestly think they're completely right to do that.
Cause there's lots of people on Twitter who the only reason I don't follow them
is too much shit is linked to their Twitter.
Like back in the day when everyone's Tumblr was linked to their Twitter and
you'd follow somebody and it would just be links to their Tumblr and I would
unfollow those people.
I know, I still follow some people who do that and it drives me insane.
The worst thing is like Tumblr has an image preview and you don't realize
it's Tumblr, so you just click, I want to see this picture and then it loads up
a page and I instantly back up because I don't want to wait the fucking
10 years for this to load.
Yeah, but like they, I know Twitter actively hates Instagram because it
doesn't, if you have an Instagram link, it doesn't show an image preview at all
because they don't want you going there.
So you have to like manually do all that shit.
But I know videos do really well on Twitter.
If like you post a preview of the video because Twitter is, everyone's
on the video kick right now.
So they want more video views on their platform.
So if you make, if you take like a 30 second clip of your, your video and then
you subtitle it.
So even if no one is, cause it's going to start auto-playing, but it's not
going to have any sound.
So if you can have subtitles that go with it so they can see what they're doing.
Yeah.
And then you have the link to YouTube to watch the rest of it.
That performs the best, but that takes, you know, fucking effort.
It takes a long time to make all those, but it, I mean, that's how the fucking,
that's how the Facebookers took over.
I mean, I know that for something, if I get back into video hardcore, I'm
going to do that.
You can just go on Fiverr and like five bucks, just like do it.
Well, like pay people to do it for you or something.
I've been, I've been looking on Fiverr a lot.
I have, so I've have someone right now on Fiverr actually like managing my
Instagram, it's not working very well.
But, but just, I'm just experimenting with shit.
How do you like, can you set up like recurring payments on Fiverr or are
you just paying him every time he does, whenever he does?
I paid him, it was, it was for, it was a 15 bucks for a seven day gig.
And he was like only five.
It starts at five, but it can go up to like hundreds of thousands of dollars
depending what the services are.
But, um, yeah, it's, it's, I originally went in there because I wanted
someone to edit my videos, but nobody offers video edits, like what I
would need done, like actually like, you know, you're not going to go on
there and find someone fucking Bangladesh and be like, can you like edit
in some footage from Hoseki, you know, Cooney, relevant in the narration,
talking about things like, what do you've, what?
No, you know, it's just, it's not going to happen.
So, oh, I think I might move this table forward and bring a couple of chairs
over here because this is uncomfortable as fuck.
What did you, what did you back like breaking up?
Yeah, but I, I hunch all the time.
So this is kind of like normal, like dealing with this pain.
So I'm kind of, I sit in like a fucking expensive office chair all day.
Well, well fuck you and your money.
Okay.
I can kind of deal with this.
We should, I can sit up.
It's fucking, this is real painful.
I'm going to get those chairs anyway.
You should talk about, um, tell me about your background in, uh, okay.
I'm just going to skip to what I'm interested in and hopefully the
audience will care too.
That's fine.
I want to know what everything about M dot strange.
Okay.
Cause this guy was like a huge influence on massive.
Yeah.
And especially now that you're doing 3D work, I think it's going to be
something that maybe is more important to talk about than it was before for you.
So, um, first of all, who the fuck is M dot strange?
Try to get these chairs.
Sure.
So M dot strange is a, uh, he's a YouTuber from like way back in the early days,
but he's been creating content for fucking ever.
Like he, he, you dig deep into his stuff.
He talks about like making short films and to edit them.
He busts out two VCRs and like cuts from one back to the other back and forth.
Like that's before that shit existed.
Like he got an iMac and like flipped his shit.
Cause now he can do digital editing.
So, so this was, he's been making shit forever out of fucking way.
But yeah, he's a, uh, he's now, he's a, he's doing game design, but when I got
into him back in 2006, he was, I was wondering what the hell he was actually doing.
Yeah.
He's, um, I kind of like him less now just because like everybody does game design.
Nobody makes fucking movies by themselves.
So like, I feel like it's like less cool, but whatever.
It's, it's still good.
Um, I found him in 2006 because this was back when, uh, when YouTube wasn't a
total clusterfuck and like the featured page actually had cool shit on it.
Yeah.
Do you remember when they had like the featured videos like on the front page?
Oh dude.
I mean, back in the early days, like YouTube was like Freddie W and Epic
Meal Time and like channels you watched cause they were hilarious and cool and
we're doing something like of a caliber that stuff that was like made sense to
be on YouTube, but was a caliber above what you expected from YouTube.
You know, like Freddie W's like call of duty in real life videos.
It's like, you can't make this with a professional film studio because like
it's fucking copyright infringement.
And like, and it's for gamers, a very niche audience who's mostly on YouTube,
you know, but like it made sense there and he did it so much better than what
you expect that it was like, whoa.
Yeah, that's crazy.
And M.Dot Strange, I'm assuming was part of that sort of era because his stuff
is unbelievably impressive.
So like the whole idea was because what M.Dot was at the time and why I got
into him is he's a 3D filmmaker and he does independent 3D animated films.
He did a trilogy of them in like under 10 years.
Probably how long are they there?
An hour and a half, two hours fucking crazy.
Yeah.
And so they're full 3D and he does all of them by himself.
Like he has voice actors and his second film.
He had someone do the music for him.
But other than that, everything they look like if Tim Burton did reboot.
Yeah, like it's a good way of describing it.
They're fucking crazy out there visually just all over the place.
The first film was actually, he didn't know enough about 3D to do a straight
up 3D film, so it's mixed media.
So there's stop motion, puppetry, 3D, 2D.
There's a bunch of clashing medias.
They just kind of like stitched together in laughter effects.
Kind of better comparison.
It looks a little bit like a 3D version of the Madoka Magica witch sequences.
Yeah, especially we are the strange is very, very much like that.
But this was like years before that.
It's still but yeah, he'd been making films like live action and like music and
stuff for, for, for, I think like the better part of two decades, even before
that even hit because he was like in his thirties when that started happening.
That's crazy.
And I love, I love hearing about people who didn't make it till their thirties.
Yeah, I know.
I still have hope.
Yeah.
So, so like, but like he went through a bunch of crazy shit and like he had
like a really messed up, fucked up childhood and like question to believe
because I've read like his books and stuff, like maybe like sexual molestation
and like crazy shit happened back in the day.
But he was doing like live action stuff and he would like dress up as like a robot
and go out and send Jose and like just do chip tunes on the side of walk.
Like as a guy named agent a two zero three is to look up that stuff
and like and just like had like a band just doing like this crazy stuff.
And then he would just like put out stuff on Craigslist.
Like we're shooting a movie this weekend.
You want to be in it?
Come show up and people would come just just make videos with random people.
And he like always had like this one homeless lady that he became friends
with in all of his videos and she was like kind of crazy.
Like he did this whole thing called the potato phone experiment with her.
He just carved the word phone into a potato and like put her in a public place
and just pretend you're on the phone and like make a scene and you record it.
So she's like going to like restaurants just talking to a potato.
That's fucking hilarious.
It's amazing.
The guy's a fucking genius.
But then he did like these three feature films all by himself.
And I was glued to his production diaries because he just like was cranking it out.
And he just like, yeah, I bought like five computers.
Is he rich or like no money come from like he just like he's just like got
like the he just saved up like five grand and just like doing what I think.
And when at that point, I think he was doing like wedding photography
or something like that or like making wedding videos.
So he had like professional cameras and you know, I don't know
because he doesn't talk at all about that side of his life at all.
Like multiple times when he's done like Q&A things, I've asked like, how do you live?
That's what I'm interested in.
And he always never, never, never says anything.
I think that's the hugest difference between like the way millennial artists
are willing to talk about themselves and like the previous generation.
Because like people like just above our age don't like to talk about how much
they make at all.
They don't like to talk about like, you know, who their influences are.
Like because they want to like people used to say, oh, I try not to have influences.
I want to be original.
And now everyone's just like, no, my influences are why I make any money.
You know, like nobody would have played fucking undertale if you didn't tell
people like, oh, it's like Earthbound.
But you know, it's good.
It's good for my birthbound and Homestuck combined.
Yeah, it's good stuff.
So well, I guess Homestuck is already Earthbound.
But whatever point point being like that.
Yeah, it's it's it's it's just like a difference in perspective.
And like for our generation, we grew up with YouTubers who will like
tell us everything about like ever since Game Grumps, you know, I feel like
it's been passe for YouTubers to talk about like, yeah, we make a career out of this.
And like, here's how good of a living we can have.
And here we went to Disney World today on the back of the fucking Game Grumps.
One episode of Game Grumps, you know, it's fucking crazy.
But but yeah, I mean, the guy, the guys, he's like open.
But like for some reason is just like how he makes money.
I almost feel like it's probably because like he doesn't want to admit
that like this doesn't make him a fucking ton of money almost,
even though it's painfully obvious.
I mean, why would it?
Like, I think the most like it's weird.
The most disturbing aspect of my entire life creatively was like when I was
like knee deep in like the pony stuff and I went to check on EmDot and I
realized I had more subs in him.
I like almost killed myself.
I was like, this is not like the world is fucked and we're never going to recover.
That was how I felt when I fucking passed any of the artists I liked.
Like I remember passing like the band Clipping.
I remember passing I passed like Chance the rapper in his early days.
Now he's huge.
But like, like, I mean, not even early days, like when acid rapid come out,
he was blowing up, but I blew up a little faster on YouTube at least.
Obviously not in like album sales or anything.
But yeah, I was passing a bunch of my favorite artists and I was like really
upset about it because I was like, these people are way better than me.
Like even at the time when I was making the pony content, I did not consider it
like great art.
You know, I was just like, this is just something I do because people are
willing to pay me for something I want to do.
Yeah, it was just a fun little distraction.
But it had turned into something.
Yeah.
And like it when it became like, OK, this is just a job now.
That was when it was like, we need to consider ending this, you know, regardless
of what it means for our careers, which I mean, God, could we still we could still
be making money if we were still pony people.
We could probably be making more.
I don't know because there's less people.
There's less people to go around.
Like you don't understand.
Like there is still a core fervent amount of people knee deep in that.
Like my buddy Matt, it's crazy.
He still does like art, like porn art for that.
And his YCH is like go for it.
Oh, you mean a deep pony?
Yeah, like three hundred fifty dollars for like a YCH.
And it's just like, oh, my God.
I mean, that's why a lot of those people are in there is they can't leave.
It's too lucrative.
Like it took my friend Fern a long time to like focus.
Like Fern had burned out on the show even before I did, but was still like in the
community because like when she posted original songs, they just wouldn't get
listened to, you know, like if it wasn't a poor song, no one gave a fuck.
That's the whole thing.
That community was like lucrative, but also insanely insular.
Oh, yeah.
Like they don't they literally don't care about anything else.
Like I would try to make videos when I, you know, first started making anime videos.
I was still making pony and I did like probably 10 anime videos and they all
had like barely any views compared to the pony shit.
Music videos, nothing, you know.
So they you you got to you literally have to sell your soul.
Like if you're still in pony, I'm sorry that you've had to lose that part of your soul.
Well, I mean, there are people who still genuinely love it.
Like I know some people who do.
Sure, I mean, more power to you, I guess.
Like I have no, no, I can't mock you for it because I was there for like three years.
Yeah, if you're still, I mean, if you like, I think it was hilarious when
Jesse and hippo started up the whore, the horsey whore.
What the fuck is the horse?
Because the pony cast, the pony cast, the pony cast was hilarious
because they just kind of like, like, hey, we got a new thing.
And it's just a podcast and it's got a Patreon.
They still make like a hundred dollars or two hundred dollars a month off of it or something.
And I was like, how is this possible?
Like back then we, we thought there was a minimum level of quality control
that we had to do in order for anyone to care.
And it turns out we were wrong.
We just needed to talk about my little pony.
It was, you know, I mean, not to knock that Jesse and Gibbon can do
an entertaining podcast deserving of money, but just the fact that like
they couldn't have made that much talking about anything else.
You know, it's insane.
It's funny because there was, it was like a couple of months
where I was talking with Matt D.V. again about starting after I had like
ended the last channel and I was like, wanted to make easy money.
I was like, what if I just made a whole new channel and uppitched my voice
and just talked about the new scene.
Dude, I've considered, oh, well, that wouldn't do with ponies,
but I've considered doing that plan like for other things.
Yeah.
Just like come back as a different guy.
My plan was like to uppitch my voice enough to make it sound like it was a woman
to like double down on like getting more money.
Oh, boy, that's fucked.
And then I would have.
You could do that.
I could still could.
Yeah.
It'd have been, it'd be very easy, but no.
I can't do it.
Sainter Minds prevailed.
The only reason I can't do stuff like that.
I one time wanted to make a manga review channel that was going to be
me, which a pitch foot with a pitch shifted voice.
And the reason is back when I was doing anime blogging, I had gotten so known
for like this particular style of like really abrasive and like incendiary
dialogue that I wanted to like reset my identity and have people like,
because I had made like several other blogs, but I just wanted people to not
know it was me and make like a polite character.
So my manga blog was like very polite and serious and like no one knew it was
me at all, but also it had very few readers.
But like, I would want to do that.
The funny thing is if I had done this pony channel, the exact opposite would
have happened.
I have no doubt that because the plan was, was insidious and genius.
It would have been girl, a pitch, the voice.
So no one would know me girl would have been very agreeable.
And that's what everybody wants.
They want you to suck the dick, the show's dick.
And then the piece de resistance would have been, never can show my face
because I was sexually abused and I don't want anyone to know who I am.
So you would have just fucking crushed on SJW money.
It would have been so good.
Oh, if you ever got found, oh, shit, the camera stopped.
No one can know my crime.
These are, thankfully, when you have a microphone and it keeps cutting,
it's real easy to sync back up.
That's true.
Yeah.
So well, obviously neither of us went through with those plans.
In my case, I realized that the cadence of my voice is too recognizable.
Like if I read off of a script, I always read it the same way.
And like no amount of voice morphing can make it like, not obviously me.
It's real sad, but you might have better odds because your cadence is not as
recognized.
Another thing I could have just done is paid $5 to some girl read it on fire.
That you could have done.
Yeah.
So, you know, but that would be a total evil scheme.
And the best part is you could get away with it and just never tell anyone.
Like you don't even have to tell us you could have actually done this.
Maybe I'm doing it right now.
Who knows?
Yeah, I said that he wouldn't be quite as like, you probably wouldn't be
begging for money on page.
I just keep the character gone.
It's fine.
So, all right, you were talking about M dot strange.
Yeah, you actually, you actually worked with them before, right?
I have worked with them a little bit a couple of times.
The first thing I mean, I didn't really work with them on this, but like
since I was glued to the production diaries on We Are The Strange,
she was like, all right, I'm going to need a bunch of extras.
So like send me your photo and I'll like fuck it up and like make you look
like a psychopath and you'll be in like a shot in this church scene.
So I was like, OK, and I'm in the church scene at the in the middle of the movie.
OK, yeah, that's the people find you.
Like if yeah, yeah, it's it's it's like it's a quick thing in a church
scene, but it's more like it's also in the end credits and it's pretty obvious.
So that that's I guess it's kind of scour the end credits for Tom Oliver
and We Are The Strange.
Before podcasting and like like like live streaming and stuff became a thing.
He did live streaming on something called blog talk radio.
Have you ever heard of that?
I've heard the name, but I don't know what it was.
What it was was that instead of like just talking live,
you would you would do a live stream on the Internet.
But instead of like having people call in.
Yeah, my phone's going off.
Someone's trying to fucking call me.
I'm trying to ignore it.
Oh, it's not a spam call.
I made the mistake.
I bought polystation2.com and I didn't get the domain protection.
So every day I get thousands of spam calls and like tons of what the fuck things
in my inbox saying, do you need web service?
I'm like, bitch, I make websites.
Don't don't don't get out of here.
But that's something I'm going to ask you about a bit.
But yeah, so what was I even saying?
Wasn't there something you worked on him with the head to do with mindless
self-indulgence? Yes, I did.
I did all the lip syncing for the characters in one of those
minus self-indulgence videos he did because he did videos for
minus self-indulgence and rabbit junk.
What songs?
Because I've never seen only one I've ever seen animal from that's from if, right?
I think so.
I don't even remember which fucking song that is.
It's an animal, it's an animal, it's an animal, I'm believable.
OK, that sounds familiar.
That might be from the, oh, you know what?
It's probably from the three heart album or the heart maybe the heart shape one.
I remember I did this during college.
So when I should have been doing homework, that's probably the album
that would have been coming out at the time.
Like 2010 ish 2008, 2009 ish problem.
OK, that's yeah, it's either from if or less than three.
I think it's if because less than three was like the short EP that came right
after that and I wouldn't recognize the songs as well on that.
In any case, so how do you do you think that like his style has influenced yours
at all because yours doesn't really look like his.
Your style is more like comic book.
Yeah, I wouldn't say he influenced my style in terms of like his artwork.
Like I think I'm more interested as much as I love his movies.
I'm much more interested in him as a person and his work ethic.
Yeah.
Because I just what I really liked about him back in the day and to this day
is that he's like not afraid to like say things that are like fucking insane
and like just like raw.
Like he'll talk about like how much he hates like Hollywood
and how much he hates like all this like shit because he just like is uncompromising
and like because he could do like actual things that worked.
But he just doesn't give a fuck.
He's like he could be like he could be working on like Coraline or something.
Yeah, easily like here's the thing.
Like, you know, he for somehow through like some like fucking
I think it's just because it was unprecedented.
Like he submitted We Are the Strange to the Sundance Film Festival
and got accepted. Right.
So the movie showed there and he he while he was there,
like this is like him.
He's still like not didn't know much about Hollywood and everything
hated the entire experience because they like that he got an agent from there
and they're like, well, we need to buy out the theater.
So we need to like have all the theater when we play has to be full of plants.
So everybody loves the movie.
They react crazily over the top so they can they get people to buy it.
And he was like, get fucked.
So instead, he just like went on Twitter and was like, hey,
you want to come see the movie?
Why would they think a guy like that would be they didn't?
They had no idea who they were dealing with.
Like did they watch the movie?
Yeah. So what happened instead is that like they're just like normal
people from the film vessel came in and then he had an army of people
from Twitter who came in like my buddy, my buddy,
Ed went up there and like shit and went and see it.
And like so everyone who was just there from the theater got up and left
because they were disgusted by the movie.
Everyone who brought there like fucking lost their shit.
And so but the regardless, he got like, I think like 10 or 15 deals
on the movie and turned them all down.
So like there was like big money on the table and you just like get fucked
and just publish it himself instead.
Didn't want to go through any more bullshit.
Yeah, because he's just like he looked through the contracts like, OK,
like I don't own my movie anymore.
Like fuck you.
Yeah, you know, at this point, I'm sure he's probably made more
on Blu-ray and DVD sales don't need to do that in today's world.
Yeah, but this is like 2007 and he's like, you know, like had the foresight
just like fuck that curve for sure.
Yeah, he's like published like books like.
But that's the thing.
I think though a lot of I think a lot of the
God, I'm about to sound real fucking old and I'm accusing myself of this too.
But I think a lot of our generation of like content creators
are spoiled because we knew it was possible.
Like a lot of the people before us were like hoping it was possible
or like had the like thought like, hmm, well, you know,
you guys might not want to buy my movie, but I see the Internet over there
and I'll bet if I release it there, people might like it.
But like we know that we know it's possible as a result.
I think that's why a lot more people now are like just doing like YouTube
du jour instead of their unique ideas.
The generation before us and, you know, it wasn't possible for them.
So I understand the confusion.
But like the thing that really worked for MDOT for me is that he made
me realize that I wanted to be my own boss.
Because before that, like my plan was like my big influence
before that was a Joan Vasquez.
And so I was like, oh, I'll just like make a really cool comic.
It's very closely related to MSI.
Have you ever been into MSI or do you just happen to like?
I just I just happen.
I mean, I've listened to a bit of mindless self-indulgence,
but it's like it's good, but not like I'm a huge fan.
Yeah, so like it's weird how like it just worked like that
because I watched his video.
He did too.
Yeah, I was like, this is fucking dope, but it wasn't animated.
And I was very disappointed because I wanted to be a fun video and super cool.
But yeah, like so my plan before that was like, I'm going to publish
with SLG or something like that, because I was listening to a podcast
called Indie Spinner Rack all throughout high school and just these two guys
who just like knew everything about the indie comic scene.
And I ended up going to the Mocha Art Festival in New York and like met a bunch
of people and like was like shopping to recommend me that podcast.
Is it like, is it good to get into if you don't know anything about indie comics?
I knew nothing about indie comics going into it.
They they name drop a lot and don't provide a lot of context,
but they give you things to Google.
The podcast is long defunct.
Like it ended like five years ago, but all the information on it's still pretty good.
Yeah, they recommend a lot like like artists.
They recommend are like people like indie.
Yeah, because they're older.
So it's like indie to them is like not like web comics.
It's like the Xerox books and like ship them out.
The hardest thing about getting into like indie comics is just that nobody talks about them.
Yeah, these guys did a really good job.
And I just like started like learning like the names of the presses and like people.
And I was like, I bought a bunch of books.
They did like a they did two anthologies and I bought both of those.
And the guys like they did they did work.
So they went to both went to the Joke Hubert School for comics.
Yeah. And I learned about where is that?
Is that like famous?
Oh, yeah, Joke Hubert is like a famous like comic artist.
And like you go there and like you learn it's just you just go there to learn how to draw comics.
And then there was another school that opened.
Oh, my God, was it the Center for Cartoon Studies?
And I learned about it through that podcast.
And I was like, this is the college I'm going to.
And I was so fucking stoked.
And I was because like this was like the tail end of high school and my parents
like you need to go to college.
I'm like, I don't want I just want to draw.
And they're like, no, do it.
So I'm like, I want to go to I want to go I want to go to CCS.
And they're like, we are not signing loans for you to go throw your life away.
Little did they know I was going to throw my life away regardless.
Yeah. So what did you end up doing?
Well, after that, I went to a bunch of art schools, like quote unquote, regular art schools.
How old are you in the city?
17, 17, 18 ish at that around that age.
Like it's just, you know, your birthday, November 8th.
OK, so so you would have turned 18, like towards the start of senior year.
Yeah. So this is like right before that.
So we're looking at colleges and stuff.
And so everyone I go to
doesn't take me like I remember I went to the Art Institute of Boston
and the guy sat me down and just like I'm sick and tired of seeing portfolios
that are just shit get out.
Was it shit?
Yeah. OK.
I was a really bad artist and I knew it.
You have improved a lot.
Yeah, no, I'm definitely like way better than I was back then.
Do you think you'd get accepted there now?
Probably not just because like that there was a fine art school.
Like I never had a chance in hell of getting to a school like that.
And that's kind of what I.
Yeah, this is why I wanted to go to CCS.
Yes, because they're they're they would see your potential
and think this is a totally right because your art style is real different.
And I want to ask you about that, too.
Like how the fuck did you develop this art style?
Because I have literally never seen anyone with the style that even
like resembles yours.
Um, I don't.
And yours has changed a lot, too.
Yeah, because when you started doing my little pony art,
you were doing very show accurate stuff and your stuff on its own was
a little bit more, I don't know.
Like you you're very into variable line widths.
Yeah, which I don't think most people even know what the fuck that means.
I only learned that term from you.
But it's where the I mean, it's as it sounds when you draw the outline
of a character, it like has curves and like it gets thicker and thinner as it goes.
A lot of it is very hard to do thick, thick, thick line, thicker lines are usually
kind of used to highlight shadows or like places that are supposed to be darker.
It's done a lot.
I mean, it's not done in animation basically ever because it's so hard to animate.
Yeah, because like if you're doing variable line width, you have to keep
that line with placement consistent from frame to frame, which like,
which is why when people like watch like a one punch man
soccer casino, they're like so blown away, you know, since like how the fuck?
Like you're insane.
But yeah, I'm super big into like line art and stuff like that.
I don't know.
I mean, anime was the first big artistic influence for me.
I mean, trying to draw anime, but I never could really do it.
The only anime I can think of that has outlines as fucking thick
with two Cs as yours is DBZ.
But I mean, you were into that.
Yeah.
No, I was huge into DBZ or Powerpuff Girls.
Yeah, I did.
I did like Powerpuff Girls a lot.
I don't know.
I just I just consumed a lot of different things.
I watched like everything that was on TUNAMI.
I really liked the original full about Huckmus and that was airing.
I was obsessed with that.
I don't think that comes through much in your art style.
Maybe you're writing, but not so much the.
No, I don't think artistically, it's a lot of influence there.
I mean, was there a comic artist who was like your
favorite, who you used to list as like your biggest influence?
Let's see.
I I mean, one guy who worked in like all black and white.
Aren't you like a fan of Bone?
I do love Bone.
Jeff Smith's Bone is fucking gorgeous.
Bone is a little bit like your art.
A little bit.
Yeah, it's way more detail.
That guy is like fucking super pro.
I like.
Wait, am I thinking of his bone?
The one that's like a detective?
No, I wait.
What is is it all black and white?
It is. They did a reprint.
Scholastic did a color reprint.
That's why I've seen a color version.
But yeah, I really like Dave Sim.
He did Sarabis, which is another one of those like he did.
How God fucking Dave Sim.
What a fucking winner.
I just my favorite artists are them people who are just like
everything fucking sucks.
Do it anyway.
Like that just gets me like rock hard.
It's so good.
Like Dave Sim is just like like, oh, God, he's such a cool guy.
So like he he did all this like 300 issue comic by himself.
Like the tail end of it.
He had some guy do the backgrounds with him, but he's just like
an alcoholic guy who just draws comics and and and just like says,
fuck you.
Like like he had this book that came out because he started in the 70s,
I think, and like he was quoted early in an early menu series when someone
asked him, like, how long is Sarabis going to be?
Because it was like blowing up at the time.
He's like 300 issues, like just kind of just not thinking.
And then he's like, fuck, now I got to do 300 issues.
So like he finished it in like 2005.
So like 30 years, just grinding this shit out.
And like, I remember because they were talking about an indie
spinner rack and they interviewed him.
They were one of their first gigs.
Their first like gags on the show was called dialing Dave
because this is like when the internet still isn't this.
So they would just look in phone books for people named Dave Sim,
then call them live on the phone.
They're like, are you Dave Sim who made Sarabis?
Like some random guy like, who the fuck is that?
And they're like, click.
Well, that's not Dave Sim.
So like there's like episodes of episodes that they eventually
like found the actual Dave Sim.
I think like he contacted them or something.
But Dave Sim hates all technology, doesn't own a computer,
doesn't have an email address or anything like that.
So he drew everything by hand and like cut out the zippitone dots
and glued them down and like, like fucking he cut.
Wait, so you know, like the halftone dots.
You don't mean like individually.
No, no, no, he did screen tone the screen tone.
I mean, isn't that normal in Japanese manga though?
The Japanese are insane.
All right.
Over here in America, where we take shortcuts.
We have Cuban rights.
Yeah, we laugh.
That's not even that far from the truth.
So yeah, he does this and and they, I guess at the end of Sarabis,
they spoiled the end of Sarabis for me because I still haven't finished it
because it's like 300 issues.
So it's like he published because he had his own publishing company
called Ardvark Veraheim Press and he published everything himself
because then this is the 70s.
I'm like, it's not internet.
And even now he's like internet is gay.
So he has some guy run his website and everything.
But so he had these big volumes that he called phone books
because they were the size of phone books that had his comics in them.
And so at the end of the run, he kills Sarabis.
Like Sarabis dies at the end of everything.
Well, now you spoiled Sarabis.
Yeah.
So I mean, if I have to suffer with knowing how it ends, all of you do too.
I think actually on his emails, I think he started a new service.
There's only two ways you get into story.
Right.
The main character does or doesn't die.
Like those are the two endings.
So that's a spoiler for you.
Then who the coin toss, you know, like.
So like, I think he actually is doing a new Sarabis series.
I need to look for it because I just got a message in my inbox
like two days ago called Sarabis and hell issue two is out.
I'm like, whoa, so.
But yeah, well, the character has gone to hell.
Yeah, like in the nature of the series to have, I mean, or is that weird?
I'm not super far into it
because I have the first three volumes, which is a fuck ton of comics by itself.
But there's still like, I think nine more that I have to get.
And they're hard to track down.
So. But yeah, at the.
So he dies.
I'm like, they're they're talking to Dave Sim.
They're like, I was really emotional.
Like at the end of the series, like, like, did you feel like
as you have been with this character for 30 years?
And he's like, how did you feel about like killing your character?
And he's like, so glad the fucker's dead.
Yeah, I imagine.
Like, oh, my God, it's always been looking forward to you for 30 years.
Like halfway through, Sarah, this is run.
He came out with a book called the Sarah, this style guide.
And he was just like, look, you got to do a page a day.
And what you need to do is need to for a month, you have to do a page a day.
And every day you don't fucking do it.
You have to reflect on why you would get it done.
Was it was it?
He's like, was it because was it because you were lazy?
You know, was your girlfriend?
You got to choose the page or the girlfriend.
That's the power of of comics is that because it's a well-established
medium to go in for 100 years, like there's generally like a speed.
People have agreed upon like a page a day is healthy.
More than that is necessary if you're doing a Shonen Jump comic.
Yeah, you need to like, but you need a team, probably.
I can't imagine.
I get like as much as I like making art, I could never publish for Shonen Jump.
You well, you have to be real dedicated to both a.
Doing manga and be making money.
Yeah, it's like to make it and Shonen Jump.
It's not about doing the manga that you're the most passionate about.
It's about doing the manga that is the best idea.
When I read Bakuman, I like literally like every every Shonen anime
I ever read dropped like two points across the board.
I realized that they were all fake.
I mean, I felt that way too.
But at the same time, it made it more special when something is that good.
And you're like, fuck, they did.
Like Bakuman makes Death Note more enjoyable
because they talk about the serious comedy thing.
And when you read about that and then you read Death Note
and you see how they did that and that the anime left it out.
Yeah, you're just like, mm, the manga was better.
You know, like this is why I read eight volumes of this
and why I did not finish the show, even though I was interested, you know.
But but in any case, so these comic book
authors are big influences on you.
Yeah, comedy wise.
It sounds like you were you did the same thing I did,
which was brainwash yourself into believing that you can work from home
and not have to answer to anybody.
Well, the thing was just that I've never, ever, ever, ever
been able to visualize myself in a professional environment.
Yeah, I just do it.
It's fucking impossible.
Well, the thing is just like my biggest thing is I know that I'm going to die.
Yeah. And the fact of like even like like that's I hate being depressed
because I spent half my time doing something I don't want to ever do
anything you don't want to do.
If you might get hit by a car tomorrow, right, you'll be like,
didn't do anything I wanted to do.
And that's that's why I was told to do when we did the the the art
apologies thing, like that's why I hate that I haven't done any of this shit yet.
So like my thing right now is I'm doing this Polystation two thing
and I'm like practicing my craft and getting better at doing like these fan
art pieces.
But like if nothing big happens with it, I'm just like, fuck it.
I'm just going to do Sorcerous Lost.
And like if I have to live in a box, so so be it.
All right, heavy question.
Would you say that that desire to like have completed things is what's keeping you alive?
Yes, because I got the sense that like because you've been you've been openly
very suicidal for a long time.
Sure. Yeah.
And but it seems as though like the reason that you've never been like gung ho
about I'm going to go die today is that like you haven't made a masterpiece yet.
I'm like I'm like it's it's I'm I'm depressed and anxious at the same time.
And so it's just like I want I definitely their days.
I'm just like, I'm just going to like end my life.
Like I feel like crap scenario.
You create something that you legitimately believe is like a work of merit.
No one cares about it.
What happens?
Nothing, because I'm already operating under the assumption that that's what's
going to happen, like deep down in my mind, I'm kind of convinced at this point,
like probably not going to be a Digi Bro.
Like that's probably not going to happen for me.
Like becoming as big as I am because I don't intend to stay at this level.
Right. But like I'm not even going to reach that point.
I think I'm going to be this weird, awkward guy who's just going to not.
I don't know. It depends on I think it depends on how legitimately good
could the projects you come out with are.
Because like so far, your narrative projects have never really come out.
Yeah. Yeah.
Except for the My Little Pony fan fiction.
Yeah.
But like you can't recommend that to your friends too easily.
No. No, unfortunately.
No. But like I just think that it's hard to say, like one of the problems I've
always had with with with trying to, you know, when you come to me for advice,
I'm like, well, the problem is that it's hard to say if you need to like,
like you're good enough that I'm like, clearly this guy could do like an
amazing series, like a great, he could write a great novel.
He could write a great comic.
He could write a great whatever, but like it hasn't happened yet.
Right.
And so it's hard for me to say, like, oh, you're, you know,
people just don't care about your art style as opposed to, well,
if you gave them like a great story, they might.
And maybe the kinds of stories that you are best at telling can't be done
in a short amount of time, you know, like, because there are some people
who can just like draw a picture in an hour and it somehow tells a story
and people are like entranced by it.
And then there's other people who are like, I can tell a way better story
than that, but you're going to have to give me a year.
Right.
Well, that's my, I just, I work insanely slowly.
And I don't know, I don't know if it's because I just have a really shit
work ethic or if I'm just like, I think it's your, I, I'm going to go ahead
and say, I don't think that your work ethic is your biggest problem.
Because I think that the work I've seen you do is unbelievably taxing
the way you do it.
Like back when you used to draw, because you did a few art
live streams and you were doing the Trixie comic, do you want to explain
that period of time?
How, what happened there?
Actually, we might have to cut off and upload footage and then read, restart
if this is going to be long, probably only like six minutes left of recording.
I can probably get through this in six minutes.
All right.
Um, no, well, that was just, I got, I got big into vectoring
during MLP because that's like how they did the show was with vector graphics.
The difference between doing vector graphics in the show versus when I was
doing them, because like a vector graphic is just, it's infinitely scalable.
Yeah.
So like it's all done with points and math instead of pixels.
Um, but the way you do vict vector art, like precisely is use the pen tool.
And so you base, it's all done with bestie.
Do you not do that anymore when you draw?
No, I've moved, I've moved.
I mean, sometimes I still do.
Because when you were doing that, I watched some of those live streams
and you would be like drawing a tree for three hours.
Yeah.
And I was like, this is what, like you could, you were doing
commissions that you literally could charge somebody like $50.
And you're, you're only getting paid like a dollar an hour
for the amount of work you did.
I'm running into that problem right now with 3D because like I'm doing,
I'm pricing it out.
Like if I wanted to start commissions or you're just planning on it.
But the problem is like to, to charge minimum wage to do a commission.
It would start at like $300.
And how long is the commission?
Or just, is it just a model or it's just like a model to do a model
with like a turnaround and one pose would take probably like, there's some
people who would buy it, but they're not in your YouTube audience.
No, they're not like, they're, they're no, I don't know them yet.
Essentially.
All right.
The card is filled up.
So we'll take a short break to, uh, unfilled.
Here we go.
So before we just took a little break, you were talking about your influences
and how you have a lot of clear influences on like your lifestyle and
mentality, but not so much on your actual aesthetic art style.
Yeah.
I guess it's kind of, that's a bit more nebulous to track.
Um, my, my art style has changed a lot, uh, as, as time has gone by.
Uh, I, I can definitely recall like specific artists that I was trying
to integrate into my style, but like my, my art really took off when I
stopped trying to actively develop it.
Um, Jonah Vasquez was huge back in the day.
I think everybody had a Jonah Vasquez phase who was into drawing
comics or art in the mid 2000s, like invaders him, killed all of us.
And then Johnny the homicidal maniac and squee and all that shit.
Um, I remember distinctly, uh, I started getting into spawn, like the original,
like spawn run from image and, uh, Oh God, what's the guy's name?
Not Tard McFarlane.
I like, I love his art too, but like the guy specifically, uh, Steve, no.
Hmm.
Oh God, I'm blanking, but it was specific, specific artists, artists on
spawn that I really fucking liked, um, Dave Capullo, he was fucking dope.
And like his arts, the complete antithesis of what I do, cause it was
like really thin lines, tons of cross hatching and extraneous detail everywhere.
And like really soft painterly colors.
It was like, he took like Todd's art style and like pushed it further.
Um, and I, but I really liked him.
There was a whole phase during college where I was desperately trying to do
that and failing miserably because I have no patients.
And at one point specifically, I remember in illustration class, I was like,
fuck it, I'm not this.
So I did the exact opposite.
It did really simple cartoony things.
And I think that's probably where my style like kind of became its own.
Cause I realized like I'm way too lazy to sit there and spend 10 hours on one
drawing that people can look at like your old fucking like super detailed shit.
I mean, I don't think any of it's online anymore.
Uh, was it any good?
No, that was the whole problem is like, I didn't have the patience to be a
Dave Caputo cause like his art, like you could zoom in that shit like extensively
to make it work.
It's just like, I don't, I don't know how, how people sit there.
Cause like my whole thing is like, I want to tell the story and the art.
Well, you've always been way more of a narrative as than an esthetician, I suppose,
which is kind of funny because you do mostly work in visual mediums or
you've, you've, like you've always considered like visual mediums to be at
the forefront of your career, except for the period where you were trying to be
a novelist.
Yeah.
Um, how do you like reconcile that?
Sure.
I think I really enjoy my, my favorite things, like ever since I was a little kid,
like stories and like experiencing stories have been really thing.
I think one of my very, very, very, very first influences was Animorphs.
That scholastic book series, like everybody laughs them for the covers.
That book series was fucking crazy.
Like people were killed.
You just reread that a couple of years ago.
I did.
I read, I bought, I bought the whole series again to read, check it out.
And like the writing is super basic, but like, it's about like high school kids
being traumatized by war.
Like that's what the entire thing's about.
And like the book ends super solemnly.
There's no happy ending.
They don't win.
Shit's bad.
Oh, that's like, they, they end up like spoilers for Animorphs.
I'll actually warn you this time.
They end up like repelling the aliens and everything, but the book,
the last book is like 15 years later, one of the characters has post-traumatic
stress disorder and nobody knows where he is.
He just dropped off, faced the planet.
The ship that was through the entire book, Cassie and Jake never happens.
They break up because Jake is like not able to like parse, like not being in war.
So they can't work out.
And like it's just like super, like just like how like soldiers, they never recover.
Yeah.
And so like the book ends with like Jake, like going back into space to go on another
mission and like the book ends with them encountering some other aliens.
And like, it's like, do they live or die?
We don't know.
That's some heavy shit.
Yeah.
Like the thing is, like they like get stabbed and murdered and like severed.
And like, like there's one point where like, uh, like one of them gets cut in half
and they have to like de-morph back to human.
Cause when you, your wounds recover, when you go back to your regular form.
So like they almost die a bunch of times.
There's like torture and murder and like all this crazy shit.
That's like, I never actually read any of it.
It's so good.
Oh God.
I really wish they was like an adult revision of this.
Cause the way it works is that, um, there's these aliens called the yurks and like
they're parasites, they go into your ear and they take, they wrap around your
brain and take over your body.
And so there, there's like these aliens everywhere.
Um, like parasite, they're parasitic aliens and, uh, they have like these, they've
taken over tons of tons of worlds and now they're coming to earth.
Cause in this world, earth is like, we're basically, we breed like cattle.
So like there's like, we're billions of people on earth that like doesn't happen.
Like all these other planets, there's a couple million of both species, but here
it's like a gold mine for this alien race.
I'm like, we're super underdeveloped, but our bodies are like really great for them.
So they're like trying to take over the planet.
And then there's other aliens called the andolites who are fighting them.
And so, um, the way they fight them have this to basically for espionage is morphing.
So you can like acquire the DNA of an animal by touching it.
And then for two hours, you can transform and become them.
Um, but if you don't de-morph in two hours, you're trapped in that form forever.
So the characters don't have like a specific animal they morph into.
They just can morph into animals.
You can pull a bunch of different ones.
And once you acquire DNA, essentially, yeah, but the interesting thing is when
you transform into an animal, the first time you have to fight its instincts
because it can take over your mind.
So that never happened to any characters.
It does.
It does temporarily.
Like one of the scariest things is like when they have to morph into ants
and like ants are just like automata.
So for like 15 pages, they're just like they find another ant colony and like
they're describing what happens when they have no control of themselves.
They're like biting other ants and have it having a huge colony war.
And like halfway through it, they realize what's going on.
And like they de-morph in the middle.
Like they burst through a wall and like fall out and it's like they're all
traumatized and like like 20, 30 books later, they're like, well, it's never
morph into ants again ever.
But one of the kids Tobias, like he the very first book he gets stuck trapped
in the form of a hawk.
So for like half the series, he's just a hawk.
And so he lives, he lives in the woods.
He and like he for the first for the first like 20 or 30 books, like people are
like he'll like go to like Jake's house and like he'll like feed him like a
hamburger or something because he has to just eat meat now because he's a bird.
Um, and, uh, eventually, uh, he just like, he's been in a hawk so long, like he
just succumbs to the, the, uh, the instinct and he starts hunting and like killing.
Like they describe in great detail.
He finds a mouse or rips it open.
It starts feasting on its intestines and he has like a fucking panic attack.
But eventually like his like subplot is like learning to just accept the fact
that like this is who he is now narrates through this, this hawk and every,
every book changes narration, its first person narration, but every single
book it changes from one of the five, one of the six main characters.
So this is one of his books where he just describes it like, yeah, I just
ate this thing and it was fucking great.
So like, he just starts doing that.
And like at the end in the last book in the series, they're like,
because he never, he's just a hawk.
So like there was like, we don't know what happened to Tobias.
Like hawks only live for a few years.
He could be dead.
We don't know.
He just disappeared.
That's nuts.
It's, it's, it's so fucking good.
But like that's like that and Digimon are probably like my two big, like super
big influences in the beginning.
Cause those are like the only things that had like a continuous narrative that
kept going on.
Um, so all right.
Well, I guess we kind of got to the heart of your, uh, your influences.
Unless there's any other, like, are there any influences that aren't really
like art related, but are like way more than most people realize, like affect
your life, you know, um, I don't know.
I mean, like I, I watched a lot of like, like YouTube, like, uh, I really
liked Gary Vee.
He's fucking dope.
Never heard of him.
Uh, he does like, uh, business and like social media and personal
brand development and stuff.
He's super cool.
I'm about to read his new book.
What would you say are your biggest influences as a YouTuber?
Oh, I don't know.
I really don't.
I mean, it's just kind of an amalgam of like, yeah, it's just like, I don't
styles that have sort of sprung from the primordial ooze of the biggest one
that we both had in the beginning was a sequelitis.
Like that's where our whole format initially came from.
Pretty much was just like trying to, I mean, he took it from Mr.
Plinkett.
So it really, he's like the forefather of this current style, you know, um, in
terms of like, I really liked just like tech YouTubers when I was doing
Rebel pixels, a lot of MKBHD and like Austin Evans and, and, and I pocket
out a bunch of all the big ones.
You definitely had MKBHD is like, uh, attitude towards tech, which is like
these, everything should be like kind of sleek and modern.
And like, I mean, it's unfortunate that you were filming it in a basement as
compared to his fucking studio.
I mean, not that he always had that, but like, you know, you have, you, you
branded it very strongly to look like that kind of channel.
Like everything is like modern and cool.
Yeah.
I mean, that's what I went to school for.
Tell me more about that.
Cause again, um, a lot of the things about you that fascinate me the most are
the things that have nothing to do with YouTube at all, um, such as your
graphic design and website design history.
Cause you make good, how the fuck did you make the sorceress lost website?
The motion comic site, a lot of work.
It was just like all, I mean, I still have the file.
You can look at it.
It's all hand coded and just like, those aren't like gifts or no, they're
or anything they were video files with no audio.
And then you, there's an HTML five.
They have like a video embed, like, uh, I don't even remember the word before it
is at this point, just like a option you can do.
In case anyone doesn't know what we're talking about, go to the sorceress
lost site, it's still up.
Unfortunately, some of the fonts don't work anymore.
Cause like Dropbox, I was hosting a bunch of stuff for it on Dropbox.
Um, and then Dropbox changed the way their files work.
So you can't link out to other files anymore.
So all the web fonts that I was hosting all don't work.
So it's like in times in Roman, it looks 10 times worse than it used to.
Um, but yeah, it's just, uh, and then I went into the player, you can
edit the properties of the player.
So I set it to autoplay and then to hide the controls.
So they look like gifts, they act like gifts, but they're video files.
So like a 10th of the size of the gift that would be,
but you can scroll over it and like, yeah, when you scroll over it, the
controllers, the pot, they pop up, right?
It's really sleek looking.
And I'd never seen anything presented that way, but I assume that the
bottom line is, it is not worth the amount of effort to tell that story that way.
Um, I mean, now that I can do 3D, it would be so much easier to do the same thing.
Do you still think you might take that direction with, uh, it's very
sourceable, I've realized to go back to the question that you initially asked
was how do I reconcile wanting to do visuals, but being a very narrative
centric person?
The reason I started writing for a while is because like I came to the
conclusion, like all I really care about is telling the story and like,
why not just do that?
And the problem, not even the problem, but like what I realized through
doing that is that my really like visual storytelling.
I like being able to like move the camera around and like do things without,
just, I hate description.
Yeah.
Like every time I got to get to a book and like, when they have to
describe all this shit, like, like the Scootaloo book that I wrote, it
doesn't have the word said in there ever.
I never made an active decision to never have a said tag because I
hate that so fucking much.
The word said.
Yeah.
So every time, instead of like saying, like they said, I'd be like, you know,
that the opposite is what is preached is correct.
Right.
Well, the thing is, I, it's because they say don't change said to like, he
replied or he did.
So what I did instead is I would use what's called an action tag.
So instead of being like saying like, like, Hey, did you, I said or something,
I'd be like, I picked up the can off the table.
Hey, did you?
And then, you know, I love stuff like that.
So it was, I don't put any saids in my stories usually either, but I'll just
like full paragraph break for dialogue.
Yeah.
I mean, write it like a script, you know, the thing, that's how I usually
start when I would write all those chapters, like, because the dialogues
apart, I love doing the most.
I just write the dialogue out and then like, okay, I guess what I'm going to
do while they're talking and then just go back through and like slowly piece
the scene together.
Yeah.
Um, that's interesting.
But that, but doing all that, like, I loved writing the dialogue.
I loved coming it up with this story conceptually, but I would get super bogged
down and like trying to not a, um, writing like descriptions of things because
like, I'm like, I could just draw this and then be like transitioning from
scene to scene was also tricky.
I don't, I don't know how to like, I don't know if it's just that back in
the old times when you had to read books.
I think people had a just more ability to imagine what those places looked like.
Cause when I read like a long descriptive part of a book, I cannot
picture it at all.
Like I just come up with whatever I think it might, but I'm just like, this
doesn't feel right.
The same way that just seeing a picture, you in a picture, whoever said pictures
worth a thousand words underestimated the worth of a picture, right?
Like a thousand words ain't that much.
And you can tell a fucking big story with a picture.
Like just show a picture of someone's room and you can tell me like a thousand
things about that character, you know?
So I totally agree that like with certain scopes of stories, like a big
fantasy story, like it's real hard to be able to like write enough minute
details without it bogging down.
Like a lot of fantasy novels and shit, I have a great example of this in
Sorcerous Laws depth of why like this is actually one scene in the beginning
of SL that I don't think I'm going to use anymore.
But at the time in the first revision I was working on really made me like think,
fuck, I don't really think I can work with books the way I want to.
Cause there's, there's a shot that I had that in the beginning of the story, Sarah
was going to go to like the docks and meet somebody who was coming in for her
mentor and pick up these scrolls that he needed.
So what I want to do, she was going to sit down on like a bench, wait for the
ship to come in and then they're like, we got sound like the ship's coming into
dock. She turned around and like it was the camera would zoom out and you see
that not only is that ship coming to dock, the islands like floating in the
sky being suspended by magic.
So there's like this airship coming into dock, not just a regular ship.
So it zooms out, you have this big glory shot.
And I was like, oh, this is so cool.
But then I switched to a book.
I'm like, how the fuck am I going to do this scene?
There's no way to give the camera pants out and like it would sound like, but
that's how I think of a visual art.
So I'm like, I can't write it.
Like it's exactly, I can write the dialogue just fine.
But like in terms of like telling this story and just telling stories in general,
I'm thinking like a director and not.
When I was trying to write the the book that I wrote back in 2010 for Nana
Remo, like it took me two years to get it to the stage of a novel because the
initial idea I had was just of like a scene of someone firing a bullet and then
like time stopping and the character like flicking it around and shooting it back
or something like that.
But the only way it made sense in my head was visually.
It's like, no one will understand how cool this power looks if I describe it in
text because you don't see the bullet stop.
Right.
You know, so it won't.
This story can't be told that way.
Yeah.
And eventually it just changed the story.
So that worked for me.
Yeah, I cut that scene out of the written version.
It's up on Tumblr.
You can read it.
It doesn't happen like that.
But like, I don't, I don't.
I mean, every time someone makes a YouTube video about any adaptation of anything,
they're like, oh, mediums can't be crossed.
Like it's new information.
But like, you do kind of have to keep reminding people, including yourself,
like, hey, some of your ideas just won't be.
Yeah.
Do I mean, to, to, to, in defensive books, something that's really easy to do
with books that's harder to do with other visuals is engage even not even
expedition thing I was going to say is engage all the senses.
Yeah, you can describe easily how things smell, how they feel without having to
like, like if you're going to do that in a visual thing, like you can either imply
it with visuals or you'd be like, Hey, it stinks in here.
You know, you, you can't really like elegantly integrate in senses.
I think I think the best thing about text is just that like a character can
easily give their reactions to a situation.
Yeah.
And I think that like a lot of the reason that adaptations from like books to
film always end up so bad is that like the book, the book is not focused on the
visual element because it can't do that well.
Right.
It's focused on the fucking thoughts in the character's head.
So like most books are more focused on character development.
Well, I think, you know, and like something that I was noticing while I was
writing, because I was trying to figure this out myself is that like any visual
medium kind of always like has the issue of time, right?
Cause like most, most of a movie is done basically, like each scene is in real
time, whereas in a book, like in between two people talking, like one sentence
and another, the character can have a thought that goes on for like 16 pages.
Yeah, exactly.
And like there's no way to, you can't just like stop the frame.
Like and then the character thinks like it feels totally weird.
And what are you going to show?
Right.
You can't really do anything.
Like you, like, like you'd have to like go into their head and like animate
all this stuff, but like it feels awkward because like nothing's shot like that.
Yeah.
And I mean, obviously there's lots of books that like, like House of Leaves,
there's no way to make not a book because like it's constant notations
and active reader participation.
You can maybe make it a visual novel, but not, not a book, you know?
But, um, yeah.
So, so Sorceress Lost is still in the works, would you say?
For sure.
Okay.
Um, I just finished like a rewrite, like a month and a change ago.
I have the first chapter redone.
So how like glued to this universe are you a Sorceress Lost?
I really enjoy it.
And depending on how I mean, my plan initially was like, I would want to
have like any future stories I do take place in Salon as well, which is
like the name of the world.
Yeah.
I, uh, speaking as one former aspiring author who gave up on his world to
another, um, because for me, the hardest thing about any project is I have an
idea for the next project.
And so like it becomes, I don't want to let this project take up too much of my
time because I want to move on to the next one.
Do you ever feel that way about Sorceress Lost?
Like, is there another project like underneath that waiting to get out?
Or is it more like this is my thing and I want it to fucking happen?
The weird thing for me, and like this almost undermines everything I've
been saying so far is that I, and like this is something I've been dealing
with a lot recently and trying to figure out.
And I think I've kind of understood it is that because I have like all
these self-esteem problems, like my projects don't feel real or as special.
Like I can't be as passionate about SL as like how I got, I can't be as into
SL as I was into like MLP or something like that.
Just because like, because it's from me, it feels tainted almost like intrinsically.
But like the way I'm trying to like get around that is I've, I've, I've found
that some of my best work and the things I can get most hype about that I
work on is when I'm working as a group, because then the project transcends
just me and it becomes bigger and more important.
Did you watch my Dear Artists video?
I did.
Cause I, you inspired that video.
I figured when I was like the first photo to come up as like artists
struggling, I was like, I think, I think I was watching, did you recent, like in
the last week put out like a hyperbolic wine chamber or something?
Yes.
Cause it was, I was watching that and you were just talking about like the
difficulties of marketing yourself and stuff.
And I just somehow the thought crossed my mind about Vocaloid or something.
And I was just like, Tom should do that or something.
I don't know.
I was just like artists can team up and they can make it like take
some of the burden off of yourself, you know, it doesn't have to be all you most.
I think that the YouTube sphere is very individualistic, even though there's
like tons of YouTube channels that are teams, you know, like, especially a lot
of the big ones have multiple persons behind them.
But like, I think the romantic idea of the YouTuber is like guys like Casey
Neistat who are just like, I don't sleep and I make a video every day and it's
always good.
And so we pressure ourselves to be like that.
Um, and obviously, you know, the idea of like odd tour artists and shit, but like
even a fucking, you could look at Quentin Tarantino and be like, oh, he's
my favorite director, but it's like, he would be nothing without the
cinematographers who bring those fucking shots to life because his cinematographers
are God tier.
So like, you know, I think not enough people to some, some people responded
to my video, like, isn't this all obvious?
This is one on one shit.
And other people were like, thanks, Digi revolutionized my life going to
implement this right now.
I was looking through the comments because like I was kind of like in both
camps because it was like, yeah, this is like something I've been considering.
And at the same time, other people were like, I don't know.
So I guess it depends on where you are.
Yeah.
I mean, for some people, they just never even think about how like marketing
yourself is extremely difficult.
Cause first of all, you have to recognize what about yourself is marketable.
And then you've got to figure out like who is going to care.
And how do I find those people and show it to them?
Well, I think one of the things that like I've had issues with is that like,
I've always been afraid that the stuff I actually want to do has no market value.
Right.
Cause like even with police station two right now, I think, like
it's I'm doing fan art on police station too.
When like at my core, like if you ask me, what do I think of fan art?
I think it's stupid.
I think it's a waste of time.
Yeah.
Like it's not like it's obviously a great marketing tactic to use, but I don't feel
like I feel like it has inherently less artistic value than doing original work.
But ironically, it is the only thing anybody cares about.
Exactly.
Unless, unless, well, okay.
At the same time, though, I do feel like there's a little bit of anytime.
Well, okay.
You're going to agree with me on this because you're really hard on yourself.
You would probably say that if you made a good enough story, you would need to
rely on fan art.
I mean, some people do that.
I mean, I think if you get to a certain, there's a certain like level that
once you hit that, like the work speaks for itself.
Most people aren't there.
Everything that people are drawing fan art of is something that reached that level.
Exactly.
You know, like it had to be good enough that people, it inspired fan art and, you know,
it was, I got a really interesting comment on that wine chamber.
I did someone said, like, it's like, I've never really personally connected to
your work because the most stuff you've been doing recently is fan art.
Whereas I really connect to Ben because everything he's doing is his own work.
Right.
I'm like, that's an interesting.
I mean, for me, the difficulties with connecting with your work is mostly that I
know how much you hate it.
And it's hard for me, like, especially the YouTube videos.
Yeah, I just, I'm not like, if I watch a YouTube
video that I know you didn't want to make, then I'm just like, well, he obvious.
Like sometimes you just seem like you're having fun with it.
Like you put out a vlog because you just wanted to rant about this thing.
And like, that's why a lot of my videos exist.
They weren't made for an audience.
They were made because I had an idea and I thought, eh, 3,000 people will click on this.
It's worth posting.
You know, like someone might think this is quotable or funny or they've had the same
thought, but, uh, but when it's one that I can see that you like forced yourself to
do, I'm just like, Tom, you got to get out of there.
Like you got to get out of there.
You got to make the stuff you want to do, you know?
Yeah.
And that's like, I'm the next couple of months.
Like I have my nest egg for moving, which is going to happen, I guess, in a few months.
So I quit my job before coming to RAGCon because I'm like, I'm just going to focus
on getting that.
Tell us about the job you've been doing.
I want people to understand the, because you've talked about it briefly, but the
conditions of this job are terrible.
And it's cause I guess the guy who hires you owns half the city and can just do
whatever he wants.
Yeah.
Um, cause we, we actually, uh, when it got really bad, we actually talked to one of
the, uh, like officials for the town and he was like, yeah, it's fine, but you can't
do anything about it.
Like, don't try.
So I'm just like, okay.
Uh, but yeah, no, I work for the last like two years, I've worked as a quote unquote
security guard at an abandoned building, uh, Draper mill in the center of our tiny
little town, and it's an old, old building.
It's like stripped to the bone.
There's just nothing in there, but like asbestos, probably, and lead, even though
apparently they've done, you know, inspections and it's fine, maybe, but, uh,
yeah, and I just like do the graveyard shift.
So 11 PM to seven in the morning.
And you just wander around an abandoned building, wander around the abandoned
building, just to, to what?
Make sure homeless people don't sleep there.
I mean, we don't even have homeless people in Hopedale, but, uh, what did
anything ever happen that would there were the only thing you having been there?
Okay.
Well, the reason I'm tech, they call you a security guard.
The reason I'm there is I'm babysitting the building because we go around the
entire building and like, make sure the fire extinguishers are fine because
there's the building isn't up to fire code.
And so legally this guy has to have someone in there to use the fire
extinguishers in case the building catches on fire, but we're neighbors with
the head of the fire department.
And he said, if you want to die, do your job.
If you want to live, get the fuck out of that building.
If it ever catches on fire.
Well, so you've been doing this incredible, dangerous, dirty job.
Does it pay over the table?
Yeah.
Okay.
So, but it's just a shit job that you, that the guy can't be taken to task for it.
Yeah.
And he just owns.
You were doing that for like over a year, right?
Yeah, two years.
Holy shit.
But you kindly quit.
Yeah.
I figured whatever.
I mean, you're not going to have a house in a month anyway.
So fuck it.
So, okay.
I need to understand exactly the plan because I kind of like the idea that
you're just going to try to live in your car and do art from there.
What do you, what is the plan?
Like, well, where are you taking the car first?
Well, here's the thing.
The thing is I have a couple options, apparently.
I have a friend who might want to move in with me, but she's been very slow on
the uptake on that.
So I'm not really relying on that.
But if I did that, I have to like be a normal person and get another real job.
And like, I don't really technically want to do that.
So that's like one of the options.
The second option would be to buy a tiny house.
Are they cheap?
That cheap?
They can be.
Okay.
Some of them are.
Cause usually like a tiny house can be just like.
Is a tiny house cheaper than a trailer?
So you can just get a trailer.
A trailer.
Put yourself down.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm looking into options right now.
Trailer is definitely one option.
Tiny house is, I mean, a lot of tiny houses are just like houses built on a
trailer bed anyway.
So they're around the same size, but just a bit nicer.
Okay.
And then the other option is to convert a cargo van into a mini like apartment on
wheels and drive.
Are you aware of the YouTuber Noah called?
Well, I told you about him.
Okay.
So this guy is a gaming YouTuber whose thing is that he does like two and a
half hour long analysis videos of entire franchises.
Like he'll, he'll do like dragon's age and then he'll go through all the
dragon's age games and talk about all the storylines and compare everything and
say like, here's what was good.
Here's what was bad.
And, uh, his audio is dog shit.
He doesn't edit the audio at all.
So you can hear him like wrestling with papers and fucking up lines.
And, um, fucking stuttering.
He's got a very dry voice.
He barely edits the video.
It's usually just like long gameplay footage, but just because of the fact
that he talks about an entire game series all the way and talks about everything.
And because of the fact that it's all PC games that have like fervent cult
followings, he's got a huge Patreon, uh, not, not huge like mine, but like, you
know, big enough to sustain himself on and he had been a pizza boy at the time.
But he had this, he's like a huge into road novels, like obsessed with road novels.
So he like refurbished a Volkswagen van for like three years.
And now him and his wife like live out of the van and just travel the country.
Do he just uploads YouTube videos from wherever and like subsist off of Patreon
and like sort of him doing that was part of what inspired me to hit the road, you know,
and be like, oh, shit, we can do this from anywhere.
I gotta fucking the camera.
Stop.
When you told me you were going to be doing PS2 graphics out of the back of a car,
I was like, hey, it's Noah Coldwell.
Jervay is doing it.
There's, there's a whole making as much as he is.
There's a whole, uh, like culture of people doing that.
Like I follow tons of YouTubers right now who are just traveling and just
traveling doing that.
Like the difference is that they do it because like they love living on the road.
I'm doing it because I hate having a life.
Have a house to go back to though.
Noah Coldwell Jervay was just dirt poor.
He like just sold off the house and all of their belongings and went into the
Volkswagen van.
Like that is the life now.
There are people who do that.
They just like, they live the van life.
Like they've just decided.
So I could live the RV life.
I could not live the van life.
The like Volkswagen van where the bed is like your body went from the ceiling.
Yeah, that's pretty.
It's it's cramped as fuck, dude.
But I mean, I don't feel like I would be that much.
You don't take up much space except as being like six foot.
Yeah, but like in terms of, you know, your, your, your range of activity.
Yeah.
I mean, I would only sleep in the thing.
I've been planning on probably just like going to like coffee shops or whatever
and get out and net cafes and just, I mean, I can do my work there.
Yeah.
So, but like a tiny house would be kind of the same idea.
Um, I just, I don't, like it said, I can't even imagine like getting up at like
six a.m. putting on like dress clothes, going into a cubicle.
Like I would either like get a gun and either kill myself for everyone around
me, because I mean, I've done that.
I did an internship for my dad at Hanscom Air Force Base for like a summer
and a winter and it paid good money.
Yeah.
I want to be clear.
You like you are like, uh, first of all, how old are you?
29.
So you're 29.
I think you're the, as you were Ben, the oldest Ben is the oldest by
a couple of months.
Okay.
So you're sort of a battle hardened veteran of many life trials.
Uh, I guess I don't feel like, I feel like my life's been pretty easy, which
is, I mean, compared to, let me put it, I was telling Munchie about how I got
fucked over on my job and he was like flabbergasted, but I'm just like, I don't
know.
Well, I mean, it's that you have, you've been to enough things that I wouldn't
say that when you're, when you're saying, I can't even imagine myself at a
normal job, it's like you, you've worked them.
You're not just saying that cause like, I know there's a lot of people, like I
like to say things like, oh, like I could never go back to work, but like, I
didn't even really hate the one job I've ever had.
And like, so I could probably do a normal job.
Like I probably could not for long cause I'd be constantly scheming to quit.
But like, um, you know, you are not just saying this out of nowhere.
You've worked a bunch of places.
I think you worked at a Whole Foods.
I did.
That was probably my longest stint.
Yeah.
Was I did like, I was, I have like this curse, like, except for this job, which
was like, to make it clear, I was so bad even at this job that I probably
should have been fired, but there was nobody else there to fire me.
So it was impossible and nobody else would do that shift.
So like, I, when I put in my notice, like a day before I came here, the guy
was like, are you sure we can give you like two months off to like not be sick
and dying anymore?
And I'm just like, no, dude, I'm cool.
They're just going to offer you months off.
Yeah.
They're just like, we can give you two months off if you need to like recover.
And I'm just like, I'm okay because they know how bad, right?
Because they know, they know that no one's going to take that slot before the
winter even started, but the winter was bad to enjoy the summer.
Okay.
To, to tell you how bad it was, um, I can actually show you a photo after this
to show you what the office ended up looking like.
If you want to laugh your ass off, uh, I kept it for legal reasons.
I figured if it was going to go down, I needed ammo, but, um, if anybody decides
to class action this guy, so I think that's how that works.
The, uh, the building for almost the entirety of the summer had no, for the
entire, the winter had no heat anymore.
The heat was broken.
So, uh, even imagined that he would be involved.
Yeah.
So like, there was a picture of this place.
It's not even like walls.
There's like one little office where they kind of had heat, but the heat stopped
working.
Yeah.
So it was just like, and then the whole building leaks.
So every time it rains, the office floods, the entire building floods, but
like the building never completely dries.
So there's mold and mildew all through the whole place.
Why is they keeping it up?
Because they can't get rid of it.
The problem is like the town's water supply runs under this building.
So if they do anything to it, the entire water supply is fucked.
Oh boy.
And, and they're just stuck with the shitty building.
Yeah.
There's nothing.
It's, it's just a relic of a lost age that can't be salvaged and can't be
destroyed to, and this guy has to pay somebody to do this job.
Legally.
But he won't like take care of them because it's a worthless job.
Exactly.
Cause there's no, there's no money in it though.
Yeah.
He's just doing it to keep himself from getting sued.
Actually, funny enough though, a lot of people out there have probably seen this
building because if you've seen the movie, the surrogates.
I have not.
Okay.
It's the, the movie of Bruce was based on a comic and indie comic, which was really
good.
There's a scene where they go to the slums and this movie had a multimillion
dollar budget.
They could have gone anywhere in the world to film the shithole of the movie.
And where were they for about three weeks and everyone was freaking out because
Bruce Willis was in Hopedale, Massachusetts in the building I worked at.
So the slums of that movie is where I worked for two years.
Look at the literal cyberpunk slum.
Yeah.
That's a cyberpunk movie, right?
Sort of.
I mean, it's, it's not like, so it's, it's kind of more like a general
culture, sci-fi kind of.
Yeah.
I guess, I guess you could classify it as cyberpunk.
It doesn't play the aesthetic very, very hard.
It looks very kind of normal.
It's still fucking hilarious.
Yeah.
That building.
Every, but that was the whole thing.
I was like stunned.
Everyone's like, oh my God, Bruce Willis is here.
It's just so amazing.
I'm like, we, we're officially the shittiest place on the planet Earth.
Like, do you understand?
Like, like they could go anywhere.
They could have filmed us in Africa if they wanted to.
They came here.
How many years was it between you saying that and then working there?
Um, oh God, when did that movie come out?
At least five years.
It was a while.
That's nuts.
Well, yeah, go check out Tom's building in Syragates with Bruce Willis.
I'm sure they CGI'd up a little bit, but they didn't go that far.
Let me tell you.
All right.
Well, so do you think that your life's going to be better or worse once you're
out of your parents' house?
Better, for sure.
So you think even though, even though you're going to be in, uh, like
living possibly living out of a car, would you still say that was like better
than nothing material things don't interest me, you know, like, like, I'm
the person that if like I made like a million dollars a year, I wouldn't
have a big house.
Do you think that you are going to like in the, the, this, you sort of
talked about like being liberated by this.
Um, yeah, I think there's just a lot of like, because like the interesting
thing is like you have moved around your entire life.
Yeah.
Constantly.
I went to sixth grade right down the street from where I live right now.
I see.
My entire life has been this tiring, tiny little fucking.
So you think that by escaping that you might open something up?
I, yeah, definitely.
I like it's imagine.
It's weird when you drive to work and you pass by your high school.
Yeah.
At 29.
Yeah, a little like that's super fucking.
That's why I like literally it's funny.
You say that because like, you know, I moved to my, my girlfriend's town, like
with the intention of getting her out of there and like we pass all of her
schools all the time and she's just like, this is why we can't be here anymore.
Cause every time I see that high school, I want to burn it down.
So you need to get me away from it.
So, but yeah, I do think that'll help.
Um, obviously this, just the fact that you are, um, considering the
possibility that would be even better of a lifestyle, doesn't mean people
should give you any less money or that you don't need help.
Um, I mean, I, I mentioned in the wine chamber that I want people, I don't
want people to give me money because they think like they, they are being a charity
case.
I want to make work that people think is worth paying for.
So you, you want to make sure that people know that like if Patreon.com slash
save me is not about Tom needs the money.
It's not even safe anymore.
I changed it to slash Polystation too.
Cause I didn't, I didn't want to be, I think the joke kind of outlived itself at
this point.
Um, I think it's just the kind of meme that when you push it entirely yourself,
people aren't as receptive to it.
Yeah.
Like Patreon.com slash Ben St took off, I think more because other people were
like, like propping it up more than, uh, than him himself or not more so, but
like as much, um, your meme was too forced.
Unfortunately, I'm not good at comedy.
I, I don't think you're like bad at comedy.
I'm, I'm bad at like, I can do like off the cuff reactionary comedy, but I can't
like sit down and script a joke.
You're better at reacting to someone else's thing and piling onto it.
I would say like on PCP, that's your funniest shit is like quips, like response
quips that come out like, you know, exactly.
But, uh,
wrote that point of the interview with a quick draw word play, and I'm trying
to like remember what questions I need to ask you.
Like, what do I need to know about Tom?
Um, or do people need to know about Tom?
Um, okay.
So right now you consider yourself mostly a 3D graphic artist.
Yeah.
I mean, ever since I got a watch, we are the strange, like it's something
it's always been in the back of my mind.
Like this is kind of cool.
And I always thought conceptually it would be a good move to make because
like the hardest thing for me to do with drawing is, uh, foreshortening.
Like, like drawing anything in perspective is just like, uh, like that sort of shit.
It's just like, yeah, yeah, that specifically that that pose.
Exactly.
Um, so, so I've always been like, well, 3D, like that's all done for you.
Cause that's like the entire nature of it.
Like the extra, the seeds mentioned, it's not like that, right?
Well, I mean, it, it, it is essentially cause you don't, you make the model
and then you, the camera does all the foreshortening.
But you can't do like, you can't do certain things that you think you can.
Like that would be possible in 2D.
Yeah.
I mean, you can't like do like, cause like a lot of the crazy foreshortening
stuff is like breaking perspective.
You can, you can like, fudge it for sure.
And you can like change camera settings and stuff to kind of get like a crazy
dramatic kind of depth of field sort of thing.
But just in terms of just like, if I wanted to draw a person from an angle,
even if it's not like crazy foreshortening, like it's difficult for me,
but like 3D, you just do it.
So like it makes up for a weakness of mine.
Like I think just doing the 3D that I've done, like this is more how my
brain thinks of like objects.
Yeah.
Cause like you, you don't so much want to have to like, uh, draw the entire character
every time you just want to put the character in the goddamn environment
basically and like pose them.
And like, I think if you don't really need your care, like you tend to draw
your characters pretty consistently.
They're not like extremely expressive where they're going to be changing
expressions wildly from page to page or anything like that.
Like it's safe for them to just be models that could be posed enough.
And especially in like a fantasy story where, you know, like the facial
expressions are not driving the story.
Yeah.
It's not like, not like tech savory cartoons or anything like that.
It's pretty restrained.
Um, so it just, it works out really well.
And like, I've always loved that like low poly PS two kind of look.
Yeah.
I grew up with it.
I mean, I don't think, I think, I think doing low poly is probably going to
limit the, the reach of anything I do because I think most people, I think
there's nostalgia for like eight bit.
There's nostalgia for like that PS one kind of thing.
It's coming.
That the PS tune, cause the thing is that, uh, you know, you're 29, you're not
old enough to, to be nostalgia baiting yet.
Really.
You know, it's possible.
I'm just too ahead of the curve right now.
Okay.
Cause I did not grow up with any eight or 16 big games.
So I have no nostalgia for that shit.
Like for me, my era of playing those games is mostly the fucking on steam.
Like someone like Munchy, that motherfucker was born in 2000.
Like his first console is probably the fucking we, it was, you know, so like disgusting.
So for someone like him, you know, he'll be nostalgic for like Minecraft, you know,
which I mean Minecraft looks dated anyways, but he'll be nostalgic for it
because that was the, the zeitgeist of the time.
And I think that, you know, I mean, obviously you got Hippo who's
constantly talking about how like the PS two was the best era for graphics, you
know, like that's his whole fucking channel's identity.
It's like PS two is the only graphics I ever want to see.
So when you come out with Polystation two, it's like this, there's your target
audience is right there to give me like all this patron money and that'll be fine.
But, uh, do you have any concerns about the idea of trying to do a fantasy story
in CG?
Cause I've always felt that like one of the biggest problems I have with the
Berserk movies was that like, I thought that the extremely like wispy,
fanciful art of the manga did not really translate to anime.
But since you're not really adapting this from a source material, I think, I
mean, I really like one of, one of the, I really liked the, the PS
two JRPG, something like, like a Dragon Quest eight fuzzy piece in this night.
You didn't get it.
Oh God.
Where is it?
It's not very evident.
So it's hard to, oh, God, we got a mirror.
Herpaderb.
Yeah.
Um, I think because it's not an adaptation, like a building the
aesthetic from the ground up, I think it will probably be okay.
I'll definitely be like making sure that it doesn't become too ugly or anything.
How did you translate your drawing style into 3D?
Cause you've done your 3D art looks just like your 2D art.
The only big concession I had to make was like making the eyes a little bit
smaller and there were ways I could have gotten around that.
But the thing is like I'm doing everything super low poly and like the
eye socket in the model has eight points to define it.
So when I stretch it to that big, it looks basically like a really ugly
octagon and it doesn't look right.
But when you have a smaller sort of eye, it kind of reads more
smoothly.
I see.
Um, I could have done it as a texture, but I wanted to give it that flexibility
because the way I do all the expression is something called shape keys.
So like you have the basis of the face, just kind of neutral.
And then you make a new key and then you pull the point.
So it looks more like an expression.
Then you have a slider that kind of transitions between those two.
That's how the face morphs from one expression to another.
Okay.
So you can make the faces move and everything like in real time in your comic.
Um, that's cool.
I don't know why I'm like impressed with that.
Like that's not normal, but I mean, I was like, whoa, you can make their mouths
move like for in my mind that I was like reacting that strong.
I got like a thing of false, like going through a couple of different expression
loops on, on Instagram came out pretty good.
So fuck, I forgot how I wanted to phrase this.
So yeah, your art style is so particular.
How much of that is like, you have to draw that way and how much of it is
you want to draw that way?
You know, it's interesting because now that I'm doing 3d and I feel so much
more comfortable with it, like a lot of that was just like, this is just how
it's coming out, but like I'm doing a couple of models right now that they're
not like super different.
Cause like I did the thing, the way the 3d like work throw works is that you
work off a reference image.
So you get like a front and a side view and then you kind of model from both
angles and it makes a 3d version of it.
And like the techniques I could apply to anything, like I could get like, you
know, anybody's art of a front and side view and I could reconstruct it.
Right.
Um, but I'm making sure like I'm doing like Bayonetta right now is like the
next big model I'm working on.
I could just gotten like a, you know, from the design Bible for Bayonetta
modeled off that, but like I redrew it myself because I wanted it to be my
proportions and my kind of art style.
So there's definitely like, um, I'm doing that because I feel like that's my
identity and I like it.
Um, cause I don't want to just like turn into like, I don't want it to
become just technical of just like, yo, I can like recreate other people's stuff.
Do you think that your, um, like art style is going to radically shift as you
one of the, one of the big things that is coming right now is I'm going to start
using way more color.
I've, I've been super big into black and white forever.
Yeah.
Your aesthetic has always been very, my big push now, cause like what I really
love about 3ds, I love that like that low poly like hand painted like world of
warcraft is so fucking gorgeous.
It's fucking great.
So I'm starting to, oh, if you, dude, if you can create some, like I, your
art style is pretty close to that.
Like your Trixie pub is very world of warcraft ish.
Anybody who doesn't know we're talking about, there was a Trixie comic.
We were talking about it before the camera died that, um, that you had made
this like towards the tail end of doing like, basically you quit the pony YouTube
shit and then we're like, I'm going to do this comic and then you worked on it for
a couple of months and then it switched over to sorceress loss.
I guess because I was saying in the other video, it's just like the, I wanted, I
had like this autistic obsession with keeping all my fan content, like non
conflicting with Canon and then like they shotgun ruined a bunch of ideas that
were going to happen.
Like the whole story of the Trixie arc, she was going to go into the every
forest and find like, like all this crazy shit.
Then they like retcon like, oh, we're just in the Everfree and we figured out
all that shit and what it is.
I'm like, well, that whole story is just torpedoed.
So I was just like, well, all the passion died with that.
And then like the more stuff I did, like the more I like, kind of like we're
sort of tweaking little things.
Like I wanted to like Celestine Luna to be made way more like gods and stuff.
Cause like I thought that was like a cool idea from the first season that
they totally fucked up after that.
So then I was like, why don't I just make my own thing where like there are
gods and they are gods and they do God shit.
Yeah.
So like that's what it is.
There's like 13 big countries and they all ruled by a God and they all have
different cultures and stuff.
And like, so it just, I just started running with it and like it came,
it became way better.
Yeah.
So, um, I don't know if this is the same technique that you use for the
motion comic and sorceress loss, but in the Trixie comic, while it was a two
dimensional comic, all the backgrounds were 3D environments you created that so
that you could just, you know, put a character against an environment and
from whatever angle and just shoot it easily.
Again, you're much more into just having the elements rather than having to draw
them 2000 times differently.
But the pub is very World of Warcraft looking now that you've mentioned it.
And I think if you could nail that, like not just, just World of Warcraft, but
if you could nail an aesthetic like that, I do think people would be really
attracted to that.
Well, I found out, well, I knew about it, but I learned how to start doing it.
Like the FOSS model, like I did, I, all of that was painted directly on the
model because there's a way of doing it.
But usually like you unwrap a model, like you put seams in it and you flatten
it out like a papercraft doll and then you like kind of like texture it on the
flatten thing.
And then when you put it back, it wraps around, but like blender has a thing
where you can just take a brush and just draw right on the model on the screen.
So you can get a lot more subtlety going on there.
Cause like you don't have to like kind of like think abstract, like how will this
look when it's wrapped back up?
Yeah, you just like draw right on it.
And like I'm just painting.
I just painted the whole thing and it looked really nice.
And like I've never really done much with color, but I'm going to try
experimenting with that.
Probably a lot faster than building a whole texture to wrap around.
Right.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah, it's more, it's faster cause it's more intuitive.
Like you don't have to like think like, okay, like part of the foot's over there.
Part of the arms up here.
How am I going to make them mesh together?
You just, just draw.
It's much more natural.
Um, so that's, that's really exciting, but I'm doing a lot of experiments with that.
Like one of the first things I did actually, I did like a 3D reconstruction of
the first room from Undertale and Frisk and that was all hand painted too.
That looked pretty cool.
So I'm just like, yeah, yeah, it's going to be dope.
All right.
Let's take a short break.
Cause I got a piss and get another drink and we'll come right back.
I don't know, dude.
All right, Tom, we've asked you about your influences, your art, your plans for the
future.
Do you, would you say that you currently see yourself as having like, uh, are you
living project to project or is there something like is, or would you say that,
uh, you're more focused on the big project?
Uh, in terms of like, like art, art project wise, like, uh, I find myself, if
I'm working on a big thing, then it's like, that's what I'm doing.
And like, there's other things that come out, but the big thing is the important
thing and other times it's just like, uh, well, it's a new week.
What am I going to make next?
Yeah.
Well, my problem is that I flip flop constantly between like, should I run
myself as a business or should I be an artist that's like destined to kill
myself or something?
Cause, cause like so hard, like business wise, business wise, I should be like
just pumping out more fan art, trying to get my name out there, build a
personal brand and like build an audience.
So like when I said, oh, I'm going to start doing original work, like I have
like a thousand dollars a month based on my art and like a huge following to
actually support it.
Uh, but the artist in me is just like, fuck that, that stuff's never going to
take off because your passion isn't in there.
You should just like let your passion shine through on like something you're
actually super fucking invested in, even if it's like a smaller thing.
I mean, I think that's the way to go.
But I mean, I'm one to talk cause I, I, your, your, your passion
happens to be insanely like marketable.
I, you know, not anymore because like I, I found myself, we can't, we
can't control the audience that, that props us up.
Unfortunately.
Yeah.
I mean, it's just a simple matter of that.
I was more willing to, not even that I'm more willing to, but like less ambitious.
It's like the more ambitious you are, the harder it's going to be because, um,
if you want to communicate a really complicated idea, then you probably
can't do that in a simplistic way.
I don't know, like it's not, you can't just sit down in front of a video and
explain the entire plot of sorceress lost and have people care about sorceress
lost, you know, um, on some level, they might be interested in it, but cause
yeah, I've done that before.
I've been like, Hey, here's the plot of some novel I've got an idea for.
And people are like, wow, I'd love to see that, you know, but while you're not
getting it cause it's just an idea, um, feel free to steal it.
So you're just kind of bouncing between those two streams all the time.
It's, it's, it's complicated because like ideally in a perfect world, like I
wouldn't have financial obligations, you know, cause it's even the problem is
like, even if I like drop off the face of the earth and live in a, in a van, I
still have student debt.
So I'm going to have to defer on all of that to actually like make it work.
What does that do?
Uh, you basically just like, I can get like a deferment.
So it's still gaining interest, but you're not required to pay it back at that point.
So you're just basically like, owing more money so you don't have to pay it right
now.
Okay.
But in the future, you will have to pay it.
Right.
So you just got to try to make a big thing right now before you got to pay my only
scheme, but Trump, Trump's America seems to be on its way to ruining it is that
they have a thing right now where if you're poor for 15 years, they'll forgive
your federal loans.
I'm like halfway through that right now.
Oh yeah.
And, uh, and if Trump has his way, that's going to go away.
And then I'm going to go fucking shoot up the White House cause fuck you, you
ruined my long game here, you dick.
So for what it's worth, that was satire.
Yeah.
I heard that the secret service shows up at your house.
I mean, half the secret service would support me if I did that at this point.
Um, yeah, I don't know.
It's just, I would like to just do that.
Just like focus on that one thing.
Cause like I'm someone who's like really just unit task minded.
Like I can't, like I had a schedule for a while where I'd like on this day, I'll
do this project.
And I'll just see all this project and I just end up doing nothing cause my
brain was too scattered.
Like what I'm doing right now, which is working a little bit better is that like
I'm just going to do this one thing until it's done and move on to the next
thing until that's done.
Yeah.
And I just, I don't know, simple, simple, just like doing this and it makes it
better to get done.
Um, what do you think is the current, like, uh, let's say six months from now,
what do you think your content is going to look like?
Like what can people expect?
Cause like for me, um, one of the harder things about following you as a content
creator is that you've changed gears so many times.
I never know if you're planning to stay there.
Right.
No, it's, it's bad.
Like my personal brand's a mess, which was the name of that last wine chamber.
My personal brand's a mess, but it's not pity.
Uh, yeah, I need to just like really, that's why I wanted to get, take the, get
off work and take these next couple of months.
Like really just like hammer away a game plan.
Like the, the biggest, like fucking breakthrough of like the last 10 years has
been like, I enjoy making art and not just the finest finished product, which
has never happened.
Like it's, it's like the fucking craziest, God damn shit.
Cause you were saying like, Oh, you just like look for all these shortcuts.
The shortcuts were because I hated doing it.
Yeah.
Now that's, I mean, that's the thing is that if you try to work in a medium that
you don't enjoy doing the thing, then it's always going to fail.
And the interesting thing is fucking sucks.
I'd done it for so long that I thought it was just cause I was lazy, but I'm not.
I mean, I am lazy, but that's the hardest part is that like there, everybody,
everybody's lazy about doing shit.
They don't want to do, you know, and like for me, when I wanted to be an
author or a filmmaker and all that stuff, like I didn't realize that when I was
a teenager, like there was a solid year and a half.
I wanted to be a filmmaker and I never made any fucking films.
And at the end of that, I had to go, well, clearly I'm not a fucking filmmaker
cause I had all the time and opportunities and like, I just didn't do it.
So meanwhile, like anime blogging was just happening naturally, you know, and I feel
like if you can find something that you just enjoy doing it and there's any way
it could be marketable, it's worth exploring.
And if it's not marketable, well, you got a fun hobby making fucking PS2.
Well, that's like kind of why I want to take these
couple of months because like I have no, I'll have no responsibility, nothing else.
So if I can't do it in this situation, there's no way it's going to happen when
other things are added on top.
If you can't bust your own ass.
I mean, they always say that like having the rug pulled out from under you is a
good way to hit the ground running.
I don't know if anybody's ever like premeditated that to the extent that this is
though, but I mean, the whole thing is just like, I just, I can't.
It's really, I fantasized about the things that's happening to you have happening
to me back when I was a teenager.
Like I wanted to run away and thought like, oh, if I like, if I have to bust
my ass, I'll work, you know, but I never did, obviously.
But I'm real curious if it'll.
Yeah, I mean, ideally, like if I could get myself into one thing that I'm slowly
like trying to do is like delegation and like trying to like, I want to work
with other people because like I said earlier, like I bust my ass way harder
like working for a PCP than I do for myself.
Like I would not, I would not sit down and make a hundred t-shirts for myself.
Like I'll do it for PCP because it's a bigger thing that I believe in outside.
But if I like doing like Polystation to branded shirts, I'm like, just go on
red bubble, pay double.
I don't give a fuck.
Yeah.
It also can be really, it can be way easier to just riff off of someone else's
thing, you know, like it's easier to come up with ideas if it's like someone has
already set up the baseline and you're just like riffing off of that baseline.
It's not even like, like the, the idea part.
It's because I, when I think of myself and my work, it's just me.
And so like, because I don't think too highly of myself yet, I can't get too
excited about it, but like when I work with PCP or just with anybody else,
like I remember I did a project with my buddy, like right after college.
And like we both busted our ass for a week because like, and I worked hard
because it was like, this isn't just me, like it's something bigger than me now.
I'm working towards something larger than just like my like, you know,
artistic masturbation.
Do you think you're okay with like a life where it was never like, oh,
I did it all by myself?
Well, that was a, that was something I'm letting go of.
I was super obsessed with that.
Like I wouldn't want, like I'd rather do this bad than myself and get it done.
Right.
But now I'm just like, it's been 10 years of that and nothing's been done.
So like now I'm just like, I'd rather have something done than something not done.
Right.
I met at the point now where like, I continually hire the DeVoo because even
though I've been getting better as an editor, so has he.
And it's like, you know, that, that's the kind of delegation where at the time
that I hired him, everyone in the PCP was terrified of hiring editors
because we were all like, oh, I want to have, I want it to all be my personal
mark. It has to be me, me, me.
It has to be like my perfect vision.
But then I just found a guy who kind of understood my vision.
But at the time I was writing stuff that's nowhere near as advanced as
like what Jesse was doing where Jesse was like, oh, I can't hire an editor
because like he won't understand my vision.
And I'm like, well, yeah, you're doing like a really complicated thing,
which is more fun to edit anyways.
Like ironically, it's more fun to edit something that forces you to be creative
and think about it.
But because of the fact that DeVoo's been editing for me for so long that now
if I do want to give him something more advanced, that's like, oh, this is more
of my personal vision thing.
Like he can, he can deliver on my vision better than I can because I can
just describe it to him and he'll show me something and I'll be like, well,
that's way cooler than how I had imagined it.
You know, I mean, that's, that's like the advice they give you.
You want to hire people better than yourself.
And like that's what I want to do.
Like it really starts with just being honest.
Like I would love like my ideal situation.
I'd love to do something like, like Ruby where like I'm like the creative
director and I'm doing, like I want to still be in the trenches and like doing
a lot of the modeling and like doing story.
Ruby right there is proof that that brand of PS2 model is popular.
Especially it's low poly as fuck, right?
The newer ones have gotten better, but the initial ones, they were pretty rough.
And like, I remember watching like the first, I just watched Ruby a little
while ago and I was like, oh my God, this is aesthetics on point.
And then they changed to my, I was like, oh, it's looks so modern.
What happened?
I definitely can say I like your models more than the Ruby models.
Well, the Ruby models were like, what, like 10 years ago or something
like that at this point.
Shit.
Um, okay.
Uh, well, now I want to ask you some more philosophical questions, I guess.
Okay.
Uh, like, you know, how do you see the world?
How is the world right now?
How are things?
Okay.
Um, like in terms of just society, how do you think is going things going in
a direction that you, uh, that is good.
Well, okay.
I don't think the reaction things are going is like necessarily good for anybody,
but like, have you felt yourself like burdened with the, the, the foibles of
modern society much, or are you more just like concerned about your shit?
Um, I'm kind of like torn on this because like there's, there's, I definitely
feel like, I think I brought this up on a PCP episode once where I was saying how
like, because of social media and like the internet and stuff, like.
Our, our like, uh, scale in which we can judge our personal ability has
like been expanded like a thousand fold.
You know, that's kind of what I adjusted at the start of that deer artist
video is like, there's so many people online who legitimately deserve to be
famous and you're competing with all of them.
Right.
Like all of us, if we were just like new, like the people in our city, we'd all
be like the 99th percentile of what we do, but the problem is we're online and
it's like, I mean, yeah, there's a lot of you're, you're in the biggest pond.
Like, I mean, you can be within a sub pond of like, Oh, I'm the biggest pony guy
or I'm the biggest anime guy or whatever.
But like, you know, you're still a small fish in the YouTube pond of guys with
millions of subscribers.
So, I mean, it's the same thing with art or anything else.
Any, any niche, like you're just, you're competing on, on like a global level.
And the problem is because all the cream rises to the crop, the top 1% feels
like normal.
And so when you're not the top 1%, you feel inadequate when you really
shouldn't be.
No, I mean, like, yeah, you're constantly looking at shit that's better than yours.
Yeah, like you can't help it.
But like for me, the way that I process that information is, I have to get as
good as that guy.
Right.
How do you feel when you see that stuff?
Well, it's interesting because up until I started doing 3D, I would feel
miserable, but now I just get jazzed.
Like, this is fucking dope.
And for some, I guess it's just like a mindset change of just like, I feel
like this medium is within my grasp.
Like I could do that with enough application of effort, whereas with drawing
and stuff, it never felt like I would, would get there.
Yeah.
So it's definitely been a big project can get done within a timely enough fashion
that they will make sense and be like positive experiences to have worked on.
I mean, I don't know.
I, the big mystery for me is always like the marketing aspect because I feel
like despite all the best practices and stuff, there's always a degree of luck.
Like because that aspect, you can't control it.
Like I can't control people coming to me.
I can't control you liking what I do.
And I mean, I think there's also a strong element though of like, uh, you, you
can't, you might not be able to make them drink, but you can lead the horse to
water at the very least by like just making people understand.
Like I think when people talk about having a personal narrative online and
everything, like this has been construed as like be a vlogger and be a fun
online persona.
But I think the main thing people just want to know is like, why do you care
so much about this goddamn thing?
Well, there's a, there's a, it's a great, I think we had to talk about this.
I told you about Simon Sinek when he says people, people buy why you do things,
not what you do.
Yeah.
It's so true.
It's, it is definitely.
I mean, especially for me, like a lot of my audience is about the why of like
and that's something I really kind of want to get more into on Polystation
too, which is kind of the reason why I kind of think maybe pivoting away from
fan art.
Cause like if I, I think that if I did an impassioned rant or something,
I mean, like how, why fan art sucks or like not even being that blunt about it,
but like why like the artistic integrity is important.
I think there's a group of people that would really resonate with that.
Certainly.
I, I also think that you, uh, yeah.
If you did more original content, it would just show more.
I think people want to know like what's the message you're trying to send.
Like I know a lot of random things about source or a slosh,
but I don't know what the themes are, you know?
So that's like kind of the problem is I don't think enough people know what
you're trying to explore with your work, you know, like it, or even if you know
what you're trying to explore with your work, do you, do you have like a strong
sense of like what, I mean, the, the theme, the theme of, of the story is actually
like, I guess it's ironically kind of similar to what I've been doing.
It's like there's, there's, there's another, another way of accomplishing
what you want to do.
Cause like the main thrust of it is that Sarah's in a world of mages or a
culture of mages and she can't do magic.
And so like she wants to be like a great mage or whatever.
So she goes to all these other countries outside of hers and like each country
has a different culture and there's different ways of doing magic.
And she kind of becomes like this amalgamation of all these different
schools of thought and becomes like better and stronger that way.
And it's going to be like this cultural clash between her and her
brother, who like is very traditionalist from her culture and like how they
play off of each other and things like that.
And like a lot of more, more is going to happen.
And is this more like down to earth or does this expand in like story scope?
Like, does it, is there a war?
You know, I distinctly wanted to make it not like a chosen one on the world
in the brink of war kind of story.
The entire like culture is stable.
Okay.
So it's just going to be exploring like these different cultures, like being
able to look at a fantasy world that's not like unstable.
I'm like, it's closer to like a My Little Pony tonality.
Like, yeah, because I mean, that's where it came from at the end of the day.
It's just like a world where I still find that so refreshing.
There's a lot of politics and magic and everything, but it's not violent.
Yeah.
I mean, there can be violence.
Like in isolated cases, like there's a certain short story I want to tell.
Like I want to like challenge like perceptions and stuff because like she
comes from this culture where magic is like the be all end all.
And then like there's going to be cities like we're like magics look down upon.
Like there's going to be a whole like culture that's basically going to be kind
of like steampunk where they're like, like they're basically going to be like
what atheists would be in a world where gods exist.
Like fuck God, I don't want to have anything to do with them.
So they reject magic because magic is like the power of the gods.
So like just make technology and but the gods are literally real.
Yes.
They, they, they're the rulers of each of each country.
So, okay.
Well, that's interesting.
It's more than I've ever known about the long-term plot of Sorcerer's loss.
I mean, that's because it just kind of got finalized a little while ago.
It was a lot different before.
Um, but like the original one of the, it was, it's funny.
Like it's the original plot was going to be like sometimes you just like have to
like realize your limitations.
And I think a big problem is that because I don't believe that at all.
Yeah.
And so like,
No, you got that girl in the gun.
Yeah.
So go beyond the impossible, maybe impossible possible.
So I was just like, eh, it didn't resonate.
So I had to go back and scrap that and redo it.
And like this is, and it's funny because like as I was developing the story,
like it happened with my own life because like 3ds, I'm going to push these
barriers that I couldn't do before.
So it's like, huh.
Yeah.
How badly do you wish you'd got into 3d art like four years ago or 10 years ago?
Well, you know, that the, the, the, the technology has advanced to a place where
like it's definitely more feasible to do it now than it was then.
And also like, there were a couple like key YouTube videos that like kind of
unlocked a way of doing it that I kind of wrapped my brain around that if I
hadn't decided to do it now, I might not have stumbled across and I might not have
been able to push to where I am at this point.
So I try, like even with, with like all these rewrites of SL and stuff,
like it's going to be so much better than it would have been if I had just
pushed through with it before.
So there is a part of me that's like grateful that it had extra time to incubate.
Yeah.
I mean, in a lot of ways, um, people always say you have to get like your
first story out there.
You have to get, you have to, like, like Munchie was saying in the podcast,
you and him did, I don't know what the release order of any of this shit's
going to be, but, uh, you and Munchie did a podcast about, uh, do you know what
that video is going to be called?
Art, apologies, you know, in the art, apologies, um, podcast.
Munchie was talking about how you need to get your early work out of the way
because it's always going to be your worst and like you can keep making it
better, but then the paradox that, uh, the longer you work on it, the better
it gets, but in a lot of ways you've just created multiple stories.
Like by the time the, the story I wrote as a, as a novel, like I said,
originally it was going to be a movie.
I spent like two years redeveloping it until it was a book.
And by that point it was yet vastly better than the pre, than what it would have
been.
And if I made it again now, it would be two, but it would also just be another story.
Like the same character is the same plot, but it's not the same story.
You know, I mean, I've written other stuff.
So it's not like this is my first rodeo on writing a story.
Right.
And it's also, but I'm just saying that like, even if none of this stuff's been
published, like silently in the background, you're grinding the power level,
which used to be how it was, like most people didn't crack the scene till they
were of a certain power level.
Now it's like all your old shit can be on your DeviantArt.
Some people try to cover that stuff up, but I'm one of those people.
All my old Deviantarts are gone.
You'll never see them.
What's the farthest back of your content that's viewable online?
Uh, well, I actually just axed all my pony work off of DeviantArt a couple
weeks ago, so, uh, like two years ago, it's the longest it goes back.
Um, is that true on like all social media or the, okay, but to clarify,
the reason that I decided to, to get rid of the pony stuff wasn't even
because I was super embarrassed by it.
It was because I didn't want that metadata to fuck up with anything that's
going forward.
I didn't remove my pony videos out of embarrassment either.
It was just like, for a while, I'm like an anime channel that has like three
rows of anime videos and then pages of pony videos.
And I was like, these all need to go.
That was the thing, cause like I'm rebranding is like all those 3D stuff.
And then you go back and there's all this pony stuff and it doesn't make any sense.
And like, because like all these things are driven by algorithms now,
traffic to that is going to fuck up directing where you're supposed to go.
Oh God, they're ruining the internet.
It's really bad.
They're ruining the fucking internet.
And the only reason that the only thing that's going to save it is that everyone
knows they're doing it.
That's how we can all escape.
Um, all right, how long, how far are we into this?
Could I am running out of questions?
Well, is there anything, anything?
Cause I don't want to ask you about any broad topic stuff cause we talk about
enough of that on the PCP right now.
Is there anything else you want to share?
I guess like going back to what we were saying about like how we feel about like
society or whatever, like how that shit goes.
I think there's a lot of negative that comes on with this whole internet shit.
But like we were saying before, like, you know, the last generation couldn't do
what we're doing.
Like there's no way that, like, can you imagine like, like the ridiculousness
of like, Oh, like five friends are sitting around a table having a discussion
and you get like almost a grand for it.
I mean, like the, this whole setup that we're currently in right now is exceedingly
strange.
Yeah, it's kind of ridiculous.
Renting a house to make like to fly six guys in and make YouTube videos for 10
days.
Like it's utterly nuts and definitely it couldn't have existed before.
Yeah.
So I know we all give social media a lot of shit, but like,
I, I'm also like really just grateful that like, I'm, I really, I like being the
age that I am because I'm like young enough to be able to take advantage of
all this, but old enough to understand like how important it is.
Oh yeah.
How like to not take it for granted.
Right.
Yeah.
So.
But at the same time, I feel as though we are just too old to understand certain
like why things become trendy on social media.
For sure.
There's definitely a disconnect.
Like every once in a while, um, I'll just like hear some new song that's like all
over Vine and I'm like, why, why, why this is just is not my generation.
I guess, you know, that's, I, I definitely am terrified of growing old just because
of like, I'm terrified of death in general.
I remember that like, you know, there's always people your age, like people,
people act like if you, um, I mean, granted, like teenagers are the most
interested in art because they need it to like understand the world around them.
And they have tons of free time, but like adults still consume it and they want shit
for them.
I'm just terrified of dying.
Yeah.
Well, that's pretty bad.
I mean, we're all terrified of dying.
Me, I think it's just because I haven't done what I want to do yet.
Like I think if I can get enough shit out of me, I'd be like, if I died tomorrow,
like it, it take a lot because like for me, there's so much.
Well, that's a whole problem.
It's like, there's, there's, I'm never, my brain's never going to turn off.
There's always going to be another idea.
So like, I'm going to die unfulfilled somehow.
I really want you to read, um, or maybe I sent this to you.
I don't even remember.
Did you read a thing, um, by this comic artist about like how he wasted 14 years
or whatever drawing this comic that was only supposed to take five and like his
tips on how to not do that?
Um, possibly was a YouTube video.
No, it's recent.
It's fairly recent.
It was a, it was a blog post, but it was a, I saw a video kind of
similar to that or no, it was a YouTube video.
I'm wrong.
It was a YouTube video.
I think I watched that.
It was like, and it was like kind of like an edutainment video, but it was a,
a guy who was a comic artist who had spent like an obscene amount of time over a
decade drawing like this three volume comic.
And it was because he copied the style of like, um, oh yeah, because he did all
that super insane patching and stuff.
Yeah, I did watch it.
Yeah, but then he talks about like where you need to cut to like, he's like,
pick your battles.
Like this shot was not important and didn't need to be shot in a location that
had four layers of detail.
Uh, I will not do that next time, but the most fascinating part was when he was
talking about like, so this took me this many years.
And that means that if I only do three more comics than that, or if I, if I
keep doing comments at this rate, I will only get three done before I die.
And I have more than three ideas.
And, uh, do you ever find yourself like, do you worry about that?
Especially with like sorceress, that's like my number one thing.
Like, I remember yesterday when I was on my way here, I was like, do I really
have a week to spare?
Like, should I just be working right now?
Cause I have like two models like that have just been in limbo.
I feel very similar because like two weeks for the last two weeks, I've done
nothing, but read the guilty.
Get wiki.
God damn fucking lecture.
And I still have all of XR to get through for me.
It was the dick show like days and days.
And I was like sick of it.
And I was, I was, I was talking to my friend.
He's like, why the fuck are you even doing this?
All fighting game stories are retarded.
I'm like, I mean, you're right.
But I said, I said, I do hard stories for target.
It's got 150,000 views.
So dude, this lecture, the first, the first half an hour is a hundred years
before the first game because that's, you need to know all of that.
It's really, but, uh, yeah.
Yeah, I, I too was like at the, at the like very beginning of like the
project that is going to define my career for the next year.
And I'm like, gotta not work on that yet.
Let's go to Radcon.
But like,
it's been really frustrating.
Cause I'm just like, I want to keep going on that.
Right.
But you're, you've been talking about you and Munchie, uh, inspiring
each other to try to work here.
So yeah, no, I got those, those two files have just been open for
like the last two weeks.
Just like, are you sure?
Are you sure?
God, that feeling of having it open and like, or
especially if you have something for a project on a tab in your fucking
chrome and it's there for days or like a half finished movie and you're just
like, I'm never going to finish this movie.
It's the worst.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, uh, I think we're about done here cause I am sick of sitting in this
chair and I've run out of questions.
All right.
So that's the interview with Tom.
Hope you all enjoyed interviews are not like back.
There's only like two that need to be done.
It was you and mage, I think.
Yeah.
And now this one's knocked out.
So, uh, I hope you enjoyed it with video and look forward to more rad con
video because there's a thousand of them.
We've literally filmed like, like probably over 20 vlogs today or 20 pieces
of entertainment today.
Yeah, look forward to everything.
Peace.